<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1542</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 10:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> be there for her, but dont be her world. if she relies on you for everything, you will eventually fail because that isnt a burden you are meant to bear, and it will break her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 06:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 06:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LMFAO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 23:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude thats awesome man congrats!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 10:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sonya curry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not truly an INFJ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 09:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I actually an ENFJ? I am very good at talking to people and I'm generally not nervous, but I think about everything so much and am so internal. but I also start to feel lonely and even depressed if I'm alone too much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 08:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha you're right. maybe rinse* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 08:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you go in there?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my fight coach was getting frustrated with me because i kept thinking i understood the instruction but actually didnt. he got mad at me and said "YOU DONT LISTEN". seemingly small but it really messed with me and i got surprisingly sad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 01:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i love it. i think its worth the risk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you scrub your butthole/feet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 00:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've learned that a lot of guys just think "water will get it" but man that is not true. Especially if you play sports, you have to scrub your feet, and everyone poops, you have to have to have to soap your butthole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 10:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did you ask her what she expected? was the card made of like cheapass cardboard and old newspaper with a pen? i mean jeez. sounds like you did a good job to me lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 10:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i like the question you posed. i know in sunday school they taught us a lot that god is a jealous and self loving god. and the barbie doll argument. like if you programmed a barbie to say i love you, would it be meaningful. no. god does the same thing. he gives you a choice so it feels better when you choose him. just quoting what they taught. think its stupid either way like yeah. ur gna give them the "choice" to love you then send em to hell if they choose wrong lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 09:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dadbod </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 09:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> drink a shot of protein powder to that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 09:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahah it was the most i could comfortably do without being too sexual </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 09:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think i successfully masturbated in class twice in my life. had to use my left hand both times. RAGING hormones as an 8th grader.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 09:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> into a tissue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 09:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh trust me i have not forgotten. i'm watching every single one of these games rooting for lebron. im not a cavs fan but goddamn i would HATE to see gsw get a championship </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 09:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if he calls you a slut, id be a bit worried. but when i think of myself and my friends, we wouldnt really say the word slut in front of a girl. its really judgmental and we might be joking about it as bro talk with each other but yeah definitely never in front of a girl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 09:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> best to err on the side of caution. thats what i thought was best too. i think its easier to explain/ ask for forgiveness for being too civil than for being too aggressive  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
