<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1979</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 10:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, as a person who lives with depression, anxiety, and is a recovering alcoholic,  you are not obligated to talk to your family about these things, but i think it is important to let them know you need help. Leap and the net will appear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 10:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear you. More than you know. I understand this deeply, from experience.
this is what we call a geographic change. Changing your environment or surroundings as a solution to a problem. 
Depression has a lot of factors, and I think it can be tricky.
Personally, I would love to tell you to go for it, but I know from my own experience, changing my environment didn't change my mindset, my thinking process, my depression or anxiety. 
Fresh starts are so appealing. Whatever decision you make, I support it. I support seeking happiness, just think it through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 10:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean? More school, less work?
Working out more than I do?
There are so many factors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 10:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 23. I stopped taking my meds because they were making me aggressive and I started suffering from dizzy spells. I feel better now that I'm off, not AS anxious. They worked for me until I grew out of them I guess.
I don't know. I think a lot of it is not being as active as I should in AA and the fellowship right now. I've done the steps, I've tried sponsoring, it's just being a young person in AA, it can be hard to find groups of people who take it seriously. 
I'm just so tired of feeling this way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 09:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be the millionth AA/NA person to say how fucked up that is.
Also, I've done that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 12:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok more pls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 12:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone else get that fucked up feeling like your back is exposed? Like there is something there? Fuck me, man. ALL THE BLANKETS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 13:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why even go there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 12:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate that guy. So much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 11:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't handle this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 11:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man my brain can't handle this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 12:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! And yes, I've tried many, in therapy, rehabs, dual diagnosis facilities, all of em.
I was the only thing stopping me from being happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 12:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally just posted something similar, and I'm beyond happy to see someone else feeling this too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 12:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about we stop the suicide train?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 09:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it was in good way!
Better, just consistently sad in the back of my mind. Same old. You? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 08:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahaha I'm a chick,
But yeah, I feel. I just don't know what to do with feelingswhen I feel them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 08:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
