<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2871</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 05:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I um, had an abortion earlier this year. I have been lactating a tiny bit for months now. I also recently became single and have been thinking about doing some porn. Maybe I should try and make some money off this while it lasts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 05:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I am really into being a sub. It's super hot. I also really like pain and stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 05:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not the problem. It's either from my eds or fibro. I just don't know which.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 07:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, like when I watch an episode of something and someone else shows up and decides they need to watch it. Or someone wants to rewind the movie five minutes back.     
If it were up to  me it would be an easy thing to avoid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 04:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Some of those are duplicates. I am constantly in between meds. Right now all I'm on is cymbalta, an anti inflammatory, and melatonin. But I'm about to start lyrica.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 04:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I'm so honored.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 01:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah its fine. I am sad and all but I have way more shit to worry about so it's whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 01:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they taste exactly the same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 01:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just some yuppie thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are still a lot of squatters. Hence all the couches on the side of the road with no cushions. Haha. But yeah everyone is pretty pissed about the St Roch market opening back up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that would be sketchy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When was that? I will still go a couple blocks at night. Or wherever when I'm on my bike.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. I guess just knowing people. Ha. I was in a really shitty sideshow for a little bit which was fun. Only toured with a band though doing their merch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well also once there was so many abandoned houses all the squatters and punks came in. It was only a few years ago that there were still squats in the bywater. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 20:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I have ever even been there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 20:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do what I want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 20:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I lived in the 8th ward and worked in the 9th. It's weird that it's not as sketchy as you would  think because there are so many white punk kids there. I love it there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 20:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is Tia isn't always at the rescue but she is always doing something for the dogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 20:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I probably never would have noticed I did that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 19:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't stumbling. That is actually the only time I have preemptively taken my knife all the way out. But yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um. Ok.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bat. I would totally ride that shit.       
Yes I know the username is relevant so we can just establish that now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read a book about something like that before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just became single yesterday. My life is a bit of a mess due to my health so I am just getting treatment and trying to think about what I want to do when I get better and how I will do it.       
I am going to try and learn new tricks so I can go back to sideshow performing as well as practicing more music. When my hands let me anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Re watching something I just saw.      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really liked watching my ex play pool. It was hot somehow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not live and I don't know if I ever made it into the show but I worked for Villalobos Pitbull Rescue of Pitbulls and Parolees. It's actually pretty straightforward. Those people are actually just trying to rescue dogs. They are genuinely decent people. Tia especially is exactly the way she seems. She is a total saint so long as you're on her good side.        
All the money that is donated and gotten from animal planet goes towards taking care of the 500 or so dogs they have and they really need it in order to keep the place running.        
I know it's a shitty answer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just became single yesterday. I have a lady body and my personality isn't very shitty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MwaHaHaHaHa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rubber chicken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is touching me?         
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interacting with people who are not nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a school bus. I may have just been having sex with myself. But still. Everyone was sleeping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bleach. It's all the same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love porters.       
Also tequila.         </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Half man. Half bear. Half pig. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually heard about a store in one of the dry states (that don't sell booze on Sunday) that had listerine on ice up front. I also heard of a guy that only drank listerine. Like bottles of it a day.       
People are insane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heroin. Seriously. I could never get addicted to that shit because I was so disgusted with myself.          
Edit: Apparently mistakes are okay unless it's a typo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some old crack head tried to rob me (small female) in the ghetto of New Orleans  and I scared him away. I was drunkenly walking home by myself super late after a show and already had my knife out, open, and in my hand. He was pretending to have a gun. I'm not afraid to act insane.       
It was right next to a friend's place so I just stayed there that night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been practicing those kinds of parenting skills with my drunk friends. Not really by choice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The line "Jesus freaks, out in the street" always makes me imagine Jesus having some kind of tantrum or mental breakdown on the sidewalk.       
Dude, did you see Jesus freaking out in the street earlier? Shit was crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time a guy has been like "I really want to be with you."        
Those are always the most neglectful partners.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know all the words to American Pie. It's almost a problem. Also anything Jim Croce I need to sing along to even though my range is nothing like his. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And get all gay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I secretly like it. I hate everything else popular for the most part.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there are dogs around I use it as an excuse to babble nonsense to myself. I will start out talking to the dog then just go on making weird noises to myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were several. Just broke up yesterday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The smell of garbage bags being opened that were full of towels soaked in dog urine and poo after it had sat for weeks on a hot wet New Orleans day.       
That almost knocked me on my ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to an abortion clinic in the south. I'm assuming that at least a couple people that work there are Christian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Curiosity killed the cat."        
There is a second part which is "and satisfaction brought it back." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 15:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even know what all of my pain is from anymore. Ha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 06:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it sucks. I'm not positive of everywhere I have it besides my hands. But I am pretty sure it's in my hips, wrists, elbows, neck, and jaw. Probably not too bad in most of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 06:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much. I'm glad you found it relatable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 06:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still all about forts at 23. Not so much chasing plastic bags around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 03:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I was hoping for. I know I'm not the only one who feels this way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 01:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get the dread fluff part I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 01:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you haven't performed with a sideshow or anything? There is generally more money in busking but touring is a blast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 01:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fluff fluff? My hair is actually flat and straight and asian. And my bangs are actual bangs. And those pictures are like eight years old. I am attractive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 01:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. They were actually just sitting there and that was the best way I could set my phone so my instrument wasn't way louder than my voice.      
Thanks for the feedback. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 01:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was only in one scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 00:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you.     
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit. I have too many doctors appointments for this thought to exist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes more sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start appreciating yourself. Don't let other people's bias impact what you know about yourself.        
Trust me, this is coming from a sideshow performing musician with hairy armpits  (femaleish). I really don't care what people think because I know I am a decent person and my preferences are my business.      
What I am saying is, be the person you know is great and it should work out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to the doctor. Maybe some old lady that would have had my appointment won't get in until tomorrow and will die of a UTI tonight or something.      
Wow I feel really hypothetically awful now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a teenager?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has never been a problem. We don't judge each other. I can't really work anyway but regardless I don't mind living in a van if it means I get to travel. I don't really care for nice things and no one tries to obligate me to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it was before your time. You're missing out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Fuck my lungs, the rest of my body is fucked anyway. I doubt I can make it much worse. At least cigarettes are helping keep my blood pressure up. Fuck. I want to be normal." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off I have female genitals. When I was 11 or 12 and my sister had moved out I would go through her room and look through all the stuff she had left. Under her bed I found a VHS tape titled "Women in Red".  Yeah it had Ron Jeremy in it. I would masturbate to it when I was home alone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off. How old are you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad likes to listen to that song and cry every time. It's weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean the Coneheads song? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any kind of short term injury.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people I know that have them wear them as earrings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wrote a bitter song about my chronic pain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I messed up a few times but didn't have the energy to do another take. It's also not done and still needs a better bridge. But I thought some of y'all might appreciate it anyway.         
https://youtu.be/lcs67xhaZfk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, my standards are different than yours so it is fine because I don't associate myself with people who judge me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 20:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I bet. His last few albums have been awful. It's sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do it. Manson fans are supposed to be shitty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can work. I still have a bunch of piercings in my face and now I have tattoos. I dress a little more punk rock now. Wear what you like, it doesn't matter. One of my favorite articles of clothing is a knit body suit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was the eat me drink me tour but I was actually pleasantly surprised that he only played like two songs from that album. He was actually pretty good. And he played rock n roll jigger which was awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha. Yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't log in. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm still a weirdo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I was female but yes I am now an Asian male. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Half white. Not wealthy. Just a fucking punk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 07:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a cousin named spike. I think you're good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 07:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe not the saddest, but Trouble by Cat Stevens always makes me want to kill myself a tiny bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 07:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking hate showering with anyone else. It's the worst. Making sex out of the question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 07:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm all about that shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 07:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never liked it until my current boyfriend. He's kind of a big guy so it is easy for me to be on top of him. We 69 regularly and it is pretty great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 06:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My meds that I have to take on an empty stomach. If I wait too long to eat I stop wanting to. Which doesn't work out well because I need to take other meds with food at the same time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 06:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Story of my life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 06:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um. I was actually 16. Like I said. Soooo cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 06:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just like to have sex with people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 06:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should have just played it off as a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 06:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still ask people. If I actually like them anyway. Not just a random hook up though I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 05:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was the goth kid. I made my own pair of those awful plastic cyber goth dread falls and wore them to a school dance with a corset and shit.       
I also used to shave my eyebrows and draw them on which was fine after the first year once I had figured out how to do it well. It was rough at first though.       
I am going to see if I can get on my old MySpace and find embarrassing pictures.        
EDIT: I couldn't get into my old account. Here are some pictures but they aren't as embarrassing as the ones I can't access. http://imgur.com/a/mYsgg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 04:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude when I was in high school I took a bible to a Marilyn Manson concert and tore it up and threw it on stage. I was sooooo cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 04:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it makes you feel any better I had actually been with at least twice that many people by 18. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 04:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the sort of shit I do all the time. No fucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 04:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's beautiful. Like some kind of performance art exhibition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 04:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. And yeah I also have osteoarthritis and fibro. As well ass fatigue but that comes with the territory. I'm somehow lucky enough to have no back problems.      
But yeah I appreciate hearing from you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 04:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well now that you point it out I realize there is a typo. But there was nothing intentionally wrong. I am just a huge fruit when it comes to that song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I do spend time on /r/chronicpain and /r/ehlersdanlos which I have found to be very helpful.      
I appreciate hearing from you. I know there are tons of people out there like me. It's just frustrating. I have talked with a pain psychiatrist, it was nice to be validated that I am handling my health like I should. But I kind of already know that. This would be so much easier if I could get my regular doctors to trust me enough to treat me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I can't really stand almost any new popular country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The coconut oil actually helps. I have tried several things and nothing really gets rid of it. I guess I don't care that much about it, not many people see my ass in person. I just feel a little self conscious about it sometimes.        
I had cystic acne on my face until this year so I'm hoping the rest will go away on its own eventually too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I say bluegrass community it includes other things like folk and whatnot. Most of those musicians play multiple genres revolving around the bluegrass scene. It's mostly just the musicians that hate the song and don't want to play it. Which is really the only part of the scene I am familiar with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 23:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the guy that played the fiddle in that version and we would always give him shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 23:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the regular demographic it works for. But there is actually a bluegrass karaoke with a live band somewhere one the west cost. People pay $5 or something to sing a song with the band. Wagon Wheel costs $100.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
