<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8901</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 00:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally would've preferred Ron Perlman (probable typo) as deathstroke instead of Will Smith as deadshot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 00:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude walking towards it at the end: "good job petrov, here's your payment"

Gives seagull a fry, keeps the camera </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 22:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a bunch dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 18:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its hard when no one understands your illness and think that you're only weak, i usually just keep my feelings to myself and wait for it to pass.

I usually am all over the spectrum of joy, depression and anger, just need someone to talk to that understands this feelings of dread and hopelessness, of feeling alone and falling into a dark hole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 04:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play videogames for hours, it calms me down and soothes my mind.

Used to drink but that just made it worse, whatever you do don't turn to alcohol, the first times you feel good but eventually it drags you to a deeper hole.

I'm not the right person to say it at the moment since I'm going through a very rough spot in life, but try and hang in there. Cry if you must, write your feelings out and burn the paper, please, just try and hang in there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This goes on /r/aww (hope I got the link right, still pretty new in here) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 23:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leave food and water for it, that's pretty much all you can do.

Try with an animal control center, maybe a vet clinic?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 15:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The benefits of working outdoors dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Had a visit today at work </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 05:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/YCVE8U4.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 05:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totalmente de acuerdo, justamente de eso estaba pensando hoy.

Hay que salir un poco del colectivo de ser chingon para ver nuestra cultura desde afuera y darnos cuenta de tantos y tantos errores que hay en nuestra cultura.

Que fácil es echarle la culpa al gobierno de nuestros problemas y nosotros seguir igual </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 05:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diablo 3, I was disappointed at first to be we honest but I've been playing more and more and am happy and enjoying it a lot! Old school Diablo fan here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 05:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how I hit on girls when I'm drunk...

Ahhhh just kidding fellows, I do it sober too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
