<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2252</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 05:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not Really...it just wasn't as impactful, or the people weren't as meaningful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 04:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need validation from others. You're alive. That's what counts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 04:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He did. I don't feel like I did though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 04:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We both graduated in 2012.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My best friend from high school still seeks validation from people we went to school with. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 03:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not a bad dude, just incredibly insecure. But he also holds some petty grudges and still somewhat irrationally (in my eyes) dislike some people. 

But hey, he's one of my closest friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 02:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you smoking to cope with issues? Do you do other things? Do you spend your time sober? 

Look up the CAGE questionaire. Even though it is used primarily for alcohol, you can substitute any substance for alcohol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 02:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 21. I don't give a shit whether you're 5 or 85. If I can learn something from you, then I will be glad to learn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 02:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least you know how fucking magnets work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have caught myself mid swear before around children and tried to correct myself. Children and family are the only people I don't swear around (outside of a professional setting) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 09:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having someone else tell me I have a chance is wonderful. And of course I plan on wooing her. It would be foolish of me not to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 08:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be true, but I refuse to believe it. I would have to be the same...or brainwashed to be compelled to like her then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 08:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is true. That, and I'm assuming she's like me, not big on jumping on the relationship boat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 08:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had leftover credit from my app store, and your comment was reassuring.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 08:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the vote of confidence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 08:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But...she's 23 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 08:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think 23 qualifies as teenager though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 07:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will. Just you know, not aggressively  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 07:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think so? I'm not 100% sure but the only things that are 100% sure in life are that we will pay taxes, and George Washington was the only unanimous choice for President </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 07:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's such a weird way of wording it though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 07:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly believe I do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 07:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course. I have enough past mistakes to know when something coming up is about to be wrong on my part  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 07:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a shot?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 07:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That could be it. I'm thinking positive on this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 07:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that double negative weirded me out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 06:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with /u/RulerOfSlides on this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New development with the girl I've been talking to </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 06:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I told her what I've been dealing with lately, and she said that it's almost fascinating that I can seem so level around her, and in general. Anyway, I apologize for being so distant and not making that extra effort to charm her. That goes over well; and I ask her if she really likes me (insecurity on 100 right here) and she tells me that she doesn't not like me. Idk how to feel about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 09:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Likewise, if a rep tells me they don't need an e-mail, then they are looking for another source of info </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 08:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is wonderful. I'm sure mine would do the same, but I haven't seen any evidence of it in the last 7 years...minimum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 07:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I had that reassurance from my dad. We have no common interests, but I wish he would tell me he cared, without being forced to do so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 05:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least yours tries to give you direction. Anymore, my dad and I only exchange the small talk you would see between two people forced to be in the same elevator together </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 05:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine has been around physically, but it only seems like he is around to Harp on the slightest thing I've done wrong, never offers any positive encouragement, and blatantly favors my brother in every facet of life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 05:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted over in /r/depression with all the details about my situation, but I had a separate question. What's it like to have a loving, supporting father? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 05:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not suicidal (anymore)   
And I'm able to get myself out of bed on a consistent basis for things other than work. 

I just wish I had 2 parents who cared about me and wanted me to happy and prosper in life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not off the cheeseburgers, lookin like that. He's obviously on the cheeseburgers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your abbreviation of Olive Garden made me laugh. Haha OG shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first half of this is used as a title card in a later episode of the Boondocks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT DOES THE FOX SAY? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You have enemies? Good. That means you stood up for something, sometime in your life."

-Winston Churchill, A.K.A.

NOT FUCKING EMINEM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or even better, have Cage travel back to 1776, and kidnap Thomas Jefferson while he is holding The Declaration of Independence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shenanigans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Littering and...smoking the reefer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 19:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always been wary of anyone named Emily (or any spelling thereof) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 21:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck! If you need someone to talk to, I'll be available. I'm going sober as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 21:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This post means a lot, especially as I am increasing my therapy schedule for my depression. I decided to go more frequently after surviving my last suicide attempt. I've tried three times in the past 6 months, and the main responses I've heard were "oh its just a phase" and "what do you have to depressed about?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 06:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound like my best friend from when I was at Ball State  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 05:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except his terrible PR is actually helping his poll numbers. Old, white Americans hate things that aren't them, including the young, blacks, and Mexicans...and they hate them even more if they are a combo of previously stated demographics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! Have you ever heard of Reaganomics? Or seen our prison statistics...by percentage, not number </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 03:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I went to the woods because I wished to live deliberately, to front only the essential facts of life, and see if I could not learn what it had to teach, and not, when I came to die, discover that I had not lived." - Thoreau

-Thornton Mellon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 21:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm saying. They should tie him to a tree, beat him half to death, shoot him in both his legs, and leave him to die.

And since he is an illegal alien, we should ignore the 6th and 8th Amendments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 15:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought California had the 3 strikes rule? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 08:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't Supes treat Olson like shit on several occasions  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 08:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People's Elbow has so much more hype. Many more people have seen Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson use the elbow than Zelda using "The Knee of Justice"

More people have seen the WWE/WWF at its peak than SSBM/SS Brawl/ SS4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 07:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most street level characters lose at round 4, if they don't already lose at round 3. Dhalsim is a range attacking mofo who breathes fire. Reed Richards is not what I would consider street level, either by his intellect or powers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are 3 of the most consistently crime and violence ridden cities in the U.S. over the last 15 years or so. 

Personally, STL is only bad in the north and east, and certain parts of the city itself. 

Source: born and raised in the area </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm actually thankful I got arrested </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 13:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 13:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just did my math...also 25 grand in 4 years. An extra 25 grand? That's a down payment on a house </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 07:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not with the new CBA. He'll sign 1 or 2 at the most, then restructure when the salary cap jumps from 60 mil to 108 mil  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 07:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I added rounds because I forgot to address this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the strongest character Composite Liam Neeson can defeat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 05:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This includes composites of other actors' roles, as well as particular characters. 

Also: exclude the fact that he played Jesus Christ in the film Pilgrim's Progress.

Y'all can add in more roles that he has played, but right off the top of my head, he has played:

Ras Al-Ghul    
Gawain (Excalibur)   
Qui-Gon Jinn    
Oskar Schindler     
Aslan (Narnia)   
Zeus (Clash of the Titans)   
The guy from the Taken movies

Edit: Rounds for this.

Round 1: using movie roles only. 

Round 2: using source material only. 

Round 3: anything and everything goes (except for the Jesus thing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 08:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The owner of this laptop will respond, they will get their laptop back, and then this post will end up on /r/bestof

I give it 24 hours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 08:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Panem et Circenses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 08:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks kinda trippy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 04:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas, if you can handle it or follow it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 01:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally dozens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 01:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 37? In a row? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weed best be numero uno in an area where it is actually legal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm salty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 12:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wake up early, decide to watch a movie on Netflix, I'm thinking Taxi Driver, why not....good film, great film. Wouldn't you know, Netflix just removed it from their services 7 hours ago!?!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah they shouldn't. I'm getting my suit pressed just for this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arrested. Can't be around, or test positive for THC. But my BAC can sure rise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good info </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kokomo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Changes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may not be able to indulge in my #1 activity anymore, but I can sure as fuck indulge in activity #2: drinking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if we burn it, then how can our Lord and Saviour Nic Cage steal it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 06:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude that sucks. How did they get the consent to search the car? But yeah I'm calling around tomorrow for lawyers to see if they can drop my record, and what they have to say about not acknowledging my Miranda rights </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 04:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 04:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doubting that; the more I read.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 04:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blue state vs red state differences  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 04:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading is my Xanax for when Xanax isn't available. And I'm reasonably good at making first impressions so I should be ok.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 04:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because it is medically legal in Illinois, as far as I know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 04:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was told that it was more than likely going to be worked down to a littering charge, which would be a moderate fine and some community service </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 04:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking it will be fine. I'm only 21. Just some fines and shit to pay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 04:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was what the state trooper and CO I talked to told me. I'm just a little worried because I've never been in legal trouble before. Not even a speeding ticket </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's funny, but no one around had a sense of humor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am 21. I was forward with the officer, told him what he would find when he searched the vehicle, and admitted what I had was mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Idk if Narcan is even legal as well  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I'm caught with anything in the next 5 years, it's an instant felony with jail time, so I'm going to be overcautious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much. They got me a quick court date, so I'm thinking they have more important cases...or its a decently quick court system in Indiana </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He probably didn't bother with reading my rights because the most talking I did was small talk on the way to booking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is interesting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll just see how everything falls into place tomorrow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've talked to a few people who have been in my shoes in this state. They said that I could get the charges pled down to just a fine and either community service or rehab </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I'm seeing a lawyer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that would be insanely fucked. Then I probably would find my way into a jail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did they get you for, and what kind of punishment are you looking at, if you don't mind me asking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking Miranda v Arizona but I don't know if that will apply here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh it's literally a Supreme Court precedent. Miranda v Arizona </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 00:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're telling me. At least I have drinking. I can legally do that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 00:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably not, but I don't plan on being back in there in any capacity, so I honestly don't care about that. The guy in the cell with me looked like a legitimate Aryan skinhead...but who knows  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 00:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only know about Dresden because of Kurt Vonnegut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 00:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indiana. 

Edit: Where most people are hard laced conservatives, every drug is equally horrible and our governor thinks SCOTUS made the wrong decision.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 00:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had nothing else to do, so I asked for a book or something to read. It was the only book they had, apparently  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 23:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It stunned me more than anything. I figured he would either take it himself to smoke, or throw it out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 23:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll still ask either way, but I don't expect it to change a thing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 23:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What state is that? Because mine is going to likely be fines. They could press for jail time, but I have no priors, I cooperated with everything, I'm in college and have an almost full time job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 23:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not set up. Just the CO started telling me about people who went down the wrong path in life while I was changing into my jail clothes. And the other guy just happened to be in the same holding cell as me...they said he was arrested about 25 times in his life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 23:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talking to my lawyer tomorrow about it, hoping everything goes well when court rolls around. Sending good vibes your way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 22:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad called me a drug lord. The CO and I had a heart to heart, and I had a long talk with a habitual offender. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
