<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2712</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 14:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very sad situation. It sounds like you're a great guy, and I feel for you dude. I don't understand her end game though. You said she has an agenda. What is it? Why is she keeping her kids from a good father? And then being plain mean to him? Just...wtf!?!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 16:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been pretty neutral on gun control in the US. This story did it for me. A house party turning into a battle zone can't happen in most countries because of sensible gun laws. 





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 09:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks guys! 

This is a subject I don't know a lot about, so all input is appreciated. When I hear HSBC say things like "the world economy is like an ocean liner without a lifeboat" it makes me wonder what's going to happen to my RMB. That, and I'm sure China's plateauing growth can't be good either, but I don't know how that works either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm an expat living in China. I just recently received a document allowing me to wire as much of my RMB to the US. Would now be a good time to exchange my RMB into USD? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 13:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 18:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's real. In China, that might be tofu powder in Daisy's urn. Pictures like this are common to prove the job is well done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The vet said he would send confirmation after he properly cremated my friend's dog, but he didn't say how... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 17:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 08:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HAHAHA The magazine finally gave credit to "The Moth and the Flame actually not cheesy for once..." Just when I thought they couldn't get any sleezier...they totally redeem themselves!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 16:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shitty China internet. I can't read the graaaaaph </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 18:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 18:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Cherry red chariot, excess is just my nature." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 18:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Craziest story here! What's the custody situation? Did you bring up her trying to murder you in the divorce proceedings?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 18:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he's working for or the equivalent of Goldman Sachs/Marryl Lynch, it's no surprise he's working these hours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How important is a wedding engagement? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 08:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 16:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A mentally impaired man lived with his adorable parents in the house across the street.

I never saw him out of the house unless he was being led into the family's Lincoln Towncar. He shuffled. He mostly stared at the ground. He really was just a sad kid in a middle aged man's pot bellied, unshaven body, but at 6 that made zero sense to me. 

So when he was hunched over the fence, ogling me as I biked up and down our culdesac one summer afternoon, I was confused. When he asked if I had rope and tape, I was scared. When he opened the gate and chased me back to my driveway, I was terrified. 

I still have a vivid memory of me jumping off the rear bumper of my dad's car to reach the rope hanging from the bottom of the garage door, and turning the lock.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 04:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [New Slaves](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dT3swdCJrrg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 05:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good cuddle session can be better than sex. I think everyone just wants to feel connected to someone, even if it's just for a night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 14:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good stuff. If you don't mind, I'm going to go through your links later and ask some follow-up questions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do sample heavy groups like Moby or even the Avalanches make their songs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 11:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's magic to me. What equipment do they use? What software? And how are they using that equipment and software?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 11:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oklahoma Joe's? 
I haven't lived in KC for a few years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 12:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we got a badass over here!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 16:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Forgetful tourist?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
