<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7157</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 06:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. I can relate to that. I used to listen to music and would just be able to escape for a while.  I tried the other day and I really struggled with listening to music. I would turn off the music a few minutes after. Pm me if you feel like you ever want to talk to someone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 14:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am experiencing the same with ear ringing. It's irritating. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 08:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won't do it. I've been wondering about it but now I feel a bit better with others saying no and there are options.  Thank you guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forgot to take medication </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 08:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot to take my anti depressant medicine and I'm already in bed. I usually take it every evening.  Should I take it now anyway?? (2am EST here) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not sure if this is the right place... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 06:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been thinking about shaving my eyebrows off so I can grow them back and shape my eyebrows better... Has anyone have done this before? Does it help? Should I leave my eyebrows alone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm his wife, hi :) Message me as well.

UPDATE: Tickets are sold. Apologies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 06:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sharing. Needed to read this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 00:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'll check it out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 00:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 00:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you melt the coconut oil first before putting it on your face to be able to wipe the makeup off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alternative Makeup Remover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 00:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might have missed it when I was searching on reddit's search bar but because I ran out of makeup remover wipes, I was wondering what would be the best way to remove makeup? Olive oil, coconut oil, something that may be safe for me to remove makeup at home?? I have no means of transportation to buy more makeup remover wipes. (I got in a car accident, long story but I'm okay.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 00:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THEY HAVE IT IN MACY'S? WHERE HAVE I BEEN? O_O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 23:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PRODUCTS USED IN PICTURE:

* Too Faced Born This Way - Light Beige
* NYX Concealer Wand - Porcelain
* NYX Highlight and Contour Pro Palette
* NYX Baked Blush - Solistice
* Too Faced Sweethearts Perfect Flush Blush - Peach Beach
* Too Faced Chocolate Bar Eyeshadow Palette Collection - used "White Chocolate", "Salted Caramel", "Marzipan" and "Champagne Truffle"
* NYX Lush Lashes Mascara - Voluptous
* Maybelline Express Line Eyeliner - Ebony Black
* NYX Butter Lipstick - "Lollies"
* NYX Matte Finish Makeup Setting Spray </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 23:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did it really, really light.... I was a little bit scared.  I didn't want to look really heavy with the contour.  Thank you for the feedback!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 23:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!! I'll keep in mind on blending the forehead better. I'm very picky with the foundation...  I hope it's the lighting lol. Again, thank you for your wonderful comment! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 23:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes CCW :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 22:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will add products list when I can when I'm not on my phone! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
