<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1555</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 10:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "'Have I gone mad?' 'I'm afraid so. You're entirely bonkers. But I'll tell you a secret. All the best people are.'" - Alice in Wonderland 

I don't know why, but this quote has stuck with me throughout my childhood. I guess it just makes me feel better about being my normal, weird, kinda crazy, self.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 13 y/o Ms. Kitty and her favorite Okamiden plush animal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 04:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 04:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have stopped cutting for a while, but the scars are very visible and go all the way up my forearms, so i really have no reasonable excuse for them. I normally wear long sleeves but its been getting pretty warm lately, so ive been using henna tattoo pens to draw on my arms in the hopes that it will distract people from the scars. its worked for me for a while. if its recent cuts, one of my friends suggested saying that its make-up and you were practicing doing special effects make-up art.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 08:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you. I didn't know that existed until now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not sure but at this point I'm too afraid to ask.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> probably required a helluva lot of beer for the guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 08:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diana is a very conflicting name for me. on one hand I have my best friend. on the other I have my 390 lb aunt who has 6 children from 5 different one night stands.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 04:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diana, you are a self-centered waste of space who has earned the title "Jabba the Slut" from most of your family.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 04:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soundgarden in 2011. it's been a while but my next concert is going to be Foo Fighters in September.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 07:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that one squeaky spot in the floor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
