<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4298</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 06:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty dull party.... who died? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 06:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ladies and Gentlemen, we need to immediately evacuate the pool. You may continue to swim if you have no fear of piranhas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 00:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm not black. I'm back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 18:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're back too?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 17:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm... to share on Facebook or not to share on Facebook.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 17:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuckin dirty back people... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 17:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! I'm Back and I find this offensive! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 17:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How ironic: Arranges the vegetables in a sexually suggestive way, so in return he *"Gets the Sack"* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 08:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's just Dan's search history. he accidentally typed it into twitter instead of google </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 07:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't remember anything from the first one. Except that you fight Cloud in Hercules's world.

I'd much rather watch Kingdom Grumps 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 21:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just realized how long the cutscenes are combined... maybe that's why they haven't played it yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People downvote factually accurate information on this sub quite often. I don't know why </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, I wonder if he's ever shit himself and subsequently delayed a video for a decade </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know about it until Arin said it. And this was one of my favorite games growing up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they'd just get the video removed or more likely, claim all of the revenue on the video. I think they'd only sue if the person kept re-uploading the video, fully aware of his/her copyright infringement.

But they'd have to send a cease-and-desist before they brought the person to court </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's possible that they were singing songs owned by Universal Music Publishing, which Maker signed a deal with them that allows their partners to use their library of music.

It's also possible that Maker just didn't see those videos where they were singing those songs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why they haven't yet. They're such big Disney fans, Arin has an awesome Keyblade as decoration, and the game is phenomenal!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need to start a petition </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe for an hour-hour and a half one-off. I really loved the Endless Ocean videos, but those work well the way they did. I wouldn't want to see it as a series because it would last for the rest of my life (damn, imagine how much longer it'd be if they played as a stealthy character in Skyrim) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They need to play Pokemon Snap. It'd be a nice, short, but funny series. Lots of laughs to be had with throwing the apples and poison balls as Dan describes the horrific animal abuse Arin is inflicting upon these creatures </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, this is a *fine pickle!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can make it. You just kinda flap your tongue between your lips really fast while breathing in slowly

Edit: I guess my statement required some downvotes for some reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 16:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It tastes pretty good, actually </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 09:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mad Dog 20/20 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 07:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, in the contract, they do ask for access to your password (they kinda need it to view the ad revenue so they can determine their share of the profits.)

Something like this makes sense. Put a video on private so that no claims can be made against it until the Grumps resolve the issue by either censoring the singing or changing it to a parody of the original song.

Here's something I feel everyone who doesn't understand what a MCN like Maker is or does should read: (it covers all the basics)

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Multi-channel_network </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 07:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To protect the Grumps from legal action from the songs' owners.  Plain and simple. They may have had an insider tip that some people in the industry were litigiously searching for copyright infringements on youtube.

All it takes is three strikes and your channel is shut down permanently. Game Grumps has more than three videos that could be flagged for copyright infringement. And Youtube treats you as guilty until proven innocent.

Exchange of advice for money was *just an example* of the services that MCNs provide. For Game Grumps specifically, they find better brand deals and targeted advertising toward the demographic their audience is categorized as </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 18:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't "display an entire work" if the work is interactive. One person's experience playing a game will be different than another's. Again, watching a video of gameplay is not the same as playing a game. 

The LP video is a separate product entirely.

Fair use is a defense for when someone is taken to court over an issue such as this. (Civil laws are also upheld in court, in case you didn't know)

Two of the things a court would use to determine if Fair Use applies are:
the nature of the copyrighted work (In LP cases: a platform for the real product, *Commentary* to be provided)
the effect of the use upon the potential market for or value of the copyright work. (This varies based on the game's quality, but it at least represents an honest portrayal, as opposed to game trailers or reviews)

Last, but certainly most important, **there is no absolute rules as to how much of a copyrighted work may be copied and still be considered a fair use.**  http://itlaw.wikia.com/wiki/Fair_use

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 16:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say they were parodying the game, they are providing commentary. Fair use protects parody AND commentary, two different things entirely. Distributing a video of them playing a game, with commentary, doesn't infringe copyright, because the game is not meant to be observed, but interacted with.

The legality of these videos hasn't been established because nobody's ever questioned it, but one day when someone brings a LPer to court (likely Nintendo) it will (hopefully) rule in this industry's favor, because they are not releasing the same product as the game company. Watching gameplay and playing a game are not the same thing.


My point is, it's in a grey area now, legally, but as long as it is a grey area, Nintendo is not entitled to that revenue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 16:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant from a legal standpoint. If it's youtube we're talking, the biggest enemy is their policy of "you're guilty until proven innocent. And we won't listen to you when you try to prove your innocence" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 15:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first one with Jon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 15:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nintendo's been the biggest enemy since Let's Plays became a thing.

Truth is, Nintendo isn't entitled to the revenue because the players are providing commentary, which is the purpose of watching them.

This is considered a "transformative" use and is protected by copyright law.

I think the Grumps will just ignore Nintendo's greedy behaviors and play whatever they want </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 15:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but usually deals like this would specify when they'd expire, if they do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 15:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, yes, i was being silly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 04:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maker studios has signed a deal for their partners to be able to monetize and cover for the full library of music that is registered under Universal Music Publishing. http://www.billboard.com/biz/articles/news/1538590/universal-music-publishing-inks-deals-with-fullscreen-maker-studios </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 04:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, Mr. President, the floor is yours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 04:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No! Fuck this job! I don't need to answer phones all day for *your* ass! I QUIT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 04:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you like the "All-You-Can-Eat-Teeth" special? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 04:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh look, a locked bathroom door when my parents are gone for the weekend...  

[Source](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z4G0bYxuv7M) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 04:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just think.... several times a year they'll just keep changing it to something even shittier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 04:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **I'll start it off:**

"I'm having a waking nightmare,

I'm seeing colors in the sky...

Everybody wants to know about me,

but they don't know about my........

big ol' penis, flopping around,

it's three big feet of pleasure.

Put it in your mouth and put it in your vagine...

Everyone's having a real good time,

when they're hanging around my big floppy penis.

Can't quite stroke it really fast.

Covering three feet of skin with your hand isn't really easy.

Here's how fast I can jack my whole dick,

"Hah, ah, ah, ah, aaahhh."

That includes the back and forth motion,

let's do it again, "Ah aahhh."

"Ah ah ah ah ah ah aaahhhh..."

That's how fast I can jack my peen.

Everybody thinks that they have seen my penis,

but they haven't,

'cuz if they have...

they'd shit themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 03:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maker does not own his content, so his partnership with them is irrelevant. Youtube is an international platform and they also do not own his content. 

Okay, I guess I didn't realize (or care) where he lives, but it seems he currently lives in England.

A quick search of England's definition of Fair Use seems to indicate that their copyright laws are nearly identical to America's.

BUT, I just found a neat little thing during my quick research:

Maker studios has signed a deal (as has Fullscreen) for their partners to be able to monetize and cover for the full library of music that is registered under Universal Music Publishing. http://www.billboard.com/biz/articles/news/1538590/universal-music-publishing-inks-deals-with-fullscreen-maker-studios

That's a pretty big conglomerate and is likely where he's getting this music from (I don't know though, I've only seen a video or two of his, and immediately had to click away before I destroyed my laptop) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 03:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't miss it, I just felt like rectifying it. Too many people seem to think hearsay = fact </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 02:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pretty loose with the word "confirmed" aren't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 02:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweden doesn't recognize all of the U.S's copyright laws.

There is also no broad statutory limitation of fair use or fair dealing in Sweden, so he's far more protected in this area than anyone from America, where you literally can't even sing a song without the rights to do so, or a mechanical license and royalty payments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 02:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not fact. Straight up myth

Edit: I already received a downvote for being factually accurate, so lemme post this here:

Fair use is a defense one can use if taken to court for using a copyrighted work without permission. 

In its most general sense, a fair use is any copying of copyrighted material done for a limited (less than 30 seconds) and transformative purpose, such as to comment upon, criticize, or parody a copyrighted work. Such uses can be done without permission from the copyright owner.

Game Grumps singing random songs (in most of their cases) even people on youtube singing cover songs are NOT covered by this. It's illegal because it is a violation of U.S copyright law </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 02:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They weren't "assimilated" by them. Too many people fail to understand what a MCN is and what it does. This is what it boils down to; a channel signs with them and they find good brand deals, better CPM rates, advice for growing a fanbase, or production assistance in return for a very small cut of the channel's profits. The end.

Maker doesn't own them, therefore they couldn't have 'assimilated' them. They're still an independent channel. MCNs function like a talent agency.

As for whether they started out **partnering** with Maker, that depends on whether or not Egoraptor and Jon were partnered with them before starting the channel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 21:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may now *kiss the bride*  (under his breath) ......ya filthy animal.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 16:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, that was really funny! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 06:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10 outta 10 would watch.

2 outta 10 might enjoy

:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remember When Uncle Jerry Would Molest Us? [Video] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 02:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 01:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will Jacques and Arin ever finish off the creators of Sonic 06? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 00:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> man, people will complain about anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 00:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want you to know that I watched the whole video and didn't learn ONE DAMN THING! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 19:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, Arin originally conceived of the show as a podcast.

I'm curious as to what the format of it was before they decided to include gameplay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 19:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he's just working on something that just hasn't come out yet.

Like more Table Flip or editing Guild Grumps. Or maybe business-y shit. Or some secret, unrevealed projects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 19:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you are correct. He's also in others.

https://www.youtube.com/results?search_query=idiots+always+ask

I also can't count on my hands how many times I've seen this video posted on the subreddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 19:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the point of the show is to talk and make jokes. They're performing, and that's a completely different mindset than just carrying a conversation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 04:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to dress up like a rabbit and go hide some eggs! I hope being dead for three days didn't affect my brain cells </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 16:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the wit is strong with this one :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's had several jobs, but the one he quit after Starbomb sold a lot of copies was at Maker Studios, which he's been pretty private about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he used the word 'tutelage.' They can't comprehend his classiness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn! you beat me to my comment! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So he shoots web from his anus, and he bites his enemies to knock em unconscious and he eats em while they're still alive.... we think Tobey Macguire should play this Man-Spider character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming THIS summer... Remember that thing from the 80's that was really popular with kids because kids are stupid and they grow up remembering it as a masterpiece?

**THAT!** Rated PG-13 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today we learned that Blue used to be on the police force as a drug sniffing dog! They had to let him go when he got addicted to all the cocaine he snuffed out... but there was NO ONE better at finding it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe you cheated on me! You USED me! I'm gonna go fucking CUT that bitch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Man, yawning sure is contagious... I bet if we both yawn at the same time, we can get this whole group to yawn..............." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may be asking yourself.... did he fire six Nerf bullets? Or five? Well, this my friend, is from Hasbro... the most powerful Nerf gun in the neighborhood... so you gotta ask yourself one question... do you feel lucky, buttface? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where the sun ACTUALLY goes at night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ba da.... ba........ ba BA....... I'm........ Loving it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now imagine a world where Bing had the monopoly on search engines.

How weird would it be to say "I need information... lemme Bing that."

or "I Binged myself the other day.... Apparently there's a gay pornstar with the same name as me.... he's actually quite talented" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last week I pooped and it didn't need wiping at all... thinking back, I'm wondering if I was just not paying attention, pulled up my pants, and walked around with a poopy ass all day.... I wonder if my co-workers smelled it on me.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean I'm not special, Daddy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was gonna make a comment, wondering why a company named itself pizza hut, but hell, if they invented it, it's a fair name </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be patented, trademarked, and only sold by the shittiest company out there... probably pizza hut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty fucked, considering there are people in this world that have super-powers and I'm not one of em! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Man, I just wanna cum on that dude's cock and make another dude suck the cum off of his cock while jerking off into a pudding cup.... then I'll give the pudding to my grampa and call him a cum-swallowing faggot"

...pretty vulgar, eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Warning: Mature Content.

I've been looking to create more improvised content on my youtube channel. I've always ad-libbed here and there in my videos, but this is our first attempt at just straight improvising something from beginning to end and I'm actually quite proud of it, and wanted to share it with fellow improv aficionados.

I need to get my improvisation chops up because I'm conceptualizing a daily improv show/webseries </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 03:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not a monthly Toon Grumps on Grumpout or Arin/Ross's channel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 07:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if they cancelled Game Grumps on April 1st purely by coincidence?

"Oh, Ross, I didn't even realize it was April Fool's Day... they all think we're joking..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Gamer's Love Song - Music Video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 23:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 17:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, the end of your comment had my sides hurtin a bit :D XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 17:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are so many explanations out there, but the gist of it is, it's impossible to put out content on a consistent basis. Therefore, the CPM rates are low (cost of an ad every time it reaches 1,000 people) and when your paycheck is low when you're already only putting out a video every few months, that's impossible to live on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 17:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Astronaut suits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 05:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. It looks more artistic and significant with polygonal graphics.

God, I miss the polygon era. Everyone's nostalgic about 16-bit graphics, I'm nostalgic about N64/PS1 graphics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 05:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wouldn't it be wiser to include a link if you're going to promote your channel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 21:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They missed ALL of the levels I was really looking forward to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 21:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Covering songs without paying for the rights is copyright infringement. That's why its an issue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 21:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That recent Endless Ocean 2 one-off was phenomenal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 21:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why does every rap battle on youtube have to steal the format of ERB?

And why are they so quiet? It's like they were recording the lyrics, but didn't want their mom to hear them. Not to mention that they don't enunciate a lot of those words, and rap in mumbles. Did they think it was okay to not be understandable as long as they include subtitles?

I'm not usually critical, but my god, that was horrible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 21:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10/10 Would Bang </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 21:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is Adan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
