<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6825</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 06:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over-analyzing a shitty comedian's joke for internal philosophical consistency? 

Congratulations, you're a libertarian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hickenlooper Ally: You Toothless Rednecks Dont Even Have Roads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 00:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 23:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not calling her a liar, but, unless she has a certain amount of familiarity with firearms, it's unlikely she would be able to differentiate between a gun that has jammed vs once that has been shot until empty, especially during the course of the event. 

I suspect that the experts with the Pima County Sheriffs Department would be able to suss out the difference, however.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 23:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His opinion of the places shows the typical New Yorker disdain for any place outside of NYC. 

No wonder he and other big money groups dropped their support for Morse and Giron after they lost.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 22:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://tucson13.nytimes-institute.com/2013/05/23/sheriff-releases-photos-of-11-tucson-shooting/

During the attack, Loughner emptied one 33-round magazine into the crowd.* A second magazine jammed, giving bystanders a chance to tackle him before the first police officers arrived.*

http://articles.latimes.com/2011/jan/09/nation/la-na-0110-gabrielle-giffords-20110110

He finally changed the magazine and tried to fire, *but the gun jammed. * Meanwhile, two men from the crowd grabbed him and subdued him, officials said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 22:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The after-action reports and analyses for most mass shooting events are freely available. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 22:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Violent crime is only the justification for selling these cockamamie ideas to the public. 

The people who supported these laws knew they would not do anything to actually reduce violence. 

Rather, it was all about sticking it to an out-of-power constituency in order to put on a show for the national-level party bosses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 22:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loughner was shooting people at contact distance and was taken down when his gun jammed, not when he was reloading. 

So your one and only example of a shooting where limited capacity magazines might have made a difference is pretty much a useless data point. 

Your claim is clearly counter-balanced by all of the mass shooters who clearly had no problems killing many people despite their limited capacity guns.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bloomberg dismisses Colo. Springs, Pueblo as roadless, rural backwaters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 22:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Misguided Open-Carry Movement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 20:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jailed For 3 Months In Mexico, U.S. Marine Reservist Gets Hearing : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 19:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For Residents, Chicago Violence Is 'Very Personal' : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 18:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roy Exum: Groundhog Day In Chicago - 07/09/2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 18:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 15:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I generally like Texans, but holy fuck you guys suck at winter driving.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 06:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the karma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 05:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are clearly a moron.

Go take an actual firearms safety class and learn how guns actually work and then maybe we can talk when you have dealt with your ignorance.

But you won't, because actually learning things is hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 23:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So your solution to violent crime is to pass a ban on a form of device that is mechanically simple, essentially lasts forever, and where teens of millions of them already exist in the wild? 

Never mind the fact that a magazine ban will have no effect on the outcome of a mass shooting event. 

What your argument boils down to is that you're willing to arrest, try, convict, and imprison tens of millions of lawful citizens simply because they own a plastic box with a spring in it. 

That's pathetic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No Lawyers - Only Guns and Money: Media Bias Or Lazy Reporting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 21:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 19:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, you're the one that enables violence by disallowing people effective means of self defense.

Your policies would result in far more deaths, on aggregate, than pro-gun policies do, but I guess you would find that acceptable as long as people are murdered by methods other than shooting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senators Cruz, Paul and Lee Insist on Pro-gun Amendments to Do-Nothing Harry Reid Preservation Bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 19:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Responding to Parking Lot Law Critics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 19:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10 Years for the Bloomberg Model Gun Control Mayor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 19:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 16:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your feels don't trump others civil rights. 

Don't like guns? 

Fine. 

Don't carry one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 03:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sara Brady doesn't speak as brazenly or as often about guns as Piers Morgan did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 23:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John Walsh? 

Where the hell is CNN recruiting their talent from, a timer warp to 1986? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 14:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to give a name/email/zip to submit your votes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 13:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. Probably hit by a car or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> View From The Porch: Le sigh... (TSA and flying with guns.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 19:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 19:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a big fat list compiling examples of anti-gun activists threatening violence or engaging in violence. 

http://www.saysuncle.com/index.php?s=%22so+violent%22 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 18:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stumbled across this post a year or so ago, and had been unable to relocate it. 

Thanks for posting this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 05:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't twist your words, you mouth-breathing imbecile.

The bottom line is that TSA has never, not once, stopped a terrorist, and there's no evidence that they're any more effective than pre 9-11 security, especially given that they have such a tremendous failure rate.

Furthermore, the fact that TSA does actually manage to find a gun now and then, or a shampoo bottle that holds more than 3 oz. is hardly indicative of their utility.

In case you hadn't noticed, this is the USA, and a lot of people here own a lot of guns, and, frankly, the way the TSA trots them out like they're any sort of proof to justify their phoney-baloney jobs is utterly laughable.

The way TSA agents react to the finding of even a single shell casing (or toy gun) like they've just found a case full of plutonium is laughable.

As for actual guns, yeah, people forget that they may have one in a bag, and yet they do it less regularly than TSA forgets about their own protocols for being able to legally fly with firearms.

But, yes, please do continue to justify feeling up toddlers, your posts amuse me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 05:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's hilarious that youcompared TSA to actual law enforcement officers who apprehend actual criminals committing actual crimes.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 04:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, what you're saying is that the TSA has stopped exactly zero terrorists, but they have confiscated a list of things you find scawwy, (things that would have been just as easily detected by pre-TSA security) as well as leveled charges against one guy who you expect us to hate because he's a rich douchebag or something.

What's it like being the kind of person that defends a useless federal organization that spends most of it's time finding ways to justify touching children and attractive women?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 01:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that the book that claims that a Glock can go through a metal detector? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 01:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I don't have a problem with people interested in honest debate, but good posts have clearly been nothing but outright trolling for quite some time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 01:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Australia, that's the country where the criminals make guns in clandestine machine shops, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 01:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a shame you wish to see people dissenters and unable to defend themselves. 

I know people who have successfully used guns in self defense. 

Why do you want to see them dead?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-06 23:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About damn time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 23:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That stock wouldn't be legal for use in service rifle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 21:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The original proposal for instituting the NFA would have made handguns NFA items.

Of course, if handguns are an NFA item, you can't have someone cutting the barrel down on a rifle or shotgun to make it easier to conceal, hence the barrel length requirements.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 20:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even Bota Box is better than yellow tail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 18:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love when they make that argument, frankly, because it means that you've won.

Here, let me explain:

The people who make that argument aren't giving any actual thought to the enormous failures our government would have to suffer for that to happen.

They're essentially unconcerned that for that scenario to play out, the entire Bill of Rights would have to be suspended, along with prohibitions on the military operating on US soil, and a whole host of other things that would have to fail in order for such a confiscation to happen.

What they're focused on isn't the scenario, or whether citizens could successfully fight a military, or anything else.

Rather, they're engaging in a form of public masturbation.

On a visceral level, these people *hate* gun owners. They see gun owners as an impediment to the ability to create a better world.

As a result, they want nothing more than to see gun owners killed.

On top of that, most of the people who make the argument that gun owners can't stand up to the military also hail from the same political viewpoint that has an ardent hatred for the military as well, seeing them as the embodiment of America's crass imperialistic designs.

From where I sit, the people who make this argument don't make it out of any actual practical sense, but engage in it because, frankly, they hate the military and they hate gun owners, and (being too cowardly to take direct action themselves) they would like nothing better than to pit two groups of people they hate against one another.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 22:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll occasionally do two WODs in a day at my gym. 

Depending on what they morning workout is, I'll usually opt to do something different. 

If the morning WOD was a metcon, I'll focus on strength, or vice-versa. 

The trainers at my gym are good about putting together an alternate workout for me, though sometimes space is a consideration that has to be worked around. 

You'll feel a little self conscious during the workout, but you'll get over it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSSF study- Target Shooting in America: Millions of Shooters, Billions of Dollars - The Firearm Blog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 19:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 15:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Avoid Paras. They're cheap because they fall apart.

There's a reason why none of the high level USPSA shooters use them (unless they're sponsored by Para.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 03:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh,look, he thinks he's still presidential material. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Firearms makers moving to more gun-friendly U.S. southern states </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 19:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CSGV: Trouble in Marketing Paradise. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 01:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pro-Gun Control Lawmaker Indicted for 'Improper Sexual Relationship' with Teen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 22:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Racist Open Carry in Ohio is not a Bloomberg False Flag </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 19:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Not Really Doing Anything New On Guns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 18:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Metcalf Really Needs to Stop Digging </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 18:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why We Can't Talk About Gun Control </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 17:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 03:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something about invertebrates killing vertebrates makes me uncomfortable on a truly deep level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analysis Shows Gun Websites of All Kinds Get Far, Far More Traffic Than Gun Control Websites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 21:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 19:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many of the posts there are a great example of the deep-seated psychological anxieties of gun control fans. 

It's really amazing how simple-minded and profoundly fearful they are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obamas Biggest Disappointment? Guns - Washington Wire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 13:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 06:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to be able to use a firearm for self defense without getting yourself dead or into legal hot water, your very first step should be to get enrolled in one of the NRA training courses that focus on home defense.

To find a list of local training courses, go to this website:
http://www.nrainstructors.org/searchcourse.aspx

Or look up your local gun shops, give them a call, and ask if they offer courses or can recommend a local instructor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 23:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you liked it, however, nothing I can possibly say would be worth the spillage of good whiskey!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 20:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So your solution to end gun violence is to threaten peaceful gun owning citizens with gun violence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 20:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the mods don't really ban anyone, which is not a policy I agree with. 

I'm all for open discussions with fence-sitters and curious/open-minded anti-gun people, but the toleration of people who have admitted to being here only to troll mystifies me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colorado Restaurant Wants Customers, Employees To Carry Guns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 19:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 18:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He really is.

I mean, he sucks at arguing.
He's not creative.
His posts are neither witty, insightful, or relevant.

Yet he keeps coming back, saying stupid things that demonstrate his foolishness.

I suspect he likes to troll because mommy and daddy are too busy to give little extremeftw* the attention he so craves.


*Even his name is a sad little bleat for attention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 17:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no reason why Bloomberg's people couldn't have hired a group of locals to pull this off.

After all, when you're a multibillionaire, throwing a few thousand bucks at some white trash yokels, plus the cost of a few rifles, is nothing.

That said, until there's evidence to the contrary, I don't think there's a conspiracy here, and these "people" really are that stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 17:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So your solution to over a century of failed gun control policies is to double down on failure?

What's it like being a loser? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 13:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have federal gun control, clearly it's an abject failure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 20:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For what it's worth, it was a pleasure reading your posts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 20:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the overall rates of homicide for both the US and Australia are roughly the same and have been trending downwards for the same period of time, which is a pretty clear indicator that whatever has caused a drop in crime in Australia isn't actually the removal of Australia's gun rights.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 20:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd rather be burned alive than shot?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 20:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last time I checked, Australian criminals had built quite a decent side business importing illicit guns or constructing them in clandestine machine shops.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 20:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cars and booze weren't designed to kill, yet kill far more people than guns, which supposedly are only for killing. 

You'd think that someone who was worried about preventable deaths would be far more concerned with the far higher number of deaths caused by devices that aren't even supposed to be deadly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 05:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a lot of firearms that don't have manual safeties, e.g. high end target pistols, revolvers, and some striker fired guns like Glocks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 05:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In an ideal world, no one would graduate high school without knowing these rules.

It'd be the same as driver's ed or sex ed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 05:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Modern guns (with the exception of some rimfires) will stand up to tens of thousands of rounds of dry fire practice before suffering any kind of wear and tear.

All of the best competition shooters swear by dry fire practice, and it's a cheap and easy way to build your skill set.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 02:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dry fire practice is one of the best ways to increase your marksmanship abilities. 

All of the best competition shooters use dry fire and advocate for it as a training aid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A New Jersey Law That's Kept Smart Guns Off Shelves Nationwide : All Tech Considered : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 19:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 05:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awhile back there was a woman who made three posts about a malevolent creature that showed up.

The description of it was creepy: arms of uneven length, short, large head and skin that looked like it was bruised all over.

The interactions she described were downright terrifying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge upholds Colorados gun laws, tosses lawsuit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 23:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Search Data Shows AR-15 Searches Far More Popular Than Searches For Moms Demand Action </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 22:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not happy with Kirkland Brand Omega 3 Fish Oil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 01:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So since getting interested in supplements, I've been supplementing with Kirkland Brand Fish Oil. The label says the capsules are 1,000mg each.

However, when looking at the nutrition label, it says that each tablet only contains 250 mg of EPA and DHA, and 50 mg of "Other Omega-3 fatty acids."

Examine.com references 250 mg as the minimum dose, and 6 g as being optimal for combatting muscle soreness, etc.

My plan was to kind of hit somewhere in the middle, and get a daily dose of 3 g, but frankly, the idea of swallowing upwards of 12 capsules (in addition to my other supplements) just holds no appeal.

Is there a better brand of fish oil that has a higher amount of EPA/DHA that anyone recommends?

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 22:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually quite relevant. 

I'd like to hear you're justification for some of the gun control laws that you endorse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 21:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The conditioning I refer to started in 1994 with the Republican revolution, something that would not have been possible without the massive political backlash resulting from the passage of the Federal Assault Weapon ban.

Bill Clinton, among others, acknowledged that it was the passage of gun control that sank the party in that election.

As a political issue, gun control has been shown to be a consistent loser for the democratic party, and the most ardent prohibitionists have been forced to moderate their tone and stridency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yes... yes they did : funny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 19:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 19:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say the you're the one with a problem of understanding how the world works. 

Murder and drunk driving both represent actions that in and of themselves are harmful to others.

Gun control laws, on the other hand, tend to treat all people exactly the same, regardless of whether they're a career criminal with a history of violence or an athlete competing in a shooting sport. 

While no one advocates for allowing criminals unfettered  access to guns, you have to be daft to support the kinds of gun control laws that would result in prison time simply because someone puts an adjustable stock on a target rifle or chooses to own a magazine that holds more than an arbitrarily-designated number of rounds.  

In short, the law can only punish people after an act has been committed, which is why laws punishing a murderer are good, and laws punishing someone who hasn't victimised anyone, but owns something you think is scary, are idiotic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 18:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most gun control advocates don't openly talk about confiscation because they've been conditioned, through years of lost elections and public mockery, to avoid using the c-word.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 15:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for posting a primary source, I agree that they're preferable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 06:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The better example would be the 1911.

What's particularly interesting is his attempt to create categories of acceptable guns vs. unacceptable guns, and its all wrapped in an appeal to antiquity.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 06:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. You can verify it via the BATFE web page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 06:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its probably just the one progun puff piece they run per year so they can still claim to be unbiased. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 02:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NSSF is based there as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 00:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spoiler:

Lady in the Water didn't have a twist, and that was kind of surprising.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Josh Sugarmann: Crazy Pants Fearmonger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 21:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That Awkward Moment A Judge Throws Out Your "Murder" Case Because You're A Moron Of A Prosecutor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 20:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Floating the idea of tiered carry permits for Indiana. (Kind of an interesting idea.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 20:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little Andrew: Cuomo has trouble in NY </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 19:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dell statement on schools web blocking suggests low traffic on anti-gun sites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 19:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.examiner.com/article/dell-statement-on-school-s-web-blocking-suggests-low-traffic-on-anti-gun-sites


For some reason I couldn't get the link to submit the normal way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CSGV: That pretty much sums it up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 19:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hickenlooper silent on gun law comments; supporters and foes baffled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 19:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 19:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how Josh Sugarmann comes across in this article. 

He's a fun-hating, finger-wagging, prohibitionist scold who thinks that kids who are winning state and regional level shooting competitions are too stupid to be safe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats in pro-gun states turn down help from Giffords </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 19:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gun sports gain favor among youth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 16:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 04:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they have to add up the numbers from an arbitrarily-picked date range, then you can pretty well be assured they're just trying to scare people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 04:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not creepy, but haunting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 04:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is stupid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 03:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Understanding this reference officially makes you old.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 05:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the infertile?

I guess they're just fucked, eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 04:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had no idea that moving money through a governmental intermediary erased the cost of this policy to a small business owner.

What an amazing economic discovery you've made! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 01:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which means he actually is paying for it. 

Unless he's cheating on his taxes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 23:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In retrospect, I've never been so effectively trolled by a video game.

It was a complete inversion of what happens in COD, and I almost quit playing at that point before realizing what an awesome commentary had been made.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bloomberg is Buying Calls to Congress, and Its Working </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 19:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For $4.95, This Service Will Lobby Politicians On Issues You Care About (Bloomberg pays money for people to call Congress.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 19:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No Second Amendment Protection for Hunting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 19:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Pennsylvania Have Its Own Firearm? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 19:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 17:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would agree. Most of the reporters there probably aren't even aware of their bias, but you really only have to see how they portray organizations like the NRA and compare that to how they portray gun control groups. 

You can also see it in what they choose to cover. 

For example, here's a story they posted about the father of the Santa Barbara rampage killer meeting with the father who gave a speech in favor of gun control after the rampage. 

http://www.npr.org/blogs/thetwo-way/2014/06/16/322592320/photos-father-of-santa-barbara-killer-meets-victims-dad

Take note of the context, though. 

They didn't do any actual reporting because no NPR reporter was actually present, and the photographs were provided by a communications firm that works with anti-gun advocacy groups. 

Given the context, it's clear that the story isn't a news report in the slightest, but rather the regurgitation of a press release accompanied by some emotionally loaded photos. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 17:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the first article NPR head posted that's even somewhat pro-rights in about a year. 

Every other story on guns they post is just yet more drum beating demonizing gun owners and spreading misinformation. 

So either this one somehow managed to sneak through, or it's the rare story they post as top cover so they can claim that they're an impartial news source.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 17:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gun buy-ups aren't about effective crime reduction.

From a left-wing perspective there are two advantages to this. 

1.) Good feels and lots of back-patting.
2.) When the buy-up policy ultimately doesn't work, it allows them to claim that the failure was the result of not "going far enough." They can then campaign for stronger gun control laws. 

This is a common theme on the left. Failure of their policies is always going to lead to calls for ever stronger policies which will inevitable fail just as badly, leading to yet more calls for stronger policies, wash, rinse, repeat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone Track Supplement Usage in a Spreadsheet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 01:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've started taking a combination of supplements and vitamins, and instead of trying to keep track of everything in my head, I'm thinking about creating a spreadsheet of some sort to keep track of my supplement use, dosages, times, and any perceived effects.

Does anyone have any tips, or even a template on how to go about doing this?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN is a right-wing news outlet according to CSGV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 19:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook Accidentally Trolls Brady and CSGV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 18:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 18:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have I mentioned that you're one of my favorite people here? 

Because you are. 

N/H </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 18:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They both believe in having a monopoly on force in order to control the populace. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Guns Kept People Alive' During The Civil Rights Movement : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 17:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 16:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So now you're drawing comparisons between the left and WBC? 

Damn, that's harsh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 16:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the old saying goes, if you're taking fire, it's because you're on target.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 16:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that was kind of my first thought, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 16:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In regards to gun control, they sure are. 

:-D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 16:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clayton Cramer us a well-recognized 2nd Amendment subject matter expert. 

I find it interesting you don't actually take his arguments to task,increase just resort to name calling.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 16:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the truth, and until they clean up their own house, I will continue to mock them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Q.) What does ISIS have in common with the American left? A.) They both love gun control! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 15:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 15:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I log the strength work and WOD. I also keep a page in the back of my notebook for recording 1 Rep maxes.

I don't really log any other stuff like food intake or how I was feeling unless its something unusual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 05:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it just me or does it seem like Hillary is actively campaigning to lose the presidential election?

I mean, she just keeps saying and doing things that almost seem deliberately designed to piss off anyone to the right of Amy Goodman, which is pretty much the entire country outside of a few metropolitan enclaves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 05:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the things I love about my CrossFit box is the culture, lots of good people who want to see others succeed no matter their skill level. 

Its alright to be nervous, I certainly was when I first started, but the best way to get passed that is to go get involved with a gym and see how it goes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 05:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. 

Maybe try a few sessions with a massage therapist. I've had some good results there as well.

Other than that, I know some people who've reported good results from having dry needling work done, but I don't have any first hand experience there.

I wonder if it's possible there's anything that would help on the nutrition or supplement side of things?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 04:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go sign up for some yoga classes. If you can go twice a week, that's great, but I've noticed some improvement just from going once a week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Court Rules Against Gun 'Straw Purchases' : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 23:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could Finland Teach The U.S. A Lesson On Guns? : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 23:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 22:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PF is selling the modern equivalent of indulgences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High capacity handgun from 1855. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 21:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 21:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a couple of the blender bottles and they work well, though I don't think they'd be secure enough to put in a backpack, it would be easy for the mouth to be bumped open by other items in the pack. 

In general, I've had really good luck with products made by Contigo, you can jostle them, knock them over, drop them, and they will leak very little, if at all. 

I don't know if they make anything with a blender ball, but it would be worth checking into. 

Costco regularly has Contigo products for sale at decent prices.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hickenlooper acknowledges speaking with Bloomberg after flap with sheriffs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 20:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hickenlooper acknowledges speaking with Bloomberg after flap with sheriffs (CO) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 20:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hickenlooper: Let Me Feed You Another Lie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 20:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The message of the Brooklyn Bridge march: it's not just about "background checks." MDA also demands magazine bans, restrictions on concealed and open carry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 19:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Days of our Trailers: Even More Made Up Mom's Demand Numbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 19:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shannon Watts channels George C. Parker. (Updated) (there likely were not a thousand people at the MDA March in NYC) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 19:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 18:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the same attitude, and only recently began supplementing after doing quite a bit of research on examine.com.

I've been using creatine for about a month now, along with some targeted use of vitamins and minerals (D3, zinc, magnesium, krill oil) and have noticed gains in my ability to complete WODs.

The difference isn't something massive, but I find that in really hard WODs where I have to really dig deep to finish, there's actually something at the bottom to use. 

Frankly, I wish I had started supplementing years ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 15:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that people like you, or Browning, know what they're talking about.

To the average layman, the term "automatic" is synonymouse with "machine gun" and unfortunately gun control activists have attempted to capitalize on this confusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Messaging Problem of Mass Shootings: Former MAIG head admits gun control proposals wouldn't stop mass shootings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 14:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gun-Control Advocate: Snowden, Obamacare Hurt Our Cause </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 14:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 14:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This chart was the first hit I found on Tootle.

 http://www.wehealny.org/healthinfo/dietaryfiber/fibercontentchart.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 06:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Banned from /rguncontrol?

Go team tolerance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 21:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this list.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 19:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I understand it, there's generally more fiber in a serving off most kinds of fruit than in grains.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 19:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be argued that it wasn't the diet that was responsible for the early deaths of paleolithic man, but rather the fact that medical care was nonexistent, fire was the best killer app we had, food was scarce, and then when it wasn't, your chosen meal was unlikely to cotton to your notions of being dinner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 16:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many of those things you listed are unproven or outright false. 

For instance, if you check the examine.com entry for green coffee bean extract, you'll see that there's very little evidence for it's efficacy, even compared to other herbal supplements that are totes to do the same thing. 

Regardless of whether or not he's shilling for an actual product, he's still willfully endorsing things that are not proven to work in an attempt to build an audience of credulous people and body hid ratings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 01:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the courtroom arguments have been over since April, we're just waiting on the judge to render a decision, which should happen by the end of the year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gun Control Activists March Across The Brooklyn Bridge Demanding Action : The Two-Way : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 01:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 04:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they find the we linked to them and I hope so odd the mockery in this thread causes them to cry into their pillows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SAF seeks injunction against handgun law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 19:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 18:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They forgot to include OKC and 9/11. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FreeThinker: Reference Post: Mass Killings by other means </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 18:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 17:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, Bradley Cooper's character wins in the end, and frankly, it's awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 05:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or they'll resort to the use of arson or explosives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 03:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's see. Magazines have something like four-six parts. Are robust enough to last for years, and are essentially untraceable.

Good luck enforcing that ban, poindexter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only Cowards Carry Weapons Awareness : Teaching You About Knife Crime (UK knife control organization. They won't stop at guns.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 03:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 18:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the gun ban hasn't stopped violent crime, but it has stopped a particular kind of event that was so rare there was really only one example of it to start with. 

And to think, all you had to do was have the government steal property from its citizens and strip them off their ability to actually defend themselves! 

What a deal!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legislators Not Optimistic about OC Bill in Texas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 04:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 04:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what you're saying is that you're on with more people getting stabbed on a daily basis if it makes you feel slightly better about reducing the already minuscule odds of a mass shooting? 

Wow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama: Country Needs To Do Some 'Soul Searching' On Gun Control : The Two-Way : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 19:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 18:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His tears of rage are so sweet and yummy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> View From The Porch: Did we all learn our lesson? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 18:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SAFEs effect on New York City (shootings are up.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 18:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 18:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I care only insofar as Obama's statement is a concise and perfect way to respond to anyone who claims that "no one wants to take your guns, that's just paranoia."

Sorry, but the President just endorsed confiscation, so it's clear that anyone who claims otherwise is lying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If You Want To Ban Guns, Just Say So </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 18:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Of Arms and the Law: What is known about the Las Vegas murderers... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 18:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clayton Cramer.: So, Why Didn't You Call the Police? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 18:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
