<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1805</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 13:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schmeichel - Denmark

Rafael -Brazil

Stam - Netherlands

Vidic - Serbia

Irwin - ROI

Ronaldo - Portugal

Bobby Charlton - England

Ryan Giggs - Wales

Best - Northern Ireland

Cantona - France

Law - Scotland


Just going with one from each country for a team, had to make sacrifices like Irwin in over Keane who is obviously the best player we have had from ROI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 10:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 94th time we have signed him in the last 4 years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 11:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus my memory is better than I thought, good find  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 11:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last I heard and this was about 5 years ago it would cost about 114 million quid to go over the railway. They've said repeatedly it's not feasible at the minute but think it's because it would affect attendance for a bit so they don't want too yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 20:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have been chronically underfunded for years so we needed some heavy reinvestment, you can't expect brand new players to come in and settle straight away as you know. We got destroyed last year, had pretty much our whole back line leave and got a new manager with a completely new play style. This year was just bedding in, we got the minimum that we set out for, it's disappointing of course but after last year I'm happy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 20:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all fairness city came 9th in 07/08 then spent 125 mil in the summer and then finished 08/09 in 10th so wouldn't really be talking if I were you but I'm sure you know that was all building blocks for the club as ours is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 19:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it was Liverpool fans last year when they looked set for the title after City </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 01:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fellaini, Duncan Ferguson etc I want to play football not get the shit kicked out of me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 16:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kevin Bacon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 12:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supermans first flight in man of steel, it just makes me smile like a child and makes me really happy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 23:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went to school with him, he was so much better than everyone else and we all thought we were the dogs bollocks. He's a top lad and is a great laugh and hope he is doing alright with everything, it's absolutely shit when something like that happens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 04:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking about that myself but I'm going with the experienced head, that and the fact my grandad loved Byrne and said he was our true captain and could play anywhere himself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 04:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much what you said, watch the original trilogy then move onto the prequels. After that you can watch the clone wars which will fill in a bit more for you and marvel are currently doing some comics to add more story. There will also be a book released in a couple of months with more story between the end of 6 and start of 7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 04:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bioshock or Mass Effect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 03:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schmeichel, Roger Byrne at LB, Ferdinand, Bruce, Irwin at RB, Keane, Robson, Charlton, Ronaldo, Best, Law

Bench - VDS, Stam, Vidic, Pallister, RVN, Tommy Taylor, Duncan Edwards

*Edit, changed it to bench instead  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 03:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silver Surfer Requiem is a brilliant story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 20:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your all time is not great, should be best, charlton and then argued between law, robson, keane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 01:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sucker Punch, brilliant soundtrack for a sadly rubbish film </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
