<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7067</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 08:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reporting this thread for being brigaded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 22:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So which is the real confederate flag?  The one you linked? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 04:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, freaking rtz, quit trolling and drop dat fiya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 23:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And nigma is newer to dota, he's hon trash, he even admitted so when he transferred over, so you there goes that.  Nigma's skill/knowledge is nowhere near the vets of the game, he's just good at making content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 21:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops there you are!  Sorry for stealing your comment, it was just awful it got downvoted to oblivion before anyone could see it.  But it's gonna be nuked again anyway kappa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 20:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was from yesterday, borrowed from u/noodlenonger

 m-muh skillcap

Can we stop this? It genuinely affects the skillcap of the item. Stop avoiding that fact. If you have arguments for why it should be changed then that's fine but don't act like it doesn't affect the skillcap and that anyone who mentions the skillcap should have their argument invalidated. Automatically attempting to invalidate people's legitimate points is exactly how you make yourself look like an idiot.

Srsly, whiners need to quit ruining everything for everyone else.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course nigma responds "it's dumb," dont' forget he came from HoN, not even true dota player, so how the fuck would he know about blink mechanic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 16:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad she sued as a "white" for racism against a predominantly black university.  Nice try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
