<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject71</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 17:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't believe no one said EPC out in St. Chuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 02:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You did a good deed for that family, and I hate to say it but in that condition that birthday could've very well been that kid's last. Good job on the cop for not taking him in in front of his son. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 02:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/gk33ydg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 22:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs some glaze.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 22:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Living in the U.S. I feel left out. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 21:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to ITT-Tech and have an associate's degree in Criminal Justice so my brother from another mother calls me Chef Batman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 21:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where at? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 17:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah forgot the B A Start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 17:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks I'll try that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 17:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Want to send me the money to upgrade? Plus I asked here because I figured that was one of the purposes of this subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 16:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Microsoft Windows 7 or later.

With Windows Vista being before 7 it won't work but Thanks anyway for the info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 15:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which one do I want then, and where do I download it from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 15:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Windows Vista....yeah I know Ugh! lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 15:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downloaded the retail software recovery tool but it's not compatible with my computer's OS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 15:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It got to the gears, ended real fast, restarted the phone, and popped up sorry we're unable to install this update at this time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 19:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you can't train give a fuck, you have to hire give a fuck and teach it to cook.

Such poetry here but very fuckin true.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 16:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He looks like a white Gabriel Iglesias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 16:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually know the guy who made this. This was done at the Alton, IL McDonald's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 23:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This all coming from the fucker who wrote that Hello Kitty ear bleeder for his wife. Yeeeeah ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 22:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll just be some copy and paste response more than likely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 22:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, I think they mean company wide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick Little Mention About RT In The Latest Variety Magazine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 16:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 15:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're Welcome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 15:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish I had the money to donate as well but I'm broke as a joke and the joke is broke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 23:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well most certainly the one this subreddit was named after. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 23:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In most professional kitchens these days, long gone are the times when dick jokes, drug use and alcohol consumption were the norm. 

Wait alcohol consumption and dick jokes are long gone??? Well SHIT! Goodbye cruel world.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 23:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 86 slang as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 23:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought the same. It looks like a fish bowl to me. I'd go with a much shallower dish, and try to tighten up the food placement because the way it is now looks like you said play it where it lands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 22:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buy a bag of potatoes and practice practice practice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 17:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only way to rectify this is to walk up behind a mule and let him kick you in the nuts. It's one of the sacred bro codes so it must be done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 02:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buddy and me just downloaded it as well and so far nothing is new. Also no popups in story mode like there usually is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 01:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ferguson? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 23:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to sound mean buy you either have no balls and letting the Chef walk all over you or you don't know any better and should find another line of work like was previously stated. I suggest that you stand up to the chef and believe me there's a chance of mad respect.

When I was still green under the collar in this industry I had a coworker be a dick towards me everyday, and one day the Chef himself pulled me aside and said don't let him walk all over you. Next day I grew the balls and got major respect from the Chef and the other guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 23:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lived in GA for 2 1/2 weeks and between the spiders and micro-frogs I lost count. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 23:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 23:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the memorial went up in flames he showed up to the scene with two pastor, and was booed when they got out of the car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 23:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any maker marks on the bottom of anything. Maker marks could consist of a stamp or something engraved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 23:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was thinking this too. Announcer/Interviewer Vince </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 23:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ellen DeGeneres is that you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 19:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember these days. Meat slicer was my best friend on those days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 19:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heart attack Grill  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 14:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have hung out with a few of them at one of my old job. Have to say with them being federal and all they're a fun crowd to hang with. I'm going with it being Ferguson related as well and the reason for them staying in Chesterfield might have to do with the airport right there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 04:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I 2nd this. It looks to be a fastener such as the type you find on large manila envelopes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 04:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. It looks like nothing more than a keychain you pick up at a tourist shop/gas station. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rosehill - The Bible and the Gun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 04:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 01:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was just about to post this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 01:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never met him but he did an episode of Restaurant Impossible at a restaurant by me that I used to pass all the time. Was one of the funniest thing I've seen. One clip had him calling a place for a sign (sign place is right next door), and another one had him driving back to the restaurant after asking people to come to the reveal (they were in the parking lot of the restaurant the whole time). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 01:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I was to get that form it'd be a paper airplane within 30 seconds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 01:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serve this with some goat cheese and Ritz for $25. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 01:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bandanas is more of the stop on the way home and pick up dinner in a hurry type place. I say close to the airport go with SugarFire Smokehouse. I'm a chef and all I keep hearing is nothing but good things about the place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 06:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly those. They're grrrrrrreat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 03:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn people are still pissed about this. Not sorry but I think he was a shitty wrestler no matter what organization, and I know I'm not the only one who thinks that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 02:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The part of this that makes me SMH is getting little kids involved in this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 01:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You cheeky lil bastard!

Congrats and if you haven't already we're going to need a full 30min long review posted on YouTube tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 00:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the link. Found this as well: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RuJWpl7W6mc

Give a more in depth explanation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 21:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it was my First kitchen job and I didn't know any better.

I was the KM/Cook of a Mom   Pop Pizza shop. The owner was a cool guy who I got along with to an extent and I pretty much had full control over the place since he was barely around. Well he would hire in these teeny bopper girls to run the counter, and started to notice why he would hire in these girls is so he could try to get a piece of jailbait ass. In the long run the business started to take on water fast. We ended up losing our contract with pepsi because the bill wasn't getting paid on top of them being unable to deliver. I had no key to the place or I would've accepted it. He also let somebody other than himself handle the books and she ended up screwing him over and the place shut down without notice.

Oh and to answer the P.S. No because I was paid under the table in cash. Come to think of it I was hired under the table as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 20:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would love to see a video of how it goes about brewing the tea each morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 20:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Duck Season Muahahahaha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 17:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He did but the Lion no longer had a Choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody Else Having Problems Updating To Windows Phone 8.1.1 build 14203? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 17:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have tried 5 times to download the update and everytime I get an error that says Unable To Update Your Phone At This Time Try Again Later (0xfffffffb). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 15:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anybody having problems updating? Everytime I try to it pops up Unable To Update At This Time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 15:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lumia 520 and biggest gripe is the app store. If I would've known that 90% of the apps I used on my android was unavailable with Windows I would've stuck with Android or got an iPhone 5. Besides that the 8.1 update fixed a ton of the problems like the others folder that was just there with no means of dumping the file build up so my storage space kept getting lower while that kept getting higher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 04:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it free with a trade in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 03:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where the fuck you get your info from a cracker jack box?

I'll just leave this here: http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aneurysm_of_heart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 03:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not join it? If I'm stuck with this phone for the time being might as join a subreddit where I can get info on it and ask question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 21:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In that case have fun. Still wondering if he got an S5 which is only a few months old why is he wanting to trade in so soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 21:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well for example no official app for Snapchat, Instagram is still in beta, and Vine hasn't been updated since God knows when along with many other apps. Also very well known companies are looking at WP users like they have Ebola or something and aren't even creating apps for this OS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 21:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 20:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much sums up my degree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 19:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's like asking if you should trade in a Lambo for a Pinto. The answer is no. As a convert from Android I could kick my own ass. For one thing calling the app market limited is an understatement. While the cameras are good IMO that's the only thing good about these phones. So in turn if you have an S5 keep it, enjoy it, cherish it, and stay away from WP like most companies are doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 19:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hate to say it but what else is new. WP is like the damn plague to companies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 19:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't matter because by that time the damage was already done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 18:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The kind that remembers that the cause of death was due to a heart aneurism cause by years of drug abuse aka his own doings is what killed him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 18:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take a vid of it and we'll call it The Suckering. Make at least a couple dollars off of Larry that lives in Forest Park. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 18:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've either lived a very sheltered life or don't know racism if it hit them in the face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 18:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well shit ok I'll admit I was wrong. Still don't want the bullshit out here though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 17:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit I'm a 27yo virgin but I'm not going to go out and fuck just any woman to get rid of it. Don't get me wrong I'd like to get rid of it shit what man wouldn't but getting rid of it by means of a meaningless one night stand is just fucked up IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 17:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference is with the buses you have to transfer between buses to get downtown. With this it's a straight shot from new part of the county to the city. Thus making it easier to commit the crime and get back to the city in no time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 17:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 17:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHOO HOO GO ME! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 17:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit might as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 16:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmhmm you know why that is right? Because the criminals from the city are coming out here breaking into houses and robbing places.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 16:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let the butthurt begin with this comment: I didn't like him. IMO he wasn't that great and his own doing is what killed him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 15:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You did read the proposed stop didn't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 06:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love Garfield so obviously loving this teapot. Where did you get it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 06:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No Lambchops, No Peace! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 06:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I oppose this for the very reason that we don't need no more damn criminals from the city coming into the county. That is why St. Charles has been keeping it out of their area for years. For example look at the arrest reports from the Ferguson riots. A mass majority of those arrested were from the city so all this will do is give them another means of access to the county. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 05:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I can think of is here we go again. First Josh and now Oscar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 05:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of The Pineapple from HIMYM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Jackson   The Cleveland Orchestra - Will You Be There [Pop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 02:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 04:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MORTAL KOMBAAAAAT!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 02:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everybody is just over here kung fu fighting and you're over there butthurt over some jokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 18:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me it's like googling something. Too many results that you don't know what you should click on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 18:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He stand up and starts shaking hands until someone tells him there's still a chance of a straight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 15:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait that was him? Well that explains everything now. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What NOT to say when ALL IN! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 05:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 05:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this crap keeps happening they won't make it another two. With them being busy with the kids I wonder if they even know what is really happening in their places. I say make an anonymous call to the health department but that's just me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 19:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Culinary Institute of St. Louis

It was just the standard industrial roll plastic wrap found in most commercial kitchens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 15:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theirs are mostly Crosley and Third Street Records(Jack White's label). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 15:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://rs1img.memecdn.com/you-stay-classy-st-louis_o_2565061.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 15:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a chain we'd know or a local mom   pop spot? Reason I'm asking is because if it's a chain then this sadly doesn't surprise me but if it's a mom   pop then it's kinda shocking they would turn the blind eye at this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 15:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought the same but it's how I was taught in Culinary School. Still don't fully understand it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 04:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the basis of seeing an accident and not stopping to check on the people because it's "not your problem." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 03:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably has been covered but TL;DR: Anybody else do a quick glance and thought holy shit Rob Lowe??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 00:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoever requested this I thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 15:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! Hell the standard burritos could feed a small village for a year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 15:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah saw John Pertzborn post about it on twitter when it happened but for some reason it's just now making the news. One of the 13 year olds involved is pregnant so that kind of tells you something about her parents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 22:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took the words from my mouth. Also gonna add MOAR!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
