<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4218</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-02 21:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The theist posits that there is a "God" with some baring on human life, but fails to provide a coherent definition of God or indeed the slightest bit of evidence for its existence. A good skeptic has no time for such baseless assertions, and is therefore not a theist--they are rather a non-theist, an *a*theist, to use the popular prefix. Atheism is nothing more or less than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-02 09:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great video. I'm reminded of how even as a populist entertainer, Chaplin was widely credited with many of the innovations that led early cinema to be recognized as a serious medium of art and expression; seems appropriate that his work should be paired with similarly ambitious games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-27 19:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this bright-eyed post of optimism, and decided to make a joke about how any second this notoriously bitter and critical subreddit will begin telling you what you're doing wrong.

Little did I know, the top three posts were already discouragement. Jesus, people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-26 16:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a stupid world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-23 04:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I was looking for. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-23 04:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> presumably he was a non-student? what were the repercussions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens if I don't pay an MSU parking ticket? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-23 04:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any legal weight behind it? I'm an alumnus, so I'm not worried about holds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-20 18:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's silly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-15 16:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I ever feel like watching hard core misogynists execute dozens of people without due process because they think God told them to, I'll join al Quaeda. But I won't, because that's fucking crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-13 15:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That little brother thing hurt a lot more when we were consistently losing football games. I think we can safely co-opt it now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-13 02:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Nope, just confused.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gb_qHP7VaZE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-13 02:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hmm... had no idea that subreddit existed. I was just using it as a general term for denizens of r/atheism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-13 01:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's okay, this is just a part of his growing up process. Be sure to sure to politely stand by your convictions and consistently go on the record in favor of tolerance... it'll make coming out of the closet that much easier for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-13 01:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an alumnus of your younger sibling University (if you even went to Michigan!), I'm probably a little biased. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wonder if any r/atheists have the same relationship with this song that I do: Smoke - Ben Folds Five </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-13 01:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-12 23:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have fixed nothing, Andy51. NOTHING. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-11 01:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Das ist sehr gut! Ja! Glcklich! Ein Dner bitte! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a racist singing cat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-31 02:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-25 19:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While your friend is oversimplifying things a bit, I do see where he's coming from and largely sympathize: there are huge segments of modern philosophical thought that either ignore or directly attack the scientific method as a useful avenue for obtaining knowledge. I think this stems from  insecurity about sharing or ceding the discipline's historical position as sole harbinger of truth. Philosophy enthusiasts either consciously or unconsciously try to ensure its continued relevance by downplaying science, and in return hard scientists become increasingly hostile toward the discipline of philosophy. In my opinion, this is harmful toward both fields of study.

Unfortunately, it seems that this simplistic liberal arts vs. sciences binary keeps popping up everywhere. r/philosophy is littered with complaints about r/atheism. There's an all-too-common assumption in this subreddit and, in my experience, wider liberal arts academia that one can end a debate by accusing someone of "scientism" or "positivism" or "empiricism," in much the same way that Fox News employs "socialism." It's embarrassing.

None of this is to say that science is beyond question; indeed everything of value should be questioned. But the thing is, science loves to be questioned, *demands* to be questioned, and employs a rigorous system of empiricism *and* rationality to ensure its own accuracy. The pure skeptic could call this a closed loop, but at that point they've argued themselves back inside Descartes's head. That is undoubtedly a crucial point in anyone's philosophical development, but there's so much more to the human experience when we step outside into the "real" world, and use science to further our asymptotic progression toward understanding what "reality" is.

Anyway, your friend and I are hardly alone in feeling this way. I highly recommend [John Searle's U.C. Berkeley course on Philosophy of Mind](http://itunes.apple.com/us/itunes-u/philosophy-132-001-spring/id438307693), downloadable on iTunes; Searle has a special talent for contextualizing modern scientific developments against the history of philosophy, and, in my opinion, cutting through the bullshit. The future of philosophy *is* married to science, and vice versa.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-25 17:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm interested in this too, particularly for Hulu. Anybody know any solutions on that front? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-24 19:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. That is the moral of drugs in my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-20 04:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are shirts available? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-18 00:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I subscribe to both subreddits, I've seen a lot of interesting content and stimulating discussion in both, but fuck fuckity fuck does it piss me off when r/philosophy goes off the rails into this post-fucking-modern anti-"scientism" bullshit. There are genuinely only two possibilities here:

1) "Foundationalistic, verification empiricist-heavy" research, while imperfect, engages with universal truths that exist independent of human thought to the extent that any contradictory manmade "truths" are inherently false

***or***

$) Poodle fluke unicorn fuckwad jiggity joop mubble zook. Fuck.


**EDIT**: I thought it might be kind if funny--and, full disclosure, pretty honest--to argue the antithesis of the O.P.'s point with a comparable level of rage and frustration. I have now been downvoted.

Seriously though, if you're arguing for an understanding of truth antithetical to science, then you're arguing for a philosophy with no baring on the the human experience or indeed any other component of the decidedly law-based universe, so you might as well just floobley fuck woopty zoop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-16 20:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I mean--I used to think of G4 as a solid niche network, something I could flip to and see something fun, something I was actually pretty pumped to have on my cable package when I lived in a college dorm. Now it's fucking Cheaters and Cops.

Seriously, is it worth drawing the half-hourly ratings bump of the crowd that actively seeks out Cheaters if it compromises the network brand so badly? Any network heads misunderstanding their target demographic this badly should be fucking fired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the fuck does G4 air shows like Cheaters and Cops? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-16 18:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-12 21:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's not terribly surprising; did any of the other consoles do that in the jump to HD? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-11 23:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stopped thinking about any of these people as soon as I graduated from college. Seriously, it was like a light switch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-11 01:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-11 00:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I get a whole lot of "Sorry, I actually hate Ted"s also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-11 00:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hmm. bummer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-10 23:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was pursuing *my* useless film degree, my first feature script was a deadly serious, deeply personal disaster movie called "The Ground is Lava." It involved a self-centered stand-in for my self-centered self trying to stave off nihilism while futilely trying to engage with other human beings in his world as God and the Devil fought each other until they both disappeared in a fit of pointlessness, and also the ground was literally lava. I knew that it was dumb as soon as I finished it, but that didn't stop it from being any more devastating when my unbacked-up laptop was stolen from *my* disreputable living quarters.

Needless to say, I can relate to Jason Segel's early situation as well.

But you know what? I love film, and I love my own stupid self, and I fully plan on loving the stupid no-budget revision of "The Ground is Lava" that I still intend to shoot sometime in the next year or two, because fuck it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-10 17:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I got a whole lot of "Have you met Ted?"s before ever seeing an episode of the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Jason Segal wrote the Forgetting Sarah Marshall Dracula musical as a serious, unrelated project while desperately trying to launch his career. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-10 16:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have this weird recurring dream where all my leptons fall out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-10 02:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 23:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it *is* you! yay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 17:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ron... Paul, is it? Liberty, you say? *He's* certainly never appeared on Reddit before! God bless you and your heretofore unspoken message, Masterbench. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-06 19:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game "Tanks" from the [*Wii Play*](http://www.amazon.com/Wii-Play-No-Remote-Nintendo/dp/B0013E9HP6/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 qid=1325875885 sr=8-1) collection took up many happy hours between my college housemates and I. Works best with a second nunchuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-05 19:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Better" is obviously a subjective word. My point isn't about the number of tracks in their library, but rather the sonic and emotional breadth of it. Whatever stimulation I might want out of music--emotion, melodicism, creative orchestration, sonic experimentalism, nostolgia, rebellion, dance music, heavy music, light music, humor, misery, joy, etc.--there is always a segment of the Beatles' catalog that I can turn to, and mine is hardly a unique experience. The Beatles were capable of and accomplished more than Win Butler, and don't really see a debate to be had there.

Again, you can like whatever you want, but it's silly to say that the suburban-angst-on-loop music of Arcade Fire can stand next to the Fucking Beatles Discography--it isn't even *trying* to accomplish the same thing. I like "Wake Up" and "No Cars Go" as much as the next guy, but come on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-05 18:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In their ten years of existence, Arcade Fire have written three good to great albums of melancholy baroque pop.

In the Beatles' ten years of existence, they wrote all of the fucking Beatles' music.

Like whatever you want, but your opinion doesn't make their anthologies comparable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-05 18:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a song needed a standard rock and roll drum pattern, Ringo would play it.

If it needed a radical departure from all pop/rock drumming heard at the time, he'd play that to.

[Tomorrow Never Knows](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6a3NcwfOBzQ)

[Come Together](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-Aa8aKN4jwo)

[Strawberry Fields](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-7ICzQn_AHc)

[Rain](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MPjDMZiuhbQ)

[A Day in the Life](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZF4oQCG4vOc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 01:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like they changed it now; you can see from the half-time update that if started out as a way different article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VICTORY FOR MSU </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-02 23:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-31 21:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a politics to his distaste for Transformers, particularly in the creepy way that the camera ogles commercial products, destruction and women in the same pornographic fashion in what is ostensibly a kid's film. He sums it up nicely in [this showstopping review](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g__bQ-Y7D8Q) of the second one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-29 00:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When reduced to the quantum level, the laser has no direction. There is a range, yes, but the absolute simply isn't there.

I've always known that quantum particles behave differently, as I'm sure everyone else does, but this video just made the point real to me that it doesn't just appear that way because of an intrinsic limit on our knowledge. There is a threshold over which absolute truth does not exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the Heisenberg Uncertainty Principle doesn't just limit our knowledge of quantum behavior, but that the information provably doesn't exist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-28 23:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-28 20:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have the slightest bit of evidence? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-22 01:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And how! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-21 21:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it okay that I didn't laugh? Like, not because I'm offended, but because overt shock racism on the internet is entirely played out for me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-21 10:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw. That first frame almost makes me want to believe again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-19 15:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your interesting point on this complex issue is somewhat undone by

I read a survey recently, I forget where

Lucky for you, I backed up your claim with a quick google search; the survey I believe you're citing is in the "Motivated for Others" section of [this link](http://www.strategicstudiesinstitute.army.mil/pdffiles/pub179.pdf)--you might consider bookmarking that for future arguments.

Thing is though, it's wrong to assume that soldiers' personal motivations are antithetical to "the right thing," at least in their minds. Most soldiers I know enlist because they receive personal benefits by (to their mind) serving society, much like a doctor makes a ton of money by treating illness. Your implication that the average soldier is fundamentally self-serving is severely undermined by the article I believe you're citing, as the overwhelming majority of soldiers are on the record as valuing their squadmates' lives as much if not more than their own; whether or not you see that as "principle," it is undoubtedly selflessness.

You and I are in almost total agreement on the practical realities of our military's role in the world, but the fact remains that the vast majority of enlisted servicemen and women believe they are doing good. If your worldview and argument are based on a conception of the typical U.S. soldier torturing and killing civilians for personal gain, I invite you to examine the ways in which you yourself may be a victim of ideological indoctrination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-16 22:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, it doesn't follow the new character capitalization rule of screenwriting--it's not a hard law or anything, but the Dark Night script certainly followed it, even going so far as to capitalize emphasized props. I suspect we're looking at a transcript. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-16 21:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All this movie did for me was remind me how much I love Spike Jonze's *Where the Wild Things Are*. When I want a sprawling, visually beautiful representation of childhood emotions at war with an incomprehensible universe, I prefer puppets to be involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-13 20:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But lazy is *the greatest news media conspiracy of all!*

I'm not entirely joking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-11 22:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless of how you or I personally feel, it is a divisive issue in philosophy of mind, as evidenced by my links above. If the subjective experience is a form of knowledge, it is literally the only form of knowledge that is inherently inarticulable, which to my mind does make it worthy of linguistic segregation, or at least specificity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-11 17:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, now that the fantastically silly "science is lying to you" answers are out of the way, what you're talking about is [qualia](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Qualia), perhaps best summed up in the ["What Mary Knew"](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mary%27s_room) thought experiment. It's my understanding that there's no clear consensus on whether or not qualia constitute a form of knowledge. I personally consider the outsider with research and data to have "more" knowledge on the subject, but that may change as we begin to better understand consciousness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-09 18:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes. I remember watching your audition, and thinking "yup, he's a redditor."

How did the process of arranging your own backing tracks work? Did you just give them a track to play, or was there some kind of involvement from their music department? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-09 02:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever your personal journey has been, I'm genuinely happy for you that you've arrived at something you consider happiness and enlightenment--I was raised Catholic, I can relate. My point is that beautiful snowflake that you are, we're all beautiful snowflakes here: it's the philosophy subreddit, we're *all* pretentious assholes who view the world in terms of invisible social influences. Instead of writing like a cult leader and spreading your words across subreddits 'cause you're just that important, try engaging us as fellow thinking people. Don't try to enlighten us, try to relate to us. I suspect we've got more in common than you think, and arrogant pricks that we are, we don't like being talked down to. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-07 16:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mean to sound like a dick, but the self-important prose, deliberately obtuse multi-subreddit format, and general air of enlightened superiority revealing heretofore unknown thruths make this post really fucking annoying. Yes, high school sucked, yes, we're aware of vaguely sinister social systems operating on us, yes, everybody hurts sometimes. Welcome to Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-05 17:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great pop album, well worth a 
[listen.](http://grooveshark.com/#/album/Good+and+Evil/6463716) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Flaming Lips: The Fearless Freaks - Full Documentary Film </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-27 06:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-17 22:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prompted by "fuck basic courtesy." I just give people the argument they seem to want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-17 18:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, it's proven to be pretty dubious--again, beautiful sentiment, but it seems fairly disingenuous to attribute it to Aurelius. I just believe people should check the toilet for purple ass unicorns, so to speak, so I'm satisfied. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-17 00:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, It's an example of a falsifiable claim presented as a belief, made without evidence. Try taking some of that effort you're expending trying to be clever, and maybe route it toward actually keeping up with the substance of what we're fucking talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-16 18:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh for fuck's sake. This same quote gets voted to the top of the subreddit  every few month, *and every single fucking time* nobody can point to the passage this is allegedly from. The closest passage that invariably comes up conveys a sentement that is *almost entirely entirely at odds with the factual fucking semantics* of the quote above, namely that we needn't fear because gods are undoubtedly real and just. The quote above is a lovely fucking sentiment, but if someone is going to claim they know something about this topic and say "yeah that sounds right," *it's completely fucking reasonable to ask for a citation.*

Also, "opinion" has nothing to do with this. If I say "I believe Star Wars is a good movie" that's an opinion. If I say "I believe purple fucking unicorns are flying out of my ass" that's something else entirely. The second relates to an independent truth or falsehood, and therefore my beliefs are irrelevant to whether or not the statement has value. If I say I have purple fucking unicorns flying out of my ass, and somebody notes that there's not one shred of evidence that purple fucking unicorns are flying out of my ass, and *flying fucking purple ass unicorns get voted to the top of the atheism subreddit multiple times per year without ever giving so much as a purple ass whinny or neigh to prove their existence*, then my belief statement is entirely worthless until I can finger the exact corner of my asshole that shits purple ponies.

Also, speaking of assholes, you are one. I know you're just gonna absorb that into the take-no-prisoners truth teller self perception schema you've got going on here, but seriously, it's not cute. Grow up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-16 05:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that was a pain in the ass to read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-16 05:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So to recap: a wishy washy fact is voted toward the top, but because the poster *knows and acknowledges* it's wishy washy, that means that anyone who wants citation is a "dickhead." This is a "truth" that trumps basic courtesy, and it's a "truth" worth defending three replies deep into this stupid thread. Yes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-15 16:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For us, calling people dickheads without warrant is just not very nice. If you think morality requires citation, I know some theists who have books for you. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-15 15:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Citation is needed if the comment is to carry any weight. By including his credentials, he lends the "maybe" statement more credibility than otherwise--it reads as a credible statement of fact, even if he does hedge his bets. That means that it's worth evaluating as a true or false factual statement, and that citation is required for such evaluation. None of which implies any wrongdoing on mrBWB's part, just that his popular comment conveying an unconfirmed fact would be more valuable if cited.

Regardless, no need to call mleeeeeee a dickhead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-13 21:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Synecdoche, New York](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0383028/).

Terrible things will happen to us and we're all going to die.

Nothing else has ever made that message so real to me, and it is in turn one of the most motivational works of art in my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-12 22:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I were Alex Castello Jr. or Stephanie San Juan, I'd be a little pissed that you inadequately hid my name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-11 02:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for linking to this, gorange! Feels very cool to have my song submitted on reddit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-10 23:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "social conservative"

That's putting it mildly... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-09 21:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw, that's nice. I really like his Star Wars movie. Give him my thanks next time you see him! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-08 06:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, am I wrong? *Or did I just transcend life into fucking Nirvana!?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-04 19:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair though, those signs are retarded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-03 20:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [conan o'brien push the envelope](http://www.google.com/search?rlz=1C1CHFX_enUS379US379 gcx=w sourceid=chrome ie=UTF-8 q=conan+o'brien+push+the+envelope) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-03 18:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the difference is that the scientific method is built to weed out the bullshit--even if nonsense slips through, it can't have much of a legacy without review, testing, duplication and modification, a process which nonsense cannot withstand. In my experience, the humanities have unfortunately been far less open to structured, methodical criticism, largely because major segments of thought seem to be wrapped up in the idea that there is no truth. Try telling someone in my former English department that you're a logical positivist, they'll look at you with pure condescending pity before ignoring everything you say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-03 00:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-02 01:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough, though I think that the fact that they had no expertise was pretty much the point. It's one isolated incident, and it's then left to us to critically examine whether or not similar propagation of trendy bullshit is happening elsewhere. My personal distaste for the anti-science strains of postmodernism notwithstanding, I think that it's always worthwhile to be reminded that reason and substance *should* trump authority and fashion, even if that's not always the case in popular thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 1996, physicist Alan Sokal wrote an article proposing that quantum gravity is a social construct, satirizing post-modern attitudes toward science. It was published as a legitimate theory on the basis of his academic credentials and mock fawning embrace of popular thought. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-01 23:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-30 00:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, actually, fuck everything about this post and the fact that it gets a positive reception here. 1) This is not a gender-specific behavior, and 2) it's fucking ridiculous to address this criticism to *all* women. This is completely fucking sexist, Reddit, and also completely fucking embarrassing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Solo Live Beatles Tracks for DLC? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-27 23:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just wondering about the likelihood of ever including solo Beatle performances of Beatles songs as DLC -- Lennon's 1972 ["Come Together,"](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qHJAZZTTXiw) Harrison's Concert for Bangladesh version of ["Something,"](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YSTIg08bguk) McCartney's many excellent live versions of ["Hey Jude,"](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CVJMhnPzhts) ["Helter Skelter,"](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZV18scOsX54) etc. I know they have different licensing then the studio Beatles versions, as they often appear on music sites that don't stream original Beatles songs, and these songs deserve to be played with pro keys parts. Other Lennon and McCartney tracks have appeared before, so why not these? Do you think there's any likelihood, and would anyone else be interested? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-26 21:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey now. *Everyone* is better than those people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-26 20:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flaming Lips! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-25 18:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn, you got us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A fascinating look at how cognitive psychology could help shape gaze theory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-25 16:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kristen Schaal is a horse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-24 07:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-21 19:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, I've never followed Edge, but that list is right up my alley. I maintain that Rock Band 3 is *the* perfect music game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Flaming Lips - Waitin' For A Superman (Piano Version) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-17 20:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-11 17:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This capitalist grading system, much like real capitalism, works perfectly if everyone starts off on equal footing. It would be far more accurate to start every student with their parents' cumulative GPA heavily weighted in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-10 17:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some light weight but equally smart stuff, I love [North American Scum](http://grooveshark.com/#/s/North+American+Scum/2yfiK8?src=5) and [Drunk Girls](http://grooveshark.com/#/s/Drunk+Girls/2HR5Kw?src=5). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-10 16:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, [We Close Our Eyes](http://grooveshark.com/#/s/We+Close+Our+Eyes/3UUkqF?src=5) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-10 16:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Slow Nerve Action](http://grooveshark.com/#/s/Slow+Nerve+Action/2D4C9E?src=5) and [Waitin For a Superman](http://grooveshark.com/#/s/Waitin+For+A+Superman+wxpn+Version+live+previously+Unreleased+/3Q3wGA?src=5) would top my list, but Do you Realize remains an awesome song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-30 06:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please please please share a link to some of your songs. I'm eager to hear these exquisitely crafted melodies and arrangements that put hack songwriter Paul McCartney to shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-29 05:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that.

heh heh yeah, we do things a little differently here at metacirclejerk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-26 23:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...so then I grabbed my long skinny dick and slapped it onto the ATM screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-24 07:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference between punchliny jokes and a good poetic rant like this is the difference between r/funny and r/humor. Kind of surprised at all the comment negativity, I thought it was great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-24 03:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay, what hipster fuck downvotes the explanation link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-23 09:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (ahem)

I'll make a Chan out of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-22 23:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was with you up to the Beatles diss. Songwriting skill married to genuine boundary-pushing experimentalism resonates with me regardless of its time-period; arbitrarily loving or hating music for its age is equally dumb on both fronts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> . </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-22 22:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
