<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4484</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 14:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diamond is the aircraft manufacturer that makes the plane in the picture. They also make one called the Katana, but it's not this one (it's a Twin Star).

To further explain, air traffic control sometimes replaces the first letters for the name of the manufacturer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 21:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only things that need fixing in that game are a shortcut to take things out of your bag and longer days. 

Other than that, the game is perfect, especially the music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 00:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm... not correcting myself. It is near the horizon at sunrise, my first post wasn't wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 00:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it rises at sunset and sets at sunrise. My window is to the west so I see it setting at sunrise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 23:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only picked it up because I recently moved to an apartment where my bedroom window faces the west. I woke up one morning with the full moon near the horizon at sunrise and thought "oh yeah, that makes sense." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 13:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just go [here](http://www.youtube.com/account), there should be a link to disconnect it from G+ right bellow your e-mail.

No need to delete your youtube account like the other guy said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 14:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the biggest giveaway is that HL3 would make everyone change focus from all the Steam Box stuff, which they clearly put a huge effort into. That would be just a bad business plan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 03:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Administrative assistant is just a fancy term for secretary/receptionist, in most cases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 03:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is, just got the notice I have premium today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 03:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have experience with getting their OS for a build from Dreamspark? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 03:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing my first build and intended to get my Windows 8 from Dreamspark, but at the checkout I see this message:

*c.  Using Windows Desktop Operating Systems.  Your DreamSpark Direct Subscription includes certain Windows operating system products. You may install these products only on a computer that is already licensed to run a full version of a Windows operating system on it, as evidenced by a valid Certificate of Authenticity (COA) for a Windows operating system affixed to the computer.*

Does that mean I can't use it for a build?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
