<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8022</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 21:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 28 yo single male. Making a decent 6 figure income since 21 yo and now putting away about $4k or $5k each month. Savings are mostly with Edward Jones (well balanced portfolio) but also present in JP Morgan (mutual fund), Fidelity (vesting company stock and personal trading) and Chase (cash).

Right now I have zero debt but am looking for a house in an aggressive and expensive market. After doing so I will be about $200k in debt with the mortgage. I'm really not looking forward to it, but it seems better than throwing $2000 of rent into a financial black hole each month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 03:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on historical prices it seems likely, as to my knowledge we haven't really seen any major events that typically precipitate a huge price drop. Additionally Saudi Arabia's recent decision to not cut output goes against its previous behavior in similar conditions. Some people may say Japan's sinking economy could be a factor, but I feel that China's growing economy and oil usage should easily counter that...

If it is orchestrated, it's a good move, Russia is bleeding from this at the time they need it most. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian submarine test-launches new intercontinental missile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 23:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 09:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To put the violence in Mexico into perspective: the number of deaths from the Mexican Drug War since 2006 is estimated to be 4-5x higher than the deaths (including civilians) occurring in the ENTIRE Afghanistan War since the US invasion in 2001. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia to boost relations with Assad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 08:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 11:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The post has been removed from the frontpage. I suggest everyone message the TIL moderators and ask them to have a sense of humor and allow it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 11:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Op, now that the story is climbing you should delete your post. People will continue upvoting the other fake post because they'll just assume it's true without looking at the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 10:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting fact: When the government came up with the Navy Seal teams they gave them names like "Navy Seal Team Six" even though there were not six teams. This was to throw off enemies to make them assume more teams were available. The base location for the team was "leaked" out during the Cold War. The location leaked was Thompson Falls, Montana.

So basically a non-existent city which is a side effect of the cold war is still in feigned existence today. It's pretty cool actually. It'd be even cooler to know why they continue to cover it up though.

**Edit:** Removing the article link as requested by the mods. Apparently people were getting malware warnings. My apologies!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 07:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's in a fuel cell it isn't really 'burned' right? It's a chemical reaction without combustion that produces water and electricity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 02:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A 7% functional 'cure' rate on an illness that has seen few new marketable treatments in the last several decades? This is absolutely amazing if it shows similar results across common patient populations.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> France suspends delivery of warship to Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 02:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 02:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have a nice day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 02:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't care what you believe. You are a self proclaimed "anarchist" and likely contribute nothing to society. You complain about people whining, yet you take whining to the extreme by contributing nothing towards the solutions of the problems you complain about.

Have a nice day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 01:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When referring to my own opinion of the protests and how my opinion is not swayed by race, yes I think I can confidently say it's not because of race because I say it isn't. Are you suggesting I don't know my own thoughts? 

I wonder if you have voices speaking to you. When I saw this http://www.kirotv.com/news/news/kiro-7-confronts-self-proclaimed-anarchist-accused/nczb9/ things became a lot more clear about what you represent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 01:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Care to elaborate? Your message makes no sense to me... 

I don't agree with these protests, but it's not because of race like you seem to imply. You do realize that most of those protesting in Seattle are white right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia funds French National Front and other extremest groups to sow unrest across Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 00:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Army may station tanks in Eastern Europe: general </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 00:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New protests over Ferguson decision as up to 2000 protesters block traffic in Seattle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 23:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 23:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound really really cynical. I hope you never have to rely on a police officer to help you, it might make your head explode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 22:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's because of escalating racial tensions all over the country causing people to post things they wouldn't normally post. It's not limited to reddit. For example a black friend of mine on Facebook just called for a purge of all whites, and some white friends of mine are posting about lynching blacks. People will regret what they said when things calm down. Right now it's a tinderbox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 08:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Didn't realize it was the final game that had the riot though. My bad. Still I don't think anyone predicted the Stanley Cup game would result in a riot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 08:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But apparently you chose to ignore the many disturbances that occur after other non-championship events:

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2011_Vancouver_Stanley_Cup_riot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 07:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Just an update**: I-5 through Seattle has been shutdown and crowds are swelling as the protests have turned violent. Teargas/flashbangs/pepper-spray have been deployed and protesters are splitting off into large groups marching in different directions.

**10:48PM:** Windows at Wells Fargo Bank have been broken

**11:02 PM:** I-5 has now been re-opened and traffic is flowing freely. Fireworks being thrown at police elsewhere in Seattle

**11:10 PM:** Protests igniting in Capital Hill. All available cops are being asked to assist in riot gear.

**12:10 AM:** Things seem to be dying down in terms of spread. Some protesters have spray painted businesses along Pine.

**Update at 12:35 AM:** Protests have really died down. Only about 60 protesters left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 07:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was referring to Ferguson, but perhaps that was misunderstood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 05:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who said they were rioting? As of right now it's just a peaceful protest. Which is why I called them protesters in the title, and not rioters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 05:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They certainly aren't given a pass, there is just less of a coordinated response because they cannot easily be predicted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 05:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean a lot of those causing riots after sporting events are likely intoxicated, so that alone is a pretty big difference from these Ferguson related protests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 04:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *intoxicated people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 04:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There probably would have been riots either way, some people are just out to start conflict instead of deescalating and looking to find ways to prevent similar situations in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Developing: Protesters massing in downtown Seattle in response to Ferguson verdict (Live KOMO News Stream) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 04:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 03:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello race war! Raceeeeeeee war!!!!!! RACE WAR EVERYONE!!!!!!!! RACE WAR!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia unexpectedly suspends coal supplies to Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 01:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia begins further annexation of breakaway Georgia region after signing a treaty that gives Russia more control </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 23:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 12:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you won't be at an equal pressure because you'll have A LOT of extra weight added by everything that isn't "normal air". The vessel would sink down into the atmosphere and the pressure inside would be much different than that on the outside before the vessel becomes stabilized. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 10:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Japan was one of the most aggressive countries in modern history. They just recently started firing back up their offensive military machine to face potential future conflict with China. A well armed Japan is one of the last things anyone should fuck with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Santas at malls are literally paid to have kids sit on their lap while they lie to them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 01:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 01:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing he's mentioned to me is that he looks for suburbs with good schools. I don't know what effect that really has though, other than reducing the chance of lower class renters.

When I've been looking (but have not bought any yet) I'm using Craigslist to find how much rents are in an area, and then using sites like Zillow to find the areas where the difference between mortgages and rents are the most extreme, but still affordable to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 23:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the same type of situation. I'm 28 and pulling in about 100k after taxes each year. But I also feel like I am being paid for my life, as outside of work I don't really do anything. I'm almost 100% work focused, and I don't want to live this way for the rest of my life.

I've been aggressively saving/investing for a house, but around here a decent house close to work costs about $700k. My plan is to pay much of it off in a down payment, and then have a minimal mortgage, that way I have bigger incoming cash flow that I feel I can spend on 'fun purchases'. That however, is still not **wealth**. 

Luckily I work with many many others my age that make similar amounts of money or more from their day job. It allows me to get a lot of comparisons into what works wealth-wise, and what does not. At this point I'm convinced that one of the best ways to generate wealth outside of owning a business is to own property and rent it out. 

I have a friend the same age as me that currently owns 3 properties in the suburbs and rents them out. From those he's paying about $3,000 in mortgages each month, but getting about $6,000 in rent. Excluding repairs and maintenance, that's an **extra** cash flow that nets him $3,000 each month in addition to his regular work pay. To me that is wealth... Because if he were to quit his job he'd still have income to live on while he searches for another job. PLUS like me he's 28, so I would not be surprised if he continues to add another property every 2-3 years. That's wealth generating income that can increase relatively fast, and it's also a real world example of someone our age gaining wealth so he will not have to work into his 50s.

So my advice would be to look into owning property in an affordable area and renting it out, as I know it is a wealth generating method proven to work by one of my friends with similar income. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 11:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ummm. No. Have fun with your anonymous mask though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine to cancel its non-aligned status, resume integration with NATO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 00:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 23:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They keep missing one too. If I'm going to call any country a terrorist state, it's going to be Saudi Arabia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 23:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably not the wisest thing to say as the President of a nation that only has ~3 million people.

I don't understand comments like this from heads of state, it's only going to escalate things. Does she really think Russia will hear her and just be like: "Oh you're right. We're sorry. We're pulling out of Ukraine now." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 09:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tina is out getting her ham </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pakistan, Russia sign 'milestone' military cooperation pact </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 07:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 07:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *from a chair in front of our computers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 03:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't you heard? You're part of the Latin Spring! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 03:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we return it and exchange it for something else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 00:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RAID is often used when data integrity is important (for example backups). If you have a bunch of SD cards in a array and have failing cards, you're going to have to rebuild the array often or face total failure. 

TL;DR: If you have a RAID setup with fault prone nodes, you're going to have a bad time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 07:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can, but the SD cards are usually much different/lower quality flash memory. They don't have nearly as much tolerance for failure and the number of write cycles is typically much less due to the type of memory used.

It'd be a nice 'fun RAID' perhaps. But I wouldn't use one to hold the keys to life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 03:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can buy them today, so it's already reaching consumers. I may buy one for an off-grid cabin because unlike many other batteries these aren't chemically dangerous, and they claim they have very long lives with minimal degradation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin Calls for Closer Ties Between Russia and North Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 22:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin says United States will never 'subdue' Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 22:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 22:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hot Wheels is proud to announce our new 89' Geo Metro model with separable exhaust!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 21:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sometimes wonder if this administration is TRYING to stir up racial tensions. Imagine what a heated country it would be if this announcement and also the grand jury decision from Ferguson were made the same week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 09:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Uncle Dave!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 08:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is the original? This uploader just takes other peoples videos and reuploads or rehashes them together so they can get advertisement money through youtube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 06:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When someone mentions asymptomatic I think a lot of people associate it with other contagious diseases where there can be carriers that spread the disease without exhibiting any symptoms. A very dangerous and alarming prospect. Like typhoid Mary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 05:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? An "Asymptomatic" flair on the post? It's like it was only added to cause unnecessary panic. It's well known that Ebola can still be detected in semen weeks or months after infection. This guy was symptomatic at one time, and defeated the virus. He already went through the extremely contagious phase when he was still in Africa.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 03:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They come through our solar system, they just don't do so on a regular basis:

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_non-periodic_comets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comets are probably of interest to any intelligent alien lifeform(s) in the galaxy. So if humans were to attach a device/object with information to a comet that doesn't orbit our sun, it probably has a higher chance of being discovered by aliens than a small manmade satellite floating through space </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 03:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 01:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not really giving something physical (certificate or otherwise) to your user base. But I think it would be cool if there were some X-Prize like "Reddit Prize" for huge scientific/technological/consumer breakthroughs that may affect many Reddit users. 

It would take someone to manage it. But it would also be incredibly awesome and allow Reddit to really give back to society. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 10:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps you'd like to fly there and show them how it's properly done in a war-torn country? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 04:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inspections are still done, they are just done while the money is in escrow and the buyer/seller agree that the buyer can walk away if the inspection finds something that changes the buyer's mind. It is rare for buyers to waive them completely (and stupid in my opinion).

My agent told me the reason agents are pushing against pre-offer inspections is because the market here is so competitive a lot of buyers were getting upset when they'd pay for inspections and not have their offers accepted post-inspection. I was also getting upset, as I have paid for inspections on 4 other homes which ended up going to other buyers with better offers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 03:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not yet. In my region there is a push against pre-inspections because it was beginning to become way too taxing on potential buyers. 

I could probably do this, and claim it's due to a defect, as long as they don't call my bluff and offer to address it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 00:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can back out, but I believe I will lose my earnest money which is $20k unless I find a defect with the house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 22:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't help but to feel a bit cynical about his words. His party just lost a mid-term election, and NOW he decides to be so vocal about opposing net neutrality?!? If he believes so strongly in opposing it, where were his strong reactions before he had to save face?

It's fucked up and quite honestly it makes me a bit depressed at our current political state of affairs. It's all such a joke.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 02:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even fire rated bricks tend to crack over time when exposed to both fire and outdoor elements. For $6 they'll still probably get a lot of good use out of the pit, and from my experience even after the bricks begin cracking, people don't care that much as it's all about the fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany's Merkel says situation in Ukraine unacceptable, EU considering further sanctions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 12:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prospect of all-out war with Russia prompts call to build stronger Ukraine army </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 04:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian chill permeates G20 summit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 04:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian military flights near US raise concern </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 04:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sweden confirms foreign submarine incursion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 04:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU nearing collapse as Britain is prepared to exit the union </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 03:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 06:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That single tall tree a bit from the left looks like it just gave up. 

"I'm this tall! I don't want to be any taller!!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 01:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi I'm Johnny Knoxville and this is the "Sweat Trap Bike Ride". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 22:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A CBO study in 2007 concluded:

 "The tax revenues that unauthorized immigrants generate for state and local governments do not offset the total cost of services provided to those immigrants"

Since then there has been a larger flood of illegals that can be considered 'dependents', so I believe it would be an even greater difference today.

[Source](http://www.cbo.gov/sites/default/files/12-6-immigration.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 22:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was wrong... But seriously, it's the US's fault that people don't want to live in Mexico? The Mexican Government is full of corruption, and Mexico was chaotic before the Drug War too. Shifting blame to the US is pretty uncalled for here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 22:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not direct harm. But it is indirect harm as services are used for free that those legally here help pay for. It hits hospitals especially hard, and others are forced to pay more because of it. It's well documented and understood, and it's not fair to those who obey the laws. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 21:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this happens I don't think Obama will be acting in the interest of the United States. Those who knowingly commit illegal acts that harm others (stressing US infrastructure in this case) should not be rewarded.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 01:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is an article somewhere online written by a hostage that was set free by ISIS. He was sold by the FSA (which is considered 'moderate' by the US) to ISIS. Later on he was held by a mix of ISIS and FSA fighters, and some of the FSA fighters told him they received training from the US military, and that they simply lied when they said they would not work with ISIS.

I truly believe the best thing to do at this point is support Assad in limited fashion, and setup ways to hold his soldiers accountable if any atrocities are committed after that partnership begins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 00:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If people are willing to do the work and you aren't asking for an employee, but rather a service provider, why shouldn't they? Even though this 'ad' was a PR stunt... There are companies out there that do nothing but remote security system monitoring for businesses (even if not using their equipment). It's not inconceivable to think you could hire one for relatively cheap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 22:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say don't do this. I work at a company where quite a few of my coworkers are timid/shy, and a couple of them have stared at my eyebrows before during conversation. It will make me seem more intimidating, because it makes me annoyed. Nothing is more annoying then talking to someone who is staring above my eyes, because it makes me self-conscious of whether I have a mark on my face or something.

My brother and I actually did this when we were younger to ANNOY each other. If you have a brother/close friend, try it. Hold a conversation with them but only look at their eyebrows. They will become very uncomfortable and/or angry. I guarantee it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 21:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, leave your love life out of this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 09:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have friends that hate on the US all the time, and in particular they repeatedly claim the US has the most violent cops in the world. They also say they want to move away from the US... part of me hopes they buy a ticket to a place like Brazil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 08:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Balls of steel. At that point the helmet is really just for decoration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 02:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but none were in circumstances to make me cry. All those that passed on were elderly and in failing health, so I think I was mentally prepared for it.

If a close family member killed themselves I think I would cry too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 22:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could take proactive steps that may help minimize the future progression severity: Eating healthier, sleeping healthier, exercising more, and staying mentally active. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
