<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1208</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 17:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mutu....

Now that's a name I haven't heard in a loooong time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 22:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I... don't get it. What a waste of a meme. A hipster cop would obviously go around arresting people for breaking archaic laws that nobody knows are still in effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 20:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #JusticeForColby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 19:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AYYYY LMAO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 21:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I love moments like this purely for the quick little glimpse it gives into a person's real nature. I live in a majority black country and grew up thinking all my white friends weren't racist. But over time, every now and then, one of them would let slip a moment like this, and I'm grateful every time. I don't say anything, just make a mental note, then slowly eek them out of my life.

EDIT: I'm not talking about wee little moments of prejudice, or politically incorrect views. I'm talking about flashes of outright racism. It's something I hate with the core of my being and it fundamentally changes my view of people to the point that I don't want to know them anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 16:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/quityourbullshit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 18:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This girl had her life ruined over this video when the guy she sent it to uploaded it to the TOR site Pink Meth. Guilty boner....... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 16:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened to me in London. Travelled from one end of the city to the other, getting off and changing at all the same spots as a really cute girl. I was thinking I'd say something to her jokingly and we ended up getting off at my stop. She looks back. I go to say "heh I swear I'm not stalking you" but she bolts before I can. Shaved my moustache as soon as I got home... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 15:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goats? Psh. My dog killed geese. GEESE. Lovely little black lab taking on dozens of 3-foot honking pieces of hell. It was a bloodbath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 20:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being seen as a "trusted student" by a teacher the rest of the class dislikes puts that student at odds with their classmates, fostering distrust among their peers. In the hyper-social setting of a classroom, this can be severely detrimental to the student's social standing among the group. 

"This kills the ____" is a meme, in this case applied glibly to signify that such an action by the teacher would leave the "trusted student" figuratively "dead". 

In comedy, hyperbole is often used to "play up" a truth. In this instance, "This kills the student" is referencing the social strain being labeled a "trusted student" would induce. 

While one could have commented: "This would severely hamper the student's social standing among his peers", such matter-of-fact comments often go unnoticed on forums such as Reddit, where one-liners and popular references tend to generate more reaction and, in turn, karma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 19:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Send a trusted student

This kills the student </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 17:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repost or not, I love seeing this. It's really the simplest advice you can give. I write for a living, so I get a lot of people asking me "how to become a writer" etc. The answer is literally in the job description.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 23:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A wave hit it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 22:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://media.giphy.com/media/awRutawdcWLJe/giphy.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 22:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 21:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention Suzuka 2006. Put it on pole then gave the lead to Schumacher, who would've won the championship if his engine hadn't blown on the final laps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 18:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may not have ever seen a Whitmarsh car in person, but we in Bermuda are super fucking stoked to see what he can come up with for BAR racing. [Here's](http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-LlGp21ZReTY/VMGTeYMQmkI/AAAAAAAAdCg/WdQ5Pt6eBWs/s1600/Nacra20ACBARBermudac.jpg) what they are sailing in our waters right now. Gorgeous, frankly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 12:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make it hail? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 22:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  JayZ Wentworth 

My sides.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 17:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These boots were made for scissoring?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 16:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [For that bitter taste.](https://boots.scene7.com/is/image/Boots/10136964?id=VhVah0 fmt=jpg fit=constrain,1 wid=504 hei=548) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 12:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Thine network is Telus

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 02:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Welcome to the fucking show.](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=b22_1422986532) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 01:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being the best at the second most popular sport on Earth is probably worth bragging about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 20:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite a posh accent too. She'd do well in Parliament. 

"What Mr Cameron was meaning..."

DC: "POINT OF ORDER, MR SPEAKER. I'M NOT MEAN." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 18:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing he's better at football than chewing gum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 18:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/ComedyCemetery  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 17:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_burn_centers_in_the_United_States </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 17:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just calling two black men monkeys. There isn't even an attempt at making a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 16:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not offended. It's just not funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 16:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More of a response to low effort racism that isn't remotely funny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 16:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/Bermuda here

Legend has it that if a corn-rowed white girl shows up before the end of May, summer comes early. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 16:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snort it back up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 16:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol black ppl are monkeys right guise?

/r/shitpost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 14:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sarong is so fucking fetch I literally can't even </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 14:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold the fucking phone. 

There's a girl named Kate Micucci?

Is her mother named Munch?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 07:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come to Bermuda. 20 minute swim from my dock with a spear, and you'll have one in no time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 06:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fuck you say to me, paragraph? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 04:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They used the local media and now they're beating you. This is called being outsmarted. Nothing to do with a pussy pass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best of luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well telling them they just don't get it, or explaining things in a condescending and dismissive way, is how you make sure they never get it.

Clinic defenders protect abortion clinic workers and clients from protesters who try and shame women as they walk in. IIRC you get some training and they call you up when a local abortion clinic is being protested for whatever reason. It's a great cause that always needs more help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps try taking your activism beyond the internet. Volunteer as a clinic defender. You'll find no empathy here when you come in guns blazing with lines like 

 The only people that think women don't have issues in the US are men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really hoping you're a troll. Ignorance is not an indicator of intelligence. You have a flair for the kind of melodramatic rage that makes everyone think feminists are perpetually triggered cuntnuggets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lolwut? 

"Feminist" work differs wildly from country to country, according to how much work is needed to be done for the rights of women IN that country. American feminism, as the average person sees it, looks like Tumblr. Turkish feminism looks like a woman beheading her rapist in the fucking street.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 02:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "American feminism" would imply feminism in America is different. 

"American feminists" implies feminist women in America are different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 02:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know saying you complain about feminism = spouting off about feminism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 02:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubtful. Quotes but no name is a pretty big indicator that the story is bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 01:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the new Brangelina!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 01:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talking about how Superman makes us question our priority in the universe? Yup. That's exactly who is talking. Has to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 01:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just did a quick google. In California alone there are five different endangered fox species, five endangered species of rat, two species of endangered mice...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 00:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Lindsey works for the Washington Animal Clinic in Brenham. In the comment section of her post, she wrote no I did not lose my job. Lol. Psshh. Like someone would get rid of me. Im awesome!

lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 00:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also indigenous and endangered species. I live in Bermuda and have to keep a constant eye out for my cat getting its paws on a skink, one of world's rarest lizards. He's killed 4 already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 00:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All great advice until

 take the story to a sympathetic media outlet.

I hire a lot of freelancers. While I sympathise that you are working at an unethical company, I wouldn't trust you further than I could throw you if you quit your job because of the reasons you've listed then told another news outlet about it. Unless it's a story that has real value, like interns being forced to pay for rec letters, you'd be shooting yourself in the foot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 00:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please don't do that.

Lovingly, Bermuda </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 23:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubtful. It's one of my many pet names for him. Haz, Hazzy, Jazz Haz, Hazmat, Hazdribal, Hazilla, Hazim Zalabim, El Hazerino (if you're not into the whole brevity thing). Sometimes I just refer to the entire left side of the pitch as Hazpilicueta.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 21:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not with that attitude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 17:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'keepers don't tend to get worse until their physicality REALLY drops off. Even then that drop-off can be compensated for with wise positioning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 17:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must be watching a different player. IMO he's been excellent in those positions. His presence in a melee is precisely why I'd choose him over Cech.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 16:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird. I remember a very boisterous chorus of "Adebayor, your dad washes elephants and your mum is a whore" echoing around the Emirates for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 16:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try using Colgate Xtra Fresh mouthwash. Excellent for getting rid of lingering bitter taste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 15:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's probably his only weakness. He can get overzealous. With Haz on that left wing I don't blame him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 15:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is one uncanny airplane impression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 15:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His distribution, primarily. He's had a number of shoddy throws. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 15:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a TV reporter for a while. Got pulled over for speeding with a girl I was dating and she says to the cop: "Do you know who he is?" Never been more mortified in my life. We broke up a few weeks later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 18:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has any of your work shown up on /r/wheredidthesodago? Any good stories? I worked in advertising for a hot second so I KNOW you've got a few... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 16:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoring out my hair for karma is better than whoring out my mum though, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 15:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tropical islander here. Have to deal with this most of the year. All the advice here is spot on. I'd only add that I've found the best underwear for this in Banana Republic's Untra Pro sport trunk. Toss some Gold Bond in there and you've got yourself a smooth, dry coinpurse for the rest of the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 15:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You paint with words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 05:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I CAN DO A REALLY GOOD WOOKIE IMPRESSION ^^^sorry ^^^I ^^^panicked ^^^and ^^^didn't ^^^know ^^^what ^^^else ^^^to ^^^say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 03:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a fucking sandcastle mold you numpty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 03:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have lived in the US, Bermuda, Canada, and the UK. In a bumfuck nowhere town in Canada I'm having a smoke on the sidewalk by a traffic light, outside a bar. Truck pulls up. Rolls down window. Guy looks at me: "How ya doin'?"

Um, fine.

"Don't look like you're from around here."

No, just here for my sister's graduation.

"Oh! Well give the little lady all my best!"

Light goes green. Truck drives off.

NOWHERE, and I mean NOWHERE, has that ever happened to me. Canada has earned it's reputation. Now siddown and eat your poutine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 03:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smile big and walk fast. Nobody will notice. Unless you get obese. Then everyone will notice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 00:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITT: the exact kind of speculation Funny or Die wanted to stir up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 00:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's SOP to film multiple takes of a scene from multiple angles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 23:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 21:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's from PinkMeth, a TOR revenge porn site where they doxx women on social media and make them write apology letters to get everything taken down. Remember coming across it a while ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 17:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found the purple. 

#Grey4Lyf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 14:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's always sounded like bullshit to me. Do we have any proof that being fat was once found attractive? I don't see any beautiful statues of fat people... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 05:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not trivial at all, especially since the DP was [Shane Hurlbut.](http://www.imdb.com/name/nm0403397/) So, not exactly like he's going to ruin the guy's career.

I've done really small time broadcast news, and I'd get super pissed if anyone, let alone the director of photography, was walking around in front of me during filming. Everyone knew not to do that. 

How the fucking DP of a major motion film doesn't know that is actually pretty astounding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 05:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a really shitty version of a smoker's retort to people on high horses telling them how much money they'd save if they didn't smoke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 03:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smoking a joint as I read this. Have I just been sorted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 02:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/zoophilia

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 22:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God fucking dammit. This sub is hell. Ducks, not chicks. Capybara, not guinea pig. Jesus. Someone get the oncologist, this post just gave me lymphoma.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 06:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YAY. Does this mean I can finally use the term "Malthusian Catastrophe" and people will know what I'm saying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 06:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having your girlfriend of two years leave you because she's a lesbian is not quite the same... But Eh for Effort? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 04:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [K](http://www.reactiongifs.com/r/ktf.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 04:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 03:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a club!? GOOD. Because I'd really like to discuss how fucking confusing it is thinking about the woman I loved having lesbian sex. The dichotomy between a man's heart and his dick has never been more apparent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 03:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuckit, I'll jump on this downvote train. Fuck that show. Fuck Chuck. Fuck sitcoms. They're all terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 03:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure Reddit is comprised of a wide variety of people from all walks of life with similar taste in pop culture. But what do I know, I'm just an outcast loser neckbeard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 03:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take it from a guy who fell deeply in love with a girl who was questioning her sexuality, you dodged a bullet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 03:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Sigh.](http://thatmarriedguy.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/j002e3d.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 20:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The request and fulfilment of said request are too perfect. I think we need to bring in /r/KarmaConspiracy on this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 19:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be happy to if there's an actual interest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 18:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Night court????? I didn't know there was such a thing!

And honestly, if you haven't ever been to plea court (dont know what the American equivalent is), you need to go check it out. I've always referred to it as the most fun you can have for free with your pants on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 17:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was fine, except that he kept trying to explain to the magistrate that he and his cousin (the owner) had sorted it out. The magistrate kept telling him if they had sorted it out, he wouldn't be here. That was hard for him to understand. Here's the article. http://www.royalgazette.com/article/20131113/NEWS02/131119909 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 17:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's much more succinct than I've been putting it. I hate this new trend of looking at the world like it should be a crime free paradise. Should the Ferguson kid have been shot? Of course not. Should he have obeyed the law? Of course. Did Charlie Hebdo deserve it? No. Should they have seen it coming? No shit. Should women get to wear whatever they want? Sure! Should women know wearing certain clothing will elicit certain responses? Fucking duh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 17:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Court reporter here. Can confirm. Especially in plea court, these idiots are a dime a dozen. Once [wrote a story](http://www.royalgazette.com/article/20131113/NEWS02/131119909) on a guy who kicked in a restaurant's door because he had to pay $3.25 for some bacon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 17:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There's not very many automatic weapons

Quite the opposite. Automatic weapons dominated trench warfare. The machine gun is responsible for the brutality of WWI. Jump out of trench, get mowed down, repeat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear America,

Sort out your pansy ass college students. We didn't help you fuck up the redcoats so cry-baby college kids can waste their time banning a goddamn film from being shown to whoever wants to see it.


Sincerely,

/r/bermuda  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 15:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the NATO Tigers patch, IIRC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 13:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  freakshow

Tagged as deep closet homo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 05:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES. Islander here. Happened to my parents' friends. I go full panic mode whenever I see a kid sitting like that now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 05:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Chickensaurus is already in dev.](http://www.washingtonpost.com/national/health-science/paleontologist-jack-horner-is-hard-at-work-trying-to-turn-a-chicken-into-a-dinosaur/2014/11/10/cb35e46e-4e59-11e4-babe-e91da079cb8a_story.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 05:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Grab some popcorn.](http://www.reddit.com/r/SubredditDrama/comments/2c9ida/recap_unibanned_a_recap_of_the_fallout_of_reddits)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
