<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8344</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to make an Amazon Wishlist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 22:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posting this so I can put the link on the sidebar. A tutorial to make it easy. :D


-----------------------

**How to make an Amazon wishlist:**

First make an amazon account:

* https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B37BFyksMPvcQmM2ZE5CUHpsZEU/view

Then make your wishlist:

* https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B37BFyksMPvcZ2xlOXlLMkVYWG8/view

Add your shipping address:

* https://docs.google.com/file/d/0B37BFyksMPvcNUpNeW9VT0N2TGc/view

While on the page with your wishlist appearing, copy the link on the address bar and share that with anyone you want to see the list.

If you need any assistance, let us know. We would be happy to help you. Good luck. :D

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The #1 cause of death in Tennessee and Alabama: Accidental discharge of gun. Mississippi is undetermined gun discharge - Only thing worse is Louisiana: Syphilis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 22:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Right Baits the Left to Turn Against Hillary Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 17:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mitt Romney Lasts 2 Rounds Against Holyfield in Boxing Match </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 08:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekend Wisdom - May 16th - 17th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 08:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Happiness comes more easily when you feel good about yourself without feeling the need for anyone elses approval.

*unknown* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Friday May 15th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 09:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #When you smile about the life you live, you end up living a life worth smiling about.

*unknown* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bush Finally Says, I Would Have Not Gone Into Iraq </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 22:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit new policy on harassment of users </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 18:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Thursday May 13th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 05:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #It only takes one person to make you happy and change your life: YOU

*unknown* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Wednesday, May 13th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 16:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Life is like trying to ride a bicycle - To keep your balance, you have to keep moving

Albert Einstein </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Navy SEAL who says he killed bin Laden refutes Hersh account </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 01:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Tuesday, May 11th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 08:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Negative people need drama like it's oxygen. Stay positive and take their breath away.

*Unknown* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans, how can you be against both abortion and birth control? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 04:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Colorado program  deemed the most successful in the country which provided birth control for teens, reduced teen pregnancy by 40%. It also reduced abortions by 35%. Republicans just voted to defund that program.


I just don't get it. I respect your right to have an opinion. But these two positions seem so counter-productive to each other. You hate abortion so much, how can you be against something that reduces it so significantly?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congratulations to /u/wenchette - The winner of r/democrats practical joke </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 20:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes that is Carly Florina pictured in the banner on the top of our page. And yes she is upside down.

* http://oi62.tinypic.com/289wyl1.jpg


#Congratulations to /u/wenchette  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Monday, May 11th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 07:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #A year from now you will wish you had started today.

*Karen Lamb*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone who just said they took a bunch of pills. Is there anyone here that can help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 04:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dozens of TV Shows Cancelled as Networks Clean House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 08:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekend Wisdom - May 9th - 10th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 09:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #By changing nothing, nothing changes.

*Tony Robbins*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Modern GOP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 21:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Friday May 8th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 14:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #The greatest mistake you can make in life is to be continually fearing you will make one.

*Elbert Hubbard*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Thursday, May 7th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 08:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Sometimes the questions are complicated and the answers are simple

*Dr. Seuss* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What life insurance should I get? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 21:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a single 57 year old male and am thinking I should get some life insurance. Nothing extravagant. Do you have any recommendations? 


Additional information: I don;t really understand what type and how much I should get. To be honest, I'm not even sure why I need to get it. It just seems like something I should have. I make a modest income and can't afford to pay a huge amount. But if it is something I should have, I am willing to put some money toward it each month. Sorry for my lack of knowledge on this subject. Your expertise is what I am seeking.

I own a mobile home but not the land. I rent that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Wednesday, May 6th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 07:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #An entire sea of water cant sink a ship unless it gets inside the ship. Similarly, the negativity of the world cant put you down unless you allow it to get inside you. 

*Goi Nasu* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 2015 GOP Presidential Primary Debate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 06:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Monday, May 4th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 06:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Whether you think you can or whether you think you can't, you're right.

*Henry Ford* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN saw something we all missed at the Mayweather/Pacquiao fight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 07:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN saw something I didn't during the Mayweather/Pacquiao fight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 07:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 50 Shades of Hay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 23:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekend Wisdom - May 2nd - 3rd </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 18:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Kindness is language the deaf can hear and the blind can see

*Mark Twain* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MDA Telethon Ends Historic Run, Urgent Fight for Families Continues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 04:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Hillary Clinton might solve the student debt crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 03:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary's secret weapon? - GOP praise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 08:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Friday May 1st </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 06:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Everything is okay in the end, if it's not OK, then it's not the end.

*Ed Sheeran* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YSK how to tell if your batteries are dead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 22:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A quick way to tell if your batteries are good or not:

https://www.yahoo.com/makers/video-buzzfeed-is-your-battery-dead-we-test-a-117187544025.html
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> R/assistance will no longer allow gofundme campaigns for disaster relief - Only requests where the money goes directly to the cause will be allowed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 21:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When big disasters occur, we all care and want to help if we can. But we here at /r/assistance have noticed a rash of gofundme-type fundraiser pop up when these disasters occur. There is no way we can assure the money raised from these, actually go to the cause.

Therefore we will only allow requests where the money goes directly to the relief efforts.  This rule goes into effect immediately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Thursday April 30th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 07:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #The opposite of anger is not calmness, it is empathy.

*Mehmet Oz*

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Wednesday April 29th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 06:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Any fool can criticize, condemn and complain - and most fools do.

*Benjamin Franklin*

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Tuesday April 28th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 10:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Work for a cause NOT for applause. 

#Live life to express, NOT to impress. 

#Don't strive to make your presence noticed, just make your absence felt.

*author unknown* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Lindsey Graham: Send U.S. troops to topple Assad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 06:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Monday, April 27th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 08:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Courage is what it takes to stand up and speak; courage is also what it takes to sit down and listen.

*Winston S. Churchill* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Experts came to Nepal a week ago to ready them for an earthquake they knew would come </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 06:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you think Obama did at the Correspondents Dinner? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 05:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think he was funny? 

And what the hell happened to Cecily Strong? Did any of you think she was actually funny in the least bit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekend Wisdom - April 25th - 26th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 07:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Never believe that a few caring people can't change the world. For, indeed, that's all who ever have.

*Margaret Mead*

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jared Polis Trolls Steve King With Bill To Block Him From Legislating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 06:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chargers and Raiders overhaul design for potential L.A. stadium </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 09:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American Indian actors quit Adam Sandler movie over names </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 08:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a Tomy Pull and Pop for a disabled child </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 06:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
It is made by Tomy - Pull 'N Pop ball party dome gumball machine
It's the exact one as shown in this picture:

http://i.imgur.com/KXZAPaX.jpg 


They have searched everywhere and can not find one. Do you have one laying around we can buy from you. Or can you find one we can purchase for this awesome kid?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Friday April 24rd </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 04:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Life is like photography. You develop from the negatives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate Change Denial Disorder with Ed Begley Jr. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 07:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Wednesday, April 22nd </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 06:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Live so that when your children think of fairness, caring, and integrity, they think of you.

*H. Jackson Brown, Jr.*

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the absolute worst extreme right-wing websites? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 23:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for the worst ones. Like Brietbart.com who could not tell the truth if their life depended on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Tuesday, April 21st </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 08:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #A candle is never diminished by lighting another candle

*anonymous* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Koch Brothers Are Reportedly Ready To Back Scott Walker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 03:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Christie on the Bridgegate Scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 07:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Monday, April 20th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 06:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Blessed are those who give without remembering. And blessed are those who take without forgetting.

*Bernard Meltzer*

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The GOP in a nutshell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 06:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apparently god is for sale for $58 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 10:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP Hopefuls Divided on Cotton Claim that Attack on Iran would be over Several Days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 07:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What can I use to replace the reward system I currently use cigarettes for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 19:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After some 40 years of smoking, I have come to use cigarettes as kind of a reward system that gets me through my work day and home life. 

Finish this and I can go have a cigarette, do 30 more of these and I can go have a cigarette, get through 30 more minutes of this and I can go have a cigarette, etc. etc. etc.

When I attempt my quit, I know this will be a **MAJOR** issue for me. I could use some food but we all know what that will lead to. I don't want to gain a lot of weight. 

I need some others rewards to pacify and motivate me to get through my day. Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekend Wisdom - April 18th -19 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 08:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #We should stop waiting to get into heaven, and start trying to... create it.

*Randy Marsh* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Captain Kirk's Kickstarter plan to save California </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 02:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch Jon Stewart Crush Dick Cheney In Epic Takedown Over Iran </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 19:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Friday April 17th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 07:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Our prime purpose in this life is to help others. And if you can't help them, at least don't hurt them.

*Dalai Lama*


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last Call: Reid to McConnell: Schedule a Lynch Vote, or Ill Force One </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 04:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Thursday April 16th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 06:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Life is ten percent what happens to you and ninety percent how you respond to it.

*Lou Holtz*

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rock Hudson's 'True Love' Talks About Their Life Together: 'He Was a Sweetheart' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 04:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rock Hudson's 'True Love' Talks About Their Life Together: 'He Was a Sweetheart' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 04:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Wednesday April 15th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 07:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #In the end, it's not the years in your life that count. It's the life in your years.

*Abraham Lincoln*


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get a Job? Most Welfare Recipients Already Have One </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 06:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get a job? Most welfare recipients already have one </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 05:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Tuesday, April 14th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 06:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Life is really simple, but we insist on making it complicated.

*Confucius*


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My plans for the next five weeks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 05:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get ready for a very punny president - Here is the 404 page for Hillary's site </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 03:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Monday, April 12th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 07:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Don't judge each day by the harvest you reap but by the seeds that you plant.

*Robert Louis Stevenson* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who turned out to be the Loch Ness Monster? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 02:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today I watched the "Succubus" episode for about the tree hundred and fiddy time.  But I noticed something I had never noticed before. Do you know what character in that episode turned out to be the Loch Ness Monster?

--------------

Edit: Eric's optometrist is the Loch Ness Monster. The entire episode they make Chef's dad out as some looney who imagines everyone disguised as the Loch Ness monster asking for tree fiddy. But in the very last scene we find out that he wasn't imagining it. Watch the episode again and you will see. Eric's optometrist is the Loch Ness Monster.
Here is the script from the episode. Look at the last line. The optometrist asks Eric for three fifty.

http://www.imsdb.com/transcripts/South-Park-The-Succubus.html
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CLOSED UNTIL UNTIL NOVEMBER 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 19:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking forward to another wonderful season at Santa's Little Helpers.

We'll see you in November. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekend Wisdom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 15:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Its not the destination giving meaning to the mile - Its all we touch along the way that makes our lives worthwhile

*train_subject8344* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought for the Day - April 10th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 06:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Life isnt about waiting for the storm to pass, its about learning to dance in the rain. 

*Vivian Greene* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought for the Day - Thursday April 9th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 07:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Life always offers you a second chance - It's called tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul releases new campaign ad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 21:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Wednesday April 8th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 09:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Dream as if you'll live forever - Live as if you'll die today

*James Dean* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Irans Leaders Fall Into Line Behind Nuclear Accord </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 07:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the Alternative to Obama's Iran Deal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 02:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Home Shopping Network in Indiana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 01:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought of the Day - Tuesday, April 7th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 09:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Life has a way of testing a person's will, either by having nothing happen at all or everything happen at once.

*Paulo Coelho* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THOUGHT OF THE DAY - Monday, April 6th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 09:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Wisdom comes from the ear. And nothing near as valuable ever comes from the mouth.

*Backpackwayne* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What role did other countries play in Iran nuclear talks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 05:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Simple Guide To The Iranian Nuclear Deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 17:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 	Two types of nuclear weapons material: Uranium, which is mined. And Plutonium, which produced.

	Uranium needs to be about 90% pure to work in a nuclear weapon and only 5% for a power plant

	They have been enriching it to 20% - The agreement is that will stop  and they will only enrich it past 3.67% for 15 years

	They currently have 2200 pounds of the 20% enriched. They have agreed to give up 97% they already have.

	It is enriched by centrifuges.  There are two types. 

	One is designed in the 70s which runs on very old outdate software comparable to an Atari game.

	The other is a high tech version that is much faster   efficiently  Iran has none and will not be allowed to have any of these.

	Iran currently has 19,000 of the old inefficient type.

	The deal specifies this number be reduced to 6,000. And only the old and inefficient ones

	Iran would be allowed to conduct research and development on advanced centrifuges. But not produced or possess them.

	 Two ways to make plutonium: 

	Spent fuel rods used in enriching uranium can be used to make plutonium. Iran does not have this reprocessing ability. The deal specifies they cannot seek to gain this knowledge or ability and bans such processing plants.

	The second way is a reactor that is specifically designed to produce it. Iran currently has one such reactor that is not yet operational. 

	The deal specifies this core from this facility be  destroyed or removed from the country 

	Anything produced from this facility is required to be shipped out of the country.

	The other underground facility would partly converted to advanced nuclear research and the production of medical isotopes. About two thirds of its centrifuges would be removed. Foreign scientists would be present. It would have no fissile material that could be used to make a bomb.

	This was one of Israels biggest concerns 

	Unprecedented levels of inspections including on site inspectors, camera and Seals. Uranium is tracked from the time it comes out of the ground, through the processing until it is stored in cylinders. Ability to see what they are importing and exporting. Inventory control.

	Inspections anywhere in the country that could investigate suspicious sites or allegations of a covert enrichment facility. (details still be worked out)

	The issue of when the sanctions are to be removed still looms as one of the potential obstacles to a final agreement on June 30.

	UN Security Council resolutions on Irans nuclear program will be lifted simultaneously. A transparent procurement channel will be established, allowing Iran to get what it needs for civilian nuclear development while giving assurances to the world that the materials will not be diverted for non-peaceful use.

	 International cooperation to help Iran in research and development.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WEEKEND WISDOM - April 4-5th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 08:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #When nothing goes right..., just sit back and enjoy what's left.

*Backpackwayne* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spring is Here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 22:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought for the Day - Friday April 3rd </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 15:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Any child can make a mistake -  It takes a man to admit hes made one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought For The Day - Thursday April 2nd </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 08:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Everyone Falls - But that doesn't negate the climb

(a train_subject8344 original)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After almost five years, the time has come for me to resign as the head mod of r/assistance - Thank you all for everything. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 08:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #APRIL FOOLS!!! - Can't get rid of me that easy. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought for Today: Tuesday March 31st </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 08:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Don't Worry if Plan A Fails. There Are 25 More Letters in the Alphabet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Church Of Marijuana Gets Boost From Indiana's Anti-Gay 'Religious Freedom' Bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 06:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought For The Day: Monday 3/30 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 08:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #When tempted to fight fire with fire, remember the Fire Department usually uses water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran Backs Away From Key Detail in Nuclear Deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 05:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comedy Central gets ready to make another mistake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 03:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A New Star Trek TV Series May Be Closer Than You Think. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 08:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought for the Weekend - 3/28-29 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 06:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Love Your Enemies - It Really Pisses Them Off

**Have a great weekend everyone. :D** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought for the Day - Saturday, 3/27 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 06:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harry Reid is and was one badass Mo-Fo - Here he is as a young man the crap out another boxer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 04:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker suggests being an Eagle Scout has prepared him to be commander in chief </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 03:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to totally piss off your driver instuctor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 03:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tip of the Day: How to Never Forget Your Password </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 06:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Change all your passwords to "incorrect." 

#That way when you forget it, it will always tell you:

#"Your password is incorrect." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul Channels His Inner Tom Cotton, Calls For Defense Spending Hike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 17:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought for the Day (Thursday March 26th) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 06:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to relax:

* http://www.loveoflifequotes.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/Relax-were-all-crazy.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quote of the Day For Wednesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 08:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the battle of positive thinking verses reality, there comes a time when one must realize one thing:

* http://cdn.emgn.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/Funny-quotes-2.jpg

----------------------





**EDIT** - It's a joke people. I think tomorrow's quote will be  about not taking life so serious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boehner "Baffled" by reports Israel spoed on Iran </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 18:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today's Quote of the Day to make you day a little brighter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 17:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today's quote of the day to make your day a little brighter:

* http://cdn.emgn.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/Funny-quotes-3.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disturbed Man Tries to Break Into White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 22:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Cruz To Announce Presidential Run On Monday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 18:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Says He Told Netanyahu That Talk Before Election Hurt the Peace Process </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 18:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hate at a new level: "Shoot the gays" initiative likely to be circulated in California </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 03:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9,000 Animals Rescued From 'Worst Torture Operation' In The U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 18:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] Help us at r/assistance compile a list of places where needy folks can get help for their pets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 04:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We at r/assistance are compiling lists where people can find the help they need at the touch of a finger. This week we are doing pets. And we need your help to find as many charities, organizations, rescue centers and other services pet owners  in need may be looking for. 

**Please provide any help organizations you know of in this format:**

-------------------

* Name of Organization 

* Link to the site

* Service provide

* Area served (city, county, state or country)



-----------------



**For general help with lists to other sites please write it in this format:**

* Area served: Followed by a link to the site


---------------

We appreciate your help as it will help us help you and animals around the world.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help us make a list for r/assistance of animal assistance and charities organization around the world - We need you help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 03:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We at r/assistance are compiling lists where people can find the help they need at the touch of a finger. This week we are doing pets. And we need your help to find as many charities, organizations, rescue centers and other services pet owners  in need may be looking for. 

**Please provide any help organizations you know of in this format:**

-------------------

* Name of Organization 

* Link to the site

* Service provide

* Area served (city, county, state or country)



-----------------



**For general help with lists to other sites please write it in this format:**

* Area served: Followed by a link to the site


---------------

We appreciate your help as it will help us help you and animals around the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Referral Subject of the Week - Pet Charities - Please list all the pet charities and assistance you know of </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 23:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So that our subscribers will have the benefit of your wisdom and knowledge at their fingertips, We here at /r/assistance have decide to compile list of resources in one handy place to put on our sidebar.

So each week we will ask you to share all your resources for one specific area.

This week it is: 

#PET CHARITIES

We have many posts for the critters that can make our life worthwhile. 

We ask that you include the following:

* **Name of the organization**

* **A link to the site**

* **The specific area it serves** (city, county, state or country)

   We'd like to get resources around the world

* **The service it provides**

Please be concise so we can put these resources in a neat and easily accessible form. Please follow us in the coming weeks as we ask for resources in other areas that are needed on a regular basis. Next week it will be for the HOMELESS. 

Let's make this the most thorough list we can. Thanks for all your help

-------------------

**Edit: Please write it in this format to make it easier to compile and list later:**


* Name of Organization 

* Link to the site

* Service provide

* Area served

This will make it much easier for me to list when I do the compilation.

-----------------



**For general help with lists to other sites please write it in this format:**

* Area served   Service: Followed by a link to the site


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jon Cryer Reveals the Inside, Insane Account of Charlie Sheen's Infamous Meltdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 21:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It Took Tom Cotton Less Than A Minute To Invoke Hitler In First Senate Speech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 04:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul: I Signed Iran Letter In Order To Help Obama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 05:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tab Hunter opens up about his closeted career and Anthony Perkins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 01:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where's Putin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 19:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Burns Boehner at last night's Gridiron Club Dinner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 04:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting older changes a guy, President Barack Obama says, and he admits he's getting crankier.

"Next week I'm signing an executive order to get off my lawn," Obama joked Saturday night at the Gridiron Club and Foundation's annual dinner. On top of that, the nation's graying chief executive says he's having trouble now with his morning cup of joe. "Coffee really disagrees with me these days," he says, "which is why John Boehner just invited coffee to address the joint House." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This guy has some balls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 03:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How The Iran Letter Is Playing In The 2016 Campaign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 00:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time magazine responds to fuss over Hillary Clinton devil horns cover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 23:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So-Called 'Journalists' Poisoning Hillary's Well -- Again! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 23:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm old guy that just bought his first cell phone - Are there classes I can take to learn how to use it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 01:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought it an HTC 150 Smartphone at a cricket store. I'm good at the computer but I am having a hard time learning how to use this phone. Everyone keeps telling just keep trying, you will get it. Well I am not.

I would like to take a class to help me with it. Does anyone know of any such classes near Fullerton, CA? Or maybe a good online tutorial. Something that teaches you like you are five years old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm an old guy who just got his first cell phone - Is there a class I can take to learn how to use this thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 00:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought it  an HTC Smartphone a cricket store. I'm good at the computer but I am having a time learning how to use this thing.. Everyone keeps telling just keep trying, you will get it. Well I am not. 

I would like to take a class to help me with it. Does anyone know of any such classes near Fullerton? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dan Savage Challenges Ben Carson to "Suck MY Dick." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 07:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think of Verizon for TV, Internet and phone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 03:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AT T has pissed me off for the last time. I could go for paragraphs about how they keep raising my prices. I just want a place that I make a deal and they stick with it. I hate having to call and argue every four or five months.

I checked out Verizon, and they seem to have a decent deal but I fear all the same BS tactics of AT T. Are my fears justified. 

Do they have good service? Do they stick with their contract? Do they play games?

Would appreciate your opinions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what do you think of Verizon for TV, Internet and phone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 03:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something cool we can do for someone at a construction job for his birthday? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 21:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something cool we can do for someone at a construction job for his birthday? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 21:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confessions of a Theme Park Mascot: Don't Taunt Us, or Else </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 21:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA discovers that Mars once looked like Eric Cartman's head </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 07:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA discovers that Mars once looked like Eric Cartman's head </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 06:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News Doesn't Care If Bill O'Reilly Is A Liar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 23:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Supreme Court at Stake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 07:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Two Month Stand Off, House Passes Clean DHS Funding Bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 07:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edward Snowden In Talks To Return To U.S., Lawyer Says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 03:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now smile like you mean it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 03:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syfy Channel is having an all day, all night marathon of Spock heavy Star Treks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 22:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now they are showing the Search For Spock. Other shows from all the series will be shown throughout the day and night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Clown Car is Here! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 19:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hilarious Full-Page Ad in NYT Skewers Boehner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 19:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nemtov A Possible 'Sacrificial Victim' Investigators Say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 07:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CPAC 2015 Straw Poll: Rand Paul wins again  but Scott Walker is surging </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 23:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Compared to regular cigarettes, how harmful are e-cigs to your health? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 07:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a long time cigarette smoker trying to talk myself into quitting using e-cigs. I was wondering, compared to regular cigarettes, How harmful are the e-cigs to your health? 

Let's say that on a scale of 1 - 10, regular cigarettes are a ten. What number would e-cigs rate?

   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Birthday To CutieJudie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 00:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Chris Christie Supporters Now Turn Their Backs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 06:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whoever sent me the Oreo pie - Bless you. It was delicious! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 05:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember someone making a post about it but for the life of me, I do not remember who it was.

But I want to let you know it was delicious!


Thank you so much. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Costa Concordia captain sentenced to 16 years in prison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 05:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the hell is up with gas prices? They have raised them 35 cents in the last week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 21:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mt. Sinabung ejects ash into the air during an eruption in Karo regency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 07:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit at it's finest: This is the r/SantasLittleHelpers 2014 Christmas Video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 22:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your must-see Video of the year - This is the r/SantasLittleHelpers 2014 Christmas Video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 22:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This year /r/SantasLittleHelpers brought Christmas to over 700 families proving together, we  can create miracles.


* **[SantasLittleHelpers Christmas Video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2aJPNO4KPIk feature=youtu.be)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Birthday our own SueOlsen - We Love You Sue! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 22:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy Birthday Sue - We couldn't do this without you.

**WE LOVE YA!**



http://www.troll.me/images/pissed-off-obama/you-happy-birthday-playa.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We now have a "NEW Registered User" flair to identify requests being made by new accounts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 07:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may notice our **New User Registered** flair featured in red. This means the request is being made by an account younger than 60 days old.  We strongly suggest you take extra precautions and try to find ways to apply help more directly rather than sending cash.

We hope this tool will assist you in making more informed decisions. 


----------------------

**Other tips and tools to promote safe giving:**


* **APPLY ASSISTANCE DIRECTLY WHEN POSSIBLE!!!**  We highly recommend you pay the bill or buy the item instead of sending the money to the OP - This assures  money is going where they say it is** (EX: If someone is asking for help with a utility bill, pay that bill rather than giving the OP money)



* **ASK LOTS OF QUESTIONS IF YOU ARE CONSIDERING GIVING** - Dont be reluctant to ask  OP personal questions by PM - You wouldn't give a perfect stranger  help without  asking them a few questions - If the OP is reluctant to supply the information  by PM,  we recommend you do not give - It is up to the OP to supply you with the comfort and proof you desire and require - Get this information **BEFORE** you give!!!

* **This does not give anyone the right to  harass someone or subject them to a public trial:** - Be polite and respectful and do not make unfounded accusations. You do **not** have the right to put someone on trial - If you have concerns, contact the mods and be prepared to present proof

* **USE COMMON SENSE:** Take a moment to gather information about the requester. - Look at their overview page and history -  Gather any information  needed to pursue someone if they do not live up to their end of the bargain before you supply  assistance - Once you have given, you will not have that opportunity


----------------

**EDIT:**

* * As pointed out bt our moderator u/rhubey,  if you help someone by paying a bill for them, talk to someone from the billing department or customer service to make sure they do not keep your card information on file as the default payment card. This will avoid your card ever being used again by accident or even on purpose. Thanks you rhubey for this excellent advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biden urges Democrats to take credit for stimulus, U.S. recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 05:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to have a few rules appear in the box when you make a post in r/assistance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 04:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to have a few rules appear in the box when you make a post in my subreddit. (r/assistance). You know so people can not miss it. 

Is there anyone out there that might be willing to do this for me?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for one of you awesome editors to make our Christmas video for r/SantasLittleHelpers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 06:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/SantasLittleHelpers brings Christmas to hundreds of families every year who wouldn't have otherwise been able to join in the giving. The only thing as awesome as the giving itself, is to see the results as pictures come in from all over the world of families opening their present on Christmas Day. 

Here is the video from Christmas 2013:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vUyt_JwBDeQ

We are looking to do the same and are eagerly searching for one of you fine and talented individuals who is willing to put together a  video for Christmas 2014.

We have hundreds and hundreds of photos and have a background song already picked out. Is there someone out there who would be willing to help us out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To all of our friends on the East Coast of the US - BE SAFE!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 07:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't do anything stupid and just stay inside. Be ready for the worst. We are here for you.  

**STAY WARM NOW!!!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John McCain Pummeled by republican boos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 05:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm making this request on behalf of someone here who has helped many - They are asking for help with funeral costs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 04:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am making this request on behalf of /u/justaluckyshot, one of our mods and a good friend. Yesterday he lost someone very dear to him and the family needs help with the funeral costs. I can provide a paypal address if you care to help.

Justaluckyshot is famous for helping folks out here with car problems of all kinds. He has helped so many and I am asking for help in his time of need. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boehner defies Obama on Iran sanctions, invites Netanyahu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 04:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you all think of the Nightly Show with Larry Wilmore Show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 03:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what do you all think of this new show that is replacing Stephen Colbert?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Republican Response to the State of the Union </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 05:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Republican Response to the State of the Union </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 05:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wisdom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 01:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peep Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 01:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Medicaid expansion may contract </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 14:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Despite the hate from the right, history will be very kind to Obama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 06:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Christie is not happy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 02:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I find out who has been deleting certain entries on our spreadsheet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 19:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a log that will tell me who has been deleting entries on a spreadsheet and what those entries were?

There are about 12 people who have full access. I believe one of them is deleting entries that they shouldn't be. I would like to find out who and the information they have been deleting. 

If this is the wrong place to post this, please let me know.

Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senator Credits Day-Old Republican Congress With Last Years Economic Growth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 03:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a good comeback when someone keeps telling you to relax? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 06:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At work I have this guy constantly telling me to relax. Actually I am very relaxed but this certain comment does kind of irk me. I'm looking for a comeback that doesn't come across like I am angry the least. Just some sort of jab to shut him up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to help a vet from Michigan in dire need with a bankruptcy and eviction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 07:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The person is a vet, already served with eviction papers. They need lots of help in many areas but my first piece of advice is to declare bankruptcy. Can you please give advice of how to declare bankruptcy in specifically in Michigan using a Paralegal.

And also if there are any option with eviction.

The user's name is /u/Alohm1ab

They really need help and might be out in the very cold streets soon. Workingon other stuff but bankruptcy seems a must here. They just owe too much money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to help a vet from Michigan in dire need with a bankruptcy and eviction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 06:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The person is a vet, already served with eviction papers. They need lots of help in many areas but my first piece of advice is to declare bankruptcy. Can you please give advice of how to declare bankruptcy in specifically in Michigan using a Paralegal.

And also if there are any option with eviction.

The user's name is /u/Alohm1ab

They really need help and might be out in the very cold streets soon. Workingon other stuff but bankruptcy seems a must here. They just owe too much money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
