<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4130</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 07:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must say though. I quite enjoyed the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 06:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Master Chief

Keepin it real like a boss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 06:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Savage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 06:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he live? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 06:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, i'd be so pissed. Idgaf if you're drunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 06:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. Now I'm curious as to what happened to her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 06:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fat = fukno </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 00:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been there. The first impression I got of the place was *wizard*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 00:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 22:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking something like this (http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/736x/06/04/66/060466c8fa8e39e8784a36df7e56a7a2.jpg)

But bigger and more majestic. It has a rustic, sort of magical architecture style.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 07:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll say that the new novel coming out written by Frank O'Connor covers this exact topic. The humanity and consciousness of AI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 05:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cuz her handwriting is that good. Pshh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 23:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. Beard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 22:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This made me laugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 22:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like that would inhibit gains though :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many of you lift alone? and those that do, what do you do about a spot? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 21:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 20:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That dude in the background lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 20:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro your hair isn't horrible. Just get it shortened on the sides.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 20:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free biscuits? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 18:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jon. Will you be uploading to machinima, or staying on your old channel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 08:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubt it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 08:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never. Browse. /r/politics. That is the biggest cesspool of Bernie circlejerking and liberal mob mentality I've ever seen.

On topic. Halo 5 plays nothing like other shooters, and the ADS operates nothing like it does in any other game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 08:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty. Keep the dark hair, goes great with your eyes. But going to need more pics in a different pose. 7.5/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 08:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. But, who gives a shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 08:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you being serious?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 02:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know what a straw man fallacy is? That's what I'm referring too. And I never said he doesn't believe what he's saying, or stand by it. But he spouts ridiculous statements about the economy that amount to nothing more then blaming rich people for societies problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 01:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually I get downvoted into oblivion when I share a critical view of what is essentially the mob mentality that Sanders is encouraging. Seriously, it's just populist rhetoric based on socialism. /r/politics is the biggest cesspool of mob mentality and has a clear lack of any critical thinking skills. 

I could go on about Sanders but I'm still baffled that this guy can garner so much support without saying a single thing of substance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 01:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are calling New Blood their favorite. Apparently it was masterfully written. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 01:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a fucking idiot. Seriously, everything this guy says is Straw man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 00:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ben got absolutely *rekt* by our boy Chips Dubbo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm thinking of joining a fraternity, how is it and what should I know? What are your experiences, opinions, advice etc? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 22:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 20:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely disgusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 19:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait. I thought it was only freshmen that had to live on campus? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 19:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh. I like Matt Smith </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 19:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. But there will just be another set of armor underneath that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 18:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. Kinda feel bad for the kid. Doesn't even look like a burgeoning neckbeard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 08:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10/10 redhead and Cap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 01:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want Johnson back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 00:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much has, but much hasn't. I guarantee that unless it's involved in banking or drugs, the money has been earned legitimately. By nature, a business's duty to society is to make a profit. It's the tell tale sign as to whether it's needed and contributing. When profit is made, money has exchanged hands and a mutual exchange of goods or service for money has occurred. That business owner is being rewarded for his contribution. This happens even with the "evil corporations" Sanders wants to stop. So the more competitive the market, the harder it is to game the system. 

The issue happens when there is no competition and then prices can gauge. Example, cable and internet companies. In this case, government regulations strangled it. Which Sanders supports. So for a variety of reasons. Capitalism  socialism in pretty much every way.

It's hard to define free flowing economy because technically it already is if it's not government. Then it would only be in other people's accounts but spread out, so it wouldn't be nearly as effective. Bill Gates can invest that money, help his own enterprise, or donate it. Which applies for most rich people and benefits the economy more then redistributing it would.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 23:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And super cool shit that's otherwise rare and hard to do.

Like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 22:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I said, neither of them are war mongers. But the economic situation is a lot more complicated then that. Like... *a lot*. Chances are, if that money ended up in someone's bank account, they either: 

1.) Had illustrious government help. Bailouts, banking cabals, cable and internet companies, funding etc etc. Basically **crony** capitalism and exempt from market competition. 

2.) Benefited society in some way to generate that capital. Take Bill Gates for example, he made his money in a way that helped society advance. He did so with no government help. Look at Elon Musk. Same example, whom without his billions in the bank account, wouldn't have been able to start SpaceX or Tesla. BOTH benefiting society in a way the government never could. 

Redistribution of wealth (if that's what you're arguing for) are basically universally bad and have the opposite of the desired effect. 

What should be done is ending corporate welfare and creating a competitive field in the market. Which mah boi Rand wants to do. And this nearly universally improves the economy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 21:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's in a difficult position, but he's more of a libertarian. He has many socially liberal views but has to appeal to a socially conservative base. So his official position on certain issues are to leave it up to the states. Even though he's introduced a bill to legalize marijuana on a federal level, and has been open in his position on ending the drug war. 

When the debate happens, Rand v Sanders. It's going to be almost completely economic. In recent years we've had candidates that were extremely similar to each other and only differed when it came to smaller issues.

Now we have candidates that *generally* share the classic American view pertaining to foreign policy and social issues, but couldn't be further apart in regard to the economy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 20:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a completely different time. You can't compare the community then to know and still have a legitimate point about the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 20:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe Rand Paul to have the same honesty but with views more aligning with my own. Specifically pertaining to economics; I simply can't support the socialist views. However, if anyone other then Rand wins the Republican primary, then I'd vote Sanders. If it becomes Hillary v Bush/Cruz or whatnot. I'm voting third party.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 20:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've been pretty popular since the 40's. Either way, that's one thing I respect him for. He's consistent and honest about his positions, unlike Hillary or Bush.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 19:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically. But the Brits like their traditions. I think it would make for an interesting story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How cool would it be to have a story or series about the new princess being a muggleborn witch and going to Hogwarts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 19:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or both the royal kids. I'd read it and then watch it when it is inevitably made into visual form media. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 19:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a fucking idiot who spouts nothing more than populist rhetoric with no empirical evidence to prove his point. Have fun with your straw man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 18:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait. So kids just keep dying? In pattern out of no where? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 18:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fucking brutal. How was there no criminal prosecution for the rapes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 18:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe the response was a good one from what I can tell. Common sense says don't let someone stay that's not supposed too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 18:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring back these physics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 18:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BERNIEBERNIEBERRRR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 08:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What part of OH? I'm from there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 07:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that bad anymore honestly. Occasional dickbag here and there but it's getting better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 05:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maxi pads. Apparently </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 05:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd feel the same way if you got to hunt the chief </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's take a moment to thank Bravo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 05:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, this guy has put up with some shit since launch that likely go above and beyond his job description, then he routinely responds to people on Twitter experiencing issues. He also writes some amazing and detailed updates letting us know what is happening along with the thought process that goes into it. I also hear he lurks here and posts occasionally. 

Then goes and casts the HCS like a boss. 

So bravo, Bravo.

Plus, thank you Josh Holmes for interacting with Beyond. Great stuff over there.

[after glancing at his post history](http://giant.gfycat.com/AncientCarefulAnaconda.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 05:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great update. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 05:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro. It's been admitted in this form multiple times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 22:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was hilarious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 19:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone told you you have MASSIVE tits? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 09:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel bad for Hamlin at that point. He got so much undeserved shit from Jimmy because Chuck didn't have the balls to tell him himself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 08:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wondered how BB had the best character development </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 08:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 08:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, you have a rare natural beauty about you. 9/10 

I think the reason you may look young is your height. But you still got it goin on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 06:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't have the game mode. Could probably get it though. GT: ZeALoTT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Halo MCC] If anyone needs someone for customs. I'm down. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 06:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gamertag is ZeALoTT. Looking to play some customs or even grifball. Just add me and send an invite whenever you'd like to play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 06:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get the fuck out. Just get. The. Fuck. **OUT**

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 06:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> file browser is a necessity. 

343 is denying me a basic halotural right that Bungie would have bestowed upon me as soon as I broke that clear plastic film with a knife and gently slid my disk in to my Xbox one to experience the n**BR**vana. 

I could be tagging pictures and maps with g4y, I'd out BR you, bush d1d 9/11, and phagit just like the glory days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 05:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1.) MCC is playable

2.) Halo 5 is shaping up to be great. Tons of info on the *arena* out there. Plus, the lore and story is looking to be pretty good. So some research. But you might not like the way it looks, but you have to play it. I've seen people hate the way out looks and think it's going to suck, only to fall in love when they play it

3.) The halo community is not what it was. But it ***is*** growing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 04:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So just a typical asshole twat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 06:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are. But I'm at a regional campus at the moment, :/

I'll be in Columbus next year though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 05:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gotta go with maybe Joe Staten doing the grunts. Nathan Fillion as Buck perhaps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 04:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw people talking about it to on Yak so I was wondering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 02:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this an English bulldog or an Olde English Bulldogge?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 02:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. On many levels. No. They are easily still in their prime and given GEN2. Could wreck a IV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the current OSU Snapchat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 02:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 01:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will there be corgis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 21:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What dicks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 20:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think chief is going to let innocent people die for the greater good. That's what ONI does </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 19:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a really good analysis. You make good points. I keep thinking this would make a really good political/action drama </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did chief and Blue leave? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 19:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious. They could have stole a pelican. But they wouldn't get far without slipspace capabilities. I'm just wondering how chief is even traveling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 18:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah I'd do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 18:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, super pretty. You have amazing hair and gorgeous eyes the compliment your style. Plus, a *killer* smile. 

Would approach and talk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 05:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I said. On a good day, it pulls upwards of 21k on average during peak hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 05:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. Honestly, that game is the shit. It's current competitive settings (MLG V7) are probably the best iteration out of any halo. The custom games community is flourishing because of how customizable forge and games are, the campaign and customization options are great. Plus the file browser makes it easy to find maps, games, and other community creations. 

It had so much potential if it had only launched with better maps, and the TU settings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 04:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck no. This guy knows absolutely nothing about economics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 01:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk why you got downvoted. It is easily the best version of competitive halo by far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 00:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck to you, Spartan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 20:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one at the moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 19:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'd be a shame if they.... lost all of them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 19:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our impenetrable fortress among the stars... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 18:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bear in mind. I believe that is only the atmosphere that is on fire. Thus causing a nuclear winter, the entire surface isn't molten.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 18:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They get 25k on a good day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 17:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There will be a bunch coming out also. So check those out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 17:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But... pls take noble 6 with you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 09:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They won't. They want it to be special for lore fans, yet still understandable by casual fans. They are making it with your concern in mind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 09:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we're purely looking at the outcomes, ODSTs don't do suicide missions. And then I'd say SIVs perform, act, and were trained more like ODSTs. SIIIs however, had slightly better augmentations than S4s, plus the advantage of augmentation at puberty and post augment being close to par with IIs, and have been raised since childhood as Spartans. 

Give them GEN2 armor and they'll wreck an S4. Not to knock the IVs, but we gotta remember the hierarchy here. I get why you explained it that way though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 08:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you got it backwards with the IIIs and IVs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 07:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's saying something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 07:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 11/10 

Jet fuel can't melt dank bemez </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 06:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So they really are the superior Spartans. I mean, they got really lucky honestly. Going into service literally when the war ends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 05:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. There is some serious room for AMAZING storytelling here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 05:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are 323 active S3s? I really feel like that's some ignored story potential there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 05:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I.. want to believe....

From a pure storytelling perspective, as others have said, he needed to die. But we never see a blade fall through him. Plus we don't know the surrounding terrain or tech. There is a slim chance he survived, but unlikely. But then again, unlikely things happen in that universe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 04:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His helmet was off and on the ground while he was still alive, that was the POV during the final scene. PLUS he had been kicking elites off of him that entire time. What's to say he didn't kick the one off and sprint his ass away and hitch a ride off planet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
