<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1324</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 20:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the feels, same movie and around the same age. Probably the most scared I've ever been by a movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 01:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coincidentally, my grandfather made this for dinner today and my grandma was pissed because the two 'don't go together." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm having trouble finding the name of an old GBA game... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 19:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 01:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even though it ended in disappointment on my part, that was definitely worth reading. Good effort for something so random! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 23:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Railway Rifle is hands down my favorite weapon. I just wish you could get it in unmoddded F:NV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favorite companion, Derpmeat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 00:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 21:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES! Came here to say that actually! Probably one of my favorite games from back in the day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 16:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking hermit crabs. Don't ask me why, but those things terrify me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Reddit, what was your first car? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 19:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got mine yesterday, 98 Cadillac sts. What was yours and what's your best story with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 98 sts questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 17:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey /r/Cadillac I got my first car yesterday, the 98 sts! Let me start by saying that I love it, it drives nice and is pretty quick. However with it being over a decade old I'm sure there are some things that I can do to make it better. Any suggestions on what I can get done? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-03 16:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised nobody said Bully. It really hits you right in the feels at several points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 20:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Once I started the only thing that stopped me was the energy running out, and then I was right back on it when it came back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 14:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine would be pretty sick :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 15:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mashed potatoes.. Imagine sticking your hand in that on a hot day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 20:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back when I was a kid I had this dream (reoccurring for months) where I was at a carnival-like place and these Smurfs with knives would chase me around and eventually kill me. Then i would appear back at the entrance and it would keep happening until I woke up. May not be as bad as some of these, but it kept me from ever watching the Smurfs again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 18:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donkey Kong 64.. That game was simply amazing to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 15:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was the most depressing thing I've read all day...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 12:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually exactly what I was talking about. Thanks for that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help switching between certain notes.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 02:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't know the technical term for this because I just started playing recently, so I'll give an example. The tabs I found for the song raining blood have you holding the eighth fret of the fifth and fourth strings, and then you have to go to the ninth fret and then back (only playing these two strings that is). However, when I try it I can't make the transition without it sounding bad. So first, any tips would be appreciated. And if someone knows the term for playing two strings at once, please share. Thanks (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Had 20 minutes to spare so I drew the best thing I could think of </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 05:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 22:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the first three paragraphs about 4 times thinking I had misread it. Then I got scared that North Korea just took over the world. Then I saw the name of the website -____- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My god. I wish there was something like that around me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need to hold a sloth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 03:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright guys, I'm on a mission to get a picture of me holding a sloth before the summer comes. Unfortunately, I live in Pennsylvania. So does anyone have any idea as to where I can go to hold a sloth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 01:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
