<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3598</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 10:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was all pre-rent control. Remember Murray Rothbard talking about growing up in New York City and everyone was moving on 1 March because it was easy to find an apartment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 08:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A great discussion, not only of the re-unionisation issue but of how the Democratic party had to be socially Conservative until the civil rights era. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 09:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A nice roundup of the arguments that ISIS is filled with opportunists from a long way back and much of its rise is to do with the murkiness of Iraqi politics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 10:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A nice roundup of the arguments as to why marriage is not the solution to child poverty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 12:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A nice little essay reminding that there is been in a supply of seemingly mad people in charge of nuclear weapons who were nonetheless deterred by the possibility of a second strike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 01:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is to review of the first volume of the three volume biography of Stalin. The first volume is 1000 pages long. 

Clearly, this guy is trying to give Robert Caro and his biography of LBJ a run for his money in terms of comprehensiveness and quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 16:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like his analogy of involuntary employment means the same thing as being involuntarily married. Both are matching problems. Adding the word involuntary is just confused to the search and matching problem at hand. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 16:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a massive trial with the polio vaccine before it was introduced in the whole community. The trial involved hundreds of thousands of children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 16:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Measles is the most contagious disease that is known. It is therefore not possible to use tort liability to sue the specific person who infected you because it is not possible to trace the infection to a specific child.

The classic example was polio. 90 to 95% of people infected with polio were asymptomatic but infectious to others. It was spread by failing to wash your hands properly after going to the toilet. Small children tend to do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 16:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Babies are too young to vaccinate.
2. The vaccine is only 95% effective.
3. People with compromised immunity system such undergoing chemotherapy are also vulnerable and of a high risk of dying.
4. Community of about 92% of the community creates herd immunity
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 16:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Babies are too young to vaccinate.
2. The vaccine is only 95% effective.
3. People with compromised immunity system such undergoing chemotherapy are also vulnerable and of a high risk of dying.
4. Community of about 92% of the community creates herd immunity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 02:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A thorough round up of both the causes and solutions to issues regarding women's economic opportunities with the solutions addressing well proven causes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 11:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT

An excellent roundup of how the religious exemptions constitutional jurisprudence moved from the courts from making balancing decisions on a case-by-case basis to the Scalia majority opinion of 1990 that the Constitution only outlaws intentional religious discrimination. 

After that, under the 1990 Scalia majority opinion, religions have to take their chances in democratic politics like the rest of us if they want special exemptions from laws. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 06:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT

An excellent interview with a brave woman who has bodyguards 24/7 because of what she says </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 05:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to add that I do not agree with this particular article, but it is an excellent statement of the case for rent control which others can then pick holes in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 05:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

This article is probably one of the best summaries of the Piketty debate I have seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 01:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't post directly to the PDF. I couldn't work out how to do that on my browser, but the PDF if you click on it is a wealth of information, I've never seen anywhere else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 12:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unmarried women haved out earned Unmarried men for some time according to Tom Sowell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 12:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The paper is silly, but represents a large number of people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 06:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did notice anywhere in the article them pointing to a country that managed to get out of the extreme poverty by increasing the minimum wage. The only evidence the author of the article pointed to was from the United States on the effects of the minimum wage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 06:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good place to take assignment problems for economics 101 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 04:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No justice, you get 6 Karma and I get none. Point of link was to show type of thinking out there and for others, a chance to rebut it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 07:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The alcohol consumption figures are interesting, given all the stories you see about teenagers drinking themselves stupid and sometimes to the point of alcohol poisoning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 07:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT

A nice discussion of why marriage is not a solution to poverty and the teen pregnancy problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 13:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, some has to be trusted somewhere along the line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 12:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that pretty much happened in that Egyptian plane, but I think the captain got back into the cabin towards the end, but couldn't pull the plane up because the suicidal pilot is pushing down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 12:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The vaccine and drugs market in general really run as prizes markets because all the prizes are handed out by government if and when they buy your new drug  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 12:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they do for cabin crew to go in in case of crew incapacitation, but there is another lock inside to prevent terrorist takeovers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 11:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATE.

Nice roundup of the politics and economics of federalism on the extent to which there should be free trade between the states and whether one state can regulate how another state produces its exports to that state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 04:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ADMISSION STATEMENT.

Another nice little roundup showing that the number of false positives in research is disturbingly large. The incentive to uncover these are small because the rewards of reinvestigating other people's data is generally small in a world of publishing or perish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 01:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

This book is a defence of attack ads and negativity in politics. It includes the best, worst, and most counter-productive attack ads broadcast all time to illustrate its points brilliantly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 09:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A nice little roundup from the Guardian on scientific fraud, which is far wider than previously thought. The key driver of this fraud is the publish or perish motivations of academics before and after they get tenure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 04:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A nice little summary of the history of diplomatic spying, much of it which is for economic advantage.  

At the 2009 G20 meetings in London, the British intelligence agency GCHQ set up fake internet cafes for delegates to use in order to log their keystrokes. If you are dumb enough to use an Internet cafe for official business, you deserve to be spied on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 00:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a massive difference between rowdy protest at a public meeting, and ambushing a politician while dining with his family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 10:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then why does Pres Obama supports charter schools? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 10:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes both Being found guilty on appeal against the not guilty verdict as well as being found not guilty appeal against a guilty verdict can happen in the civil law systems </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 07:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT

The discussion of the complex way in which personality traits interact with political dispositions. Questions not asked include:

1. People become more conservative in their voting as they get older that their personalities stabilise at 30;

2. Women change their vote more often than men, depending on whether their married divorce, single parents or have children because of the demand for social insurance. How was this connected to personality traits? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 07:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guilty at trial,  won 1st appeal,  lost final appeal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 04:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who said that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 00:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT 

a nice little article pointing out how ignorant the media are of the law. 

Our intrepid reporters do not understand the concept of on bail pending further appeal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 00:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she is on bail pending appeal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 00:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she is on bail pending appeal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 08:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The flaw in the reasoning about administrative costs been at driver of higher costs in America is competition.

Leaving to one side the Federal prohibition against interstate competition in health care plans, and any state mandates as to what must be in ill health care plan, two considerable asides, all the is saying is there is an entrepreneurial opportunity to win business in health insurance by offering simple plans that are cheap to administer.

The extent that administratively complex plan survive in competition rather than because of mandates, suggest that consumers are willing to pay for whatever they buy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 08:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A nice summary of the reasons for higher health costs in the USA by the most experienced health economist around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 04:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true. It still has a craps website. Few know of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 13:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT

A nice op-ed by Robert Aumann explaining how the blackmailers paradox bedevils Middle East peace negotiations as well as a path to get out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 13:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A nice interview with Robert Aumann about his views on how those who want peace must prepare for war and be patient and willing to walk away from the negotiating table. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 07:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The conman had access to the official plates </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 01:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine was a New Zealand mobile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 01:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When was that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 13:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not face a paywall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 10:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT

Nice summary by Bryan Caplan of his writings on his theory of voting as rational irrationality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 06:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you aware of the far more extreme views of some of his coalition partners such as the those made up of emigres from Russia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 06:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read somewhere that 74% of government employees in Canada are unionised as compared to about 15% of private employees. That makes a big difference to headline comparisons that do not make this distinction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 05:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

Part of a series in the Guardian on science and the green moment.

This entry makes it a good case in my mind that the green movement is somewhat selective in its use of science </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 04:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that the point. a national single-payer system still involves denial of service and people dying in the queue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 03:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read somewhere that the 8% success rate is similar to sitting down with a good friend and having a discussion over the fact that you drink a bit too much and that is really harming your friends and family </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 03:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, I didn't know that the public sector was so unionised in Canada. That is ignored in the international comparison.

Indeed any international comparison of unionisation should always split out the public sector in the private sector to have any use whatsoever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 03:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A new study looks at the peaks of different types of cognitive abilities over a lifespan.

Apparently, them young whippersnappers got a good memory for information, but we oldies have a better vocabulary, and superior judgement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 12:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A nice article about the extent to which lazy statistics intrude into public policy. 

More than a few statistics published by breathless journalists run into the problem that more people in the community have been a victim of a crime or some other more misfortune than there are actual people in that community with the relevant demographic characteristics be it by age or whatever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 11:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

No one doubts the sincerity of Alcoholics Anonymous and those who participate and organise that movement. This article argues that its treatment programme has simply been overtaken by events and more effective options are available.

This is important both in terms of coping with alcoholism and the fact that some people are required to attend Alcoholics Anonymous as part of sentences imposed by courts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 14:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

Nice little myth buster explaining that although gerrymanders has a bit of a role, there are many other reasons why the American electorate is so polarised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 10:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT

This is a nice roundup of the law and economics as well is the politics of financial market regulation in the aftermath of the 2008 financial crisis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 06:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The peltzman effect is well established. Originally,  safety equipment allow you to do what otherwise would not be attemped at all rather than marginal increase in risk taking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 05:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Eurozone countries spend more on food too than USA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 01:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, can't compete on costs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 12:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The test was administered to a range of Harvard students. None of them completed it in 10 minutes
see http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2831095/Harvard-students-sit-1964-Louisiana-Literacy-Test-black-voters-pass-allowed-polls-single-person-FAILED.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 11:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought state by state popular referendums had a lot to do with the decriminalisation of marijuana medical and other purposes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 08:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

Great roundup by great sociologists of the current position of the inner city black men </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 08:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hard enough to even understand all the questions, much less answer them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 00:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT

An instructive wargame played at the Pentagon in 2004 rather ably demonstrated the folly of war with Iran. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 10:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have no trouble finding volunteers from firing squads </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 10:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A nice essay by Matthew Ridley on the case for fossil fuels and how is not going anywhere any time soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 10:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT

A nice reminder of about how D-Day was a rather close run thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 10:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

An excellent case for the transpacific partnership by fine labour economist, David Autor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 01:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A marvellous roundup of trends in oil prices over the last hundred more years with great graphics and excellent analysis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 06:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT

This is a brilliant review by Brad Delong of a biography of Milton Friedman published some years ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 21:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20% of population is undatable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 21:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 21:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but the essay itself was a good  summary of the case for disinvesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 14:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT 

a nice little essay on the latest way in which small countries can trade on their sovereignty. Quite surprised that some of these passports for sale can get you visa-free access to 132 countries </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 14:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like Seinfeld's law </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 12:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT

A good list of replies to criticisms of fossil fuel disinvestment. It can't seem to make up its mind that about what it's trying to do.

In the end, the purpose is to bring moral pressure against self-interest, which is a real stayer in human affairs. You can always rely upon self-interest to keep on trying right to the end of the race. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 11:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, In 2008, Clinton showed she was a bit of a battered old warhorse who had accumulated a lot of enemies, battle scars and was rather slippery with the truth and what she actually stood for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 10:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peace treaties usually bring an end to matters such as reparations and draw a line under all claims, be they public and private </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 08:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Germany paid war reparations to Greece in about 1960. Naturally, Greek politicians stole it and hardly anything filtered down to ordinary people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 08:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A nice discussion about how ISIS is more a rabble that happens to survive because of the lack of unity among its enemies which include the Iraqi government government and its army that runaway, but there has many other enemies as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 02:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend found that acupuncture help with his knee pain as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 14:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The control group would be taking actual medicine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 12:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marijuana has active ingredients in it. 

Homoeopathic tablets etc have no active ingredients </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 12:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, there's only so much you can capture in a title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 11:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

This is a fine summary of the work on the Dunning Kruger effect by Dunning himself explaining that people lack the ability to recognise their own limitations, principally through overconfidence. 

To recognise you lack skills such as in the rules of grammar, you must have extensive knowledge of the rules of grammar to realise you don't know the rules of grammar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 08:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

Deirdre McCloskey, in this great book review, argues that Industrial Revolution just got along just fine, despite quite endemic government corruption. Something to ponder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 06:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT

Fair Trade-certified coffee is growing in consumer familiarity and sales, but strict certification requirements are resulting in uneven economic advantages for coffee growers and lower quality coffee for consumers. 

By failing to address these problems, industry confidence in Fair Trade coffee is slipping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 04:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A nice summary of Robert Putman's latest thinking. I don't agree with him but have some great data and interesting arguments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 03:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the guy who wrote this diatribe forgot to check all the studies of the voting habits of economists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 23:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A long discussion of Irish politics during the Troubles. 

Some of the tactics of the British intelligence were quite clever such as running a discount dry-cleaning service to detect bomb-making residue on clothes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 23:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT

Another contribution to a complicated debate about sources of distrust of science across the political spectrum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 23:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A nice Roundup of reviews on a hot button issue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 23:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Political management. Clinton is known for running a pretty chaotic show

what did she gained from setting herself up for criticism like this?

she has a habit of scoring too many own goals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 09:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A delightful little essay for constitutional pedants, legal pedants and those who want to know what the Logan Act when it is mentioned, which is frequently. A law honoured in the breach </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 06:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT

A nice summary of the case against performance reviews, and in particular how they are often badly run by people who focus on the negative rather than act as cheerleaders.

Peter Drucker argued that the task of a manager is to make strengths productive. I find the performance reviews focuses are not what you're good at, but what your bad at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 02:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rupert Murdoch's shifts with the political winds and is always sure to be the new best friend of the next Prime Minister. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 02:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I'm not a morning person. Let the morning, people drive to work in the dark. Might put a damper on that horrible cheerfulness they have at the breakfast table </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 22:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> see https://acesflyinghigh.wordpress.com/2012/03/17/intercepting-the-bear/ for file you want </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 11:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By the way, the author is a transsexual Libertarian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 11:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The demand for most cars above that of a small medium sedan could be explained by people wanting to drive and seen to be driving a big expensive car. They are status vehicles.

Male midlife crises would have no meaning if you couldn't buy an expensive sports car and drive it around </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 06:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A hell of a lot of people of all ages like driving their cars. Also, driverless sports cars are a contradiction in terms.

For men, investing in a shiny red sports car or some other status display has advantages to them in the marriage and dating market </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 06:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Explained about 30 years ago by Jacob mincer  the rate of depreciation on human capital during career interruptions is much higher in some careers rather than others.

For example, an IT scientist will be completely out of date, If they take four years off. If your specialty is history or literature, nothing much changes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 06:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mean to say that the insurance companies are not charging the profit maximising insurance price at the moment in these other lines of business? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 06:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put bluntly, STEM is a poor occupational choice given the skill sets of men and women as they go to college </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 04:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, they do seem to be flying target practice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 03:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about metal fatigue after 90 years of flying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 02:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT

A nice piece of myth busting about daylight saving, which happens to be very popular where I live.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 00:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A nice summary of the contemporary relevance of Machiavelli </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 11:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> know any unbiased sources? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 10:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

Another great essay by Christine Hohh Sommers on gender politics and child rearing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 10:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Karl Popper observed that the motives of researcher don't matter. What matters is the quality of the critical discussion of what they have said.

Knowledge grows through critical discussion, not studying the biographies of the speakers.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 06:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT

Nice essay about how Boys are now being left behind are becoming the second sex  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 06:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no progress at all!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 00:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> very true, especially during elections </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 23:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very interesting essay on the rise of women to the top of the corporate ladder.

The underlying research quoted in the paper shows that if you control for background (i.e. skills and talent) and exit (i.e. women staying in the workforce) women earn more than men and get more aggressively promoted than men in corporate ladders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 23:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

Very interesting essay on the rise of women to the top of the corporate ladder. 

The underlying research quoted in the paper shows that if you control for background (i.e. skills and talent) and exit (i.e. women staying in the workforce) women earn more than men and get more aggressively promoted than men in corporate ladders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 23:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

Great essay discussing when colonisation was a private enterprise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 06:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, food riots within a couple years was a rather demanding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 06:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first job was working in a bank. Serving the public back when everyone came into the bank because it was before ATMs, was I was quite shocked by the lack of manners and morals of some people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 05:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a number of economic journal articles on acting white And on oppositional identities </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 03:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 02:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fryer leads literature on economics of oppositional identities </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 01:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find these arguments about education in inequality rather puzzling considering I'm old enough to have gone to university with plenty of people who are the first member of their family to get passed high school </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 01:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compensating differentials lives! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 01:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indian curries are now the most popular foods in Britain so that was a gap in the article that was not mentioned. Also, that undermines your point about vegetarianism a bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 23:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT

The latest oppressed minority is coming forward. Apparently a wage premium of 5-10% for full beauty in the labour market is not enough compensation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 12:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite correct. There are some fanatics in it but a considerable number of opportunists too, apparently the majority fall into this category. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 10:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, perhaps the biggest worry is the political parties seem to be outbidding themselves into how hire the contribution rate can go.

There is no recognition that the maximum contribution you could possibly need for your retirement may have already been reached. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 09:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A nice reminder of the 1960s and that the Apollo program was incredibly expensive for its time. Something that is forgotten in retrospect, especially when it's put forward as a rationale for further public investment in incredibly expensive science projects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 06:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually disagree with the Australian system which I used to be subject to. 

First, people save far too much for their retirement. So much so, that they'll be wealthier in their retirement, if they make it that far, than they were during their working lives.

Secondly, there are required to save for their retirement before they have bought other basic things such as a car and a house deposit.

The practical upshot of the Australian system is that low paid workers save for their own retirement rather than rely on an means tested old age pension that would be funded by taxes on the middle-class. These low paid workers are in the peculiar position of having retirement savings but not enough savings to buy a house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 00:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no pay wall when I read it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 13:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT

A nice discussion of recent issues of capital taxation, including that the optimal rate of taxation on income from capital is zero </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 13:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

This is a great roundup of the pros and cons of cities and states entering the global subsidy market and a race to the bottom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 13:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUMMARY STATEMENT.

There is a plan behind this accumulation of enemies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 01:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually excellent news. People in developing countries are more likely to die diseases of developed countries rather than diseases that are unknown in developed countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 13:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think wireless charging will just be a major boom for the market for tinfoil for the tinfoil hat brigade </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 12:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Merv Hughes was one of the funniest cricketers of his time and that was back when cricketers had big personalities and weight problems too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 05:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pluto had so many supporters that a separate category was invented called planetoid as I recall when it was downgraded so that their opposition would be tempered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 05:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

More science research grants for proving the bleeding obvious. 

Anyone who has some capacity for emotional insight into family, friends and read the odd novel would have worked this out long long time ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 05:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 01:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many libertarians support the death penalty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 01:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A great summary of the case for drug legalisation by Gary Becker and Kevin Murphy. The chart on the devastation that the drug war is having on law and order  and governance, south of the border is well put </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 13:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great photo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 11:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A cornered North Korea is far more dangerous than a cornered Iran principally because North Korea presumably has a lot of chemical and biological weapons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 07:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A nice antidote to all those who spend time North Korean watching because they are some sort of threat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 07:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure firing a pistol in the air repeatedly is particularly safe as the bullets have to come down somewhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 07:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen any reference to this Icelandic beer ban in any of the prohibition literature </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 07:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

The title of the article says it all, and it is a very valid question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 03:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did not come up as posted when I post at almost same time as other post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 05:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Westbro is full of lawyers careful to stay within the law, winning in supreme court on what they do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 01:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting discussion of the costs and benefits of medical screening, which some people are very keen on as a way of saving money in the health sector </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 00:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT

A reply to a discussion of ISIS that was posted also on TrueReddit about a week ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 00:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 10:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Articles include:
The Libertarian Delusion
Robert Kuttner
The free-market fantasy stands discredited by events. The challenge now: redeeming effective and democratic government.

Why Economists Cling to Discredited Ideas
Jeff Madrick
Free-market economists may be at odds with reality, but it fits the needs of the rich and the powerful.

The Perils of Privatization
Ann Hagedorn
As Blackwater showed, many of the efficiencies are spurious, because contractors cut corners.

Why Markets Cant Price the Priceless
Joan Fitzgerald
It takes government planning to promote rational conservation and use of water.

Markets, States, and the Green Transition
Fred Block
To get renewable energy technologies into broad use, government needs to promote both supply and demand. Markets are too risk-averse.

Hating the Hand That Enriches You
Roger Lowenstein
What interests me is why so many successful investors are so bitterly aligned against the agency [the Federal Reserve] that, arguably, single-handedly revived the capitalist system </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 09:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is better to be misconstrued than ignored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 09:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were discussions of this in various places last year. Apparently natural born means born to a US citizen anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 04:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My previous news link was on the hypocrisy of senator cruz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 01:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kidney failure from dehydration </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 01:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> kidney failure from The associated dehydration </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 23:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Justice Samuel Alito, Justices Antonin Scalia and Clarence Thomas all dissented.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 10:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> see also http://utopiayouarestandinginit.com/2015/01/16/the-impact-of-body-cameras-on-police-brutality/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 10:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read somewhere that requiring police to wear cameras on their lapels reduced police complaints for excessive force accepted by 70% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 07:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT
addressed many of the issues raised by Edward Luttwaks article Toward Post-Heroic Warfare (Foreign Affairs. 1995), but also brought more recent issues to light in the course of five sessions: (1) Heroism and Self-Sacrifice, (2) Casualty Aversion, (3) Casualty Avoidance, (4) Combat Motivation, and (5) the potential transition from Heroes to Victims.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 03:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Healthcare is a labour-intensive industry in a well-paid country that also funds pharmaceuticals and operations far more frequently than the waiting lists in Europe.

Have you made this comparison on a purchasing power parity basis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 02:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A surprising amount of analysis of Libya seems to suggest that we should dig up Col Gadaffi and putting him back in power or at least it was a bad idea that he was overthrown.

Rather reminiscent of the 1980s neoconservative analysis of Latin America where people preferred the right-wing tyrant they knew rather the left-wing tyrant they didn't know from the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 02:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought inflation was a monetary phenomena? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 01:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought poor people in America were already eligible for Medicare, Medicaid or CHIPS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 23:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your evidence than single payer reduces costs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 09:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go China </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 02:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

A nice summary from a few years ago of the pros and cons of efficient markets and active versus passive investment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 00:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The number of times I've had to put up with denunciations of economics is the spawn of neoliberalism  wish I had a dollar for every time that happened at parties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 02:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Search and matching frictions on steroids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 23:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The author is now the Greek Finance Minister </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 23:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT
I think this analysis is overrated, but it is still worth reading regarding the interactions between psychology, personality traits and political preferences </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 23:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certainly true in the case of people on low and ordinary pay. 

On the other hand, I know hairdressers who are subject to noncompete agreements in the same area as where they used to worked so they don't take away the customers of their old salon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 12:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  every major employer forms a de facto cartel 

How many people belong to this cartel? Is the cartel stable or unstable? How was this cartel deal with cheating, defection and new entry?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 09:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The low paid workers, do you really think it's worth the litigation costs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 06:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> david Friedman argues on this that
"the employer who insists on an employee signing a non- competition agreement will find that he must pay, in additional wages or other terms of employment, the cost that the agreement imposes upon the employee, as measured by the employee and revealed in his actions.

It follows that the employer will insist on such an agreement only if he believes that its value to him is greater than its cost to the employee The contract is designed, after all, with the objective of getting the other party to sign it." 

see http://utopiayouarestandinginit.com/2014/11/21/some-economics-of-zero-hours-contracts-part-1-concepts-definitions-and-initial-puzzles/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 10:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did not know that http://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/style/how-bulgaria-saved-its-jews-from-nazi-concentration-camps/2013/05/08/e866bdda-8cb1-11e2-9838-d62f083ba93f_story.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 04:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeff Milyo gives a great summary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 04:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The author might got a bit further  by looked at the rat race aspects of academic tenure  the need to publish or perish and work a hundred hours a week in your late 20s and 30s when starting a family might be a consideration.

What is the ratio of male to female economists outside of academia? 

An analysis which particular fields prominent female economists work in might be interesting, including linking it to depreciation rates of occupational human capital, while taking time out of the workforce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 02:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weddings are extremely expensive in India. Obviously so much so, that your marry anyone by the time you get to the altar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 02:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Notice how few in Denmark fell victim </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 02:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A most unusual headline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 22:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the headline. Does the Washington Post think Walmart got as far as it did on the basis of some other motivation and business strategy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 22:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Median voter theorem explains all as does directors' law </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 12:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBMISSION STATEMENT.

Great roundup of all the issues by the leading labour economist working in the area </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 09:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Danny DeVito is also very good actor and in this case explains the economics perfectly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 05:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ethical investing funds versus investment in vice industry funds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
