<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5510</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 13:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it was like this in the UK when some fat, pig-faced cunt called Jade Goody died. She was a D-List "celeb" from a reality tv show called Big Brother. A talentless moron, really. Pretty sure she was accused of racism at one point. Then she got cancer and became the shining role model, a pillar of feminine strength. The papers that had so slated her before practically lauded her as a national hero when she died. Stupid, bald wanker.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 13:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck me, me friend does this whenever there's a social thing. Considers herself a photographer and then rudely interrupts any conversation/activities/fun so we can all POSE for a photo. I tell her, "Your photos would look much better if we all looked natural." 

I'm of the opinion that if somebody is a good photographer, you shouldn't even know they are there. FUCK OFF WITH YOUR SHITTY CANON YOU STUPID, SNAP-HAPPY CUNT AND COME AND ENJOY THE PICNIC. YOU TWAT.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 11:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely not. 

Source: worked it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 12:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downvoted you before I upvoted you so I could give you +2 points </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 12:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I don't let my ego dictate my emotional state. Being right or wrong is no expression of you as a human being.

If somebody proves you wrong, or if somebody judges you for something you've done, then so what? People are way too busy thinking about their own mistakes and lives to worry about you being wrong about something. It doesn't make you weak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-25 10:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's does smh stand for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 09:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 12:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! Thanks a lot. It's been killing me for three days now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Film where woman sells her soul at meets the buyer at a diner to ask for it back. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 09:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woman holds an art exhibition where she's displaying her pictures for sale. The pictures are based around 'the breakdown of a relationship' or something. The pictures show couples in bed. She's not selling any pictures and an art critic disses her work and leaves. 

As part of the exhibition, she sells her soul to the highest bidder. She then meets the dude that bought it in a cafe/diner because she wants it back. The guy says he has the contract for her soul in his underpants or something. 

Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 14:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally don't think girls should be called sluts at all. We shouldn't judge someone, male or female, based on their sexuality and the expression of it. It's totally natural to be very sexually active and people that are should not suffer prejudice. You wouldn't scold the lion that mated the most.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 13:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they mean they're sorry to hear that it happened. .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 13:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean by, "I went direct 99%"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 13:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get one in just four weeks if you click the adverts on the side of some website that I went on once.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 09:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah! So that's why it's wrapped in foil... I did wonder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 09:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 14:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone explain what I'm looking at here?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 14:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the... I didn't even know it could... Wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 16:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 22:22 is the same for me. I always look at the clock at that time, been happening for about two or three years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 14:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, and this sounds interesting. Might have to research.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 why Jeff Bezos bought The Washington Post and how he paid the $250,000. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 11:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's his motivation for buying a newspaper? How does a transaction like that take place? How, if at all, would he pay with assets?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 10:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, and I'm currently reading, 'The Power of Now' by Eckhart Tolle. It's about detaching from your thoughts and living in the moment. There is no past to dwell on, it's in your head. There is no future to worry about, it's in your head. Everything that has ever happened to your or will every happen to you happened Now. Check it out!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 10:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, and your comment should've had 'yes and' at the beginning! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-05 18:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sure know how to make a woman sweaty down below.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 11:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maximum word-points for using 'flabbergasting'  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-29 20:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bad kisser. Ain't no-one got time for that shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-29 06:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It stands for 'too long; didn't read.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 12:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find that dubs are often worse than the original </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 12:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I once drove passed my house all the way to the next town without even realising. Something all of a sudden clicked and I thought, "where the hell am I?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 11:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, foaming at the mouth with laughter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 15:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did anyone actually read the Whole article? It was a load of old arse, and the guy was trying to sell me catholic newsletters or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> u/Crusader1089 tells us why they will always stand up against racism. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 12:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 13:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shark in Findjng Nemo was called Bruce. Jaws copied.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 10:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, not convinced. It was definitely aliens or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mug/Glass Switcheroo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-04 11:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to play some music from my iPhone while hanging with friends, and I often put the phone in a glass or mug to magnify the sound. 

On my bedside table was a mug and a glass. As I was deciding which one to use as my DIY speaker, I said to myself specifically, 'the glass will be better to use.' Picked it up. 

Turned around and checked if my laundry was dry. When I looked down, I was holding the mug. 

Shouted, "No. Fucking. Way". The glass was still on my bedside table.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 09:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How'd I know it'd be a heart attack... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 09:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both of these statements are beautiful and should be injected into every newborn's brain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 14:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ritz Crackers: Want to know how weak your willpower is? Thought so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 10:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was always under the impression that this derived from panning for gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
