<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8959</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 06:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bullet 10, page 8 of the Senate report clearly states the CIA manipulates the media to, in turn, manipulate public opinion. Evidence that this exact type of article cannot be trusted without supporting evidence. Evidence anonymous polls are unable to provide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Sony Gets Its Way With the New York Times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 01:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 15:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laughed hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> D.C. maneuvering for marijuana showdown with Congress </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 15:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Koch: Im basically a libertarian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 04:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mysterious glitch trade foretold Apples fall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 11:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 10:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost 2015
Trying this hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If we were given a map detailing the location of a star by it's position relative to nearby pulsars (similar to how Carl Sagan charted our Suns location in the Pioneer), how could we locate the star being referenced? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 22:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading about the Pioneer plaque, and Sagans contribution to it. Then I started thinking to myself "How would we translate that same type of  message if we saw it?" Do we know the location of other stars relative to pulsars? 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A mystery woman paid off everyones layaway accounts at a Toys R Us </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 22:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 19:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can only speak for myself when I say I personally follow this because I'm stunned there's anyone left in the political process willing to call out the banks. It's encouraging to know not everyone has given up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 19:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "So let me say this to anyone who is listening at Citi  I agree with you. Dodd-Frank isnt perfect. It should have broken you into pieces.

Amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elizabeth Warren Delivers Fiery Speech Condemning Citibank Written Bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 19:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 19:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would strive to be worthy of returning as Glenn Howerton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reincarnation based on karma is suddenly proven real and inexplicably includes inanimate objects. Who or what are you going to be next time around? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 18:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 18:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If corporations are people, and Sony is paying hackers to DDOS sites on the web, the DoJ and the FBI need to start opening cases against Sony immediately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress fails to revise government records law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 15:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ever since the new financial regulations went into place, Ms. Warren said, Wall Street has been working behind the scenes to open another loophole" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 04:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 06:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are advocating terrorism. How you sleep at night is beyond me... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House passes bill that rolls back Dodd-Frank bank regulations and removes campaign finance rules. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 06:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 03:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Making this issue out to be a Bush vs Obama issue is disgusting and beneath this nations reputation. 

Obama wrote an executive order banning these techniques, an order Bush COULD have signed in the form of a bill passed by the House and the Senate but he chose instead to VETO a bill requiring CIA to conform to the Army Field Manual when utilizing interrogation strategies. 

Obama has allowed drone strikes, NSA wiretapping and many other atrocities, but don't try to tie CIA torture around his neck. This one is owned by the Bush administration generally and GWB/Dick Cheney specifically. It is a stain on our country the likes of which has not been seen since slavery and any attempt to justify it or distract from the topic is indefensibly atrocious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As Brennan gave a news conference Thursday to address the agencys "enhanced interrogation techniques" detailed this week in Feinsteins devastating Senate Intelligence Committee report, the senators staff unleashed a torrent of tweets to rebut him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 01:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Torture report shows Bush's vile legacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 04:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone on Reddit arrested someone or been arrested by someone via citizens arrest? How'd it work out for you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 04:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American lives will be saved, not lost, if we release the Senate torture report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 05:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the "Know how I know you're gay?" exchange between Paul Rudd and Seth Rogen in the film 'Knocked Up' was completely unscripted, and in the unedited film, runs over 6 minutes long. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 18:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 21:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope each box comes with only a fortune cookie. Inside the cookie, a random quote from Ted Cruz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cards Against Humanity Sold 30,000 Boxes Of Poo To Screw With People On Black Friday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 21:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 23:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 19:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite the opposite. You may have made it better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 19:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cannot unsee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My son seeing snow for the first time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 18:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mystery government spying with Regin: One of the most sophisticated pieces of malicious software ever seen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 13:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 21:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picture? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 19:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I collect things people think others shouldn't own. It's a weird hobby sometimes. My unopened series one bin laden versus USA handheld video game is probably near the top of the list. No idea of value, but just for sheer "WTF", it's my prized one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Collectors of Reddit, what do you collect and how long have you been collecting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 19:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, how much do you have/want? What is your prized possession in your collection? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 08:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is astoundingly selfless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 07:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The TLC channel to go bankrupt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You get one wish and it can't benefit you or your immediate family directly. What is it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 07:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salespeople of Reddit, what is the sleaziest tactic you or someone you worked with used to close a sale? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 01:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 03:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They definitely frighten me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 02:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking a Fleshlight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What single item would shock people the most if you sent it 50 years back in time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 02:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which gender requires higher maintenance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 21:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Band Interpol Has Been Stuck on a Tour Bus for Almost Two Days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 19:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could cross any two living things together and keep the creation as a pet, what life forms would you choose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 17:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If only more women believed this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 00:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 17:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Emma Watson has extraextramarital affair with Emma Stone" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 17:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Now That's What I Call Not Music" Volume 1? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 17:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "George W. Bush states videotaped encounters with gay escort were a  'misunderstanding' "  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 17:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I have a meeting in the morning so I can't be out too late." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 17:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Warren and agree wholeheartedly on this topic. However, she should divorce herself of Manchin immediately, he could not be a worse partner. The guy is worthless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five-year-old passes Microsoft exam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 15:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever made a decision you immediately regretted? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 14:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is a violent response ever justified? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 03:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP Used Twitter to Flout Election Laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 21:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Is This Bush Official Flip-Flopping on Obamacare? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 18:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a band named 'Blue Cheer' pioneered a punk sound in 1968 with their debut album 'Vincebus Eruptum'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 06:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 17:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calling in sick to my job in NYC, then watching the events unfold that morning on September 11th, 2001. Really messed me up. Office was next to WTC 7, and I never went back. Quit that day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "It must be questioned whether David Cameron's mocking tone on Friday night was the best way to advance the interests of the Ukrainian people." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 02:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 20:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compare George Zimmerman to Ted Bundy and he looks like a boy scout. It's not the volume. It's the act itself IMO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 20:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes one of us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Comcast throttles 12 percent of the file sharing bandwidth on their networks and Verizon "only" throttles approximately 9 percent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 17:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 16:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm interested to see your source for that definition, because I can't find anything stating a stereotype must be based on observance. In fact, the stereotypes of southern Americans being inbred would be virtually impossible to observe unless you are incredibly perverse and have a lot of time on your hands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 16:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would a poor black person afford KFC? That is an expensive place to eat. And don't get me started on Popeyes raising their menu prices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 16:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, because no stereotype ever sprung to life out of ignorance and fear... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 16:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> West Virginia. All of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What stereotypes contain even a hint of truth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 15:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 22:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until you collectively start punishing the ISP's that are paying these douche bags, you're not helping anything. You need to hit Comcast and Verizon where it counts. THE WALLET.

"I don't have any other options" you say?

Then you're contributing to the problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 04:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is Russia dependent on the US dollar? Not sure how that works. Their banking? Industry?  Sorry, genuinely curious about that.

And the shift from our currency isn't just these two, it appears to now involve Qatar, even Canada.(http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2014-11-10/petrodollar-panic-china-signs-currency-swap-deal-qatar-canada).




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:What is the potential impact of the Russia/China currency swap to the United States economy, if any? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 01:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you knew for a fact that mankind was going to wipe out life on Earth completely by nuclear war in 200 years, would you agree to a virus that wipes out 90 percent of mankind today, including you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 16:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Evil Dead' show starring Bruce Campbell is coming to Starz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 23:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jared Leto in Talks to Play The Joker Role in 'Suicide Squad' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 00:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Returns Fire in Saudi Arabia's Oil War </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 15:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skunk Works Reveals Compact Fusion Reactor Details </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 23:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Noam Chomsky calls US 'world's leading terrorist state' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 15:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 20:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> War on Soda </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 17:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice to see something funny posted to r/funny every now and then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 16:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could wear that quote on a shirt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 17:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking Pasteur, but whatever fits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 17:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Comcast welcomes the FCC ruling." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 17:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since you invited it, I'm afraid you're a defeatist. Fortunately, as history has shown, it only takes one person to create the change millions say is impossible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "No matter how you dress it up, any rules that dont clearly restore the agencys authority and prevent specialized fast lanes and paid prioritization arent real Net Neutrality. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 16:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drivers Scramble for Cash on I-270 After Crash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 15:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daniel Radcliffe slays Blackalicious Alphabet Aerobics on the The Tonight Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 15:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do characters in films and television shows always seem to find car keys in the visor of the vehicle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 17:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From Terminator II to Edge of Tomorrow and tons of examples in between, I have always seen characters discover keys to a vehicle by opening the sun visor. Does anyone actually keep keys there? Where did this start? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fishers police say don't fear mysterious clown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 19:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 01:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's in the sky. It's an object. I can't identify it. It's a UFO to me until you reverse any of those points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hovering 'UFO' found in 16th Century painting in monastery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 21:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 02:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best script for a montage ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 02:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my least favorite words in the English language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 02:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We tend to make it theatrical. Each argument has some ridiculous genesis, so the endings typically have to be creative and have a bit of flair. If it keeps up, by the time we're 50 we're going to be hiring full time script-writers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When arguing with your significant other, how does the fight typically end? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 02:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is one book you think everyone on the planet should read? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 22:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 20:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, completely different than the US? ;)

Similar for me. I think the concept of electoral college needs to go, centralized banking needs to go and I think we should elect Presidents for one 8 year term without ability to run again and Congress for one 4 year term without ability to run again so they get in office, focus on the work and then get out without having a few years of campaigning overlapping with "work".

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 19:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LONG answer, sorry in advance but - 

Similar situation with me, as you saw in prior discussion. My heart still feels "abnormal" and it's been 10 months. A heaviness or squeeze...I can't explain it  but I feel like I am cognizant of every heartbeat and this is new to me since my heart attack/myocarditis dx.

I had the flu last December, then a week or two after recovering, I was drinking with my wife at an event and felt sudden pain in my heart. Significant. I was half drunk  so I actually joked about it with her. "Wow if my arm starts to hurt I'm in tr- OW FUCK". I took way more aspirin than I should have and went to the ER, they doubted me until they saw lab results blah blah blah.

Long story short, staying at Johns Hopkins, the cardiologist told me myocarditis is difficult to positively diagnose and even more difficult to treat since many times the root cause of the issue is unknown. While still in the hospital, I receive a call from the wife of a friend of mine who I had not seen in several years. Come to find out he had a heart attack post myocarditis diagnosis and was in intensive care.35 years old. I'm 34. 

His wife asked me for advice about what to tell the doctors, what to have them look for since I seemed like I was about to be discharged and he was in a hospital in another state. 

The next day, he died.

Fast forward to now, and sometimes I think I'm losing my mind. I still feel each heart beat, I'm fucking terrified of getting the flu again and it feels like the medical community as a whole knows fuck all about myocarditis or what to do to prevent it. Every single doctor I've dealt with has a different opinion.

I love Johns Hopkins and I do feel it's an amazing medical center, but even their internal staff have differing opinions on what it is and how it should be dealt with. Some told me it will resolve and I'll be fine. Others told me it can be chronic and I have to weigh myself daily to watch for fluid retention or congestive heart failure symptoms. Some told me it was "just one of those things" and I'm fine. Others told me it could significantly impair me for the rest of my life.

One doctor (Hopkins is a learning hospital so you get a million docs) told me this summary "Myocarditis is so incredibly rare, it's essentially winning the worst lottery you can think of. And I have a better chance of guessing tonights winning numbers than telling you if you will go through this again."

What I have learned of myocarditis is : It seems to strike a disproportionate amount of healthy young men between 18-35 (obviously it affects more than just healthy young guys), it's possible to survive it with minimal scarring or damage if you take aspirin or blood thinners the moment you feel a true onset (at least that's how it went for me. Heart MRI showed "virtually no scarring"), it causes anxiety, depression, insomnia etc, it feels as if it changes the way my heart feels in my chest, there are many cases of chronic myocarditis and there's no definitive way anyone has explained to me to be declared "cleared" of it or to be certain it won't happen again. 

Sorry for the lengthy rambling, I am at work on break and this is something I'm incredibly passionate about. I wish you the best in health, you are so much younger than me and I felt like a kid on the telemetry wing, I can;t imagine how this is impacting you. Feel free to message me if you ever need to vent, I'm as sympathetic as anyone. Take care.

tl:dr - myocarditis is largely a mystery in healthcare and it messes with your head
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suppose you have been tasked with creating the perfect government. How would it function? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 19:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heart attack survivors of Reddit, how do you get over the constant concern that another one is around the corner? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 19:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I found this when exploring text files in Android OS and would love to know what it is </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 01:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 06:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humanoid figures that communicate in Gilbert Gottfrieds voice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 05:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious how they managed to keep this buried until now. Then they only admitted it in regulatory filings. They didn't even come out and admit this happened until they absolutely had to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JP Morgan finally reveals the full extent of this summers security breach - 76 million accounts compromised in one of the largest corporate hacks ever discovered. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 23:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 16:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hearing scheduled to start at 09:00 Mountain Time in Colorado. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Link to live stream of Coats vs Dish Networks, a case in CO Supreme Court that may determine if employers can use positive marijuana tests to fire when it is prescribed to a patient. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 16:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook Ads Will Now Follow You No Matter What Device You're Using </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 22:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Portugal. The Man - [Alternative/Rock] Opening of a surprise midnight set the band performed atop Dr. Johns float at Bonnaroo 2011 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 16:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 00:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL SJW's post more exaggerated stories on Reddit than any other website I visit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL actor Danny Trejo is 70 years old. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 04:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 16:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> chemistry.about.com/cs/howthingswork/a/aa011604a.html

"Why the flu vaccine doesn't work"

This is coincidental correlation in OP article. Please stop posting this garbage, it makes those of us who are pro vaccine look like assholes. The flu vaccine is one the least beneficial health tactics ever, and yes I'm counting thalidomide when I say this.

It invokes a false sense of trust that makes people like OP and the thousands who upvoted this article feel "safer" when they receive it, when the science says otherwise. Denying the science behind the ineffectiveness of flu vaccinations is like denying the science behind climate change - you are intentionally skewing data to see things the way you want to see them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in 2010, Rep. Eric Cantor held a private meeting with Israeli President Benjamin Netanyahu and pledged the House would take Israels side against Obama on any issues that may offend Israeli interests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 16:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 21:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, I don't speak stupid. Is there someone that can translate this? Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 22:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason, there doesn't seem to be any books to add. I looked everywhere, but you cannot add books to your Juggalo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Build Your Own Juggalo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 22:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 18:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Horrible moderation (ie Bathia). Horrible layout. Inconsistent policy enforcement. Overall it just fell apart. The failure to keep up with the times led to it becoming a joke. And I was a first/second year Farker, I used that site for nearly 8 years before abandoning it because of the above mentioned things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 19:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously it doesn't remove water from existence lol as I stated, this is based on an assumption the water would be reintroducted into the same running units as it evaporates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Science redditors, is it theoretically possible for widespread use of air conditioners to impact evaporation levels so significantly it could decrease rain levels? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 18:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Air conditioning dehumidifies and draws moisture from the air. Could millions of air conditioners in a condensed area impact rain cycles in any way? Making the assumption that the water that precipitates and falls from any of the units then evaporates and enters a unit again.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mr. Bungle - Working for the Weekend [Alternative/Rock] Live cover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 17:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feds creating database to track hate speech on Twitter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 17:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
