<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3431</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OT] Wrote this piece when I was ten years old, how is it (haven't edited it at all)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 10:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aqofm231EO34o(C34^2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 09:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 08:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bottled water. 

I mean, everyone was like who the heck would want to buy water at the price of softdrinks? Look at them now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditers who broke up with their SO, why did you do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 08:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 02:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's sad to hear :( how can I widen my skillset then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 02:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the input, could you provide more details please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 02:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an Australian degree for the bachelors in engineering and masters in engineering. Right now I could switch over to either civil, structural or environmental but i'm not too sure about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 02:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was actually called Geomatics Engineering but my university renamed it for some reason. It is accredited by Engineers Australia, EUR-ACE and RICS and material we cover include:

Using SQL to program (also learnt C, C++, Java and Python), SDI, GIS, GNSS, Geodesy, Standard math (calc+lin. algebra), land administration, ER Modelling, relational algebra, remote sensing.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes on first dates I like to just stare into the other person's eyes, hold their hand and tell them: 


"Did you know Ho Chi Minh used to work as a baker in London"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take out the white cream in Oreos and fill them with white toothpaste and leave them on the counter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can for a while then your body gives in. Try refraining from thirst and hunger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Freewill doesn't exist, we are controlled by our bodies. We eat because we are hungry. We play videogames because our minds demand it. We procrastinate because we are bored. We have sex because our bodies desire it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like.... *drumroll* ... BONERMAN! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a freshman majoring in BEng/MEng in Geomatic/Spatial Engineering and have no idea on what to do after graduation. Any advice on what job sectors I could enter and what to do while still in college? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to give an overview of what courses we have to take:

Using SQL to program (also learnt C, C++, Java and Python), SDI, GIS, GNSS, Geodesy, Standard math (calc+lin. algebra), land administration, ER Modelling, relational algebra, remote sensing and some geology courses like applications of geophysics, tectonics   geodynamics, field mapping and sedimentary geology.



Are GIS careers really my only option? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Reddit, if I structure a mini, no-interval recital with this repertoire, will it be okay? (Suggestions are welcome) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 15:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, just planning for a not-to-serious performance for my residential college and picked some pieces out that are somewhat entertaining both for classical and non-classical audiences which are as follows:


1) Palmgren - Snowflakes (Fitting, it's almost winter right now!)

2) Bartok - Allegro Babaro 

3) Schubert Sonata no.14 - Movement I or III

4) Liszt Legende no.2

5) Prokofiev - Suggestion Diabolique

6) Aaron Copland - Cat and Mouse


What do you guys think? Too many "short" pieces? I'm open to any suggestions and advice :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what was the first post on Reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 16:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If object X produces a sound at 50dB and object Y produces a sound at 50 dB, will having both sounds together produce a sound of 100 dB? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 14:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If object X produces a sound at 50dB and object Y produces a sound at 50 dB, will having both sounds together produce a sound of 100 dB. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 13:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some of the toughest truth questions you can ask? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 12:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Reddit, what were some of the limitations of the invisible hand? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 10:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Historically, was the Invisible Hand useful as an idea? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 08:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, compared to other bio-sciences majors, are pharmacology majors seeing a grim job outlook as well? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 17:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the title Champion Slayer hard to get? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 10:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 06:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP UPDATE PLEASE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 06:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better safe than sorry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
