<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1541</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 03:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Join the 944 master race, 3 years or 20,000 miles
Edit: forgot to mention balance shaft belt, rollers, and water pumps as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 18:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had no idea this existed... Your friend is very lucky  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 17:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was this at Stafford? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 15:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 15:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First gen Honda NSX, Porsche 964 Turbo 3.8 or 993 GT2, and a Dauer 962 which is the street legal homolgation Porsche 962 Le Mans car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 15:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm level 32, the only car I got was a beetle, and I've never gotten a payout above 18,000 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 01:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember reading somewhere, the 25 year rule had to do with Mercedes. If I'm not mistaken, it had to do with buying car cheaper overseas and importing them, rather than buying directly from show rooms. And yeah, emissions and safety are a massive thing too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 01:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably not, the AE111 had a high revving naturally aspirated 4 banger with ITBs and a 6 speed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 01:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every single time I see a petition for it, I back it up and it always gets shot down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 01:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 20:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look! Another car we can't get in the USA but we all want! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 02:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mines a 1986, and what I like about it most over the other ones, is that it has the newer interior. But if I'm not mistaken, 87 was the first year when air bags and anti lock brakes were introduced, so if your going for a more mechanical feel, I'd say go 86 or older. As for cost, I can't say for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 20:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to go out on a limb and say the 2.0 VTEC. I have it swapped into my AE86, with a maxed out naturally aspirated build and it just revs and makes the coolest induction noise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 17:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll enjoy it, I'm really glad for you it worked out in the end. Post some pics when you get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 00:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.etsy.com/listing/186489964/my-bad-autocross-road-cone-decal-choose?utm_source=google utm_medium=product_listing_promoted utm_campaign=geekery-humor-low-other ione_adtype=pla ione_creative=56602783835 ione_product_id=186489964 ione_product_partition_id=91551949235 ione_store_code= ione_device=m ione_product_channel=online ione_merchant_id=14469981 ione_product_country=US ione_product_language=en gclid=Cj0KEQiAhvujBRDUpomG5cq_mI0BEiQA7TYq-vHw4KZigZzKNJEPRbbnbpRGgmRkKM0IETKX4q0WVqUaAtVA8P8HAQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 02:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 02:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just turned 18, and I can say that trying to find decent rates has been pretty hard just because of age. My dad has Hagerty insurance on his cars, so I threw my 944 on there and I only pay $100 a year. The o my problem is, I'm not allowed to drive it without my dad in the car until I turn 21. What really puzzles me is Hagerty actually has something on their website about younger drivers and getting them involved in the car scene, yet they don't want to insure us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 21:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 964 is easily one of my favorite generations, congrats on the purchase!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 01:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want a 4AG in my 944 with ITBs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 01:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's with all the not silver 918s on here lately? Not in a bad way though, the Orange one that was posted here a couple days ago was fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was sick of looking for wallpapers, so I made my own in Forza </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 01:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 18:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it is the CTR, CTR 2 is the 993 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 13:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd be correct, black headlight buckets and HRE 935s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm in love with the CTR2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 02:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 21:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude your girlfriend has an FRS and 993! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 03:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who'd you normally do the track days through? NASA does HPDE for around $50 each if you have a membership. You also get instructor time as well.
Edit: I read it wrong. It's $45 membership and the actual varies from track to track. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 23:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's doing well. Its my autocross car, and starting next year dedicated track car. I'm in the process of stripping it down to bare minimum now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 21:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dig the blue accents, it suits the car very well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 18:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't the lotus esprit use them as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 15:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's nice to see a 918 that's not silver for once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 14:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do it, I bought mine last year right after I turned 17. Out of all the very few cars I've driven, the 944 is the best. I was told it would be a money pit, and since I ordered pretty much all the parts from Rock Auto I saved a bunch of money. The best part is you get the satisfaction of telling people that you fixed a Porsche yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 02:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to guess, timing belt snapped, or you need to replace it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
