<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5469</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 04:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think if you had actually read about it before you got it. Poor guppies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 04:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again: Plecs don't eat free floating algae and they grow 2 ft long. No don't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 04:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No don't. Plecostomus don't eat free floating algae and they get twice as long as that tank.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 04:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep me too. Doubt we will though, if it is nuclear burns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sudan Suffers Major Electricity Outage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 02:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NUCLEAR WEAPONS (Los Alamos) LAB WORKER SERIOUSLY BURNED IN ACCIDENT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 02:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heavy rains flood streets, close roads across the South Plains </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 02:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The number of volcanic earthquakes recorded in Hakone, Kanagawa Prefecture, surged Tuesday, with 85 quakes recorded before 8 a.m. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 02:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Severe weather warning for Tasmania </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 02:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 06:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It almost seems as if the whole garrisons etc xpac was designed to kill the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 05:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I6eIet7QRpo

Ditto
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 07:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.. Stop and Frisk - without warrant - is **exactly** what we were warned of happening if one of those evil commie countries took over and communism spread. That and listening in on our phone calls, reading our mail, etc. These were the things the KGB did. 


Pheonix = 'supposedly'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 07:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck language is that?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 05:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being stopped for no reason is humiliating and destroys police-community relationship.

I remember being taught in school that we were fighting the Cold War because in 'those evil countries' the police could stop people on the street for no reason, spy on them, arrest them on the smallest pretense. We went to Vietnam supposedly to prevent the spread of that behavior around the world. My beloved Uncle died for this. Now to see it codified into law and todays law enforcement officers performing it is both enraging and deeply saddening. 

Stop- just stop. This is not fascist/soviet Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 08:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well we know now how long Baltimore could take it. Of course they are under worse pressures than most 'mid poverty white' areas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 08:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder if Whole Foods is going to be supplying snacks to the Texas National Guard   Military during Jade Helm? Support the Troops motherfucker!

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 05:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what do we call the police who have killed over 110 people - unarmed people?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 05:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They said the same thing during the cold war about the commies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 09:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They had an outbreak of this in the southern US last year. Very painful disease.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From drought to flood, but the drought still persists- Oklahoma </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 09:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least 39 people are now included in an outbreak of multidrug-resistant infections spread by contaminated medical scopes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 09:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nepal earthquake: Landslide buries trekking village, leaving 250 missing in latest tragedy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 09:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dozens feared dead in Afghanistan landslide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 09:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fire Threatens To Spread Chernobyl Radiation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 09:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 08:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a very strange event. I wonder if they are going to have another major quake soon. I would be nervous to be there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 08:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Promoted mind fuckery. Looks like most fell for it.  That line of 'civilians' are undercover police officers. It's a staged photo shoot. You should see other pics of these guys in 'feel good' photos over the next week designed to make all the white folks go aawww.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 07:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I was the only one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 03:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice try there Baltimore Police Keyboard Jockey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 03:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you have a link to that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Damaging Storm leaves 30K without power- Alabama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 08:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chikungunya outbreak reported in Kiribati </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 08:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Millions of dead jellyfish washed up on a beach  /r/WTF </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 08:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drone captures TONS of Fukushima Nuclear Waste being stored in plastic bags right beside the ocean- no barriers whatsoever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 22:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All 8 Pumps at Fukushima stopped for 11 hours, Strontium tainted water from the destroyed reactors ran into the Pacific </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 22:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extremely high levels of radiation discovered in a playground in Tokyo. Soil radiation readings of up to 480 microsieverts per hour! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 22:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazing shelf cloud north of Kearney, Neb. (Ryan McGinnis/Getty Images) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 19:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> India Severe Storms Kill 42, Injure More Than 100 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 19:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The drought is behind California's skyrocketing West Nile Virus numbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 18:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Update: Calbuco Volcano - 2 Major Eruptions, expecting a 3rd. Ice and snow melt may cause flooding. Thousands more evacuating. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 16:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man Survives 2nd Bear Attack in 4 Years; bit more than 40 times. May be same bear. Why bear no like you, Bob? : StormComing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 04:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man Survives 2nd Bear Attack in 4 Years; Bit more than 40 times. WA. Why bears no like you, Bob? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 04:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Residents ordered to evacuate as collapsing ravine threatens homes in NJ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 04:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rabid raccoon found in Poquoson (VA). 2 Dogs who killed it possibly infected as well. Local Alert on this. : StormComing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 04:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rabid raccoon found in Poquoson (VA). 2 Dogs who killed it possibly infected as well. Local Alert on this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 04:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Strong storms hit Coastal Bend with flooding and high winds. Utility poles "knocked down like dominoes". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 04:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> USDA Designates Lincoln County in Nevada as a Primary Natural Disaster Area Due to Extreme Drought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 04:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tornado Strikes Brazil, Killing at Least Two People </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 23:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australia Storm Hammers Sydney, New South Wales; 3 Dead, Hundreds Evacuated as Flooding Washes Away Homes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 23:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One Racehorse named after a very famous wow trinket- minus one. And then there's ARRRRR! (xpost videos) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 05:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Multiple Tornado Warnings in GA - Rest of the south is under the Gun for Severe Storms-Tornados </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 16:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heavy Rain Floods Houston Homes, Power Outage Causes Massive Sewage Spill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 16:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nearly 150 dolphins beached on Japanese shore | Japanese worried event is Quake precursor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 17:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alexandria residents start clean up after homes flooded- VA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton County gets disaster declaration - IA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bear River landslide has closed River Road completely </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Landslide threatens to cut off Harmar Twp. neighborhood- PA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tornado Spotted In Western Oklahoma, More Storms Possible - </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spring Storm Brings Blinding Dust, Heavy Snow Out West </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waterlogged Storm Sets Denver Record   Its Not Over Yet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earthworms rain from sky over Norway: I saw thousands of earthworms on the surface of the snow, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wild fires in Siberia  /r/WTF </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 23:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Premis: Mars was once inhabited by an advanced species of humanlike beings who destroyed the atmosphere and then the planet. Some came here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 07:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some came here when it became obvious that Mars was toast. 

This would explain a few things, such as 

1. Who were the [Denisovians](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Denisovan)? 

2. Did Atlantis exist? Every ancient culture has an 'Atlantean' tale, myth or fable.

3. What is the origin of unique, advanced technologies that are discovered on occasion (such as the [Antikythera Mechanism](http://www.antikythera-mechanism.gr))?

4. What is the origin of similar ancient stories of massive wars that occurred on earth, many of which involved [air transit and nuclear type damage](http://www.theepochtimes.com/n3/23630-ancient-atomic-bombs/), such as the Indian Vedas. 

I have been considering this since the 1990's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Impression that People from other countries have of us because of Abusive Cops </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 02:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was watching [a video on youtube of police officers shooting a pregnant woman](https://youtu.be/UKJZanyNUhE) who had a knife. 
I am always interested in comments and saw this interchange between Russians, and translated it:

English: 

*Antonioni Bardzini 2 days ago*

   **Once again, afraid so killed a man/woman shoot to kill, this nation can be defeated in less than a month**

 
*Roman Brovko 1 day ago*

   Executing = fright?

 
*Antonioni Bardzini 1 day ago*

   + Roman Brovko they could safely shoot in the legs but they always shot in the chest, let the will of man will kill.


So it is how I see this 'new generation' of police officers in the U.S.. They can't manage themselves and have a strong streak of cowardice- and so they use the gun. Interesting that others, including these Russians, now see American males as cowards. 

Russian:

  2 days ago
          ,         
 Reply   2 
 
  1 day ago
   = ? 
 Reply  
 
  1 day ago
 +             ,     

Youtube Video: https://youtu.be/UKJZanyNUhE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> By Request, A Fairy Tale [1920x1080] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 00:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Day Has Come </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 19:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And a little more class [2560x1600] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Decided this place needed a little class </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 06:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pre-Video 'News' report of Walter Scott Killing: Lies and more Lies from the local newspaper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 18:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Pasting the entire thing here in case it gets deleted from the Post and Courier website. Check the extreme 'pro-officer', anti-victim slant on this 'news' story. It made me want to puke.

In case the page is deleted- top and center showed a large, glorious picture of the police officer, looking nearly regal.*


**Attorney: North Charleston police officer felt threatened before fatal shooting**
-----------------------------------------------
Andrew Knapp
Andrew Knapp Email Facebook @offlede
Apr 6 2015 1:09 pm Apr 7 4:37 pm
Slager


A North Charleston police officer felt threatened last weekend when the driver he had stopped for a broken brake light tried to overpower him and take his Taser.

Thats why Patrolman 1st Class Michael Thomas Slager, a former Coast Guardsman, fatally shot the man, the officers attorney said Monday.

Investigators collect evidence after a North Charleston police officer fatally shot a man Saturday morning.

Slager thinks he properly followed all procedures and policies before resorting to deadly force, lawyer David Aylor said in a statement.

   This is a very tragic event for all of the families, Aylor said. I believe once the community hears all the facts of this shooting, theyll have a better understanding of the circumstances surrounding this investigation.

Mondays developments filled in some of the blanks in what was South Carolinas 11th police shooting of the year. Authorities publicly identified Slager, an officer with the city since December 2009, and gave his reason for the traffic stop that led to the fatal confrontation. Police documents also revealed that Slager announced within seconds why he had fired.

Shots fired, and the subject is down, he said into his radio, according to an incident report. He took my Taser.

Walter Lamer Scott, 50, of Meadowlawn Drive in West Ashley died soon after the encounter near Craig Street and Remount Road.

He has been arrested about 10 times in his lifetime, mostly for failure to appear for court hearings and to pay child support.

The only indicator of violence in his past came with his first arrest in 1987 on an assault and battery charge.

Slager, 33, served honorably in the military before joining the North Charleston Police Department more than five years ago, Aylor said.

*He has never been disciplined during his time on the force, the attorney added.*

Slager was on a boarding team when he served in the Coast Guard in Port Canaveral, Fla., his personnel file showed. The 91 pages of documents were released Monday after The Post and Courier filed a S.C. Freedom of Information Act request.

He passed courses on how to use the Taser X26 when he was hired in North Charleston and performed well on shooting tests with his .45-caliber Glock 21. Supervisors indicated in performance reviews that he met expectations as an officer and kept a tidy patrol car.

Of the two complaints in his file, one dealt with a residents allegation of unnecessary use of force.

Slager went to the mans Delaware Avenue home in September 2013 to investigate a burglary. When the resident opened the door for Slager, the burglary victim yelled that he wasnt the suspect, the documents stated.

The man also insisted that he wasnt the perpetrator, but he later told internal investigators that Slager threatened to use a Taser against him if he didnt come outside. When the man followed the order and stepped outside, he said Slager Tased (him) for no reason and ... slammed him and dragged him.

But another officer there said Slager had been forced to use the device during a struggle. The investigators exonerated Slager of wrongdoing.

Slager will keep working during a State Law Enforcement Division investigation into whether Saturdays shooting was justified, but Pryor said he would be on administrative duty.

While the police released Slagers file, one lawmaker said the episode again points out the need for body-mounted cameras whose footage can stave off community speculation.

The city is expected to get 115 of the devices through $275,000 in state funding for that and other anti-crime initiatives.

Rep. Wendell Gilliard, D-Charleston, said it cant come soon enough. Gilliard has authored legislation to require police agencies to outfit their officers with cameras. As an alternative, he also offered a bill calling for a study of such programs. But he expressed frustration because the measures had not advanced.

People will say Im using this (shooting) as a springboard, he said. But Ive said these types of incidents will continue, and when they do, its going to be unfortunate that we are not using modern-day technology to stop the speculation and rumors.

The authorities have not said whether anyone else saw Slagers struggle with Scott.

No one called Charleston Countys 911 Center after the gunfire, and Slagers communications with dispatchers will not be made public until SLED approves it, county spokeswoman Natalie Hauff said.

SLED spokesman Thom Berry said prosecutors also would have to review the recordings and be agreeable and amenable to their release.
Quickly escalated

North Charleston community leaders have mentioned the police shooting of Michael Brown in Ferguson, Mo., in urging residents not to grow violent in light of Scotts death. But, like Missouri police said of Brown, Slager saw Scott as a threat when the officer decided to pull the trigger.

Around 9:30 a.m. Saturday, Slager noticed a Mercedes-Benz sedan with a brake light that was out and not working, the police spokesman said. He stopped his cruiser behind the sedan that had pulled into Advance Auto Parts at 1945 Remount Road.

What started out as a routine traffic stop quickly escalated after the driver fled, Slagers attorney said.

Scott ran down Craig Road, which parallels the stores parking lot and stretches southward toward the Singing Pines community. A passenger in his car stayed put.

Slager told other officers through his radio that he had gotten into a foot chase, according to the report. The police have not given details about the confrontation that followed behind the Mega Pawn shop at 5654 Rivers Ave.

But with other officers on the way to help, Slager announced on his radio that he had deployed his Taser, according to the report. But it didnt work.

The statement from Slagers attorney, though, did not say that Slager actually fired the device. Aylor said he could not offer further clarification until the officer talks with investigators.

When confronted, Officer Slager reached for his Taser  as trained by the department  and then a struggle ensued, Aylor said. The driver tried to overpower Officer Slager in an effort to take his Taser.
Felt threatened

Seconds later, the report added, he radioed that the suspect wrested control of the device. Even with the Tasers prongs deployed, the device can still be used as a stun gun to temporarily incapacitate someone.

Slager felt threatened and reached for his department-issued firearm and fired his weapon, his attorney added.

The report indicated that Slager fired multiple times, but it was not specific.

Backup officers did first aid and CPR on Scott until paramedics showed up. But Scott was pronounced dead.

Loved ones have said that Scott was a family man who recently got engaged. They insisted that he wasnt violent.

His most serious arrests came decades ago, according to his SLED rap sheet.

County police officers arrested him in 1987 on a charge of assault and battery, and he was convicted in 1991 of possession of a bludgeon.

Ten years passed before he was arrested twice in 2001 on contempt charges. He would face several similar charges occasionally during the next decade until his last arrest in 2012.

He also had convictions from 2008 for driving under suspension and having an open alcohol container in his car.

Anthony Scott met with the police near the scene soon after his brother was shot. The report did not specify, though, whether he had been the passenger in the Mercedes.

The police took his cellphone as evidence. The next day, he promised in a public statement to find out the truth about what happened.

Dave Munday contributed to this report. Reach Andrew Knapp at 937-5414 or twitter.com/offlede.


The Post and Courier, an Evening Post Industries company.


http://www.postandcourier.com/article/20150406/PC16/150409558/1177/north-charleston-police-say-officer-who-fatally-shot-man-pulled-him-over-because-of-brake-light </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tornado Warning outside Fayetteville- live on air - debris ball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 02:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tornado/Storm updates for Friday April 3. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 21:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be posting warnings / reports through the day here as long as I can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Following Brett Adairs Storm chase team today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 21:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tornado shelters across the TN Valley - List: WAFF-TV: News, Weather and Sports for Huntsville, AL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 20:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kentucky you are under the Gun- Severe weather and HIGH Tornado outbreak possible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 20:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arkansas you are under the gun- Tornado Watch with HIGH possibility of outbreak ongoing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 20:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tornado Watches - T-Storm Warnings for Southern Ill...Western-Central KY...Western-Southern Indiana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 20:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Severe Storms Ignite in Central US on Thursday- storms to tornados - will continue Friday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 02:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fire blazes on oil platform in Gulf of Mexico, 1 dead, multiple injures reported </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 18:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Californias record-setting small snowpack looks as bad as it sounds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 18:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FLOOD KILLS DOZENS NEAR LAKE TANGANYIKA, BURUNDI </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 18:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New report from Physicians for Social Responsibility: War on Terror killed 1.3 million people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 17:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New report from Physicians for Social Responsibility: War on Terror killed 1.3 million people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 17:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Major 7.7 quake strikes off Papua New Guinea, tsunami warning issued </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 04:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thunderstorms brought equivalent of 7 years of rain to Chile's Atacama desert region and caused deadly flooding Thursday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 21:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sea lions inundate Oregon Coast as they flee starvation in California </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 19:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have seen two posts today with requests to make a voice recording. Seems strange and uncool to me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 06:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A large number of companies capture voice prints of anybody that calls them and have been doing so for a number of years. None of them disclose that they are capturing your voice print even though they allegedly are doing so as a form of two-factor authentication. Then they can associate that voice print with accounts, purchases, etc.


When combined with voice prints from other companies it becomes easier for something like the NSA to be able to identify an individual by voice print - they don't have to have their name - regardless of whose phone they may be using. Plus that allows them to associate that individual to the person whose phone they used. That would include identifying people speaking on conference room phones where many individuals can be speaking over the same line on the same call from the same phone.


If recording devices are built to produce voice recordings using the same telephone voice structure the intelligence agencies could then potentially identify all of the people speaking in a room for example without there being a phone at all if a listening device were there or nearby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wild Child - Druid pvp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 23:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 30,000 Liter Oil spill in southwestern Manitoba </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 14:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another Fireball lights up Skies over Nova Scotia *Two in one week! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 14:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One person killed, several injured as tornadoes hit Oklahoma, Arkansas - Reuters | Aggregator Page </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 14:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emergency Declared After Heavy Rains Hit Atacama Desert Region-Normally the Driest Region on Earth. Chie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 14:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bees kill three dogs; sting several people in separate attacks - Santa Ana, CA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 14:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hobart storm causes flash flooding- AU </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 14:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Storm Spotting Secrets- How to spot a developing Tornado- on the ground and on radar. Great Video by a Pro Chaser I respect and admire. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 03:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tulsa, Oklahoma Braces for 'Life-Threatening' Tornado </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 01:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Severe Thunderstorms Underway in Plains, Ozarks; More Intense Storms Expected Later Today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 20:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bus Swallowed by Sinkhole, Floats Away in Brazil Crater: Video (very omg video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 20:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan audit: Millions of dollars wasted in Fukushima cleanup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 07:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video: Florida emergency manager's verbal gymnastics to avoid saying 'climate change' are hilarious: xpost: environment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 18:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the crocodiles of Ramree Island devoured hundreds of fleeing Japanese soldiers - The Ramree Massacre, WW2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 17:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dead crows put Sultanpur on avian flu alert </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 07:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chickens destroyed after bird flu found at Dutch farm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 07:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gov. Kate Brown to declare drought emergency in Lake, Malheur counties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 07:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five mountain climbers killed in China forest fire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 07:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snow to follow flooding caused by solar eclipse 'supertide' - UK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 06:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Only Place It Was Cold This Winter Was The East Coast Of The United States- Extreme heat in the West. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 15:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Outgoing winter proves warmest in Russia in history of weather monitoring </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 15:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just have to say something- and I hope the mods add this suggestion to their sub. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 08:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see more and more posters to this sub taking screenshots in dark, poorly lit places or worse, under colored lighting. No one can see the colors of the Op's x-mogs, rendering the post basically worthless.  

Leaves me wondering if the x-mogs in these dark, blurry, poorly lit screenshots look horrible or great. 

Now, get your toon to a nice, naturally lit area, (Dal, Elwynn, Jade Forest, Barrens, to name a few) zoom in so your toon is not 1/8th of an inch high in the pic and turn up your graphics. Click and post.

Thank you!!

p.s. - an example of a great shot: http://i.imgur.com/VeCuM6Q.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Midwifery in the Province of Kalinga (and you can sponsor a birth on the site) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 01:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Severe geomagnetic storm spurs beautiful aurora, could continue Tuesday evening (Photos) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 18:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blizzard hits Newfoundland- Canada - Roads Closed, St. Pats day activities cancelled. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 15:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Civil defence emergency in Chathams - NZ Impacted by remnants of Cyclone Pam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 15:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President: Cyclone devastation forcing Vanuatu to start anew. Cyclone Pam update. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 15:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dash cam footage: Massive Fireball meteor spotted in skies over Switzerland, Austria, UK, Germany, France </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 15:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chile contains huge blaze threatening Valparaiso- Thousands Evacuated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 06:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starving   sick: Sea lion pups wash ashore in record numbers, global warming blamed. Its very difficult to see so much death </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 05:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On 3/13/15 at 9am, The Eye of Cyclone Pam Fit Perfectly Over the Island of Port Vila-  /r/StormComing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 13:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On 3/13/15 at 9am, The Eye of Cyclone Pam Fit Perfectly Over the Island of Port Vila-  /r/StormComing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 13:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On 3/13/15 at 9am, The Eye of Cyclone Pam Fit Perfectly Over the Island of Port Vila- amazing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 13:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "We've seen villages that have just literally been blown away." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 04:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monstrous Category 5 cyclone makes direct hit on tiny Vanuatu | Possibly the strongest cyclone in pacific history Mashable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 04:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowstorm closes major highway into Mexico City for 8 hours </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 05:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huge Grass Fires Across the Area Burn Up Farmland- Nebraska </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 05:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Sexiest Wind Turbine I have ever seen [600x600] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 20:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Sexiest Wind Turbine I have ever seen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 18:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Record-Breaking Heat Wave This Weekend In SoCal : CaliforniaDisasters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 04:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Growing concern over increase in sea lion deaths along Southern California coastline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 01:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UPDATE: Victim identified in deadly Greenbrier Co. mudslide- WV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 01:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slow-moving landslide near Seattle destroys home, more at risk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 01:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Columbia Parkway landslide created by 1938 engineering error </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 01:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Italian village gets Record EIGHT FEET of snow in just 24 hours </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 01:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Estimated $1 Billion in Lost Wages and Profits After Winter Storm Barrage in Massachusetts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 01:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heavy Rain and Warm Weather Trigger Flooding- Video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 23:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iditarod dogsled race moved north-2nd year in a row no snow -Alaska </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 16:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Rain Bomb: How a microburst fell from the sky in Australia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 18:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dozens of new craters discovered in northern Russia-de-gassing and explosive dangers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 17:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drought-stricken Sao Paulo: Downpours have wreaked havoc, causing widespread flooding. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 17:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Phosphine poisoning: 2nd child dies in Edmonton hospital - Edmonton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 17:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> H7N9 avian influenza cases reported from Guangdong and Anhui provinces </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 17:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 15 injured as 5.8 magnitude earthquake hits Pakistan - Xinhua </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 17:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another 'Yellow Fever' Mosquito Found in Chula Vista, CA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 14:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rain, hailstorm wreak havoc, deaths in Pakistan, Fata </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 14:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bolivia Flood 2015: Flooding Forces Over 4,000 to Evacuate, Mayor to Decide to 'Rebuild a New Town' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 14:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Afghanistan hit by deadly avalanches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 17:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While Eastern US Freezes; California has warmest winter ever - </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 17:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> List of Record Lows Broken As Arctic Blast Grips Midwest, Northeast, South (FORECAST) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 18:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arctic Blast Brings Historic Cold Across US-27 states are under wind chill advisories or warnings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 18:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Winter Storms Octavia/Neptune: Emergencies Declared in Southern States; 1 Dead in Kansas Due to Icy Roads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 19:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In between Amtrak train cars during Boston's blizzard. Amazing video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 17:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia: Dozens sickened with hepatitis A linked to drinking water </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 17:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US - Highly pathogenic avian influenza has been detected in a backyard poultry flock of around 90 birds in Deschutes county, Oregon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 17:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 15 die of flu in Hong Kong in just one day-the most in a day since the epidemic began </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 17:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Black Plague Is Back, With a Disturbing Twist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 06:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boston: With potentially historic blizzard looming, Governor Deval Patrick urges people to stay off roads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 05:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least 20 killed, dozens injured as train, bus collide in Mexico </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 04:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wildfires to create second wave of radiation poisoning from Chernobyl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 04:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kosovo: Albanian authorities officially declared an epidemic of Tularemia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 04:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MERS Update: Filipino female nurse PHs 1st MERS case; DOH tracking contacts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 04:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bio-Hazard in San Fran: Tens of Thousands of San Francisco Commuters Possibly Exposed to Measles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 04:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Storms hit Melbourne, after Bureau of Meteorology issued severe weather warning for Victoria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 04:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3,500 litres of oil leak into River Usk in Wales | Environment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 04:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jakarta Floods Displace Thousands - Indonesia Real Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 04:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barcelona - Toxic Orange Cloud Hangs Over Northern Spain After Chemical Explosion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 04:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yellowstone Grizzlies Waking Up (A Month) Early Due To Mild Winter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 07:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 21 H7N9 human cases in east China's Zhejiang - Xinhua - Update on Chinas Bird Flu outbreak </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 17:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venice Carnival 2015: Revellers try to keep their costumes dry on flooded St Mark's Square </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 16:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indonesia: Torrential rain causes major flooding in Jakarta [Photos] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 16:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 16:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this. The eye looks so ancient and somehow wise. It looks like a combination of 3d elements with painted art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California turkey farm quarantined after bird flu detected </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 20:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian Infected With Deadly Strain of Bird Flu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 20:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alert as girl dies of chickenpox | Bahrain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 20:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bee swarm attacks man, stings him 150+ times - Florida </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 20:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wunderground Meteorologist: Live Blog: Constant Updates on Historic Northeast Blizzard- INC.  /r/StormComing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 00:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wunderground Meteorologist: Live Blog: Constant Updates on Historic Northeast Blizzard- INC. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 23:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disneyland measles outbreak puts California on alert </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 16:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Avian flu virus confirmed in Idaho: multi-agency investigation, highly pathogenic strain of avian influenza. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 16:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malawi floods cause devastation  Amazing pictures | </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 16:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Foot of Snow Closes Amarillo Schools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 16:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China reports additional H7N9 avian influenza cases in Shenzhen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 16:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Extreme heatwave' in WA's north brings sizzling temperatures- Australia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 16:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blue glow around Hong Kong is beautiful, but toxic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 16:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ammonia leak on U.S. section of International Space Station forces evacuation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 19:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tornado and lightning hit homes as Wales battered with Extreme Storm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 19:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 40 hospitalized in Orange County after eating cake spiked with powerful hallucinogen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 22:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UPDATE: 103 children in 34 states have developed a mysterious paralysis illness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 22:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2014 Review: The most spectacular weather photos of the year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 15:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wild duck with bird flu found in N. California </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 20:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bright light associated with meteorite crash recorded in Romania </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 20:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Record-breaking cold, 3 feet of snow closes U.S. schools, cancels flights "...no end in sight before the weekend." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 20:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gazans evacuate homes following massive storm that also hit Lebanon, Jordan, Syria, and Egypt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 20:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is the beach covered in dead birds? Mass Sea Bird die-off on California to Washington Coastline. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 20:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flooding hits Isle of Wight - UK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 20:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australian Wildfire Razes 26 Homes, 29 People Seek Treatment. "..has raged out of control for days" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 20:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 11 North Texas Earthquakes In Around 27 Hours  /r/Earthquakes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 20:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its Official: 2014 Was the Hottest Year Ever Measured on Earth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 16:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Naselle River floods, landslides and washouts that left parts of Pacific County partially isolated. Oregon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 16:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 taken to hospital after Gwinnett County 911 center hazmat call - Atlanta, GA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 16:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Concerns After 650,000+ Gallons Of Raw Sewage Flows Into Creek After Storm Cuts Power (a literal shit-storm?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 16:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least four houses destroyed by bushfire near Kersbrook in Adelaide Hills, CFS confirms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 16:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
