<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1032</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 01:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, my connection seem to just start dieing after I did that update as well. I was trying to connect to the PSN but I kept receiving an error. After a while I was able to and tried to download Outlast and that's not working Either. Lastly I decided to just watch Netflix but that's also not working for me. I know it's not my Wi-Fi because the phone and laptop connect just fine. 
I'm just gonna leave it off for a couple hours and hopefully I'll be able to play a bit of Outlast tonight. 
I'm in California, some people don't seem to have any trouble connecting online though. Not sure if it has to do with location. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 17:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks fucken siiiiiick and detailed as well! I just saw that episode too!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 16:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dios mo! You are gorgeous! 
How do you subscribe to a person's post!? Can't wait to see more of you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 06:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a fuckin beautiful shot. Just became my new wallpaper on my pc!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 15:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you did, loving that look you're giving. Good angle too ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 15:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohh very nice, excellent way to start the weekend. Would only be made better if your face was visible, with your glasses and all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 01:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very nice! Thanks for posting this! I'm always looking for new artists to listen to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
