<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4999</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 20:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha!  that's why i put something between me and him and blasted him with fireballs.  Cheese I know but hey, survivalism ya know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 19:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go back to Quelaana in Blighttown by warping to Chaos servant bonfire and going back through Queelag's boss room.  Be careful though, not to draw enemies close to her and risk aggro-ing her.  She'll upgrade your +15 to ascended +5.  I used great fireball, black flame, and great chaos fireball on Gwyn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 19:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just beat him a couple days ago on NG.  +3 Ascended pyromancy flame, and kept one of the stalagmites in between me and him i.e. Smough fight.  Done in like 5 minutes, found it suprisingly easy for the final boss.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 05:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/1nwvu3/7_movies_that_will_leave_you_devastated/.   Keep seeing donnie darko and requiem as most disturbing blah blah movies and thought I'd suggest some good alternatives.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 04:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Company of men is pretty messed up!!  Baxter is pretty intense too good double feature! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 01:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I originally saw Frontier(s) on netflix streaming.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 01:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that just kept getting worse and worse as it went along....sad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TRULY devastating movies... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 01:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donnie Darko?  Please.  Here's some truly devastating movies...
[Bedeviled](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eBq0SLWNF-E)....[In the Company of Men](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FtpmAdgl8UI)...[Martyrs](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lNpDiQimK6U)...[Frontiers](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WnoGQfW51ng)...[Inside](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YVGswuX42x0)...[Baxter](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DqJtJL6bSRg)...[In a Glass Cage](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l09AIbYPWLQ)...[Schramm](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mgk-gBoa54o)....[Angst](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cfqN2wuH_Ck)
Also 'Fat girl' by Breillat and 'Michael' by Schlienzer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 00:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donnie Darko's the most over-rated crap movie ever.  You left off Martyrs, A Serbian Film, Bedeviled, In the Company of Men and Irreversible..... among others that are WAY better than Darko and Requiem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 22:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are legion for we are many..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 00:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About two hours ago I got summoned to help someone get to O S and there was an invader right at that spot.  I gave em the ol' Wrath of God right off that ledge....was that you per chance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 03:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mega mule right?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 19:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sooo, after being a dragon for two days, I put my dragon summon in Oolacile Township.  Get two summons in about twenty minutes.  Third summon is wearing full dragon gear.  I drop a prism, he/she drops 99 of all slabs.  DRAGONBROS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 01:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's f***ing game board. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-29 19:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Block ornstein on way in to fight then run to opposite side of room staying outside pillars.  Smough isnt fast and this will help seperate them.  Pyromancy flame is great for this fight.  Rats in the depths are good for humanity farming.  Also solaire did nothing for me, just gets himself killed right away.  However he does make a nice distraction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 18:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just joined too, same question.  I know the person youre trying to invade has to have a dragon scale.  Ive had moderate success in oolacile township by pvp bonfire, other than that not so much.  I would guess the main pvp areas?  White a red signs still work fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 18:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's rock...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 00:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your soul level? If you go past 120 you'll have a hard time being summoned in earlier levels even for S O.  Also what system? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 20:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mimic!  Oh wait it's just a chest, phew </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
