<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4000</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 10:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star Wars jedi power battles? http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Star_Wars_Episode_I:_Jedi_Power_Battles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 10:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> man,  if only she had been in Showgirls instead of Elizabeth Berkley. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 10:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a kid my family had vhs copies of the karate kid and Adventures in babysitting and I was in love with Elisabeth Shue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who was your first celebrity crush? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 10:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 09:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Titus. Best sitcom Fox ever had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 09:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss Atton Rand and Mira :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE feel that something epic is happening somewhere when it's raining heavy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 04:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 07:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> true that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 07:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> who doesn't hate it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 07:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too, I always sing it Time After Time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What popular followings have you not caught onto? past or present </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 07:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a movie, book, tv show, clothing trend, whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some things you've been meaning to finish but just can't? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 15:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE create movie-type trailers in their head when they hear music? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 15:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 14:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> stories, some sci-fi and fantasy. I'm not making money or anything, it's more of a hobby. I always wrote good stories and speeches in my English classes so that's where I started. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 14:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its premise might sound weird, but it really is good. Some kind of plague wipes out every male mammal on Earth, except for this guy and his monkey. And they have to travel alongside this government agent and this scientist to find out why the plague happened and how to fix it. I think it's pretty good because it doesn't just focus on the characters, it shows you what the world would be like without men, the good and the bad. It's well written, well drawn, and since it was planned with only 60 issues in mind it doesn't feel dragged on, and by the end all plot threads are tied up. The only thing bad I can say is that the ending might not be what you want, but it's ending that leaves you satisfied. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 14:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Final Fantasy 9. It showed me how powerful fictional characters can have on you and that helped inspire me to start writing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 14:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its ok, I was touched by Airborne and Encino Man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 13:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Y: the last man

Even if you don't like comic books you need to read this. Buy it, torrent it, whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some things that you think were ahead of their time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 13:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> gadgets, movies, people, ideas..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 12:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'll help you out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 11:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's attractive when they show self-respect. For me it's a major turn-off when girls complain that they are fat, unintelligent, or too skinny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, What are some of your non-sexual dreams that could be adapted into a movie/tv show? They don't have be Oscar worthy masterpieces. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 11:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 11:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 11:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> source... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parents of Reddit, What are some times you've purposely embarrassed your children? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 11:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How Australia operated as a prison colony </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 10:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 10:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well now they have that new show coming out, Hannibal. But the guy playing Lecter is the bad guy from Casino Royale so I don't know if it's gonna be good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 10:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Harry Potter could have been a tv show, maybe not better but still. I don't know how long kids in the United Kingdom have off for summer break, but in america its 3 months, so i'm guessing a Hogwarts school year is about 9 months. That's a lot of time to sum up in about 2 hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 10:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What movie do you think would be better as a tv show? And vice-versa. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 10:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> even though some will call this a cop-out, you can answer with what you think would be better as a mini-series, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 09:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to see Catcher in the Rye as a movie, but at the same time I don't. The reason why is that I can't think of a good actor for Holden. If only they could have made a movie in the 80's, I think Anthony Michael Hall could have been a good pick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 09:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this and Kids next door were the reason I always watched cartoon network. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 09:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had a similar experience, when I was a kid my older brother used to always come back from his friends house smelling funny. And I always wondered when his friends came over why he wouldn't let me hang out with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 09:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just playing Star Wars: Shadows of the empire the other day. I was surprised how much I found it difficult compared to when I played it years ago as a kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was watching Willy Wonka and the chocolate factory earlier and when the Pure Imagination song came up I got teary eyed thinking of my child. Reddit, What makes you feel nostalgic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 09:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *childhood, goddamn I need to proofread more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
