<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9503</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Online vs. "Live" Education: The Real Issues | "It matters to me to know who my students are, to know their faces and names. Its crucial for me to hear their voices as they answer my questions and ask their own, to heed their inflections and mark the expressions on their faces." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 01:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Strategy for Filtering America's Toxic Sludge of Political Advertising | The hypocrisy of media conglomerates, which insist on transparency in government but resist it themselves, is unsurprising. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 18:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Most People Are Rationally Ignorant" | "The best way to pursue long-term democratic reform is to provide a context where the deliberative democracy of the people flourishes and can give voice to key concerns. That is the highest form of democracy." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 03:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Case For A Change Of Course In European Policy | "The crisis has not come about just because individual countries have behaved badly, but is due in large measure to systemic problems. These cannot be solved by greater efforts at the national level; they require a systemic answer." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 18:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Obama Campaign's Forlorn Hope: Just Get Unlikely Voters to Turn Out | There's a big chunk of the population that overwhelmingly favors the president. The only problem? They probably won't vote. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 17:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lessons From Sweden In Assembling A Recovery | Devaluation is no short cut to export success. Falling inflation is the main hope for a sustained recovery in consumer spending. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 17:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Confuse Technology With College Teaching | "A set of podcasts is the 21st-century equivalent of a textbook, not the 21st-century equivalent of a teacher." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 02:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Veil of Opulence would have us screen for fairness by asking what the most fortunate among us are willing to bear. The veil of ignorance would have us screen for fairness by asking what any of us would be willing to bear. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-13 23:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Elephant in the Map Room | Talking about the Israeli-Palestinian conflict is the conversational equivalent of tap-dancing on quicksand... Maybe one day the realization will dawn that the complicated and highly lethal border is separating brothers from brothers, and sisters from sisters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 01:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Moral Significance of Sex Workers and People With Disabilities | People with disabilities have never been treated better, have never felt more fulfilled, thanks to caring sex workers. We benefit no one by pretending the entire area is one that should be taboo, wrong, criminal.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 21:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Valve? Or, what do we need corporations for and how does Valves management structure fit into todays corporate world? | The current system of corporate governance is bunk. Capitalist corporations are on the way to certain extinction.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 20:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 'Separate-but-Equal' Charter School Scam | While charter proponents claim that their schools are less bureaucratic, more efficient, and more effective, the evidence doesn't really back that up. Since when is a $100-million cost-overrun a sign of cost-effectiveness? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-07 17:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The LIBOR Scandal: Why is it Scandalous? | "This is not a scandal, because what is called scandal is in fact the heart of the system.  To call the LIBOR manipulations a scandal is to draw our attention away from the fact that it is simply one more normal way of accumulating capital." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-07 05:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Medicine: We Can Do Better Than This | "Ive got no health insurance. But theres one thing I do havemy house. I guess Im not willing to mortgage itand ultimately lose itto pay off endless medical bills. My house is the only thing Ill have to leave my daughter when Im gone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-07 05:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White Correspondents Burden | Africa has 54 countries and a billion people, but the only stories of interest to the Western press involve famine, disease, poverty and civil war. Rape and genocide score double points. The news is broken. How to fix it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-04 18:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cocaine Cowboys Know Best Places To Bank | We let our laws and morals fail, rather than our banks. Banks that help drug cartels launder money and give cover to those tied to terrorism should be put out of business. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-04 18:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress Fiddles While the Post Office Burns | The default is not primarily the result of a bad market or even bad operations, but of bad legislating by Congress. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-04 17:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The First 1 Percent | "The first people known to celebrate hierarchies of power, whose inequalities of wealth were integral to their society and culture - the people you could call the first 1 percent - were the first people to ride horses." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 22:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Real Entitlement Crisis | The rich and the super-rich demand and receive special entitlements in the shape of huge subsidies from the state for their enterprises... and special access to public officials to ensure that their activities are not closely regulated in the public interest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 17:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sparkle Motion | Rhythmic gymnastics. You don't think it's a real sport? Think again. It's physically tough, highly competitive. And with its own distinct culture: "An ancient, complex civilization made up entirely of 12-year-olds named Bethany" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-01 07:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Get Ahead in Chinese Advertising | As globalization proceeds apace and the worlds markets become increasingly, inextricably interconnected, Westerners will confront the notion that individualism is not a god-given right but rather a lifestyle choice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-01 03:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Art Over Biology | Scientists have struggled since Darwin to reconcile art with evolution. How does art help survival? Some categorise it as a form of sexual display for attracting mates. But its main function may be in prompting us to think. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-31 22:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three Rings Of The Libor Circus | Exemplary presentation of complex story in simple terms. Libor is three scandals in one. Traders were rigging Libor for profit. Top management at big banks didn't notice or didn't care. Regulators turned a blind eye. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-31 22:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sparkle Motion | Rhythmic gymnastics. You don't think it's a real sport? Think again. It's physically tough, highly competitive. And with its own distinct culture: "An ancient, complex civilization made up entirely of 12-year-olds named Bethany" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-31 22:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Social Security is Not Headed for Disaster | Social Security does not depend for its resources on an entity that might run out of money, that has no way to raise more, and could go into bankruptcy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 19:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's NOT Privatize the US Postal Service | In 2006 the USPS was forced to prefund its future health care benefit payments to retirees for the next 75 years in ten years. 90 percent or more of the current deficit is a result of these artificially created debts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 19:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Will the 99% Deal with 70 Million Psychopaths? | The legal "people" we know of as corporations are all by law, psychopaths.  "...with an emotional deficiency that keeps them from feeling bad about hurting others."  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 19:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Not a Mistake': NASA in Disbelief over Rate of Melting Ice | Greenland ice sheet melted at unprecedented rate during July </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-26 16:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Man Who Invented Too Big to Fail Banks Finally Recants. Will Obama or Romney Follow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-26 16:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Big Fat Belizean, Singaporean Bank Account | Overly complex taxation of rich people and corporations all but guarantees that those people and companies will spend an inordinate amount of money figuring out how to game the system rather than come up with new ideas that improve the economy.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-25 19:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Happens If GOPs Voter Suppression Works? | A presidency premised on a racist restriction of the franchise creates a political and constitutional crisis, and responding to it with resigned acceptance or inaction would negate Americas hard-won commitment to democracy and equality. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-25 18:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three Big Lies Perpetuated by the Rich | And one fading illusion: People in the highest class are people of high class. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-23 17:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Break the Power of Big Money | "Savers and income earners must not be tortured for the sake of banks. Bankers must die for their countries - not countries for their rotten banks. Pensioners go hungry while 20-something bankers order $2,500 bottles of wine." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-22 17:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Four Spending Myths That Could Wreck Our World | How Not to Solve an American Crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-20 16:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Green Deserts of Western Civilization | "The natural world did not become a desert on its own. Both in the past and at present, human beings, with their superior knowledge, have been the ringleader in turning the earth and the human heart into wastelands." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-20 16:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Pentagon Is Quietly Transforming Its Overseas Base Empire | Washingtons garrisoning of the planet is on the rise, thanks to a new generation lily pads  small, secretive, inaccessible facilities with limited numbers of troops, spartan amenities, and prepositioned weaponry and supplies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-17 18:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After 800 Years, the Barons are Back in Control of Britain | The tradition of resistance, the assertion of independence from the laws devised to protect the landlords' ill-gotten property, long pre-date and long post-date the Magna Carta. But today they scarcely feature in national consciousness. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-17 18:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-16 18:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article:
Libor, which is set daily in London by 18 of the worlds largest banks, and has far-ranging influences, affecting the rates of mortgages, student loans and credit cards. 

Three of those banks are American.
[The American banks included in the panel surveyed by the BBA for U.S. dollar fixing are:
The Bank of America, JP Morgan Chase, Citibank, NA](http://www.americablog.com/2012/07/list-of-libor-banks-involved-in-setting.html)

So the Fed has partial control and even greater influence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Machine and the Garden | An economy cannot self-correct any more than a garden can self-tend. And regulation - the creation of standards to raise the quality of economic life - is the work of seeding useful activity and weeding harmful activity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-16 15:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fed Knew of Rate Rigging Scandal, Did Nothing  | Fox guarding the henhouse: Federal Reserve Bank of New York knew of Libor manipulation but exercised no regulatory control </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-16 14:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A lawyer tells us why the legal system in capital cases is set up to fail, and says all of us should know more about what happens in an execution | "The innocent person is predisposed to get screwed by the legal system in ways that I dont think the legal system truly appreciates." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-15 20:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's Make A Deal | Superbly accessible and enjoyable speech on bank regulation. [pdf] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-15 20:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dont Hate Just One Player, Hate the Game: 26 Corporations Have Dumped ALEC, 21 Still Dating Other ALECs | For multinational corporations and the lobbyist firms that serve them, ALEC is seen merely as one of many Groups through which to facilitate the Corporate Playbook. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-15 15:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Global Financial Fraud and Its Gatekeepers | The media's 'bad apple' thesis no longer works. We're seeing systemic corruption in banking  and systemic collusion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-15 15:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Labor Of Love | Mother goes into labor. Cue liver failure, kidney failure, heart damage, brain trauma. Doctor tells her, if she's lucky she will die. But she lives, and learns from her son: "Life, it is not simply to be alive, it is to be awake." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-14 02:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The gym teachers of academia | Michael Ruse stands up for the philosophy of science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-13 20:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lies, Damn Lies and LIBOR | We need to rethink as a society what banks are for, what exchanges are for, and what clearing houses are for. If they are for the profit of the few at the expense of the many now, that is because it is the business model we have permitted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-13 02:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Challenge To American Regulators Over LIBOR Scandal | "Everybody is doing it" corruption is way more dangerous than corruption involving one or two rogue firms going off-reservation. Regulators should impose serious, across-the-board punishments. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-11 15:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time for Banksters To Be Prosecuted | Customers defrauded by bankers are tired of fake remorse and ritual apology. That period is over. It is time for prosecutions to begin. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-11 15:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Addiction to High Stakes Testing is Killing US Education |  How long does it take to understand that standardized testing was designed in America to identify and segregate the weak, that testing is not about closing gaps but, rather, maintaining them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-11 15:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-11 03:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't strike me as any kind of protection.  By that criterion, we're all protected from any abuse since we can leave and live in another country.  You probably mean something other than that, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Families Can't "Have It All" | The solution to work-life balance lies not in the battle of the sexes, but in the policy fixes that have stalled for decades in the United States while we have watched the rest of the world pass us in the race to make life better for working families. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-10 21:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let It Bleed: Libertarianism and the Workplace | What makes the private sector, especially the workplace, such an attractive instrument of repression is precisely that it can administer punishments without being subject to the constraints of the Bill of Rights. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-10 20:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let It Bleed: Libertarianism and the Workplace | What makes the private sector, especially the workplace, such an attractive instrument of repression is precisely that it can administer punishments without being subject to the constraints of the Bill of Rights. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-10 20:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Constitution Is Just Parchment, Get Over It | Pondering what John Hancock would do is how we figure out whether one-sixth of our population deserves to have their lives lengthened by early cancer detection and intervention, or must instead resort to hospital emergency rooms. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-10 14:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What If Everything Went Straight to Hell? | When the next big problem comes online we will suffer a complexity overload. At that point, the whole intimately intertwined structure comes tumbling down just like a house of cards. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-10 02:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This much I know: Daniel Kahneman | My main work has concerned judgment and decision-making. But I never felt I was studying the stupidity of mankind in the third person. I always felt I was studying my own mistakes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-09 22:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-07 16:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made the original post and took the headline directly from the article. You might try to RTFA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Santa-ization of MLK's Radical Legacy | Like other radicals, Kings image has been appropriated by the powerful, his inconvenient radicalism ignored, his message dumbed down to a few lines that would feel at home on a Hallmark card. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 18:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Not to Get Big Pharma to Change Its Ways | Whats the point if the fines are small relative to the profits, if the wrong people are feeling the financial pinch? The only way to get big companies like these to change their behavior is to make the individuals responsible feel the heat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 18:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Future as a Commons | Do we want to continue to rob from children not yet born so that we can add a few inches to our already obscenely large TVs; a few horsepower to our crudely over-powered cars? If not, then we must vote with our pocket books and wallets as well as in our voting booths. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 18:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Libor Interest Rate Scandal: Crime of the Century | Behind the worlds financial edifice lies a reeking cesspool of unprecedented corruption. Modern-day robber barons pillage with a destructive abandon totally unfettered by law or conscience and on a scale that is almost impossible to comprehend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 18:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Lakoff: How Right-Wingers Scam People Into Buying Their Toxic Philosophy | "Progressive are just the same as conservatives on it, but they dont know how to communicate their messages. What they wind up doing is talking about policies, rather than the moral basis of those policies." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-30 01:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Real Winners | Every American who is at risk of losing their job; every American who would have found health insurance unaffordable but will now receive crucial financial help; every American with a pre-existing condition... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-29 16:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a grad student scooped the government and what it means for online privacy | A computer scientist discovered Google was secretly planting cookies before the Federal Trade Commission noticed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-29 02:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Monopoly': Calling the Global Financial Sector What It Is | The m word allows us to see the architecture of the global economy for what it is--a playground for the new robber barons, a collection of corporate fiefdoms, with all of the typical injustices that such arrangements usher forth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-28 17:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Bigger, Better Supreme Court: The Case for Reform | A string of key decisions decided by 5-4 split effectively makes it a 'court of one'. It's time to debate a less dysfunctional future </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-28 16:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Old Monopoly Tricks in the New Media Age | The cable companies seem determined to return media to their "gilded age," where a handful of gatekeepers picked what people watched, when they watched it, and how much they paid for the privilege. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-27 18:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yes, There Is an Alternative to Capitalism: Mondragon Shows the Way | Why are we told a broken system that creates vast inequality is the only choice? Spain's amazing co-op is living proof otherwise. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-25 18:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The fate of health care shouldnt come down to 9 justices. Try 19. | How would we get to a court of 19? Gradually. If Congress ordered such an expansion, no president would be allowed to appoint more than two additional justices in a term. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-25 01:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-23 18:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The astute observer will already note the profound irony here - a political group whose ideology elevates the individual over the group (Conservatives) has managed to cultivate more group cohesion than the political group whose ideology blends community well-being with that of the individual.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The REAL Reason Conservatives Always Win | When two groups compete, the one with the most social cohesion wins in the long run. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-23 18:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Capitalism and the Mad Uncle in the Attic | Our current version of capitalism is good at generating more currency, not greater wealth. And even the currency is being siphoned off by the richest and most powerful in a spiral of inequity. It isn't making us happy.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-22 19:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jonathan Chait: How Badly Will SCOTUS Screw Up Obamacare? | "I want to be clear about this: If the Court strikes down the mandate, I will lose my shit. But striking the mandate would not end the law, or even most of the law." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-22 04:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-22 03:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is about an affecting experiment in teaching.  
To enter the public world, to practice the political life, the poor had first to learn to reflect. That was what she meant by the moral life of downtown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-22 03:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is about an affecting experiment in teaching.  
To enter the public world, to practice the political life, the poor had first to learn to reflect. That was what she meant by the moral life of downtown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Power of Progressives | There is perhaps no more important issue for progressives to mobilize against than the establishment consensus around austerity as the answer to our economic difficulties...its time for progressives to shift from opposition to proposition. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-20 18:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ellen Brown : Why Congress Wont Touch Jamie Dimon: JPM Derivatives Prop Up US Debt | The private creation of money at interest is the granddaddy of all pyramid schemes; and like all such schemes, it must eventually collapse, despite a quadrillion dollar derivatives edifice propping it up.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-20 17:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super PACs and Secret Money Destroying America's Democracy | In a nation of 313 million people and an electorate of 217 million, fewer than a 100 uber-wealthy individuals and corporations (a tiny fraction of even the 1 percent) shaped the GOP presidential debate to their personal benefit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-20 17:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five Principles for a Twenty-First Century Liberalism | The primary function of the state, everywhere in the world, ought to be to give up national autonomy, voluntarily and systematically, until the state is unable to exercise formalized tyranny over its citizens. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-20 03:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> E.J. Dionne Jr.: Why History Matters to Liberalism | If the Tea Party is to be believed, radical individualism has defined American history. But their story is wrong, and progressives must say so.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-19 20:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Republicans Worry About Hurting Corporate Feelings | Republicans conveniently forget that even the Supreme Court in its heinous Citizens United decision upheld the constitutionality of disclosure requirements on corporations and other outside groups. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-19 18:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spanish Austerity Savage to the Point of Sadism | The answer to Krugmans question, why are they repeating ancient mistakes?  Because they are making out like bandits. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-16 18:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the Economy Has Only Recovered for the One Percent | Absent a revitalized upsurge from labor and its allies like the Occupy movement that places inequality at the center of the presidential campaign in 2012, we can expect even further acceleration of wage-slashing from corporate America. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-16 18:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-15 18:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DW? Here's [a 1 minute 29 second version](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uiwsP9RnbZA) . Too brief? His PhD thesis is at http://www.physics.usyd.edu.au/super/theses/PhD(Muller).pdf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Khan Academy and the Effectiveness of Science Videos [8 minute video] | Offers some skepticism as to the usefulness of science videos that only teach the facts without investigating existing misconceptions.	 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-15 17:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Progressive Morality | When Republicans run for office, they take a foursquare stand for God and country, no matter that such a stand may have the depth of a campaign poster, while Democrats usually manage to sound like nattering nabobs even when theyre speaking about substantive issues. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-14 18:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why The Economy Cant Get Out of First Gear: The Rich Have Sucked It Dry | We wont get out of first gear until the middle class regains the bargaining power it had in the first three decades after World War II to claim a much larger share of the gains from productivity growth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-14 18:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Economics and Morality: Paul Krugmans Framing | Quoting conservative language, even to argue against it, just strengthens conservatism in the brain of people who are morally complex. It is vital that they hear the progressive values of the traditional American moral system. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-14 18:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Privacy Matters Even if You Have 'Nothing to Hide' | My response is "So do you have curtains?" or "Can I see your credit-card bills for the last year?" ... Joe Stalin would have loved it. Why should anyone have to say more? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-13 22:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-13 22:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh?  What's the most critically wrong part of that article? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So You Think You Can Be a Hair Braider? | Workers need to be able to experiment and to fail (quickly and often) until they find the real, valuable skills that customers will pay for. This will take years. And in order for them to do that, we need to start by making it easier to braid hair in Utah. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-13 18:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Elites Fail | Misleading title. What it's about is why meritocracies and democracies fail. They turn into plutocracies and oligarchies. Incumbents in any meritocracy eventually capture the high ground for themselves and their heirs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-13 01:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Wisconsin Blues and a Failed Progressive Narrative | Never move to the right thinking youll get more cooperation that way. Start telling deep truths out loud all day every day: Democracy is about citizens caring about each other.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-12 17:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberals Are Ruining America. I Know Because I Am One. | ...the tragic flaw of the modern liberal. We choose to see ourselves as innocent victims of an escalating right-wing fanaticism. But too often we serve as willing accomplices to this and to the resulting degradation of our civic discourse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-10 18:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-10 03:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is indeed much that is tragic in our country.  But you paint with too broad a brush.  I'm one American who doesn't fit your portrait and I know many others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You dont need to be a lefty to support Krugman | A shopkeeper or private citizen who cannot make ends meet is unlikely to get out of his debts by borrowing more. These truisms are then wrongly applied to governments: a long-established logical error known as the fallacy of composition. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-09 19:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now is not the time to hate the state | In 2010, Americas top 1 per cent claimed 93 per cent of all income gains. Income for the great bulk of citizens actually decreased.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-09 19:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atul Gawande : Failure And Rescue | The difference between triumph and defeat isnt about willingness to take risks. Its about mastery of rescue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-08 21:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Youre Not Special | Selflessness is the best thing you can do for yourself. The sweetest joys of life, then, come only with the recognition that youre not special. Because everyone is. [commencement address] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-08 18:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Rall: Recovery? What Recovery? | At 15,000 net new jobs a month, it would take 45 years to find gigs for the victims of the 2007-to-2010 subprime mortgage meltdown. Only something big and dramatic, like a new FDR-style Works Progress Administration, could fill it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-08 16:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I will go easy on the save yourself rhetoric with my daughter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-06 05:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I will go easy on the save yourself rhetoric with my daughter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-06 04:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Murray: The Esquire Q+A | People confuse friendship and relaxation. It's incredibly important to be relaxed - you don't have a chance if you're not relaxed. So I try very hard to relax any kind of tension. But friendship is different. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-05 22:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salt, We Misjudged You | The possibility has been raised that if we were to eat as little salt as the U.S.D.A. and the C.D.C. recommend, wed be harming rather than helping ourselves. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-05 22:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Business Can't Win the Privatization Game Without a Handicap | The private sector depends on public subsidies to compete with the public sector | Examples: School busing...Medicare...private toll roads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-05 18:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Corporate Socialism Destroys | -- taxpayers contribute when the market rejects -- taxpayers donate capital, while the owners keep the profits -- divert money from other public services to company coffers -- privatize gains, socialize losses and destroy competitors who do not get subsidies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-02 20:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Economics of the Madhouse | How can it be right that the solution to this crisis involves the collective punishment of almost the entire population, apart that is, from the moneymen who caused it in the first place?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 01:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High-Stakes Testing Protests Spreading | A national resolution protesting high-stakes test released in April already has support from more than 300 organizations and more than 8,000 individuals...If this keeps up, even President Obama and Education Secretary Arne Duncan are going to have to notice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 17:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another nail in the coffin of Enlightenment reason | Providing neutral information led those who initially said they didnt believe in climate change to deny it even more. And the more educated the deniers of climate change were, the more polarizing the facts - neutral spin-free facts - became!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 05:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To Profile or Not to Profile? | A debate between Sam Harris and Bruce Schneier.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 00:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats an American Workers Life Worth? About $5,900 | The bill to modernize and upgrade OSHA has little chance of passing.  The only realistic hope workers have of working in a safe industrial environment is to join a union, because  union jobs are clearly safer than non-union jobs.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-29 19:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Workers Lose By Staying Put | Unemployed individuals living in areas with above-average unemployment rates should receive part of their unemployment insurance check in the form of a relocation voucher.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-29 05:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-28 21:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they can't help it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elections Won't Bring Progressive Change, So What Can? | Progressive change certainly remains possible in America, although neither ruling party is equipped to bring it about. The informal people's struggles that began coalescing early last year has the potential to become a mass movement. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-27 18:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can Obama Stop Casino Capitalism? | The banking oligarchy is so intertwined with the political and economic establishment at this point that real regulatory change cannot happen until the system itself is transformed from below, by a powerful social movement.   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-27 18:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will This Post Make Sam Harris Change His Mind About Free Will? | Just because I dont have absolute freedom doesnt mean I have no freedom at all. Saying that free will doesnt exist because it isnt absolutely free is like saying truth doesnt exist because we cant achieve perfect knowledge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-26 23:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Zombie Within | Skillful, fluent action is not slavery to the neural zombie within; it is liberation from the rote and the regulated. It is flexible attunement to where we find ourselves.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-26 20:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Post Office Is Being Destroyed By a Phony Budget Crisis | Congress, not the post office itself, is the problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-26 17:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well, Why Shouldn't Poor White Voters Reject Democrats? | The white working class is said to 'vote against its own interests'. This only exposes the patronising assumptions of their accusers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-26 17:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creating Change is the People's Job | We-not just the president-have to be the agents of change in our society. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-25 17:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Facebook fails | We need to start equipping buyers with their own tools for connecting with sellers, and for engaging in respectful and productive ways. That is, to improve the ability of demand to drive supply, and not to goose up supply to drive demand, and failing 99.x% of the time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-25 06:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Stop Wildlife Poachers | Over the past 20 years, chimpanzees, gorillas and other great apes have declined the most in areas lacking a security force to protect them. Conversely, parks and protected areas with armed guards and anti-poaching patrols have seen population increases. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-25 05:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Great Healthcare Rip-Off | "The more I have understood, the saner single-payer appears. If the free market cannot work in healthcare - and it has failed spectacularly in this country to provide even a semblance of value-for-money - then it may be time to grasp the nettle." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-24 20:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cooperative Banking in the Aquarian Age | Globally, the burgeoning movement for local, cooperatively-owned and community-oriented banks is blazing the trail toward a new, sustainable form of banking. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-24 20:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heist of the century: Wall Street's role in the financial crisis | Since the 1980s, much of the global financial sector has become criminalised, creating an industry culture that tolerates or even encourages systematic fraud. The crisis of 2008 was a natural outcome and continuation of this pattern. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-23 20:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "So Rich, So Poor": Peter Edelman on Ending US Poverty   Why He Left Clinton Admin over Welfare Law | "Im very much in support of Occupy. The idea ... of the 1 percent and the 99 percent ... all fits together - we really should be all one country."  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-23 18:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "So Rich, So Poor": Peter Edelman on Ending US Poverty   Why He Left Clinton Admin over Welfare Law | "Im very much in support of Occupy. The idea ... of the 1 percent and the 99 percent ... all fits together - we really should be all one country."  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-23 18:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists Turn Human Skin Cells Into Healthy Heart Cells </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-23 18:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's The Inside Story Of What Happened On The Facebook IPO | In one of the biggest IPOs in history, in which a huge amount of stock was sold to small investors, privileged Wall Street insiders once again got top-notch information...and individuals got the shaft. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-23 17:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jim Hightower: Snarling Banks | Very few Americans on this side of the ATM machine think that the biggest problem in Washington is that the moneychangers don't have enough clout. But, incredibly, here they come with a super PAC intended to force lawmakers to bow even deeper to their needs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-23 17:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Is What Tyranny Looks Like | The historic street demonstrations of 2012 will be meaningless unless citizens use the power of the vote this year to remove the worst offenders from office. They can start with the Representatives and Senators who voted NO to due process rights. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-23 17:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why China Wont Rule | The sensible question, then, is not whether China will replace the US, but whether it will start to acquire some of the attributes of a world power, particularly a sense of responsibility for global order. The question does not admit of a clear answer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-23 03:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-22 19:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article:
...we're extending the number of years that we spend needing nursing. We've gotten good at keeping people alive once they're fairly decrepit. And that sort of guarantees that you have the maximum drain on resources, while also producing the kind of minimum amount of human benefit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Radical Life Extension Is Already Here, But We're Doing it Wrong | Life spans of several hundred years are bound to be socially disruptive in one way or another; if we're headed in that direction, it's best to start teasing out the difficulties now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-22 18:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Rise of the New Economy Movement | Activists, theorists, organizations and ordinary citizens are rebuilding the American political-economic system from the ground up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-22 18:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Life Worth Ending | The era of medical miracles has created a new phase of aging, as far from living as it is from dying. A sons plea to let his mother go. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-21 21:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get Stressed, Stop Organics, Become A Better Person | One newly published study finds that exposure to organic foods reduces willingness to help others. Another reports high levels of stress can increase trustworthiness and sharing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-21 17:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Costs of Capitalism's Crisis: Who Will Pay? | Economics professor Richard Wolff gives some context to the latest economic crisis and suggests a solution to prevent this from happening again. [long video] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-21 07:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aaron Sorkin at Syracuse University Commencement | "Don't ever forget that you're a citizen of this world, and there are things you can do to lift the human spirit, things that are easy, things that are free, things that you can do every day. Civility, respect, kindness, character." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-21 00:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Normal: Majority Of Unemployed Attended College </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-20 17:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Psychedelic Drugs Can Help Patients Face Death | If insurance companies knew about our outcomes, they might get a lot more interested in what were doing here. When you make people less afraid to die, then theyre less likely to cling to life at a huge cost to society. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-19 23:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does it mean to say that something causes 16% of cancers? | Unfortunately, we have this tricky habit of seeing narratives even when there arent any. Journalists do this all the time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-19 20:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Am Whatever You Say I Am? | An admirable person cultivates an environment where she is recognized as the kind of person she imagines herself to be, but she is nevertheless happy to enter other environments where she is seen very differently.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-19 20:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some doctors unaware of long-term side effects of cancer care | Overall, only 6% of primary care physicians and 65% of oncologists were aware of all the long-term side effects that the four drugs could cause. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-19 20:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Psychiatry Giant Sorry for Backing Gay Cure | I believe I owe the gay community an apology. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-19 19:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The world is being run by one million evil men, ten million stupid men, and a hundred million cowards."   said by the character Abdul Ghani, in Shantaram by David Gregory Roberts [extended quote in comments] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 18:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A New Politics That Rejects Austerity and Wars of Whim | The same politicians who preach that there is no money for vaccinations and school lunches can always find the money for corporate tax breaks, payouts to defense contractors and wars of whim. Politicians in both parties tell austerity lies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 18:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apocalypse Fairly Soon | Realistically, the only way to provide some reasonable prospect of emerging from austerity and depression would be for the European Central Bank bank to drop its obsession with price stability, to accept and indeed encourage several years of 3 percent or 4 percent inflation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 18:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
