<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8978</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 04:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite the videos, he's actually a pretty cool character. But, to be honest, the show really isn't that great. Check out the new [BSG](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Battlestar_Galactica_%282004_TV_series%29) if you haven't already, much better show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 01:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here you go.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nXrlhN9rPoc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Birthday William S. Burroughs: "On issues as pressingly contemporary-seeming as censorship, surveillance and the War on Drugs - his work is as relevant now as it's ever been." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 18:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 04:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article in the Daily Beast was written on January 27, 2014 and does not address the claims made by Dylan Farrow in the New York Times on February 1st, 2014.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 04:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prove it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 02:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Kevin O'Leary as much of an asshole in real life as he seems to be on television?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 19:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "I expect a certain level of professionalism and respect."


Justifying a petulant, angry, pathetic answer by appealing to "professionalism and respect." Awesome.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 05:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/What%27s_the_Matter_with_Kansas%3F
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rodney Brossart, a farmer from North Dakota, is the first American to have been arrested and jailed with the assistance of a Predator drone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 20:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 22:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blood Meridian. So savage and violent with such a brutal ending. A masterpiece.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 19:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the Gawker story:

http://defamer.gawker.com/here-are-plot-details-from-quentin-tarantinos-leaked-1507675261
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quentin Tarantino Suing Gawker Over Leaked 'Hateful Eight' Script </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 19:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 20:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the wikipedia page on it, pretty horrifying really:

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/1961_Goldsboro_B-52_crash

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 18:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. So sick of hearing the "So you wanna gets rid of all techmology, huh???" argument.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 53 years ago today, a B-52 broke up in flight over Goldsboro, N.C. As the plane disintegrated, two 2.5 megaton Hydrogen bombs broke free. One of them came very, very close to detonating. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 16:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 16:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Romani ite domum! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 06:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! Good luck with your new job!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost Everything in Dr. Strangelove Was True </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 17:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 06:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Jeepers Creepers.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Bxfxfh9w44g) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 22:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the whole series is nuts, but there's something extra special about DW3. Just can't get enough of it, it's so perfectly crazy.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 21:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you haven't seen [Death Wish 3](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h0ZP4S3xZgE), you don't know what a good bad movie is. A crappy 80s sequel that turns out to be a complete masterpiece of hackery. Absolute Must See, better than every flick mentioned in the post.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 16:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like my father.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 18:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The closest thing to a perfect movie that I have ever seen." - John Woo
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 03:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ALL THESE WORLDS

ARE YOURS EXCEPT

[EUROPA](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=38EDhpxzn2g t=2m)

ATTEMPT NO

LANDING THERE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 21:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a really fun game and one that really rewards getting good at it. Once you're actually good at it and can pull off the various moves easily, it becomes quite the cinematic experience and more fun. Plus shooting people from a distance in slow-mo never gets tired. Have fun!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 02:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this Harold Bloom quote about it:

"The first time I read Blood Meridian, I was so appalled that while I was held, I gave up after about 60 pages. I dont think I was feeling very well then anyway; my health was going through a bad time, and it was more than I could take. But it intrigued me, because there was no question about the quality of the writing, which is stunning. So I went back a second time, and I got, I dont remember 140, 150 pages, and then, I think it was the Judge who got me. He was beginning to give me nightmares just as he gives the kid nightmares."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 00:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That book is a joy compared to Blood Meridian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 15:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say what you want about Lennox Lewis, the man was a great champion. He may not have been the most exciting fighter but he was patient, fought his way to the top, put up with a lot of shit and when he finally got his chance, cleared up the Heavyweight division. He beat Holyfield, Tyson and Klitschko. I always loved his [knockout against Michael Grant](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FpdGFK_mqZI). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alfred Hitchcock's unseen Holocaust documentary to be screened </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 07:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 02:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a bitch.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 15:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hyped beyond all belief, to be sure, but it is quite excellent. But when you do eventually check it out, do yourself a favor and make sure you get a good copy, have some time set aside, turn off phones, etc. Oh, and remember, The Godfather is one movie in [two parts](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3KD8c5MHrn4). (Not three!)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 00:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you have to shoot, shoot. Don't talk.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 00:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buckley came out in favor of legalizing drugs almost 20 years ago:

http://www.thirteen.org/openmind/the-law/on-legalizing-drugs%E2%80%A6with-william-f-buckley/181/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cast of Futurama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 04:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 16:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Tank Man.](http://www.famouspictures.org/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/Tank-Man1.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 20:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's Wellesley.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 19:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Wu-Tang is for the children." It doesn't even rhyme yet it's one of the best hip hop lines ever.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-29 18:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *"The essential act of war is destruction, not necessarily of human lives, but of the products of human labour. War is a way of shattering to pieces, or pouring into the stratosphere, or sinking in the depths of the sea, materials which might otherwise be used to make the masses too comfortable, and hence, in the long run, too intelligent. Even when weapons of war are not actually destroyed, their manufacture is still a convenient way of expending labour power without producing anything that can be consumed. A Floating Fortress, for example, has locked up in it the labour that would build several hundred cargo-ships. Ultimately it is scrapped as obsolete, never having brought any material benefit to anybody, and with further enormous labours another Floating Fortress is built. In principle the war effort is always so planned as to eat up any surplus that might exist after meeting the bare needs of the population."* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 16:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's  a documentary about his atrocities:

[White King, Red Rubber, Black Death](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aUZLtkLA0VE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 23:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I scream, you scream, we all scream for ice cream!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-19 19:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds cool. I liked JA but you're right, I didn't really use a lot of the fancy moves. Damn that shit was fun.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-19 16:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never got a chance to play it. Did you like it more than Academy? I really got into Academy, some levels were really fun to play over and over. Plus the mod community for it was really good.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-19 14:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jedi Academy was actually pretty cool.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-19 14:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cf. Rob Ford
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 20:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A much better movie on football hooliganism, The Firm starring Gary Oldman:

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VznoshagNbI

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 21:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those looking for a vegetarian option, The Jane Bond across from the old Princess Cinema has some of the best food in town. Specifically, try their eggplant sandwich, unbelievably good.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 20:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it wasn't so bad. Quite a few problems with it for sure, but overall, it had enough cool stuff to keep me entertained.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 22:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "In the end they will lay their freedom at our feet and say to us, Make us your slaves, but feed us." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 21:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rob Ford DOES kind of remind me of the Penguin....

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bgJ5AcsXp4M

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 14:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sure, overseas and American banks. Matt Taibbi had a good piece about this a while ago:

http://www.rollingstone.com/politics/blogs/taibblog/outrageous-hsbc-settlement-proves-the-drug-war-is-a-joke-20121213

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 05:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wikipedia says 180,000 feet. 56km! So insane....
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 03:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Banks...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 02:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, totally. It was supposed to be 6 megatons and ended up being 15! So it was 250% bigger than they expected. As a result it was the worst radiological accident in American history. There's an excellent writeup about it on this page:

http://blog.nuclearsecrecy.com/2013/06/21/castle-bravo-revisited/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 01:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Follow the money. There are so many vested interests that want it to stay illegal because that's how they earn their living. Cops, judges, lawyers, prison guards, etc. etc. etc.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 22:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks dude, hopefully I'll find out next week. Would be a nice Xmas present!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 20:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it really is a great movie and, unlike lots of other flicks, quite historically accurate.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 20:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who's been unemployed for 15 months and just had his third interview with a company yesterday, I really hope I get that fucking job.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 20:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doing the same thing and this scene was a total surprise. Can't believe how young he looks.

To be honest, I found the first season kind of underwhelming, but the second season much better. The female actors in this series are absolutely fantastic. Livia, Janice and Carmella are just brilliant.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 15:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been obsessed with this movie for a while, probably seen it a dozen times. Really worth watching the whole thing. A note about [Castle Bravo](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yEje927dygM) that always blows my mind:

Burj Khalifa: 2,722 feet

Mt. Everest: 29,029 feet

Castle Bravo: 130,000 feet in less than ten minutes.

Fuck.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 15:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Stop caring so much about what people are saying or their misconceptions, and focus on yourself. 

Boom. Solution to the issue at hand turns out to be a cardinal rule of the seduction community!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 21:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You that never done nothin

But build to destroy

You play with my world

Like its your little toy

You put a gun in my hand

And you hide from my eyes

And you turn and run farther

When the fast bullets fly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Man Who Shot John Lennon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 17:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 16:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the full video from which this was taken:

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DNttT7hDKsk

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 08:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called the Toronto attitude. People here think that's how people in NYC/LA/Tokyo/London act so they act like that. Yeah it's sad.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 23:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [We are The Fall.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wygQmJ59E4Q) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 23:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm a big Orwell fan and I've just failed to read anything from him where I'm not all, "Damn Orwell, you right again."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 14:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Antihostile's Law: Orwell is always right.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 15:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hilarious...that's exactly what I started doing. First season was kind of underwhelming to be honest, but the second season has been really good so far.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-29 16:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it was something to do with the simplicity of the story: get to the space hospital to cure the radiation. Not exactly the most compelling story. I have to care about the guy in the first place. But I did love the fact that he got beaten by the robot cops and worked in the robot cop factory. That was pretty funny.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-29 01:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering how awesome this is, was really disappointed with Elysium. Looked really good but the story just didn't grab me.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 00:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another vote for Mogwai. [My Father My King.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U4WYnSFqh6k) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 15:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of the stuff on the Nas/DM album was fantastic. "As we enter" "Nah Mean" and "Patience" were just so great.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 08:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. That moment was stunning.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-24 16:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just love the Marx Brothers. Should be more of them on reddit. Here's my favorite Harpo, Chico piano bit from The Big Store:

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZYxgjJK7kD0

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-24 16:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love Camus, absolutely brilliant philosopher, brilliant writer. My favorite is probably The Fall.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-24 16:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate, hate, hate Steely Dan.

Sorry, just had to get that off my chest.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 22:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, Lee Harvey Oswald didn't kill him.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 13:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Redditor Reveals Who Really Killed JFK:

It was Lee Harvey Oswald.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 13:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He killed both of them. He also took a shot at Edwin Walker. Busy guy.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Audrey Hepburn colorized. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-22 21:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-22 20:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I prefer [the black album](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/White_Light/White_Heat)...released 12 months earlier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-22 07:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an aside, I've been reading the New Yorker for many years and it is the best general interest magazine in America.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 18:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Motorcade Sped On.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JjyFwbSNh4o) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 00:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "[Weapons giveaway program.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dKRK8Y4gyew) It's like one of those government programs. Just come and fuckin' get anything you want. We're gonna give away all the fuckin' automatic weapons. All the side-loaders, clip-loaders, shoot-em-backs... Saturday night specials... Colt. 45s, shotguns. Anything you want, chains, knives, straight razors... bottles, brick bats, baseball bats... and big kind of slanted jagged kind of things. I wanna see a goddamn big motherfuckin'... shoot 'em up, kill 'em, bang, stab 'em, crush... slice, kill, motherfuckin' boilin' oil. Catapults throwin' rocks and shit and blowin' up. Undercover shit, yeah. So I wanna see people putting secret things in fuckin' cars... and fuckin' explodin' and see the people explodin'. I wanna see knife cuttin', slice cuttin' choppin' and blowin' up. Hah-aaah yeah. That's right. A free fuckin' weapons give away program. I see it. Gonna solve all these goddamn problems." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 20:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One hell of a slow burner. Just watch it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 18:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet Rob Ford knows Trevor.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 00:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been asking myself the same question. Is it because he's a G-Man and shit would really hit the fan if he turned up dead or disappeared? If Nucky finds out, and I think he will, he's definitely dead.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 00:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tell you whut.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 17:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeff Bridges played Cogburn in the Cohen bros. remake. It's as though he could be related to the Dude in that movie universe. The way this old guy in BE could be related to Butchie in The Wire. I think that's what he means. It's not a great analogy.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 17:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet a couple more are gonna show up. An army of [field negroes](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=znQe9nUKzvQ) taking out the ultimate house negro, Dr. Narcisse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 15:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it, it's one of my favorite books, mainly because it's so damn funny. It is absolutely hilarious. There's pretty much a laugh-out-loud moment on almost every page. Very, very funny book.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rob Ford Denies Eating Pussy During Live, Televised Press Conference </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 17:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 19:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aka ["You come at the king, you best not miss."](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WP-lrftLQaQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 18:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Garrison was a nutjob. Watch [Oswald's Ghost](http://www.pbs.org/wgbh/amex/oswald/). Garrison was certifiable and the majority of his "evidence" was useless conjecture. So Clay worked with the CIA? So what? The Kennedy Assassination is a million pieces of string that go nowhere. Fifty years later, still no hard evidence, just "Clay worked with the CIA" or "Oswald went to Russia." Yes, yes, but so what? Now that we know that, what do we know? As for the HSCA, here's an excerpt from an excellent [interview with Gerald Posner](http://www.pbs.org/wgbh/pages/frontline/shows/oswald/interviews/posner.html):

**Q: Can you explain what the House Select Committee on Assassinations (1978-79) found out in the acoustic evidence, and what happened afterward concerning the issue of the reliability of the evidence?**

*A: "The House Select Committee on Assassinations used sound experts to listen to a Dallas police Dictabelt. They concluded with a 95 percent certainty that there was a fourth shot fired at Dealey Plaza, and it came from the grassy knoll. The National Academy of Sciences reviewed their work and found a multitude of errors and omissions. The most serious of which was that at the time that the Select Committee experts thought the shots were, [it] actually, [was] one minute after the assassination had actually taken place. Dealey Plaza is a veritable echo chamber, and it makes it very difficult sometimes to analyze the acoustic testimony. However, by looking at the statements of a witness who gave an opinion as to the source of the shots, we can see certain trends. Eighty-eight percent of the 179 witnesses who expressed an opinion said there were three shots and three shots only. The largest group that identified a location, 28 percent, said they came from the book depository. Only four witnesses, 2 percent of all the witnesses at Dealey, heard shots coming from more than one location."*


Check out the whole interview, it's quite good. And really, Oswald's Ghost is excellent as well.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 08:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Americans love their conspiracy theories, but I have to say, Oswald did it. After fifty years there is no hard evidence of a conspiracy to kill JFK, but a mountain of evidence that says Oswald acted alone.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 22:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's right on the first page of his letter.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 21:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly what it's supposed to do:

The essential act of war is destruction, not necessarily of human lives, but of the products of human labour. War is a way of shattering to pieces, or pouring into the stratosphere, or sinking in the depths of the sea, materials which might otherwise be used to make the masses too comfortable, and hence, in the long run, too intelligent. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Maher: "When Did Christian Values Change From Love Thy Neighbor to Fuck Off   Die?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 19:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-10 17:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like a lot of people have trouble getting into it the first time, including [Harold Bloom](http://www.avclub.com/articles/harold-bloom-on-blood-meridian,29214/):

"The first time I read Blood Meridian, I was so appalled that while I was held, I gave up after about 60 pages. I dont think I was feeling very well then anyway; my health was going through a bad time, and it was more than I could take. But it intrigued me, because there was no question about the quality of the writing, which is stunning. So I went back a second time, and I got, I dont remember 140, 150 pages, and then, I think it was the Judge who got me. He was beginning to give me nightmares just as he gives the kid nightmares. And then the third time, it went off like a shot. I went straight through it and was exhilarated. I said, My God! This reminds me of Thomas Pynchon at his best, or Nathanael West. It was the greatest single book since Faulkners As I Lay Dying. In fact, I taught it for several years in a class I gave here at Yaleinterestingly enough, in a sequence starting with Faulkners As I Lay Dying, moving on to Miss Lonelyhearts, then The Crying of Lot 49, and the fourth in the sequence was Blood Meridian." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 18:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMHO, one of the greatest speeches of the twentieth century, rivals anything by MLK, JFK, Gandhi or Churchill. A truly powerful moment.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its Been 50 Years Since Malcolm Xs Message to the Grass Roots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 18:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 16:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Autobiography of Malcolm X.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 22:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not innately, but if that's the goal, it's a step in the right direction.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 22:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, my online activity is pretty transparent, so it wouldn't bother me that much, but in this case, I'm using a separate youtube account which is linked to my G+ account, it works for me, and I'm seeing a lot more activity recently which has worked for me.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Simon on the problem with marijuana decriminalization. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 21:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 21:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love it. Increase G+ adoption in a real way and start cleaning up youtube comments at the same time. Good idea.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 17:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking into the Kennedy Assassination for over a year now. In my mind, there's simply no doubt that Oswald did it. Fifty years after the assassination there is absolutely no hard evidence of a conspiracy whatsoever. But there is a mountain of evidence against Oswald. Some good resources:


[PBS Documentary Oswald's Ghost.](http://www.pbs.org/wgbh/amex/oswald/) 

[PBS Documentary Who Was Lee Harvey Oswald.](http://www.pbs.org/wgbh/pages/frontline/shows/oswald/) 

[Interview with Gerald Posner debunking some of the conspiracies.](http://www.pbs.org/wgbh/pages/frontline/shows/oswald/interviews/posner.html) 

[Norman Mailer's 800-page biography, Oswald's Tale.](http://www.amazon.com/Oswalds-Tale-An-American-Mystery/dp/0345404378) 

[Conspiracy theorist Mark Lane interviewed by William F. Buckley.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fI7GwBtTRvc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 23:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Who put this thing together? Me, that's who! Who do I trust? Me!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 22:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally. Coked out tough guy talking shit.

"Hey, hey who the fuck you think you're talking to huh? You wanna fuck with me? Who the fuck you think I am, your fucking bellboy? Come on, you wanna go to war, we take you to war, okay??" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 22:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was drunk. I am sorry. I was drunk. I am sorry. I was drunk. I am sorry. I was drunk. I am sorry. I was drunk. I am sorry. I was drunk. I am sorry. I was drunk. I am sorry. I was drunk. I am sorry. I was drunk. I am sorry. I was drunk. I am sorry. I was drunk. I am sorry. I was drunk. I am sorry. I was drunk. I am sorry. I was drunk. I am sorry. I was drunk. I am sorry. I was drunk. I am sorry. I was drunk. I am sorry. I was drunk. I am sorry... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 15:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes. Sometimes, believe it or not, I know this might be hard to believe....the claim is denied. It's true.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 15:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, because insurance companies are known for paying out lots of money to claimants.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 21:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, check out Ali's post-fight interview. IMHO, the greatest post-fight interview in the history of boxing (and considering we're talking about Ali, that's saying something!):

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J6Hey54O6Qs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 20:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I could go into great detail the power of various nuclear weapons and what they do

Please do. I've been fascinated by nuclear weapons for years, ever since I saw "Trinity and Beyond." Footage of Castle Bravo still sends chills up my spine. Any information here or in another thread would be much appreciated. Thanks in advance.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 20:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A fine line between MRA/MGTOW/RedPill. But I think it's definitely a useful read for this subreddit. Thanks for posting the 15 impossible things.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 20:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, Wikipedia has its own bias to be sure, but it's a decent introduction. Thanks for posting the link.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 21:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah! Hadn't even considered that. Could he do it? Would he do it? Interesting scenario.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 17:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, totally. You know Nucky's not going down. Maybe Nucky sees to it that Eli bites it and takes Willy under his wing out of some sort of guilt? Farewell Daddy...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A little information on Dave Sim, who identified the feminist infiltration of society back in 1994. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 17:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 23:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I don't know if Nucky will actually kill him, but I think he's going to die.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 21:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Larry Smith was my econ professor at UW, both micro and macro. Smart guy, funny. He actually had/has a solid reputation well before TEDx. I guess he's the exception that proves the rule.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 15:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Spearmint

Just noticed, that song is playing in the background when Knox confronts Eli.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 14:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess: Willy is gonna die.

They've sort of set him up as a quasi-Jimmy Darmody. Now that he's mixed up with gangsters, he's going to have some serious problems. I think they're foreshadowing it with Willy staying in Eddie's room. Now, with the Feds on Eli, Willy is directly mixed up in everything. We know that if Nucky has to kill Willy to save himself, he will. Plus, it would just be so incredibly tragic for Eli, it's the thing he cares about and when Nucky finds out Eli is ratting on him (and he will), Nucky will do whatever it takes to save himself, even if it means killing his brother's son, or letting him die. FWIW, the last episode of the season is called "Farewell Daddy Blues". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 13:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loved that bit. Really well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-26 22:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hyperbole is the use of exaggeration as a rhetorical device or figure of speech. It may be used to evoke strong feelings or to create a strong impression, but is not meant to be taken literally."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-26 07:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was so unfunny it makes crack babies dying of AIDS seem hilarious.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 18:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Driving cars will be illegal in 20 years. I have no problem with that.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 00:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want...


...IN.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 00:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not absolving him of anything, specifically I just wanted people to note that it didn't start under him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 22:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama deserves criticism for a lot of things, but before everyone goes blaming this on him:

"The NSA memo seen by the Guardian was written **halfway through George W Bush's second term**, when Condoleezza Rice was secretary of state and Donald Rumsfeld was in his final months as defence secretary." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 22:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama deserves criticism for a lot of things, but before everyone goes blaming this on him:

"The NSA memo seen by the Guardian was written **halfway through George W Bush's second term**, when Condoleezza Rice was secretary of state and Donald Rumsfeld was in his final months as defence secretary." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 18:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True.

http://www.livescience.com/39911-as-superbugs-rise-new-studies-point-to-factory-farms.html

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These aerial shots of factory farming look like bloody zombie wounds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 17:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 21:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You answered your own question. America doesn't close military bases because America is in the business of opening military bases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> List of reasons for admission to an insane asylum from the late 1800s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 21:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 17:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Oh come on, it's not that much of a mystery.](http://musiccourt.files.wordpress.com/2010/08/robert_smith.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dick Cheney calls tea party a boon to GOP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 14:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 03:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, gimmicky is the right word in my book...on the other hand, I really did like Memento (more than Inception) despite the obvious gimmick of that movie as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 01:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I'm the only person who didn't love love love this movie. It was okay. Wouldn't watch it twice.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-20 06:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to /r/MensRights/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-19 22:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Instead of getting married, I'm going to find a woman I don't like and buy her a house."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-19 17:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn this is a great show. My favorites:


Larry gets high:
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t3lwPd-GGn4


Larry at Hallowe'en:
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AUdfdzm0EpU


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 06:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called [The Paranoid Style in American Politics.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Paranoid_Style_in_American_Politics) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 05:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The sooner they stop acting like part of the problem and start being part of a solution, the better.

Sadly, never going to happen. As far as they were concerned, the shutdown was part of the solution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 02:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you're opposing something like healthcare on a nebulous right-wing propaganda term like "big government" you've definitely gone full retard. America is such a great place, polluted by this 38% of slack-jawed troglodytes.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 23:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! Mine was Love Over Gold.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 19:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best music documentary ever made.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Orson Welles Meets H.G. Wells </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 06:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 21:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, same here. The first one was experimental and weird enough that it was a truly crazy, unique experience. It couldn't be duplicated, even by the same director.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Business groups prepare to abandon the GOP: We have got to quit worrying about the next election, and start worrying about the country. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 18:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 18:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the article and find out.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superb breakdown of what motivates the Tea Party and radical Republicans: "One of the key factors pushing Republicans to extremes, according to Greenbergs report, is the intensity of animosity toward Obama." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 17:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 16:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, then you're missing out on a brilliant take down of what makes the Tea Party tick. Your loss.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 13:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, did you read the article? That's exactly the point he's making. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The country as a whole may think gridlock has triumphed, particularly in the midst of a Republican-led government shutdown, but Republicans see a president who has fooled and manipulated the public, lied, and gotten his secret socialist-Marxist agenda done. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 04:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 18:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can only hope!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 16:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bgJ5AcsXp4M

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 21:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even better, Gary Oldman in The Firm:

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VznoshagNbI
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jan Brewer Tries to Say 'Tuskegee' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 21:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 20:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a documentary about him, "The Day After Trinity":

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P1DhWglFeLU
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interviw with Sam Peckinpah shortly after the release of "Bring Me The Head of Alfredo Garcia". (December 1st, 1976) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 21:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 06:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't think this happens to black people a lot more than white people, you're living in a fantasy land.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-29 22:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn I'm jealous. I'd give almost anything to be able to watch this for the first time again.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How 'Return Of The Jedi' Ruined 'Star Wars' Forever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-29 03:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 05:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh....why would we do something stupid like that?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 00:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not how I remember ROTJ at all! Stupid robot!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 00:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, that's exactly what I thought. "Jesus, we're closer to nuclear terrorism than I thought." Whenever I see any footage of any hydrogen bombs, I'm just like, nope, we should not have these. Just way, way too dangerous for mankind.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 17:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We shouldn't even be doing things like this:

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fd1IFjBNNVo

Just saw Countdown to Zero, good doc on nuclear arms proliferation:

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n12Y7mo7fqM
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 17:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ, two 3.8 Megaton bombs. Here's roughly what that would have looked like:

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ncT9du2KDXQ

(Castle Romeo, March 27, 1954, expected yield of 4 Megatons, actual yield, 11 Megatons) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 21:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please, please, I can't stand all this fighting, have my seat.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 21:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember, women want what other women want.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 20:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of Peckinpah's best and that's saying something. Warren Oates is perfect. One of the greatest 70s movies ever made.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 16:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't we get to even see Jabba the Hutt? They talk about him, but you never see him. They should totally fix that.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 21:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Combine this with the massive construction disruption from the LRT and Waterloo is going to be hurting for a few years.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 14:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obligatory 'the manga is better' comment here....but it is! The manga is the full story, the anime, as much as I like it, is a truncated version created before the story was done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 13:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christoher Hitchens had an excellent piece on North Korea back in the day: ["Worse Than 1984: North Korea, slave state."](http://www.slate.com/articles/news_and_politics/fighting_words/2005/05/worse_than_1984.html)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 22:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Courtesy of Popul Vuh:

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Popol_Vuh_%28German_band%29
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 21:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have never seen this before, do yourself a favor and just watch the first fifteen minutes. Make sure you're sitting down.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 15:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crazy idea here, keep your nose out of my business.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 06:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a) A lot of people who get philosophy degrees end up getting law degrees and b) philosophy prepares you for a wide variety of careers because it educates you in logic, critical thinking, rational decision making, game theory, etc. Those kinds of skills are useful in a wide variety of jobs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 02:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an aside, philosophy graduates do very well in the long run:

http://online.wsj.com/public/resources/documents/info-Degrees_that_Pay_you_Back-sort.html

For starting salaries, engineering and things like nursing are pretty strong, but the list reorders further into peoples careers. If you looked at the pay of people 15 years out, philosophy is actually in the top 10%.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-16 05:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I'm the only one who would like to see this fight and thinks Hopkins would have a chance. So be it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-15 23:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A woman who complains about [gender roles in videogames.
](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anita_Sarkeesian) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 14:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Echoes by Pink Floyd.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 14:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sister Ray
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Differences in the prices of identical products between Ontario and Quebec enables the foreign-owned Beer Store to capture as much as $700 million in incremental profits each year because of the near-monopoly on beer retailing it enjoys in Ontario. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 22:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 22:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Handy!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 17:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considered that, maybe just a longer delay like 24 hours would help. The thing is that voting does provide some value, as a general rule (the article notwithstanding) interesting, informative comments do get upvotes and stupid, offensive ones do get downvoted. But let's face it, upvote = agree and downvote = disagree, that's just how the game is played around here.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 17:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely under the "No shit, Sherlock" category, but this is why I appreciate the fact that Reddit now has a time delay on showing the up/downvotes for comments. At least the people running the show are thinking about this and doing something about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 17:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent article. Fascinating and disturbing.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
