<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6418</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 11:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he was lesbian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lovelies who live in LA: What's it like knowing you could bump into the Grumps any day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 00:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's it like knowing they might even use the same supermarket as you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible to combine your 401(k) with a hedge fund? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 00:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 19:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, they supposedly have 250000 subscribers already so it does seem like they have happy customers.

Technical problems happen with every service. Lots of people have problems with Netflix for instance while others don't. It's just part of the modern world. I wouldn't call Sling a "terrible business" since that would qualify Netflix and HBO Go as terrible services as well since at one point I've had weeks of problems with their services too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could attend a Grumps panel and be completely anonymous and ask them any question, what would you ask? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 18:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd probably ask something extremely uncomfortable like "do any of you masturbate to lesbian porn?" just to see their reactions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 12:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you go to /r/netflix or /r/televison a lot of people claim that the only reason they still have cable is because of sports. Sling is a perfect substitute for them. They can cut their monthly cost from ~$100 that cable costs to just $20 and stream their sports. It's a good service for some people. I just don't think that the Game Grumps audience is the right group to advetise this too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 06:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yeah, like I said, adding it only to sling was dumb because not everybody is going to be interested in it.

The point of my post though was just merely to explain how Sling could be appealing to many other people and that the $20 gives you more than just Table Flip. Being able to stream ESPN is actually a huge deal for many cord cutters since previously that wasn't possible without an expensive cable subscription. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 06:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people don't like cable but still want to watch sport matches or the news the old fashioned way.

I mean, this is a good alternative for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not their target demographics. They are targeting cord cutters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 23:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From my understanding, the $20 gives you access to live TV from networks like ESPN, ABC, A E, etc. which is much cheaper than cable TV.

I can totally see the value in the $20 if you're into sports and live TV but prefer streaming it and not pay for cable.

However the addition of Polaris+ and thus Table Flip is really stupid imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys who have scissored (sex position) with girls, what was it like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 19:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Har jeg bildk? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 17:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Er min navle vk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 21:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've made several videos. Since you can't be bothered doing a 2 sec search on Youtube, here they are:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ayd-e3DZI9s

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qF71bp1yZzM

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6YeB0NucfXk

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vbnsrIMfn2U

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NxeM08qvTlU

Their last video was only 3 months ago, not 2 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 20:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeg prvede match.com men der var ikke rigtigt nogen i 20'erne s valgte at deaktivere min profil derinde. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 20:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Synes bare ikke jeg fr srligt mange matches s vil gerne supplere det med noget andet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 20:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Du m ogs gerne komme med forslag til andre tjenester som du ikke ndvendigvis bruger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 20:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Og hvad er s den forrige generation som frte til den konomiske krise som er grunden til at de unge har det svrt med at finde arbejde? Generation Spader? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hvad er nogle gode datingsider/dating apps? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 19:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 19:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6YeB0NucfXk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 19:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Games are still listed at the same coin-price. So if you listed it as 10 coins, it's still 10 coins. However because of the price change, your game is now worth $7.5 as opposed to $10.

Also here is one of the videos where they advertise about the website: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6YeB0NucfXk

I have no idea if they're still affiliated with them or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The website 99gamers that Arin and Suzy keeps advertising about, just lowered the price of their coins, making members lose money </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 19:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So now a coin is worth $.75 instead of $1 even though it still says $1 on the website. Many members have because of this lost money because their coins are now worth less. Somebody even tried pointing this out and got banned from their website.

Just putting this out there as a warning to any lovelies out there about this shady website. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 17:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lucky. Wish people would talk to me so I didn't feel so lonely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
