<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5522</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No Je Suis Charleston? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 19:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drug cops took a college kids savings and now 13 police departments want a cut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Greek Bailout Is Really a Bailout of Western Banks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brainwashed much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course people reading /r/news won't be getting this information because it is considered "news analysis" and therefore forbidden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 461 people shot dead by police this year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'My body is on fire': Writhing prisoner takes 43 minutes to die - but Supreme Court judges say midazolam use is constitutional </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This didn't take long, it's almost as if they had the exercises all mapped out and they were just waiting for a suitable pretext: Security services to carry out major anti-terror training exercise in London this week after Tunisia hotel attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Violent start to 'sham elections' in Burundi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Fifteen Most Outrageous Responses by Police After Killing Unarmed People </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 06:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 05:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to make sure this doesn't seem like more BS one side good, other side bad political partisanship, here's a good article on Hillary: [The Vileness of the Clintons](http://www.counterpunch.org/2015/06/25/the-vileness-of-the-clintons/). I just hate all of these people, I really do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bush dogged by decades of questions about business deals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 05:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 05:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only a matter of time. Prog, for all its excesses, has been unjustifiably maligned. I think a lot of the best prog like Yes is weathering the test of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tunisia hotel attack: Anger at tour operator's cancellation policy for British travellers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greece crisis: markets begin to tumble as investors flee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 19:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Chris Squire from Fish Out of Water](https://youtu.be/RA_wEnOVWcQ?t=160) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 19:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP He was an absolute legend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yes bassist Chris Squire dead at 67 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 19:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Orwell's Triumph: Joshua Cohen and Novels of Surveillance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 19:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kuwait Shia mosque bomber was Saudi national </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 19:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kuwait Shia mosque bomber was Saudi national </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 19:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japanese railworkers hold funeral for 'stationmaster' cat who helped save railway line from bankruptcy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 18:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Militants kill 11 in Mali town </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 06:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What exactly does 'one' mean? Court of Appeal passes judgement on thorny mathematical issue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 02:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 21:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just came across this last week:[Joni Mitchell with Jaco Pastorius and Pat Metheny](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bLKb9Ms68ME index=1 list=RDbLKb9Ms68ME) Not a bad band! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 21:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm dyslexic. I initially read this as "Ancient Greeks lining up at ATMs." Did kind of a double take. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of people killed by extreme weather in 2015 as El Nino arrives to bring more chaos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 21:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Security Expert Says Mass Surveillance Doesn't Stop Terror Attacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 20:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joni Mitchell unable to speak following 'traumatic brain injury' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carpet-Bombing History - Commentary on ISIS ignores Washingtons legacy of cultural ruin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analysts report that renewable energy has crossed a significant threshold: the sectors size last year reached double the level it was at just 10 years earlier. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 18:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 01:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Montreal is great for creepy statues. Here's one I love on McGill College that has a theme of immigration to Canada. If you can see the people in the back, the ones who haven't made it to Canada yet, they're basically starving, near corpses:(https://www.google.com/search?q=montreal+statue+mcgill+college biw=1920 bih=922 source=lnms tbm=isch sa=X ei=W92NVd_hI4y0-AHCpJL4DA ved=0CAcQ_AUoAg#imgrc=IexeWSMv48y-VM%3A) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 23:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That leads to the question: what does it mean to be a democracy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 22:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While it doesn't go nearly far enough, I was actually surprised that they did distribute their criticism. Here's the line from the report on the US: 

 There were worrying revelations by whistleblower, Edward Snowden that US intelligence agents spied on prominent human rights 
 organisations. Law enforcement authorities were accused of heavy-
 handedness and intimidation of protestors following demonstrations 
 against discriminatory treatment by police of African-Americans.

They could have gone on at length about how corporate interests have created legalized corruption that circumvents democracy, but maybe that makes the sequel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 22:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the short answer is you can't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 22:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over two seasons fighting in the Octagon, you don't want to mess with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 22:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That exact same line leapt out at me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Study Says Democracy on the Retreat in Over 96 of the 193 U.N. Member States </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 21:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democracy on the Retreat in Over 96 of the 193 U.N. Member States, Says New Study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 21:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disney bans the selfie-sticks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 20:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I see the American flag now, I usually think "Bow to your sensei". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 18:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China also has enormous bubbles in property and currency. Somewhere between Greece, China, the US student loan bubble, and the TPP, I can't imagine we aren't in for a giant economic shock in the near future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As China's stock market suffers worst crash in seven years, 5 facts explain how the bubble arose - and why it might be bursting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 18:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 04:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've come across this site more and more. It's very glossy and predictably pro business, pro tech. Who is behind it? Their About Us section of their web site has a lot of bullshit about digital media and says it is linked from the Atlantic but who is funding it? It strikes me as being a strange site and the lack of comment sections on many issues is suspect. Is this just a huge PR thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 03:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was actually an experiment like this in Canada during the sixties. It was only in one small city, in Manitoba but it was wildly successful. It went nowhere because of politics but for a couple of years they had a guaranteed basic income and unemployment fell to an all time low: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mincome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dutch city of Utrecht to experiment with a universal, unconditional income </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 01:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A year of the 'Islamic State': Almost 12 months after the caliphate was declared Isis has grown in strength  but has the US played into its hands? Patrick Cockburn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 01:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In an ideal world, these people would come with subtitles translating their corporatese into English. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Vileness of the Clintons  CounterPunch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Bee highway' created in Oslo to give pollinators safe passage through the city </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Field trial of genetically-modified wheat failed to show it can repel aphid pests, scientists say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Field trial of genetically-modified wheat failed to show it can repel aphid pests, scientists say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! A Bhutanese Hamlet would probably be a happy Hamlet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been following homesteading locally and would recommend sites that have localized info. Here's a good one for Buffalo to give an idea of how it works though there are a lot of others for different cities: http://buffalorising.com/2013/05/homestead-eligible-properties-buy-a-house-in-buffalo-for-a-single-dollar/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 22:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe Yankees caps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 22:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know exactly what you mean about not being able to paint apartments. Have you ever considered something like homesteading? Depending on your part of the country, it's becoming more common and is realistic for younger couples especially if there are homesteading groups near you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 22:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In other news, Shakespeare believes that Hamlet should stay Danish and perplexed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 21:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a shame we don't have some widely recognized symbol representing Northern racism that we could get these companies to ban. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 21:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a feeling that even a few minutes as King will allow him to do more damage than is conceivable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Queen perplexed by painting from German President: 'Is that supposed to be my father?' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 21:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if this is the country very many people actually wanted. I think a lot of people's wishes have been ignored or overturned by very powerful systems that don't take into account what average folks want or need. Corporations and government bureaucracy have a range of concerns that have little to do with improving the lives of the citizenry. Profit, power, trickle down, efficiency, all of these things have to line up before the quality of our lives is factored in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No Boots on the Ground and Other Fairy Tales - The Fine Print in the White House War Plan CounterPunch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A journalist who used a pseudonym to avoid rape and death threats has been kicked off Facebook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very hard to tell if these people are completely corrupt or just epically spineless. I stopped worrying about who is which a long time ago since it all ends up in the same ugly place.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homeownership Rates Drop to Historic Lows; Middle Class Feels the Strain of Rising </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pelosi Stands Down On TAA, Clearing Way For Obama's Trade Agenda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French police clash with migrants as ferry strike causes chaos in Calais </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greece crisis talks stumble: Tsipras hits out at creditors with 'no interest in an agreement' as the IMF rejects proposed Greek budget cuts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 17:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But from the fish's perspective, maybe we're humans with fish looking teeth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Testicle eating' Amazonian fish found in US lake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 16:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least we can be sure it's somehow connected to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan finally lifts its 67-year-old ban on dancing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 04:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jailed for Being Broke A broken bail system makes poor defendants collateral damage in modern policing strategies By Matt Taibbi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 04:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 02:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They forced a bunch of planes to land and examined them including one in Austria after Snowden initially went to Russia. At first, it was assumed that he had simply changed flights in Moscow. The Bolivian leader's private plane was forced to land after he'd visited Russia because it was suspected he might have Snowden on board. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 02:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not much of a shock that these people are all spying on each other, but nice to have confirmation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Franois Hollande calls emergency meeting after WikiLeaks reveals US spied on three French presidents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 02:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 02:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think would make it to Iceland. His flight would likely be intercepted even if they offered him asylum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 00:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very interesting about Canada. I didn't realize that there was low turnout there. My lasting impression was from being in Quebec during the 1995 Referendum on secession when the voter participation was well over 90%. I guess people vote when they feel they can make a tangible difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 23:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the fact that Iceland is a parliamentary system helps to encourage participation because supposedly "fringe" parties have a real chance to gain seats in government. I'm not Republican or Democrat in the US and although I vote, I really don't feel like it means anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The man who was jailed for 22 years  on the fantasy evidence of a single hair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 23:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Fast-Track Fight Is Effectively Over: Its Happening - For the next six years, Congress will be unable to amend any trade deal signed by the president, and only 50 votes will be required for Senate passage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 22:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Manhattan Landlord Is Evicting an Entire Block of Latino Business Owners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 21:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poll: The Pirate Party remains by far the most popular party in Iceland, with 37.5 percent support </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 21:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 21:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That my friend is an excellent question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 20:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Thus far, the United States has never really accepted the Nuremberg Code. While the code was being created, the U.S. was giving people syphilis in Guatemala. It did the same at Tuskegee. Also during the Nuremberg trial, children at the Pennhurst school in southeastern Pennsylvania were given hepatitis-laced feces to eat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Human Experimentation: A CIA Habit  CounterPunch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 20:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US to send 250 tanks to countries along Russian border to 'respond to Russian aggression' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 06:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Purity of Essence! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do these lunatics seriously want a war with Russia? Is that what we're dealing with? 'Unite against Moscow aggression': US nuclear missile commander says Vladimir Putin's actions echo those of Nazi Germany in the 1930s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 06:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Piracy site-blocking Bill clears Australian House | ZDNet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 03:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taliban attack Afghanistan's parliament, seize second district in north </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 03:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. data hack may be 4 times larger than the government originally said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 03:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
