<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4487</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 01:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A privy is sort of like a maker's mark, it identifies/differentiates the coin.  [Take a look at some images](https://www.google.com/search?q=privy+mark source=lnms tbm=isch sa=X ei=3sNbVYrZBMLGogS55oDACg ved=0CAcQ_AUoAQ biw=1658 bih=894), you'll notice the addition of little emblems on the coins (like animals), that's the privy mark.

Privy's typically have much lower mintages, which makes them (in theory) more valuable/collectible due to supply demand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Babel is different from other compile-to-JS systems like CoffeeScript and TypeScript, and how it's going to become the driving force for innovation in JavaScript </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 23:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beautiful Maps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 21:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Skeleton](http://getskeleton.com/) is still my go to when I need bare-bones responsive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 18:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish I could help, but I work at Stupid Shit No One Needs and Terrible Ideas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 17:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been thinking of getting a tube of these, hopefully spot will keep dropping.

If anyone is also interested, they're an [exclusive at Bullion Exchanges](http://bullionexchanges.com/buy-silver/2015-1-oz-silver-canadian-maple-leaf-e-mc2-privy-reverse-proof-5-coin.html) and they're on some sort of deal now, with 20 hours left on the deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> cssnext - a CSS transpiler that allows you to use tomorrow's CSS syntax today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 17:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple (ipad) Safari URL Spoofing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 17:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 01:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do some TED-style talks in my garage every 3rd Wednesday of the month.  Here's some recent talks:

* Ty beanie bag babies made in the 90's were filled with small plastic beads and dormant brown recluse spider eggs.....yes I said spider eggs
* Edible staples - keep your burrito or taco closed
* Is the Millennium Falcon really at the bottom of the Baltic Sea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 23:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 22:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Expected to see photos of the police actually sweeping through the growing homeless camp.  Son, I am disappoint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 22:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it. Simple. Beautiful. Elegant. It's simply beautiful elegance. Anyone who arranges their watch in perfect parallel alignment to their sketch book and takes a photo of it is definitely not fucking around.  

This is the kind of designer who says things like, "in this new design, we're using a typeface called Ahm-peere." And you reply "you mean Empire?"

Definitely not fucking around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 21:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're either injecting malware into your computer or they're using a popular scrolling javascript library.  For the latter, here's some I can immediately think of:

* superscrollorama
* scrollmagic
* wow.js

Just google those and check them out.  You'll probably want to reformat your hard drive first, get rid of that virus you and I have now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 19:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, be sure to zoom in to see MAX/buses!

I only saw the WES train/circle when I fired up the map.

What app do you use to track specific lines in real-time?

The map above seems fairly accurate.  I can see the full steel bridge from my window and the trains and buses seem to be a couple hundred feet behind what the map is showing me (trains are about 3/4 the way across when the map shows them entering the bridge). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 19:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dated an interesting girl one time. Interesting does not always equal a good time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those that ride WES, you can track it in real time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 18:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WebGL demos from 3D Web Fest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 17:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 16:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best thing you can do is relax and realize it's all going to change in 2 years. As soon as you feel like you're getting up to speed it's time to throw it all away and start over with something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 15:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Digital / Web Designer / Programmer / IT Expert"

lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many think you (or your spouse) will lose their job over the next 5 years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 15:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 20:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why would this not hold its premium?

Because dealers hit you coming and going (they make $ at either end of transactions). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 17:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you just fuck with them.  Tell them you'll send a check for $100.  If they call you back, tell them you sent a check 2 weeks ago for $100, didn't they get it?  Apologize then tell them you'll send out a check tomorrow for $150 and that you're really, really sorry they didn't get the first one.  If they call back, relay the previous two stories, then repeat, but up the check to $200.  Gosh, I don't know what's going on, do you guys have a new address?  Rinse and repeat.

The best pleasures in life are free.

I used to have a collection agency call my # asking for a Maribella (I'm a dude).  I ended up just pretending to be her at a certain point. It was great, you know, a guy pretending to be a girl, "yeah, this is Maribella...Wait, what are you calling about?....How much?....Yeah, I'm not going to pay that....Why?....Why should I? You can't collect on it, it's free money" (arguments about my morality continued).  They eventually stopped calling...At one point I just googled Maribella's full name, found her Facebook page where it listed her employer in Beaverton.   I eventually asked to speak to a supervisor and relayed this info and let him know his staff were morons. I found her in literally 20 seconds. Our calls went on for months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the average age of a minimum wage worker in the US is 36 years old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 15:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 23:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really a dashboard, more of a micro-site.  Great idea, though, every major city should have this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 21:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'd be a fun home office if it had more windows, but that's about all I think about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 19:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes you think you missed the bottom? I mean beyond naivety and wishful thinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 16:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't buy a Mt. Dew with a 1 oz round. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 16:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because fuck you, that's why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 16:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * If you were to get rid of one state in the US, which would it be and why?
* Name three previous Nobel Prize Winners.
* What's your favorite song? Perform it for us now.
* On a scale from one to ten, rate me as an interviewer.
* Who is your favorite Disney Princess? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 16:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wanted to let you know I only clicked on the link to see a larger version of the cat on Winnie the Pooh.  He's very handsome - the cat, not Pooh Bear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 16:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's really missing is a photo of you with your macbook.  I can't take you seriously as a dev if you don't have a macbook. You should probably donate that brown shirt to Goodwill and pick up some plaid while you're there. Your projects should be made with love as well.

Lastly, think about adding some percentage-based skill charts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 15:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember when we used to do this in Flash, although it was more a flashlight type of effect.  Those were the days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Data Nerds Found A 131-Year-Old Sunken Treasure - used Bayesian theory to find the ship   the gold (19 minute video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 19:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Data Nerds Found A 131-Year-Old Sunken Treasure - used Bayesian theory to find the ship   the gold (19 minute video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 19:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 17:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Respond to some job adverts, take some phone screens, go on some interviews.  You'll then have your answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Find, Hire, and Retain Developers  Interview with Cal Evans (19 minute video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://blog.fogcreek.com/how-to-find-hire-and-retain-developers-interview-with-cal-evans/

*"If you as a developer manager are not qualified to read through my GitHub Repo and look at the code that Im writing and say is this good code, and if youre not qualified to look at my LinkedIn profile and see that I show a progression of responsibilities, then I question whether youre qualified to manage me in the first place."*

Some other good stuff in the video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Selectize - hybrid of a textbox and select box </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait until you have to get a real job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 01:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll check it out, if it's cheap, I don't mind paying. Free is always good if it fits the bill, though. Screencast-o-matic is $15 a year so no big deal if I use it a handful of times and it doesn't float my boat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 01:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will check it out for sure, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 01:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I always try to get software from the actual software company domain.  The big green download button on camstudio.org is coming from their cdn but now that you mentioned it, I see they do have a link to sourceforge as well for the optional codec.

I'm checking out OBS as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 00:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seattle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 00:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Building definitely looks demo'd to me, I'd say mission accomplished. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 23:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JavaScript in high school? Christ, I was spending all my time trying to trick out my van. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 23:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The job is work from home, so it's not limited to any specific location

* https://nomadjobs.io/
* https://weworkremotely.com/
* https://authenticjobs.com/
* Stack Overflow Careers (make sure you have the telecommute option in your listing folks can filter for) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 23:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Sold this bullshit to the bubble! I can help you make some more bullshit." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 23:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it really more a countdown until unemployment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 23:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need a web style guide. These typically have a section on [logo/image guidelines](http://www.csuci.edu/tc/web/styleguide/logos-images.htm), which basically defines what you can/can not do with said logo/images. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It takes a ton of ore to get 1g of gold. But you can get the same amount from recycling the materials in 41 mobile phones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 21:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 19:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll check it out, thanks much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 18:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the front end has matured to where there is a need for front end *engineering*, not just front end *development*.

Front end is a complex environment nowadays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for free screen recording/editing software (Windows 7) to do programming screencasts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 18:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello all,

I'm looking for some free screen recording and basic editing software (**Windows 7 Home Premium**) that will allow me to do some [programming screencasts like this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QO07THdLWQo).

I'll be uploading the videos to youtube.

I thought about just doing a google hangout as I'm going to be doing all the screencasts "live",  but I want the ability to stop recording my screen as well as edit my screencasts just so I'm not including a bunch of dead air/crap as I go consult APIs or hit some stumbling blocks or what have you.

I don't need the ability to do the [screen-in-screen](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HKmBt5HDVNI list=PLViRFZPCqDBfkfF0FFbsCVbuMzuoUV6LA) type of screen recording as I don't have a webcam (I built my own PC).

Anyone have any suggestions for Windows 7 Home Premium?

Has anyone used any of these?

* http://camstudio.org/
* http://www.screencast-o-matic.com/ (premium edition for $15/year) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 18:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point about the serial #s.  This is why I engrave my luggage combination into every piece of silver I buy. If my safe deposit box is ever robbed and subsequently recovered, all I have to do is show up to the police station with my luggage and bam, case closed. It's doubtful anyone else has 1234 as their combo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PlainJS - The Vanilla JavaScript Repository. All functions work properly in IE 9+ most of them are compatible with IE 8 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 16:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 16:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should really be asking yourself "do I want a client who is paying $500 for a website?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 16:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed that bullshit not terribly long ago linking to an article, I immediately killed the tab. That's some of the worst shit I've ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 16:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geiger has:

* Milky/pearl surface
* [UV varnish security mark on the back](http://www.geiger-edelmetalle.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/Security_Line_UV.jpg) that shows up under black light.

Serial #s don't mean squat for security, [SilverTowne bars seem to be heavily faked](https://www.google.com/search?q=silvertowne+silver+bars+fake ie=utf-8 oe=utf-8).

BTW, I have both, though Geigers are my fave 10oz bar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> innerText is real, it's an old IE-specific property to set text nodes. It's IE's equivalent to textContent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure submitLecture() is even firing?  controller/scope issue going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also a concealed carry permit isn't super easy to get

From my experience in two states they are ridiculously easy if you're not a criminal. They also help during traffic stops as you can give that to the officer along with your drivers license and he will immediately be put at ease because he knows you've been "pre-screened". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out the excellent documentary *The Goonies*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just keep a pristine copy of the work you did in your portfolio.  Let your clients do whatever they want with their site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top-level domain .design just got released </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Complete Guide to SVG Fallbacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 20:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 16:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might as well ask is it a pain or enjoyable to work as a gay prostitute because that's what I feel like every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We Tested How Googlebot Crawls Javascript And Heres What We Learned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 16:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 16:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what would be the number one reason to ditch Windows? 

Fashion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 16:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We find it incredibly hard to find good front end developers

What are you paying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 15:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I'd be less ambitious](http://www.tenthousanddollarhomepage.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 15:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's no moon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 15:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I make them spin on a mouseover in dev/stage environments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 03:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [APMEX as the 2013 for $90](http://www.apmex.com/product/82228/2013-australia-1-oz-silver-kookaburra-proof-high-relief), [Silvertowne has the 2014 for $50](http://www.silvertowne.com/p-23961-2014-p-australia-silver-kookaburra-1oz-high-relief-proof.aspx).  The 2015 might be more desirable in the future as it's the 25th anniversary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2015 1oz proof high relief Kookaburra </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 02:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Talisman has it for $70](http://talismancoins.com/products/70449).

[Perth Mint has it for $75](http://www.perthmint.com.au/catalogue/25th-anniversary-australian-kookaburra-2015-1oz-and-silver-proof-high-relief-coin.aspx).

Mintage of 8,000 (in single packaging).

What does the peanut gallery think of this one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 01:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ping him and have him come here for an AMA.  Here's a start:

* Legally, are all the tiny houses classified as ADUs on the property? 
* What did the property prep work (water/electricity) cost?
* It doesn't look like anyone is using solar?
* What about sewer?

I'm also in Portland and want to do the same thing but without the immediate neighbors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upcoming Material Design CSS library  a Twitter Bootstrap killer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 17:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AudioDrop - drag and drop and decode audio files </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 17:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25+ Free JQuery Plugins For Doing Guided Tours Through A Website </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 16:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> justice.js - a performance metric bar with a streaming FPS graph </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 16:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 16:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm more a [Hardcore Pawn](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=buSx1kaCA_k) kind of guy. BTW, that guy is how I view all of you nutters here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 16:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could run a grinder over a tube of ASEs and sell to you. I would do each coin separately, not grind down the coins in the tube, that would be ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Portland Tiny House Community (5 minute video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 16:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 16:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is great. I want to do the same thing but without the immediate neighbors.

Legally, are all the tiny houses classified as ADUs on the property?  What did the property prep work (water/electricity) cost?

It doesn't look like anyone is using solar?  What about sewer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 16:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be thankful it isn't struts. I still wake up crying from that steaming pile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Centuries-Old Shipwreck Chock-Full Of Gold Found Off Finnish Coast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 18:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 15:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When your wife spits out a couple kids, you won't be laughing so much at a size 9 vagina. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 15:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is certainly nothing out of the ordinary for Colorado. What elevation are you at? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 19:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much $ can you make a month on youtube with 167k subscribers and video views from the tens of thousands to I see one with 1.58 million views.

Also, where are the Britny Fox guitar covers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 19:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scary part is, I not terribly long ago ordered a tube of ASEs from them on a deal but I don't remember whether I had to sign or not.  From my experience, it seems most vendors have a $500 threshold for signatures but I've really only started buying from vendors on ebay since the beginning of the year (I'm not a big ebayer). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 19:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 17:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know if you need a $500 order to get signature delivery via MCM ebay store?  I don't want to buy 2 bars to have them sit in my mailbox on the street.  I'd like to get two, but I'd pony up for another to have these held at the post office for me to come pick up.

Don't see mention of signature delivery or carrier, though I've done a MCM ebay before and they came USPS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 17:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted a gold deal thread from them last night, too, but [mine is showing up](http://www.reddit.com/r/Silverbugs/comments/35cchf/some_apmex_1oz_gold_deals_on_da_bay/) (membership has its privileges).

Also, MCM has a [1oz pamp gold bar for $1207](http://www.ebay.com/itm/PAMP-Suisse-1-Troy-Oz-9999-Gold-Bar-Fortuna-w-VeriScan-Assay-Cert-SKU27398-/141275762445?pt=LH_DefaultDomain_0 hash=item20e4b10f0d)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some APMEX 1oz gold deals on da bay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 01:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[1 oz Gold South African Krugerrand BU Random Year](http://www.ebay.com/itm/SPECIAL-PRICE-1-oz-Gold-South-African-Krugerrand-BU-Random-Year-SKU-85815-/141486260358?pt=LH_DefaultDomain_0 hash=item20f13d0086)**

* $20 over spot @ $1210


**[1 oz Gold Canadian Maple Leaf Brilliant Uncirculated](http://www.ebay.com/itm/2015-1-oz-Gold-Canadian-Maple-Leaf-Brilliant-Uncirculated-SKU-87114-/111559013753?pt=LH_DefaultDomain_0 hash=item19f96f7579)**

* $22 over spot @ $1,212


**[Austrian 100 Corona Gold Coin - Random Year Brilliant Uncirculated](http://www.ebay.com/itm/Austrian-100-Corona-Gold-Coin-Random-Year-Brilliant-Uncirculated-SKU-157-/111117675438?pt=LH_DefaultDomain_0 hash=item19df212bae)**

* .9802 oz gold weight
* $1223

Would sure love to see some prices like these for BU AGE or Buffaloes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 00:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The veldt gold piece in the top right is obviously a fake round. Take a look at the drop shadow, it shouldn't be uniform when you can tell the light source is coming from the top right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> jquerymy.js - a lightweight jQuery plugin for complex two-way data binding in real time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 18:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 17:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your "product manager" is shit.

It's not all bad, most of the people I work with are nice, and I genuinely like them. How ever I feel like these commutation problems are setting me up for failure and are ultimately bad for my confidence and growth as a developer.

First of all, fuck most of the people you work with, your situation is bad, stop trying to sugar coat the environment. You need to be there for you and your career. The communication problem **is** setting you up for failure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 12 Gurus Got 5 Questions About How They Set Their Rate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 17:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think the early Friday morning MAX (west side - downtown) commute will be like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 00:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm way out west side, get on MAX at 6am and end up downtown around 6:50am. Do you guys think this will be smooth sailing tomorrow morning with Obama visiting Nike? Will the MAX be shut down tomorrow am at any point? He's reportedly leaving Portland around 11am so the ride home on the train should be fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 20:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JWTs (JSON Web Tokens) aren't cookies, they're tokens that are passed back/forth between client and server. You can use them (JWTs) to handle your authorization, what traditionally was done using cookies.

But maybe I'm confused as I'm honestly not that bright...I'm not sure what you mean by "there's a JWT cookie".  I've also only used JWT in one app to date, so I'm certainly no expert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iconate.js - transform your icons with trendy animations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 19:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 19:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about using JWTs? To kill the associated session, just kill the JWT in localstorage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 19:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honest question...Why are you making a youtube video instead of talking to a lawyer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coding boot camps didnt exist four years ago. Now 80 of them pull in $59 million a year, mostly from college grads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 18:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Im an Imposter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 16:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iframe's "sandbox" attribute restricts allowed actions for iframed content. 72% of the Alexa top 5000 sites have on average 7 iframes on their landing pages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 16:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hayek - a new cryptocurrency backed by gold </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 21:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silver Mine Supply Is Running Out of Steam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 20:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sass Pixel Art </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 19:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The demise of Boneyard Studios, a tiny house community </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 18:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Infinite Jukebox - for when your favorite song just isn't long enough. Pretty interesting, some jumps on a mp3 I uploaded are very good others not so much... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 18:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kent Dodds live codes an application using the pre-release alpha version of Angular 2 (1 hour video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 17:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 16:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably because the image can't zoom to anything useful in that case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AppML  JavaScript Framework by w3schools.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 16:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AppML  JavaScript Framework by w3schools.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 16:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> zoom.js - Medium's Image Zoom for jQuery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 16:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 04:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last night, I dreamed I was a cowboy kinda guy and in third person I did some cowboy kinda things. I had to destroy some houses and then I had a final objective to destroy a statue. After that I would be rich so I went to statue and it was a statue of my wife. Then I woke up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> json-server - get a full fake REST API with zero coding in less than 30 seconds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 00:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 23:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're most likely going to get a lot of CS-type questions for any engineering position at Google. A LOT of front-end folks these days are the traditional CS types (what we think of the traditional back-end guys). Front-end is the new hotness, especially with the major shift in JavaScript development. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 23:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked with a guy at Yahoo back in 2008 that went to Google as a front-end developer so I wouldn't say Google  "is still new to that area of hiring". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should use angular where you can just wrap your elements within the pop directive. It's nifty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 16:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Gumby](http://gumbyframework.com/) is worth a look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flight - an event-driven web framework, from Twitter. Component-based JS framework that maps behavior to DOM nodes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 00:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 21:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jade Helm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 21:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about some examples that have a lot of data? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 21:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't claim to create the codepen, I just posted it to share. Am I supposed to be aware of every post that is made? Your retardation, imo is unacceptable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CSS octopus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 21:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 21:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And throwing down the pieces of silver into the shopping cart, he departed, and he went and hanged himself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Logo Experiments - demonstrate every possible way to draw a logo with modern front-end techniques </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 19:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ScrollJacking is InterfaceJacking - it's not OK to change scroll dynamics the same way it's not OK to change mouse dynamics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 17:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sally is the leanest, meanest Flexbox grid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 16:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 16:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * JB Weld those two back-to-back
* Sell as "ultra rare 20 oz NTR prototype bar"
* ???
* Profit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 16:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure the framework I've been waiting for will come out next week. That will be supplanted by the real framework I've been waiting for the following week. Which in  turn will be replaced by the framework I've been waiting for the following week. Rinse 'n repeat... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 16:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If all you need is two-way data binding, go with knockout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 16:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a build process or are you doing this manually? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 04:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christ, you didn't even separate out and individually stack your 90%. How can I take this seriously? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These Three Developments Say New Mine Supply Is Peaking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 00:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 16:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you recently single? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silver reached a 30 year high in April of 2011. Since then it has fallen nearly 70%. But how do we obtain more objective information? Use Ratios! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 02:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> APMEX has 1 oz Gold American Eagle Coin Random Year for $1,221 ($42 over spot) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 01:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ebay # [141504369404](http://www.ebay.com/itm/SPECIAL-PRICE-1-oz-Gold-American-Eagle-Coin-Random-Year-SKU-84672/141504369404?pt=LH_DefaultDomain_0 hash=item20f25152fc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 21:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I go kayaking, I always think Indians are going to appear on both banks at some point and start shooting arrows at me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting take, I suppose, though I can't say I'm with him.  What do you guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Java FX Will Outlive Most Of The JavaScript / CSS Frameworks (5 minute video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3D Folding Panel - a secondary content panel that folds flat, powered by CSS Transformations and jQuery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 17:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 16:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should include error/validation cases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> APMEX has 1 oz Gold Canadian Maple Leaf for $1,202 ($16 over spot) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 02:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ebay # [111559013753](http://www.ebay.com/itm/SPECIAL-PRICE-2015-1-oz-Gold-Canadian-Maple-Leaf-Brilliant-Uncirculated/111559013753?pt=LH_DefaultDomain_0 hash=item19f96f7579)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 02:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at their ebay listings, they have a  [1oz Perth Mint gold bar for $1,194, $10 over spot](http://www.ebay.com/itm/1-oz-Gold-Bar-Perth-Mint-99-99-Fine-in-Assay/371274281202?pt=LH_DefaultDomain_0 hash=item5671abf0f2) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL *nobody* has a job in 1 out of 5 American families </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 02:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 02:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Take it from someone with no mortgage. If you're not paying extra every month on your mortgage, make that so #1. Get it paid off ASAP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 02:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long does it take to melt those bars with that MAP?  Do you have any videos of the entire process? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 23:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *As far as a ship date, Green mentioned that the first production Angular 2.0 app at Google will ship in May 2015. While Green gave no release date, it provides a glimpse at the timeline.*

[At bottom of page](http://www.infoq.com/news/2015/03/angular-2-concerns-addressed). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 23:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mental note to self: name next project NachosBellGrande.js </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 21:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mental note to self: name next project nacho.js </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> manifold.js - the simplest way to create hosted apps across platforms and devices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 21:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 21:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised no one has brought forward the idea that perhaps JPM is simply planning on offering a free set of silverware with opening a new checking account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 21:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you know he's not pulling a Ric Flair and going "WOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!!!!!!!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 19:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related MSDN blog article: [Why we made vorlon.js and how to use it to debug your JavaScript remotely](http://blogs.msdn.com/b/eternalcoding/archive/2015/04/30/why-we-made-vorlon-js-and-how-to-use-it-to-debug-your-javascript-remotely.aspx). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vorlon.JS - open source, extensible, platform-agnostic tool for remotely debugging and testing your JavaScript </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 19:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 18:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At what point does throwback = just plain design laziness? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 16:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     script language=javascript
    !--- 
    var Yoname=prompt("Enter your name or I'll be forced to call Netscrape users Nul and Internet Exploiter users nothing at all","");
    // unhide ---
    /script
    script language=JavaScript
    !--- 
    document.write("centerh1Hello" + " ")
    document.write(Yoname + "...");
    document.write("centerh1Welcome to my Page!" + " ")
    document.write("/h1/center")
    document.write("pbrph3Reload this page./h3")
    //end of script unhide ---
    /script </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 16:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If by jquery you mean javascript, I agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 02:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr. Wilson is epic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 00:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can be read by screenreaders, though it's not guaranteed.  ARIA attributes have varying level of support across various screenreaders (just like web browsers). 

If you've never used a screenreader before, this is likely all crazy talk to you. If you're inquiring about ARIA, however, you should spend some time to actually install and use some popular screenreaders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 23:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like how my career is going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 23:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It provides more info to the user. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fed's Soft Economic Outlook Rules Out June Rate Hike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 23:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 23:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use it when you want to establish a **relationship** between elements/widgets and text that describes them.

Note how the value of the aria-describedby attribute matches the corresponding id attribute which provides a description/more info to the user:

    button aria-label="Close" aria-describedby="descriptionClose"X/button

    div id="descriptionClose"
        Closing this window will discard any information entered and return you back to the main page
    /div </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mouse Cursor Motion Blur Effect </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 22:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ramjet.js - morph DOM elements into each other </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 18:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 18:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Piggybacking on this...Grunt and Gulp do the same thing, just in different ways.  I don't think it matters which one you go with (it's personal preference), it's more important to have a build/automation process going.

You should checkout Yeoman, it's a great gateway to updating your workflow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 17:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I run reddit, AMA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 16:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Anonymous Activist Gets Potholes Fixed By Drawing Giant Penises Around Them](http://m.fastcompany.com/3045488/slicker-city/anonymous-activist-gets-potholes-fixed-by-drawing-giant-penises-around-them) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the US Homeownership Rate Is Now the Lowest Since 1989 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 16:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 16:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a leap of faith, but I've had two good transactions over there (this was pre-bot).  I don't spend much time over there but I cruise it every once and awhile to see what folks are selling. Investigate their user/posting history and go with whatever vibe you get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL it's official: being poor makes people unhappy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 03:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 23:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the heads up, just put in a telecommute request! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 23:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look on the bright side...You have to maintain it now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 21:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The legalities of living in a tiny home are the biggest issue, IMO.  Fuck what people think of how you want to live your life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 20:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I for one am glad to see private property put to the desired use of the private owner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The gory and grotesque art of Soviet antireligious propaganda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 16:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 16:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if silver files a Chapter 11 bankruptcy, hoping to reorganize its finances, instead of a Chapter 7 liquidation bankruptcy, it typically must cancel and eliminate its original silver, making that silver worthless. Should silver successfully reorganize and become financially sound, it will usually issue new silver, leaving former stackers with worthless silver. If former stackers believe silver will now succeed, they must buy some of the new post-bankruptcy silver should they want to continue their investment.

This should be stickied and become required reading here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barrick Gold Reports Q1 Profit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 05:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.kitco.com/news/2015-04-27/Barrick-Gold-Reports-Q1-Profit.html

*The company produced 1.39 million ounces of gold during the first quarter, at all-in sustaining costs (AISC) of $927 per ounce.*

*Barrick said they expected costs to be 20 percent lower in the second half of the year, with full-year AISC in line with guidance of $860-$895 per ounce.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The $200 million coin collection with a face value of $969.14 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 03:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 00:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read it online in an URGENT ECONOMIC COLLAPSE bulletin. Who would make something up like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 00:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most likely due to the price of oil being cut in half in 6 months. Also Apple hitting new highs and buying 1/3 of the world's gold for their watch. Also Grexit and Ukraine. And JP Morgan disallowing cash in their safe deposit boxes. + Shemitah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 23:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't wait for the follow-up list to relearn/master angular 2.0. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10 Fresh Gorgeous Fonts That are Free to Download </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 23:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FourD.js - a dynamic graph visualization library </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 23:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 21:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are lots of "experts" out there who advise against drinking like I do, but that isn't really working out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ultimate guide for building truly responsive logos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 21:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you interviewing more than 3x at a company? That's complete horseshit. What does the 3rd, 4th and 5th interview tell them the first and second interview doesn't? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do developers love Angular? #1 answer won't exist in Angular 2. #2 answer is the source of most performance issues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made it to many 3rd, 4th, and 5th round interviews

Wat?

what would be a reasonable amount of time for me to stay in my current position?

When you have nothing left to learn there that makes you more marketable elsewhere, leave. Building/maintaining shit that doesn't matter for your employer is secondary, your primary job is to make yourself more valuable somewhere else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone on my local craigslist was trying to sell two 100 oz bullshead/hallmark for MONTHS. They're really neat bars but they were asking too much. APMEX had them cheaper (they still have one at $1830). The seller on craigslist was $100 more than APMEX (per bar). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AnimateTransition - transition animations between blocks (pages) in a web site/app </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 18:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some CSS you may not know </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 16:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mosaic Mage - create unique mosaics from your favorite photos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 16:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 16:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Designer here - how do I learn how to electrical engineer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 21:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the MCM ebay listing @ $370](http://www.ebay.com/itm/141510997698?_trksid=p2057872.m2749.l2649 ssPageName=STRK%3AMEBIDX%3AIT) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 20:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the auction @ $343 a tube](http://www.ebay.com/itm/Special-Price-2015-American-Buffalo-Tube-of-20-1oz-Fine-Silver-by-SilverTowne-/301335158202?pt=LH_DefaultDomain_0 hash=item4628f99dba) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 17:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://seekingalpha.com/article/3102776-why-is-jpmorgan-accumulating-the-biggest-stockpile-of-physical-silver-in-history </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Provident has 1oz Silver Britannia @ $2.29 over ($18.08) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 06:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
