<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8603</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 05:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me its circle, circle, circle, circle, circle, circle, R1, L2, L1, triangle, circle, triangle. Spawned tanks until I crashed my PS2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 09:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah! Surprised I haven't seen this video yet. Here's the album. 

http://suicidegirls.com/albums/site/13576/gallery/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 08:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About a mile/20 minute walk from the hotel, but midtown is packed with bars. You have Waterworks, Spaceport, Wine Loft, Mockingbird, Leon Pub, Midtown Filling Station, and Finnegan's Wake, all within a tiny radius of each other. 
There is also a neat speakeasy in the area. You'll probably want to call ahead with a reservation and the drinks are pretty pricy, but its a cool experience. http://www.alchemymidtown.com/ Also Level 8 in Hotel Duval, and Midtown Station a little up Monroe are also there. But if you have the time, definitely take check out Fermentation Lounge. It's a really nice place to have a drink with some friends and make new ones. I now realize I look like a drunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-31 16:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sound of buzzing when they released the confetti made me think they just unleashed a horde of bees into the stadium.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 19:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just passed this 2 days ago and was sad that I missed the picture. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 01:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeaaaaaah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 03:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer the Sprite/blue Powerade mix to be more accessible, especially in a restaurant since they're both coke products and can be easily combined in any restaurant with a Coca Cola fountain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-20 06:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friend: "Happy Birthday, man!"

Me: "Thanks! You too! Fuck..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-18 01:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop by. You can tour the facilities and ask them some questions. Checked it out last year during the reddit meet up and will probably join when I move to Jax in a couple months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 06:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "...the last shall be first, and the first, last." Matthew 20:16 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-01 02:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Wasn't aware of their existence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-01 02:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't find a good way to get to someone who would know anything through the phone number.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Places to find wine crates? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 23:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any places in town where one can acquire a wine crate outside of getting lucky at a thrift store? Preferably for little to no money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-23 02:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just go to Walmart and ask for banana boxes. They have handles and are pretty great for moving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-23 02:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the video that makes me unsubscribe from this subreddit for good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 03:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of the music video for [Big Bad Wolf by Duck Sauce](http://youtu.be/VGRQGm4-A4k) (NSFW) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 09:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount of detail in the Aquaman's costume was absolutely stunning. [Here](http://i.imgur.com/dabJ1Yk.jpg)'s a high rez picture I took of him at Megacon. I believe he said it took him about a years work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 22:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't realize there was more than the one bathroom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 15:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly thought this was a post in /r/shorthairedhotties for more than a few seconds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 09:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its...its been so long. Congratulations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 01:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had far too many reasons to post this video. [(NSFW)](http://youtu.be/oolu-k3tY-g?t=38s)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 04:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video](http://youtu.be/Tq3PMhgqXsk?t=16s) of them in action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 07:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Horse Steppin' - Sun Araw from the Hotline Miami soundtrack is pretty great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 02:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick vector of Dexter. I'll get around to Dee Dee in a bit. http://i.imgur.com/M1GFcRD.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-17 01:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also if you have any Asian grocery stores in your area, they're pretty likely to have it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
