<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4034</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Isis being funded by methamphetamine sales? No... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 16:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens when you put a werewolf on the moon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 19:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's a new publisher, launched yesterday, dedicated to putting out books about the Jewish American Experience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 19:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's a new publisher focused on launching books about the Jewish American Experience. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 19:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who's 'that guy' in your office and what does he/she do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 14:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 02:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the yellowcake output of your mine? Where is it used/sold? I take it that this is still a growing industry as there are about two dozen nuclear plants slated for construction in the next decade worldwide. Any thoughts on nuclear energy as opposed to oil   gas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 22:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nabokov's wife pulled Lolita out of the trash after he tried to burn his first draft. Guess we know who won the wife contest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 22:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, those aren't books? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's a list of books I recently read. Which one is your favorite? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 22:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A random selection of books I recently read. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 22:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A random selection of books I've recently read. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 22:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 22:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fillory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 02:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snape killed Dumbledore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 18:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened to me once after an brutal car wars game. $125 seat cleaning bill delivered in all dimes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As someone who doesn't read a lot of comics, what is the significance of Marvel's push for diversification? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 14:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Female Thor, Mrs. Marvel, black Captain America, Miles Morales as Spider Man. Just curious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that this year The Library of America published their 250th volume. Here's a list of all of them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 01:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that 2014 is the year the Library of America published its 250th volume. Here's a list of all of them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 22:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 16:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would start with Drown, his first collection of short stories. His second book is a novel called The Brief Wondrous Life of Oscar Wao. This won a Pulitzer for fiction, but is usually the least liked of his books. I loved it, but I would read Drown first. Finally, This is How You Lose Her is his second collection of short stories and was released last year. He's apparently working on a Dominican Apocalypse story now, which will be amazing. If you Google him you can probably find a number of his stories online. He publishes in The New Yorker every couple of years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 15:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Junot Diaz will cure that for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 04:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go home, you're drunk. That's how we say it in the biz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 04:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what got me too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 04:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not fucker, but he definitely had his moments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 04:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
