<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8210</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas man arrested with 42 pounds of marijuana on I-40 East </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 12:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas man arrested with 42 pounds of marijuana on I-40 East </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 12:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 12:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This actually needed to go to the state supreme court? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Florida man hears daughters voice for first time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 12:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Florida man hears daughters voice for first time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 12:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress Could Strip Samuel Adams Of Its Craft Beer Crown; Senator Ron Wyden, a Democrat from Oregon, proposed the new Craft Beverage Modernization and Tax Reform Act </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 02:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress Could Strip Samuel Adams Of Its Craft Beer Crown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 02:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World's first commercial jetpack set for 2016 launch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 21:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peyton Manning sends letter, autographed photo for late fan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they have personal insecurities they don't know how to deal with so they lash out at others to make themselves feel better about themselves.  That and they have low self esteem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this CEO of reddit effectively calling all 150000+ users of FPH "idiots from that toxic shithole" ?

Her and many others.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 17:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, if it is shown in court he is real and has potential to cause harm to property.

So what you're saying is that we don't really know if this guy is legit or has the potential to cause harm to property?  

And are you also saying that a seller should be required to tell a potential buyer about **possible** things that could happen to the property from outside forces?  Give me a break pal, you're grasping at straws at this point.

First you say it's required for the people to report it to a buyer but you can't support that with factual evidence.  Second, you want to fall back on 'the courts have made exceptions before,' which still doesn't show how this would have been required.  Third, you're not even reading what the hell they mean when they use the terms "material" and "property" but instead think your own personal opinion on what it should mean is the true definition. Fourth, you think people should be required to report things that **MIGHT** happen to the property in the future from outside forces?  Really?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 16:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Materials can be any relevant information that can be deemed hazaroudous to a potential buyer.

About the house and property.  You have yet to show how this person is an actual, physical, legal component of the house and/or property.

Murder/suicides are not relevant

Ones that occurred in the actual house/property apparently were.  Lightning has the capacity to cause damage to the house.  Should the seller be required to tell the buyer that too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lego puts big bucks behind push to go green </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 16:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 16:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> material facts or who hide information about their property

Exactly.  **Material** facts about the **property**.  He is not part of the property.  The house and land is the property.

Hell, NJ courts decided that even previous murders/suicides in the house don't need to be disclosed.  UNLESS the potential buyers specifically ask about it.  In which case the seller would then need to disclose it.

Here's the [NJ Seller's Disclosure Agreement](http://www.marybajwa.com/IS2/Data/AgentSites/64976/property%20disclosure.pdf). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 15:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he can affect potential resale of the property... thats enough

Possibly.  However he does not fall under the requirement of needing to be disclosed.  Unless the buyers specifically asked about a problem that he would fall under, the sellers were not required to tell them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 15:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the former owners daughter is afraid of a ghost in the house, and its anything from a squeaky floorboard to literally nothing, 

The squeaky floorboard is the only thing that would need to be disclosed as it's an actual defect to the property.  "Hauntings", past murders in the house, or past suicides in the house are not disclosure requirements in NJ unless the potential buyer asks about it.

the realtor is required by law to disclose.

And what New Jersey law requires them to disclose an annoying person who is not part of the property?  Hell, you're not required to disclose a murder or suicide that happened in a house in NJ unless the potential buyer specifically asks about it.

I'm pretty sure the only thing they actually can't disclose is the racial makeup of your neighborhood. 

Homeowners can disclose whatever they want.  There are certain things that they are required to disclose about the property and they are required to also disclose things that the buyers ask about.  That's it.

If the HOUSE is being harassed,you can bet that falls under duty to disclose.

Source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 15:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It requires disclosure.

No it doesn't.  Show me the law in New Jersey that requires this.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 03:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the same principle.  The chemicals in the soil at the house I would have just sold you are and actual part of the house/property that I am selling you.  The bozo is not a part of the house/property. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend's dog trying to catch a cookie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 02:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 02:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's along the lines of what I was thinking.  Anything pertaining to the property?  Yes, absolutely that needs to be disclosed.  The bozo isn't part of the property being sold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 02:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would imagine they are under no obligation to disclose that.  But that's just me.  Like you said, it's a gray area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 02:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are they suing for?  The previous owners were selling the house.  The buyers bought the house.  Are homeowners supposed to provide crime stats and profiles of all people in the neighborhood now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 02:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title incorrect by the media source based on the story.  Says they were *released* in Memphis but article says:

Not only is the agency setting the criminals free, **it's also not keeping track of their whereabouts.**

    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 02:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ban Ham! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 02:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Towns across the country have reported the appearance of KKK fliers **with bags of candy on residents lawns**

Skipping out on [the recruiting van](https://punditonline.files.wordpress.com/2008/04/free-candy-truck-1.jpg)?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama shuts down White House heckler: 'You're in my house!' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 00:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dog Bunker was a cute puppy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 00:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is Owen and Mzee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's sorry he got caught. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4 arrested in shooting death of disabled teen in South Los Angeles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 16:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 11:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it was reductive as shit.

Because the answer goes against your ideal you're talking about here.

You're trying to rip the carpet out from underneath that power structure, not kiss it's ass and hope it goes away. 

Burn buildings, ruin other people's livelihood, and vandalize.  Yeah.  Let me know how that works out for you.  You're only making the "power structure" stronger.

Racial inequality will go away

Good one.

when people stop compromising with it's enemies,

Actually that's how things get solved.  

not when they water themselves down to accommodate them. 

Who's saying to accommodate?  It's called working together.  

But hey, it's obvious your goal is merely to be a vandal and cause chaos that is not going to do anything except make people more pissed off at you.  Good luck with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 06:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You didn't read it very closely then. 

Still waiting for you to show me his **goal** was positive tension.

The man's legacy has been whitewashed. He might have been a pacifist, but he was also no pushover who went around demonizing rioters like so many conservative pundits keep assuming he did. You can go on google and find plenty of quotes from him (especially towards the end of his life) defending the actions of looters during the detroit riots or property destruction.

He was a christian and thought being non-violent was gods way. But that doesn't mean he lacked understanding.

I might add that MLK was far from some sort of holy prophet who's alter we must bow before. 

Yet, you want to quote MLK yourself.  Amazing how you dismiss something he said when it doesn't fit your ideals.

Nobody ever gained liberation by asking politely. Nobody. There is no dialogue, because at the end of the day the powerful have no reason to listen. The oppressed are not meant to grovel before their oppressors for freedom, because they won't get it. 

You didn't answer the question.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 06:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Porn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 06:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I check their reddit account to see if they like to rip off hot page posts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 06:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Letter From A Birmingham Jail. 

Yes.  I read it.  Show me the source where he says his goal was to create positive tension.

Since MLK Jr. has been brought up, what's your take on this quote by him?

*Now what I'm saying is this: I would like for all of us to believe in non-violence, but I'm here to say tonight that if every Negro in the United States turns against non-violence, I'm going to stand up as a lone voice and say, "This is the wrong way!"* 

Think about it for a second.  Who are you more likely to work with hand in hand to bring about change?

Person A: YOU make someone's life miserable.  YOU discriminate against them and make their life miserable.  You discriminate, etc, etc, etc.  They come up to you and let you know the issues you are causing and want to start a dialogue.

Person B: YOU make someone's life miserable.  YOU discriminate against them and make their life miserable.  You discriminate, etc, etc, etc.  They come up to your house and break windows, spray paint the house, etc etc etc.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Dog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Martin Luther King said his goal was to create "positive tension"

Source?  Additionally, pointless vandalism that does nothing but get people more angry/resistant to others does not bring about "positive" change.

Missed all the rallies, protests, marches, and **riots** this past year, did we? And that's just the public face, never mind what's going on behind the scenes. 

Rallies, protests, and marches would accomplish something.  Much like MLK Jr. did.  Riots?  See my comment above.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It shocks and appalls people

And just gets people more pissed off at the people doing it and resistant to wanting to do anything for said people.

There has not been a single movement in human history that hasn't been accompanied by the occasional act of vandalism.

Key word there being *accompanied*.  What else is accompanying the vandalism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Direct action fights oppression. 

Explain to me how spray-painting/vandalizing fights oppression and accomplishes anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 04:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really helping the cause I'm sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 03:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The question itself was born of allegations made by the **conservative author**

I'm shocked! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 03:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all lives matter

Why the hell would this piss anybody off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 03:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh good, now we get to have different classes of terrorism.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 03:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give the offended people a trophy.  They'll be OK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 02:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taste the rainbow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 02:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However, Owens says Republicans in Congress have made it virtually impossible for the IRS to revoke the tax-exempt status of political groups after the recent, so-called Tea Party scandal. Republicans criticized the IRS for what they said was inexcusable targeting of conservative 501(c)(4)s. And the Treasury Inspector General for Tax Administration said the agency had employed inappropriate criteria in scrutinizing some groups tax-exemption applications.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 02:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember the days of picking up a phone and actually talking to someone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Understanding Civil War history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 02:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 01:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's under the care of the police.  He complained of hunger.  Inmates are required to be fed while in detention.  

What's the issue?  It's not like they gave him Filet Mignon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 01:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this has what to do with the First Amendment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is the best, quickest way to get fired when you work at Google </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 00:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 00:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're still avoiding the question..........

But in response to your silliness up above, I'll direct you to my usage of "I," "me," and "I'd."   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 00:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Continual avoidance of the question only serves to answer it for you already.  You're answer is **no** but you don't want to actually state it because then you reveal yourself to be a hypocrite.

Oh... FYI, The SC Legislature just agreed to take up a debate on the subject of removing the Confederate Flag from the Statehouse grounds.

Yes.  I know.  That story has already been posted a few times now in /r/news and I already commented on it.  At the outset, I think it's a joke to have a vote to discuss something to then have another vote.  Just do it already.  However, this is a symbolic vote in my opinion and once things cool down after a few weeks, I don't believe it'll change.  It's the typical politician "kick the can down the road until people forget and we can move on" ploy that we see all the time as it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 00:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> California Gov. Jerry Brown signed legislation on Thursday prohibiting selling or displaying items bearing the Confederate flag.

Not sure if you purposely left out some essential information or not but in case you didn't:

Governor Jerry Brown signed legislation last year **prohibiting state agencies** from selling or displaying items bearing the flag

So where exactly is the First Amendment being encroached upon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 00:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to change the subject once again? 

No.  Asking you to respond to a question I've now asked three times.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 00:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The First Amendment (Amendment I) to the United States Constitution prohibits the making of any law respecting an establishment of religion, impeding the free exercise of religion, abridging the freedom of speech, infringing on the freedom of the press, interfering with the right to peaceably assemble or prohibiting the petitioning for a governmental redress of grievances.

Right.  And where exactly is any of this happening? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 00:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you going to answer the question I directly asked you twice already?

Here, in case you forgot.  

**Do you also support banning the U.S. flag? If no, why?** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 23:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I do not agree with banning the flag but you really need to read and understand what the First Amendment actually means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 22:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why imagine? Ask them. I would imagine that if it upset me that much, I'd move elsewhere to any of the other states in the country that don't have the flag and not stay there.

However, at least recently, when issues arise I see pictures and videos of black people burning not the Confederate flag, but the U.S. flag.  As I previously stated, the KKK flies the U.S. flag at rallies.  Such as [here](http://betanews.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/06/75967545_copjvo8a.jpg), [here](http://www.authentichistory.com/1921-1929/4-resistance/2-KKK/19250809_Klan_March_on_Washington_version3-Capitol_Steps.jpg), [here](http://www.rulen.com/kkk/kkkflag3.jpg), and [here in this flyer/poster/whatever it is.](http://pictures.ozy.com/pictures/450xany/8/7/9/70879_42-15780039.jpg).

And let's not forget our slave-owning forefathers as well.

Do you also support banning the U.S. flag?  If no, why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 21:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've considered the reality that this flag is all over the place and the solid majority don't go randomly shooting people because of it.  However, one person does it and it gets banned?  Really?  

Why not ban the U.S. flag while we're at it?  The KKK, who have hung blacks, typically wave the U.S. flag around.  Let's ban the Bible.  People who attack/bomb abortion clinics are doing it because of what they perceive the Bible to say.  

To blame this on a flag is outrageously simplistic and characteristic of those who don't want to work to figure out the real problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 20:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt the removal will happen.  All of this crap is going on right now because it's the shiny new object.  Give it a few weeks and everyone will forget about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 20:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would all this flag drama be going on if the shooting happened in a different state?  It amazes me that suddenly everyone gives a damn about..........a flag.  All this does is give that symbol more power than it had before.

Then again, this is the kind of crap this country does when things go wrong.  Focus on the non-issue and ignore the real issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 20:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find the government having to take a vote to discuss something before taking another vote more infuriating than a flag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House hostage policy shift announcement coming Wednesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 19:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House hostage policy shift announcement coming Wednesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 19:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anonymous Swears Revenge If Westboro Baptist Church Protests Charleston Shooting Victims' Funerals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And why is this news?

Probably the same reason you posted an article to /r/news about the [Attorney General meeting Gray's family](http://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/34z2zz/attorney_general_loretta_lynch_meets_freddie/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All defendants plead not guilty in Freddie Gray case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because all conversation in the comments MUST follow the topic of the title. There CANNOT be any side discussion. 

Yet you're getting spun up claiming that **I** derailed the topic.  Now you're defending it.  Make up your mind pal.

Two or three news stations running a story EQUALS the whole country being thoroughly informed.

Two or three news stations cancels out your claims that the media made no peep of it.  Additionally, if you think those few, to include the #1 circulated newspaper in the country were the only ones, you're deluding yourself.  As I previously stated, I grabbed the first five I saw on the first page of a Google search.

Anyone that had 5 Hour Energy in the last 5 years and never heard of this should feel quite betrayed, by the media, stores, and FDA;

Uh, yeah, OK.  Oversensitive much?

fuck off troll

What?  No facts to support your claims?  Eh, I guess when not only I, but you yourself show your claims to be B.S., I guess this is what you resort too.  Toodles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For fuck's sake all this time I've been talking about the crime not the indictments!!!

Then, when the title of an article states *Caffeine crime: 11 indicted in a massive 5-Hour Energy scam* with the indictments being the news of the story, you shouldn't start your first response with **"This** happened 3 years ago."

Yes I was talking about a topic, and you tried to derail it with misdirection talking about something totally different, the indictments.

Wait, so, you trying to talk about media conspiracy is **NOT** trying to derail a subject but talking about the indictments, which are the main point of the news article is?  Uh huh.  OH.  

You've added nothing to the conversation, just trolling. 

I've provided factual information.  You have yet to do so.

Yes there is a literal conspiracy if many TV media stations are sponsored by 5 Hour Energy and ignore news about it. 

I already asked for the proof of this.  Are you going to show it or not?  If not, well, we all know you're full of crap.

That is the definition of a conspiracy.

Proof?  Evidence?

Conspiracies happen all the time. 

Oh boy.  How many tin foil hats do you own?

Your attempt at using "conspiracy" as a derogatory label is laughable.

And you're only supporting it.

Yes, of 5 links, you linked one news paper's online page. The rest, as I said were garbage. I also graciously pointed out that Fortune covered it too. 

They're only garbage because you don't want them to be credible.  Why?  We'll get to that in a minute.  Graciously pointed out "Fortune?"  Fortune was cited in the article up above genius.  I guess you didn't read it.

You seem to be trying really hard to disprove something that isn't here. 

No, I didn't have to try hard at all.  I already disproved the below statements you made with the five links I provided and the Fortune article that this news source cites.  Oh, and you citing Fortune yourself just kills your own conspiracy topic.

Was the public notified? 

it is that the public never heard one peep from the media about this 3 years ago 

 5 hour energy sales would have tanked if the public knew

See?  The public was made aware.  Wasn't hard to shoot your theory out the window.

There is nothing here

Yes.  I know.  I've read your posts.

but you being confused and trolling.

Says the guy playing conspiracy and sadly trying to redirect the point of the article.

You are just a time waster. 

I sure am!  Come on back now ya hear! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 15:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

If a fruit cake contains alcohol, it could remain edible for many years. For example, a fruit cake baked in 1878 is kept as an heirloom by a family (Morgan L. Ford) in Tecumseh, Michigan. In 2003 it was sampled by Jay Leno on The Tonight Show. Wrapping the cake in alcohol-soaked linen before storing is one method of lengthening its shelf life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL A fruit cake baked in 1878 is kept as an heirloom by a family in Tecumseh, Michigan. In 2003 it was sampled by Jay Leno on The Tonight Show. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 15:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 14:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

Devils Tower (Lakota: Mat Thpila ("Bear Lodge") or Pteh  ("Brown Buffalo Horn") (Arapaho: Wox Niiinon [5]) is an igneous intrusion or laccolith in the Bear Lodge Mountains (part of the Black Hills) near Hulett and Sundance in Crook County, northeastern Wyoming, above the Belle Fourche River. It rises dramatically 1,267 feet (386 m) above the surrounding terrain and the summit is 5,114 feet (1,559 m) above sea level.

Devils Tower was the first declared United States National Monument, established on September 24, 1906, by President Theodore Roosevelt. The Monument's boundary encloses an area of 1,347 acres (545 ha).

In recent years, about 1% of the Monument's 400,000 annual visitors climbed Devils Tower, mostly using traditional climbing techniques.

The name Devil's Tower originated in 1875 during an expedition led by Col. Richard Irving Dodge when his interpreter misinterpreted the name to mean Bad God's Tower, which then became Devil's Tower. All information signs in that area use the name "Devils Tower", following a geographic naming standard whereby the apostrophe is eliminated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Devils Tower was the first declared U.S. National Monument, established by President Theodore Roosevelt. The name Devil's Tower originated in 1875 during an expedition by Col. Richard Dodge when his interpreter misinterpreted the name to mean Bad God's Tower, which then became Devil's Tower. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 14:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teacher, 32, accused of sexual encounter with student, 15 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 04:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teacher, 32, accused of sexual encounter with student, 15 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 04:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 00:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You say this just happened

Yes.  The **INDICTMENTS** just happened.  Or did you not bother reading both the title and article themselves?

but then you list 5 links proving it happened up until 2012

Please provide me the sections of each of those five articles that state the indictments happened in 2012.

You keep trying to misdirect the conversation into being **about the indictments**

You mean what the posted news article is about?

which I was never talking about

Then why participate at all?  Oh, yeah, media conspiracy......

Just say, "oh, I thought you were talking about the indictment, not the actual crime."

The article is about the indictments.  You trying to go elsewhere is just preaching conspiracy from your soapbox.  Additionally, anybody who reads your first post knows you weren't focused on the crime itself.  Again, conspiracy.

Half of your news sources are unheard of crap. 

Yet they remain in existence today meaning that people are paying for it.

One is a local news source.

Well, you've got two that include the 11th and 28th rated media markets in the country.  And two other sites that reported on it that, again, remain in existence today meaning people are reading it.

US Today is the other

USA Today, the country's most widely circulated newspaper.

Fortune covered it at the time too.

So you just identified a 6th one.

Just because a couple websites covered it doesn't mean the majority of TV news which is frequently sponsored by 5-Hour Energy didn't conveniently ignore it.

Can you provide proof that others "conveniently" ignored it?  I mean hell, one of the sources was a Fox affiliate.  The very organization that would probably be least likely to go against anything corporate.  Oh, then you had this gem:

The point is not and never was that the indictments happened 3 years ago, it is that the public never heard one peep from the media about this 3 years ago

Which you just invalidated yourself by identifying one source.  Nevermind the first five I grabbed from the first page of a Google search.

Keep drinking the conspiracy Kool-Aid!



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 23:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Done.

Sorry about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 22:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened 3 years ago

Title of article: *Caffeine crime: 11 indicted in a massive 5-Hour Energy scam*

Date of article: *19 June 2015*

Thus, the indictments did not happen three years ago.  They **JUST** happened.  

Corporate control of the media in action. 5 hour energy sales would have tanked if the public knew the market was flooded with dangerous counterfeit products.

You mean like:

[This](http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2012/11/20/5-hour-energy-counterfeit-operation/1718391/)

[This one too](http://www.mlive.com/business/detroit/index.ssf/2012/11/metro_detroit_based_5-hour_ene.html)

[Another one](http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/counterfeit-5-hour-energy-operation-shut-down-179989061.html)

[Lookie here!](http://www.naturalproductsinsider.com/news/2012/11/fake-5-hour-energy-shots-seized.aspx)

[And another](http://fox5sandiego.com/2012/11/20/5-hour-energy-makers-id-counterfeit-projects/)

So, yeah.  Learn to read and comprehend a title.  Additionally, do a simple Google search before you start yelling conspiracy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 21:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And when did the indictments happen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 21:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, no, that's not the point of the article.  You should run along to /r/conspiracy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 21:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you even read the title of the article?  You know, the main point?  Where it says "11 indicted" which is the point of the article?

This happened 3 years ago

Did the indictments happen three years ago?  No.  They didn't.  Thus, this **DID NOT** happen three years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 21:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't read the article did you?

Were the people indicted three years ago?  [I think not.](http://i.giphy.com/5aLrlDiJPMPFS.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 17:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

The Native American Party, renamed in 1855 as American Party, and commonly named Know Nothing movement, was an American political party that operated on a national basis during the mid-1850s. It promised to purify American politics by limiting or ending the influence of Irish Catholics and other immigrants, thus reflecting nativism and anti-Catholic sentiment. It was empowered by popular fears that the country was being overwhelmed by German and Irish Catholic immigrants, whom they saw as hostile to republican values and controlled by the Pope in Rome. Mainly active from 1854 to 1856, it strove to curb immigration and naturalization, but met with little success. Membership was limited to Protestant men. There were few prominent leaders, and the largely middle-class membership fragmented over the issue of slavery.The origin of the "Know Nothing" term was in the semi-secret organization of the party. When a member was asked about its activities, he was supposed to reply, "I know nothing." Outsiders called them "Know-Nothings", and the name stuck. In 1855, the Know-Nothings first entered politics under the American Party label. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The Native American Party, renamed in 1855 as the American Party, was commonly referred to as the Know Nothings. The origin of the "Know Nothing" term was in the semi-secret organization of the party. When a member was asked about its activities, he was supposed to reply, "I know nothing." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 17:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 16:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

The death of Jesse James became a national sensation. The Fords made no attempt to hide their role. Indeed, Robert Ford wired the governor to claim his reward. Crowds pressed into the little house in St. Joseph to see the dead bandit, even while the Ford brothers surrendered to the authorities but they were dismayed to find that they were charged with first degree murder. In the course of a single day, the Ford brothers were indicted, pleaded guilty, were sentenced to death by hanging and two hours later were granted a full pardon by Governor Crittenden.

The governor's quick pardon suggested he knew the brothers intended to kill James rather than capture him. The implication that the chief executive of Missouri conspired to kill a private citizen startled the public and added to James' notoriety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The two brothers who killed Jesse James, Charley and Robert Ford, surrendered to authorities and were charged with first degree murder. In the course of a single day, they were indicted, pleaded guilty, sentenced to death by hanging, and two hours later were granted a full pardon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 16:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 14:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

Tajiri first thought of Pokmon around 1989 or 1990, when the Game Boy was
first released. **The concept of the Pokmon universe, in both the video games
and the general fictional world of Pokmon, stems from the hobby of insect
collecting, a popular pastime which Pokmon executive director Satoshi Tajiri
enjoyed as a child.** Players of the games are designated as Pokmon Trainers,
and in the main series Pokmon games, these trainers have two general goals.
These are to complete the Pokdex by collecting all of the available Pokmon
species found in the fictional region where that game takes place; and to
train a team of powerful Pokmon from those they have caught to compete
against teams owned by other Trainers, and eventually win the fictional
Pokmon League. These themes of collecting, training, and battling are present
in almost every version of the Pokmon franchise, including the video games,
the anime and manga series, and the Pokmon Trading Card Game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The concept of the Pokmon universe, in both the video games and the general fictional world of Pokmon, stems from the hobby of insect collecting, a popular pastime which Pokmon executive director Satoshi Tajiri enjoyed as a child. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 14:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 14:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

How Carol's previous marriage ended (i.e. due to a death or divorce) is not
mentioned. Creator and Executive Producer Sherwood Schwartz had originally
intended for Carol to be a divorcee; however, ABC refused to allow the fate of
her first marriage to be revealed on the show. Sherwood Schwartz later wished
to use her divorce to his advantage, and wanted to use Carol's previous
husband as a mechanism to replace Robert Reed on the show should the show
enter its sixth season. The show was canceled before Schwartz could execute
his plan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Carol Bradys first marriage was originally intended to be a divorce, however ABC refused to allow the fate of her first marriage to be revealed on the show. Creator Sherwood Schwartz wanted to use Carol's previous husband to replace Robert Reed on the show if it entered a sixth season. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 14:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 14:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

For three months Curcio observed a Brinks armored car make its deliveries to
the Bank of America branch in Monroe, Washington, and he took notes of the
schedule and diagrammed locations of the banks cameras and the armored cars
blind spots. He also estimated how much money was being transferred to the
bank and how much was being removed via ATM machines.

When he considered police protocol in responding to robberies, the location
of the bank and their containment of roads he realized he needed a good
getaway plan. Thats when he decided on using the local river to escape.

After weeks of hand-dredging the river (Woods Creek) and a failed practice
attempt using a jet ski for the getaway, he changed his approach and created a
cable pulley system to quickly pull himself and large bags of cash, upstream
in the river using a connected canvas-wrapped inner tube.

Curcios planning culminated with an advertisement he placed on Craigslist a
few days before the robbery. The online ad sought 15 to 20 workers for a
fictitious city cleanup project, promising $28.50 an hour. The laborers were
told to wear jeans, a blue shirt, work shoes and a yellow safety vest. The ad
also told the applicants they needed to bring safety goggles and a painters
mask. The ad directed them to meet in the Bank of America parking lot at the
exact time Curcio planned to rob the armored car.

On Sept. 30, 2008, Curcio, dressed identically to his decoy applicants,
pretended to work the grounds near the bank. Wearing a blue shirt, jeans,
yellow safety vest, work boots and painters mask, he pepper-sprayed the
Brinks armored-car guard who was pushing a dolly loaded with money into the
bank. The pepper spray forced the guard to reach for his eyes and release the
cart that held the money. Curcio grabbed two bags of money, containing more
than $400,000, and ran toward the creek. Meanwhile, police arrived to find the
banks parking lot filled with men matching the robbers description.

At the waters edge, Curcio threw the money into the inner tube, and he
pulled himself down the creek with the cables he had previously strung. He
travelled about 200 yards downstream and exited the creek behind several
businesses on the opposite side of the highway as the bank.

Curcio removed his wig and construction outfit that had been attached by Velcro revealing
different attire underneath. He hopped in a getaway vehicle and left.

Curcios careful planning and unusual getaway gained national attention. The
timing of the robbery came just days after announcements of the governments
$700 billion bailout package that included Bank of America. The unique robbery
techniques created folk lore for the mysterious robber who was referred to as
"D.B. Tuber" after famed hijacker D.B. Cooper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Anthony Curcio put an ad on Craigslist for 15-20 similarly dressed workers for a fake cleanup project and to meet in a bank parking lot at the time he was to rob an armored truck. Curcio, dressed like the others, worked the grounds, pepper-sprayed the driver, and left with over $400,000. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 14:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saddam Hussein's tomb destroyed, but Babylon is safe as ISIS targets antiquity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 13:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taliban try to attack Afghan parliament, wounding dozens of civilians </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 13:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taliban try to attack Afghan parliament, wounding dozens of civilians </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 13:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Ted Cruz returns donations from head of group linked to Charleston gunman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 12:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pakistan heat wave claims at least 140 lives in Karachi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 03:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pakistan heat wave claims at least 140 lives in Karachi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 03:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pakistan heat wave claims at least 140 lives in Karachi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 03:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 02:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> per your title

Not my title.

Per /r/news rules:

Your post will likely be removed if it:

has a title not taken from the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Florida man arrested after advertising 'top shelf' pot on Craigslist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 02:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uber says no guns or no rides </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 01:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uber says no guns or no rides </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 01:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former White House chef missing for more than a week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 01:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 03:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you even read what happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 02:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strong comeback pal. You actually deleted your last post?  Awwww. Little keyboard cowboy lost some precious useless karma. It's ok. You can try again. Just keep being a hardcore gangsta via the Internet. It's truly serious business. 

EDIT:  Nevermind. You've been here for a few hours. So hardcore you had to create an alt account to hide behind. On the Internet. On reddit. Stay tough dude. You're scaring us all. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 00:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing like the hard core gangsta reddit keyboard cowboys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 23:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a badass behind the keyboard. Keep fighting the lame fight from the seat of your ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For Ted Cruz, The Hard Part Comes Next </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 16:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 16:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly.  One should never take things like that lightly.  

Additionally, if the guy wanted to commit suicide by cop, he could have easily done it without killing someone.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 15:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "innocent until proven guilty" should include not releasing names of the accused until they're found to be guilty

100% agree.  I'm not speaking to any one case in particular, but overall the media and people who read it need to calm down, take a step back, and wait for factual evidence to come out and not be baited by crazy speculation.  

He'll never have anything close to a normal life again,

In all seriousness, at this point I'll be surprised if he's still alive in 10 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 15:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha!  You know, you're probably right.  I didn't even think of it and obviously need to go pour another cup of coffee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 15:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely awful.  If the guy wanted to die, there is absolutely no reason to take someone out with you, just do it to yourself.

Then I saw this line in the article and I can't even imagine what road she's going to have to deal with mentally/emotionally.

At some point, Hummons' mother came out onto the street. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MLB Cancels More Than 60 Million All-Star Votes for Fear of Improper Voting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 14:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google bans revenge porn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 14:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cincinnati man calls 911 on self, kills responding officer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 14:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cincinnati man calls 911 on self, kills responding officer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 14:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 21:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, when you come onto /r/askreddit and post something that is just an awful title/question, what do you expect?

I hate this girl at school?

Really, are you asking everybody if you hate this girl at school? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 21:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their scams are shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 17:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for chiming in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 15:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually had no idea!  Thanks for the heads up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 14:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

When casting his first Star Wars film, producer George Lucas needed a tall actor who could fit the role of the hairy alien Chewbacca. He originally had in mind 6 feet 6 inches (1.98 m) bodybuilder David Prowse, but instead Prowse chose to play Darth Vader. This led Lucas on a search which turned up Mayhew, who says that all he had to do to be cast in the role of Chewbacca was stand up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL When casting his first Star Wars film, George Lucas needed a tall actor who could fit the role of Chewbacca. This led Lucas on a search which turned up Peter Mayhew, who says that all he had to do to be cast in the role of Chewbacca was stand up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 14:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stowaway found dead after falling from British Airways plane in London </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 13:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Husband of alleged prison break helper Joyce Mitchell feels betrayed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 12:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man charged with attempted murder of George Zimmerman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 12:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lake Los Angeles Woman Accused of Beating Boyfriend to Death With Canned Food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 12:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dozens indicted after three L.A. gangs unify under Mexican Mafia, feds allege </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 12:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 01:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When being a dick means being honest then yes I am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 23:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or in other words, you couldn't find pictures either.

You mean like that?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 23:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't look.  Why?  I've seen naked women before.  

In real life even.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 23:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care about reddit grammar nazis either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul to GOP: It's Time to Move Beyond the Second Amendment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 22:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Cruz Rips Fellow Republicans for 'Running' from Religious Freedom Fights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 22:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 22:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% agree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 22:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, I really don't get why it's a big deal anyway for someone to be naked.  Sure, a naked woman is awesome.  But we as a society (in the U.S. anyway) seem to make it more of a taboo to be naked, which is a natural thing anyway, than to see someone get their head blown apart on television.  Makes no sense to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 21:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point in time in his presidency, any topic this controversial is not going to get something finalized, especially with this congress.  I think he's being realistic in that regard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 21:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and leave alone what's hard, like mental health

Here's the issue though.  At what point do we recognize someone has a mental health disorder?  When they do something ridiculous and out of the ordinary?  The father buying the gun and giving it to his son as a gift would circumvent the mental health issue.  

With that said, I don't think we need to get ridiculous gun laws in place either.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 21:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That one extra mouse click is a killer isn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 21:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, people on here are lazy.  I provided what I found out today and a source to back it up which amazingly enough is Susanna Hoffs herself talking about it.  If people want more they can go find it.  I'll give the second guy up above credit in that he at least went looking.  The downvotes I could care less about and in this instance chalk it up to people being pissed that the link wasn't to a nude pic of Hoff.  I find that amusing and sad at the same time.

**EDIT**: Make it rain basement dwellers.  [Make it rain.](http://i.giphy.com/WvF34HXGADO4U.gif)

**EDIT #2**: [Keep 'em coming you oversensitive clowns.  Must've hit too close to home.](http://i.giphy.com/43VO4Sf0qq95m.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 21:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/todayilearned

/r/news 

/r/politics

And I've been starting to read a bit more on this subreddit and post once in awhile as of late. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 21:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> women

More than one is too many.  I personally stick with one.

With us being in a long distance relationship, I always look forward to seeing her again as we don't get to see each other too often.  First thing I do is just shoot her a text message in the morning so she has something when she wakes up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 20:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oil drips from my car sometimes.  I must be blessed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 20:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get why the selfie shot needed to be a part of this photo. Unless the person is part of the "bathroom in a pub owned by an elderly Lebanese man" and she just hangs out there of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 18:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the record, /u/The_CT_Kid and I are not the same person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> User posts to NSFW link in TIL, knows it contains NSFW images, can't fathom why it needs NSFW tag. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 18:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 17:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certainly a solid bot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 17:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then maybe they didn't take pictures.  Tough concept for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 17:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, you mean the link that the TIL already links to that is already a non-mobile link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 17:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

After the success of their first album, RunD.M.C. looked to branch out on their follow-up. The release of King of Rock in 1985 saw the group furthering their rap-rock fusion on songs like "Can You Rock It Like This" and the title track; while "Roots, Rap, Reggae" was one of the first rap/dancehall hybrids. The music video for the single "Rock Box" was the first ever rap video to air on MTV and received heavy rotation from the channel. The song was the group's most popular hit at that point and the album was certified platinum. RunD.M.C. performed at the legendary Live Aid benefit shortly after Rock Box was released. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL "Rock Box" by Run D.M.C. was the first rap video to premiere on MTV. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 17:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 17:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here](https://www.google.com/) you go.

EDIT: So many downvotes.  So many clowns lacking the balls to actually post an opinion.

**EDIT2**:  Do any of you morons think for yourselves?  Here, [this guy](http://i.giphy.com/PyXzMAbL17lsI.gif) actually has a pair.  Though possibly not functioning anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 16:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

In 2006, an unsactioned McDonald's Videogame was released online. It is parody of the business practices of the corporate giant, taking the guise of a tycoon style business simulation game. In the game, the player plays the role of a McDonald's CEO, choosing whether or not to use controversial practices like genetically altered cow feed, plowing over rainforests, and corrupting public officials. McDonald's issued a statement distancing itself from the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL In 2006, an unsactioned McDonald's Videogame was released as a parody of the companys business practices. In the game, the player is a McDonald's CEO, choosing whether or not to use practices like genetically altered cow feed, plowing over rainforests, and corrupting public officials. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 16:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Berkeley Balcony Collapse: 'Hero Jack saved Clodagh's life.. he helped break her fall' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 15:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 14:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your title isn't supported by the source.  It was called "Nothing" well before it was abandoned in 2005.

"Nothing was abandoned by May 2005" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 14:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

The Bangles released their third album Everything in 1988, with their biggest-selling single "Eternal Flame", which was co-written and sung by Hoffs. In the BBC programme "I'm in a Girl Group" Hoffs revealed she actually sang the studio recording of the song completely naked due to the producer Davitt Sigerson pranking her by telling her Olivia Newton John had done the same thing. He later told Hoffs he had been lying the whole time." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Susanna Hoffs of The Bangles sang the studio recording of Eternal Flame completely naked due to the producer pranking her by telling her Olivia Newton John had done the same thing. He later told Hoffs he had been lying the whole time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 14:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rep. Darrell Issa Escorted Out of Congressional Panel on Benghazi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 11:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Off-Duty New Jersey Police Officer Charged With Murdering Ex-Wife in Front of Daughter, 7 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 11:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 03:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my son needs this today

This right here would have me remove his bids and block him.  This just sounds like a sympathy ploy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 03:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A dog in a loving home.  Sleep, eat, play, and gets its belly rubbed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 03:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some context, that was Babe Ruth's first year in the bigs at 19 years old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 02:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha!  Wow. Did you go back again?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 14:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last one was from five months ago.  Doing a search on Sally Ride brings up a ton of posts about her being a lesbian but this actual subject twice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 14:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last one that pops up was from five months ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everest shifted 3 centimeters after Nepal quake -- but stays same height </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 14:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waterbury officials warn residents about water scam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 14:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 13:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

In 2011 Ben   Jerry's released a flavor named Schweddy Balls, in homage to the Saturday Night Live (SNL) skit of the same name. An American group named "One Million Moms" protested, saying that the name was too explicit for grocery store shelvesspokesperson Monica Cole explained to the media: "I realize it could be a lot worse, but are they going to progressively get worse if we don't say something? Maybe they'll think twice before they come up with another inappropriate name for ice cream." However, the expression of disdain was not unanimous among U.S. parents, as mother Gina Ragusa said to the Huffington Post: "We just think it's funny, that's all, and honestly we all really want to try it", adding that she consistently checks for the item's availability at her local supermarket. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL In 2011 Ben   Jerry's released a flavor named Schweddy Balls. A group called "One Million Moms" protested, saying the name was too explicit for grocery store shelves. However one mother said "We just think it's funny, that's all, and honestly we all really want to try it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 13:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 13:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

In 1985, after spending six weeks in California training for a bodybuilding contest, he was invited to join a group of bodybuilders  Garland Donoho, Mark Miller, and Steve Borden  to form a professional wrestling team. Warrior accepted the invitation and abandoned his bodybuilding career as well as his plans to become a chiropractor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL In 1985 the Ultimate Warrior aka James Hellwig accepted an invitation to form a professional wrestling team, abandoning his plans to become a chiropractor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 13:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feet no, crack/hole absolutely.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 23:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baltimore being a prime example.  Cops pull back and the city records the most murders in one weekend since the 70s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/Edseries209  everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 18:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No need, the thugs are already shooting each other anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Registered dietitian; Strategic Director of Dietitians For Professional Integrity

Biased much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 16:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

Souls, ghosts, and other "items whose existence cannot be verified" are prohibited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Souls, ghosts, and other "items whose existence cannot be verified" are prohibited from being sold on ebay. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 16:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
