<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4778</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 18:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, you guys are on your way, the states that have legalized marihuana make it possible to carry way more of it with you then in the Netherlands... only thing thats weird is that its illegal if you travel one state further xD But talking about xtc, yeah we're pretty cool here in this small country.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 15:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! I frequently visit festivals in the Netherlands and truth is that at least 50% of the visitors are using something other then alcohol... maybe even more. I think they realise that you can't prevent people from using because they will always find a way to get it inside, then the next best thing is to at least try to make it as safe as possible and give people the opportunity to test their drugs and give them as much information as possible while they're there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 14:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that you could test pills  at festivals in the Netherlands in the 90's, so you can make sure that you had clean pills. I can't understand why thats not a thing anymore, safety should be the number one priority, people are using it anyway... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 14:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, glad you found something that helped a little... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 14:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just hoping that the Netherlands are going to be the number 1 tolerant country we were once... Now pot is legal in a lot of countries/American states, we have to become the bitching country that legalises MDMA, hup holland! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worlds first mdma pop-up shop to open in Amsterdam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 11:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 00:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those stars on his head compensate it though, he now is 50% badass viking 50% emo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 22:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure you are an amazing role model President Dick Bob </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 21:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well 95% of the selection is not older then 22, so that could be a reason... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 16:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dutch has a few, Cheetah = Hunting Lazy Horse (Jachtluipaard), and a Manatee is called a Sea Cow (Zeekoe). Which is pretty accurate i guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 16:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of them are pretty similar to Dutch, never thought of it being that funny. But translated to English its pretty weird actually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 12:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You clever bastards, the tabloids in the UK are going to have a lot of fun with that name i guess...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 12:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well said! Lets hope the PL will push him to his limits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 12:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great transfer! Really hope he can reach that next level! He can be the next Cristiano Ronaldo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 00:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One day, i'm going to be a grandad, and i'm telling my kids about this "tv"-thing, and the 10 years of pure joy that i've seen Messi play on the thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 00:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing Johan Cruijff was brainstorming like this... here's how he took a penalty (this was allowed at the time): https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MJHN1mN5SCg

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 00:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First few seconds i thought it was a lioness... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 22:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its the "hanging out" part that i'm shocked about...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 18:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ... I'm so disappointed in myself that i immediately knew what you meant... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
