<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6303</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 03:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She says her name and hi but isn't that fantastic at pronunciation.  Sometimes it sounds like she is trying to say a word but I can't make it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 03:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will go up on Bunwear.spreadshirt.com in about a month and the profits will still benefit the rescue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our gcc gets really excited when my boyfriend gets home... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 03:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 00:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spoiled rotten! Just the way it should be. Cool design </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 00:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you finally get him litter trained?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only 5 Days left to get your bunny t-shirt and help with the Rabbit Haven's massive rescue! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 19:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 05:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It totally does!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 05:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She cracks us up daily. And I don't know that our mylar coated windows are beautiful - the sunflowers are nice though. Leela really enjoys hanging out on the patio.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 05:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah! Love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 05:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. We are Futurama fans in case you wondered :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 20:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a young GCC too - she has been doing a crazy dance with her head more and has gotten more nippy with strangers recently.

Are there other changes we should be aware of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leela Beela with a big ol' grin! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 19:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 20:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moar Rox Cutes https://imgur.com/a/oZ4IE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 19:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's his sad story if anyone wants the history of the king: http://www.therabbithaven.org/Rox_Appeal_020413.html 

(cuz those days are history! boo-yah!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 19:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy first Gotcha Day to Dr. Rockso Luther King Senior! That's Rox for short. Done being a medical foster, he arrived at our house as a foster on April 5. He stole our hearts and there was no way we were ever going to get him to an adoption show. We signed the papers a year ago today and never looked back. After attempting some bonding with Walter and Gwen, we got him his very own lovebun in September and he and Izzy are now inseparable. He has come a long way from the sad, abandoned, broken leg bun he was and we are thrilled to have had the chance to get to know him, thanks to The Rabbit Haven. Long live the king! The opinionated, grunty, loving little bun he is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Adoption Day to Dr. Rockso Luther King Senior </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 19:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 18:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loves being anywhere my bf is. S/he adores him (we don't know sex but named Leela so usually gets 'she')

Lucky for me she still enjoys my scritches and affections. Moreso when he is in sight. :-p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 23:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm renting so it isn't technically mine. 

Nor do I intend to have kids let alone grandkids.

Though I may get it a pot - it is pretty cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 23:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> California. I doubt it has ever been inside.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 22:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the woman who lived here before us was the landlords now deceased mother and she apparently did the yard. could be ancient.

It does look wild - kinda like a bonsai - stunted growth but old and gnarled. How big of a pot should I get? And should I really prune it?

I don't think the landlord would even know it was gone if I took it to the next house with me... 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 22:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no idea. the woman who lived here before us was the landlords now deceased mother and she apparently did the yard. could be ancient. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 04:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hanging basket was a gift and survived the winter... they perked right back up.

The thing (jade?) Bursting out of its pot was in the yard when I moved in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My succulents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 04:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 20:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... but is it organic? o.O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our birdie being sweet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 08:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 17:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know where you are located - but shelters keep rabbits in pretty small cages and often rely on volunteers to get them out and let them run around some.

And rescues can always use hands or fosters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 17:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hehehe - you have a pic of me in your album. Grats on winning one of the villas! Leith Petwerks donates so much every year - they are awesome. 

I was so happy it cooled off for the event this year. Out of curiosity - what are some of the things you thought were nicer? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 07:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She wasn't selling them and I don't know if she does or not. I don't even know her last name :-/ Commission someone who crochets/knits?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 01:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet you miss her. Our Leela is under 2 years old according to the vet (she is a rescue and we knew nothing about her - came in as a stray) so hopefully she will be sharing her adorableness with us for a long time to come! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 01:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! We keep her wings trimmed, but her flight feathers are blue and gorgeous when they are longer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 01:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes she wants me to get the camera out of her face. Other times she does something cute for me. 

I say she because we named her/him Leela Beela. We actually have no clue what the real sex is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 01:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks - I think she's pretty, but then I'm biased </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
