<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7011</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I keep hearing this and it wouldn't matter his age if Charles died and he's just impersonating him. The actor will be making an appearance in the 6A finale. It's been confirmed he will be "involved" in the episodes of the finale or close to the finale. Wren will not be. And those that theorize Cece is Charles assume Cece is transgendered and was once a man. The actor who plays Lucas himself stated that would be a great reveal, but he thinks the network would not approve something like that. So if it's not Cece, the other only real suspect to be A, it has to be Lucas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They thought Wren was A. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 10:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> woah so charlie pushed marion? woah nice!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 10:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.bustle.com/articles/86785-is-lucas-charles-dilaurentis-on-pretty-little-liars-that-anagram-may-hold-the-answer-to-the

http://tremolux.tumblr.com/post/112758824180/uber-a-whats-in-a-name

Though i think the person meant big a not uber a </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tell me about it. We shouldn't have to guess this hard! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 07:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was Wren then I said no because Marlene said we saw A in a black hoodie. I though Jason but then we never did see him in a black hoodie and he did look sincere when they revealed charles. I thought Ezra but then, he was there to rescue the girls. Toby was also unavailable because he was at the station. The only ones left are Lucas and Cece. They both were in black hoodies, they both had connections with Jason and they both were absent a lot but still in several episodes of pll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 07:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Wren is Charles if that were the case then. I don't really think someone could fake being a doctor and treat people all within the timespan of 2 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
