<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4544</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some of the saddest moments in your life? [Serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 04:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 03:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 9.87 McChickens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 22:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITT: BritianUS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 22:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Budapest by George Ezra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 23:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Avengers just for Scarlett Johansson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 22:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like he was planking you.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 05:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch the time go right out the window </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 16:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much the same thing as endless knowledge :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did you get your mother for Mothers Day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 16:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 16:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right! This is the only comment on this thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 05:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought of that Naruto Opening song </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 05:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That game is impossible. Cr1TiKaL (penguinz0) did a video on it a while back. I'm not sure if you have seen it but if you haven't you should definitely watch it. It's one of the most hilarious videos I've ever seen on youtube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 04:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! I'm sure your relationship will be longlasting! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 03:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Family included. Sorry buddy :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The last person you saw is now madly in love with you. How screwed are you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 03:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 04:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I AGREE WITH YOU SO MUCH!! I'm thinking.. why doesn't anyone at least attempt to help Dyrus? Obviously the "leaving Dyrus to die" strategy that somehow worked for them back in the NA LCS isn't working anymore. Santorin should at least go top once early on or try to set up a countergank, knowing that the enemy junglers will take advantage of Dyrus and try to gank him early on. Bjergsen can roam more as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 23:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 five me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 23:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That DBQ was god awful. Out of all topics why did they have to give us that one!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 04:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AHQ actually beat Fnatic!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 04:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> definitely. I don't even know how many times I've spelt it wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 04:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but blue balls are no joke dude :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 04:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AP Testing. Seriously, it's the only thing worse than SATs during your Junior year in high school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 04:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America would be able to put up a good fight but there is no way they can win. Lets say it's just Russia and China against the U.S, the U.S would probably still lose. Even though we have one of the most advanced military, that won't mean shit when you have the rest of the world against you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 17:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's horrible! It's surprising how much kids can change. I used to know a few kids back in elementary school who were the sweetest kids I've ever met, I'm not sure what happened but they became major douchebags and constantly got into trouble. However, the opposite is also true. I knew some kids who I considered "bullies" in elementary school who actually became some of my closest friends! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 17:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops that went over my head. I loved Ef but the last time I saw it was close to 3 years ago so I forgot a lot of stuff. All I remember was that I loved it at the time. The drama was pretty nice too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 16:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In ef: Tale of Memories, I think someone was staying in Australia. I forgot the character's name, it's been a while since I've last seen it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 16:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm planning on studying for the AP Psychology Test that I'll have to take tomorrow but I'll probably be spending most of my time on Hearthstone or League of Legends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 16:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you could become a super villain and try to take over the world... Just sayin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 22:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite how much schools stress the importance of reporting bullying, a lot of people still don't act on it. There was a kid in my gym class in high school, he was a little weird and he acted like a 5th grader even though we were in high school. Of course, everyone picked on him and even though I felt sorry for him, I didn't do anything to help him out. Obviously as a result of this, he became isolated from the rest of the kids. He was constantly writing in his notepad during gym class. Apparently one day another student read his notepad and it was filled with death threats and comments about how he wants to shoot up to school. The kid reported it to the teacher and he got expelled. It's a really unfortunate situation but I still feel bad for the kid. If everyone wasn't so mean to him, maybe he wouldn't have felt that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 22:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Semi-Charmed Life by Third Eye Blind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 22:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Occassionally when I'm bored I like to read up on profiles of serial killers. I, for some strange reason, find psychopaths or sociopaths fascinating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 22:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice try OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 22:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a waste of a watermelon :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 22:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP your inbox </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 21:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stuff like this doesn't happen where I live :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 03:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **GOOD GUYS, BAD GUYS AND EXPLOSIONS** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 03:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think so. I never made any moves on her and we got along like any normal friend would. Just the other day we were laughing, making jokes, playing video games with each other and within 12 hours she just completely ignores me. I still don't know what I did wrong and I don't want to cause a scene by asking her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 04:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand how woman can be so kind to you and within a day they do a 180 and start flipping out over everything. I used to have a female friend that I kinda had a crush on. She was nice to me and we shared a lot of common interests until one day she randomly, out of the blue, stopped talking to me. She would ignore me everytime I try to talk to her and I still don't know what I exactly did to her. Women are confusing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 23:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gay Marriage is a totally different issue. Incest you might be able to argue for but Polygamy is just plain wrong. Why would you want to have multiple wives or husbands? That's just being unfaithful and it goes against societal standards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 22:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Polygamy and Incest are just immoral and I'm sure that it's not going to be legalized in the U.S. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 22:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you mean Euthanasia or Physician Assisted Suicide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 22:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This wasn't really an embarrassing moment but I still cringe at the thought of it. I was biking to work a few summers ago and while going downhill I crashed into a wall and fractured my shoulder. I still remember the excruciating pain today even after the injury is gone. I think that could be said for a lot of painful injuries though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 05:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hearthstone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 05:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for posting this! As someone who has been in deep depression (and still in the midst of it), everything that you mentioned is true. There are times when I just feel worthless, guilty, and lonely. There are times when I want to just break down and cry. There are times when I just wanted to end it all, slowly vanish and disappear away from this world. However, despite all these challenges, it is posts like these that makes me feel better, knowing someone out there is there for me at the end of the day :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the creepiest website you've ever been on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 21:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 22:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New Jersey


Good: Nothing ever happens here


Bad: Nothing ever happens here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 22:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "lol you're bronze 5" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 21:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tastes like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 21:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A second season of Btoooom!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 05:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whose head </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 21:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love mussels!! How can you hate them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 05:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITT: *deleted* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What song is impossible to hate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 02:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 22:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've learned to ignore those who don't understand about my depression or anxiety. It was tough at first but you get used to it for a while.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Surgeons of Reddit, do you feel guilty if you weren't able to save a person's life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 22:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]What's your biggest regret that you have so far in life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 22:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
