<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9974</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Non-US Redditors; what is the traditional bar/public house/ tavern food in your country? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 21:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty self explanatory. What are the traditional drinking foods in your country? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 21:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am an avid hunter. I try to be a thoughtful eater. Many folks who criticize hunting partake in supermarket bought meat products farmed on industrial farms where the animals are treated horribly, pumped full of hormones, and killed. I prefer eating humanely raised meat, and hunting wild game when I can. It connects you to your food, and makes the consumption process a more mindful one. I also grew up on a small family farm. We slaughtered our own sheep, hogs, and beef cows. I appreciate the meat on my table, and respect the animal who gave it to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 19:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I sure as hell plan on making higher wages when I am 60 than I do now at 22. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 19:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The military. You will learn a trade, learn valuable leadership, professionalism, and stress management skills, and if you do 20 years can get a pension and job offers of 100k plus a year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 18:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trailer park kid who read too many books joined the Army to see the shitholes of the world and still reads too many books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 18:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good books, good friends, and activity.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 18:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use a Roth IRA. It takes my taxes out now, so that when I am older and ready to retire (and probably in a higher tax bracket) I won't have to pay taxes upon withdrawal.


Before you start investing though, you need to secure a savings account with approx. 6 months of emergency savings. Major debts first, Savings second, Investment third.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 18:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because our culture is more concerned about seeing a celebrity's tits than seeing the corruption in their government. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 18:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try your local VFW or American Legion. Those organizations are usually good at helping out with these kinds of details. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 18:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because most hospitals were affiliated with universities or religious groups when they were started. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 18:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa.. Weird, I know you.


Jash here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 05:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I am not defending them by any means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 04:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they don't commit terrorist acts. Not anymore. The KKK is surprisingly peaceful nowadays, despite their offensive beliefs. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 04:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 04:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, I also use goodreads on the side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 03:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. 

I have pretty high self confidence. I have never had a problem with anxiety. It's actually really hard to worry me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 03:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ummm... Hot. As. Hell.

Thats how I would feel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody else ever see some paranormal stuff on deployment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 21:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't really get talked about a lot, but I was just curious if anyone ever saw some paranormal shit while deployed. When I was in the 'Stan I had a few odd experiences but never talked to anyone about them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unintentional double entendres directed at a police officer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 20:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 20:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "No, no, no, this is not a suit made out of my mother's skin, it is a visible representation of my ability to get in touch with my feminine side." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 20:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep a book journal. I write the book name, author, ISBN #, and two paragraphs. The first paragraph is a summary of the book, the second is my reaction to the book.


I have found this has been a useful discipline that keeps me from passively reading. It gives me an avenue to mull over the book as a whole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2014 Corolla hit a large pothole, blew out right front tire and possibly bent control arm. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 16:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need some advice guys. I was driving my 2014 Corolla last night, and it was very dark as I prepared to pull onto the interstate ramp. There was a very deep pothole which I hit at about 35-40 mph and blew my right front tire out. When I removed the tire to replace it with my spare i noticed that the control arm appeared to be bent. On the drive home there were no real issues other than the car pulling noticably to the right. The rim appears to be undented on the old tire.


Can someone give me some advice before I get tge mechanics to look at it on monday? I am taking it to a dealership mechanic because I do not want to fuck up my warranty. What kinda wallet damage am I looking at? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 05:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is based on being a consistently good soldier, but that entails a lot of self development. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 03:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not anymore.

The only "stripes" that can be given at the unit level are those of Corporal, which is only an appointment not a promotion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 03:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An officer is a leader of soldiers a Warrant officer is a technical expert. 

For example, officers in my motorpool unit plan our field exercises, set the standards, oversee the administration of our company etc.


Warrant officers are technical subject matter experts in logistics, mechanical stuff, etc.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 02:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on which branch, and whether you are an Officer, Enlisted, or Warrant officer.

I can only speak to the Army's way of doing things because I am in the Army.

**Enlisted** 

E-1 to E-4 is automatic, based on time in service. If you don't fuck up (get a dui, drugs, punctual etc) you will get promoted.

E-5 to E-6 is points based. Each MOS (job) in the Army has a certain amount of points one needs to make E-5 or E-6. A soldier has to go to a promotion board, meet certain standards (attend NCO school, certain self development classes), and have the correct number of points (points are awarded for various things, awards, PT, how well you fire a weapon, civilian education etc.)

E-7 and above is board selected. Each MOS has a specific amount of allotted slots for each of these ranks. A board meets every year and looks over all the E-6's and aboves qualifications and determines whether to promote them to one of those slots.

**Officer**

O-1 to O-2 is a pretty much automatic promotion, based on time in service.

O-3 and above is based on board selection, similar to E-7 and above on the enlisted side.

**Warrant**

WO-1 to WO-2 is pretty much automatic based on time in grade/service. The rest are determined by board selection.

**Two closing thoughts**

1. You still have many chances in peacetime to win awards. Catching attention for hard work during a field exercice, winning Soldier/NCO of the month boards, all kinds of things.

2. We (the U.S.) are not at peace and probably never will be in our lifetime. There is always somewhere to deploy to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 00:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Southerner I always shake hands with folks I know at the store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 23:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just keep it up man. Running is all about practice. I am in the Army and we run all the damn time, so I have had lots of practice. But don't overdo it. Here is my personal running schedule for speed improvement.


**Mon**- 2-4 miles at a pace that hurts. (the 7 min mile for me right now)


**Wed**- Sprintd, 61-20's, suicides, and other sprint excercises for 45 mins. Followed by lengthy streching.


**Fri**- Run for 45 mins at a pace you can carry on a conversation in. This is all about building lung capacity, learning to pace yourself well, and correct your form. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 16:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! 

Do you know what the difference is between a Presbyterian and a Southern Baptist is?

Presbyterians shake each others hands in the liquor store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 16:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He never said he was suffering from depression. He said he fell into a pit of depression early on in his academic career.


For many folks the military would not be good if they suffered from real depression. If you are easily emotionally affected by the world around you, the military sure as hell is not for you.

Others suffer depression stemming from low self esteem and feelings of low worth. The military instills you with a high level of self confidence and puts you in places of high responsibility. Accomplishing your job well only increases your worth and self confidence. This could be just the challenge they need.


The military is not for everyone. It is a rough, stressful, mucky life that not everyone can handle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 15:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like most big Army programs. 


Handling things at the big Army level never works like they hope (SHARP, EO, etc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 15:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really funny, coming from someone who doesn't know how to use a definite article (**the** military not "military").


Just because you can graduate college does not mean you are smart. I am responsible for millions of dollars of equipment and the lives of my soldiers every single day. I am held to a higher standard than all of my civilian peers. I have real world skills and marketability, leadership skills, knowledge in my field (logistics), and more experience than all your degrees. 


Who is the dumbass? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 12:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ran my four mile in 28:25 yesterday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 12:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grandpa did. Things from Vietnam, awards from his time in Cargill, etc.


I have a tuffbox that I keep important things in. I have a flag that flew over our base in Afghanistan, military coins, framed pictures with a few famous folks I have met, a dummy round from an A-10 warthog that a JTAC gave me and a few other knick knacks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 11:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot speak to the specifics of your questions because I am in the U.S. Army. I am sure the British Army does things a little differently than we do. Your local Army recruiter would be the subject matter expert for your questions. Just because you sit down and have a conversation with them does not mean you have to join.


For me, I signed my papers and was in Basic training four months later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 11:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have a degree you should have no problem joining as an officer. I have a limited amount of knowledge on the subject because I am enlisted. I would recommend talking to an Army officer recruiter, they would have all the answers you need.


A lot of guys do enlist with degrees. You come in as an E-4 so pay will be better than your peers for the first two years or so until they catch up to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 02:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Join the military. 

I was in the same place. Failing out of college because I was a dumbass. Now I have a steady and fulfilling job, real world skills, and a future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 02:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You will be fine. Have fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 02:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With whipped cream on top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 22:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well now I can never eat American cheese. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 22:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have loved this Army. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 15:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Intentionally seek out ways he *does* provide around the house and shiw gratitude. Ask him for help (not busy work, but find legitimate requests) and let him feel that he is contributing while he looks for his next job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The teacher asked Jimmy, "Why is your cat at school today Jimmy?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 03:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jimmy replied crying, "Because I heard my daddy tell my mommy, 'I am going to eat that p*ssy once Jimmy leaves for school today!'" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 03:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Lemme start this joke with a question nobody would ever ask." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 03:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, just call the police and tell them you are a weak body. They will book you overnight.


I hope you come face to face with a salty ass first sergeant with this story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 02:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he murdered Miss Piggy in her sleep and fried her up for breakfast? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 00:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of.

As a soldier Itend to do more functional fitness. Strecher carries, vest runs, ruck marches for exercise on my personal time. I am not trying to be big, but lean and strong. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 03:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Over the border </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 03:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You watch lesbian porn but your username is a request for dick pics?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 21:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but her instincts tell her that you are trying to evolve by learning through reading. As a predator she is threatened by the thought of you evolving faster than she does, so she attempts to distract you with an air of playfullness, thus hindering your evolution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 19:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It becomes Mountain Dew Baja Blast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 03:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the Earth is not flat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 03:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless he has a fedora.


Bitches love fedoras. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 03:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have so much to learn young grasshopper.


Opium helps me fight the war within myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 03:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason your link is not working? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 03:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you know I have opium? Are you hacking me? Aye, I am an old school gent and prefer the good old drugs of yesteryear, what's it to ye? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 03:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marx was that guy who taught Hitler right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 03:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds like something an ugly person would say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 03:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was counting on you to give me a good joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 02:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh come on. We are vets. The darkness of our humor is well known, but we can't take it when a VA manager has some dark fucked up humor. 

We joke about IED's, Hadjis, Suicide Bombs and the like all the time. Does this mean we don't have respect for our fallen brothers? Hell no.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 02:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your grasp of history is the joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 02:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Marines did not land at D-day. It was the Army. The largest amphibious assault in history was conducted by the Army. Remember that.


-U.S. Army NCO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 18:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have always thought Cambridge goat skin bibles were very nice. They will last forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 03:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, from what I see only 120 something US troops are involved. Seems like an interesting duty though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 03:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is not about being a military peacekeeper. That is abkut working dirrctly for the UN.


Peacekeepers are attached military members from Armed Forces of UN member nations. They wear their own nation's uniform and remain members of their nation's Armed Forces.

[This site](http://www.un.org/en/peacekeeping/resources/statistics/contributors.shtml) would be more applicable. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you know any U.S. Soldier who has served as a UN Peacekeeper? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 02:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you get selected for that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 02:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume an exclusive relationship from date one. I don't date more than one woman at a time. 

If I don't want to continue a dating relationship I will tell her. If I want to date someone else I will discontinue dating the girl I was seeing, even if we only had one date. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 00:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because women are just as capable of answering questions from a male perspective as men, duh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 00:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it is a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 00:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. But after 239 years we have our own distinct flavor.

Plus, our first Drill Instructor was Prussian not British :). His Blue Book drew on Prussian traditions not British ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 23:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, just curious. 

Its cool learning about other traditions than my own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 23:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can't maintain your discipline while you are in, you won't when you get out.

Circumstances/setting do not dictate discipline, willpower dictates discipline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 23:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spray on the neck and rub it in. One or two light sprays should be plenty.

As you sweat throughout the day the neck will release the scent.


You are not supposed to smell someones cologne until you are in close contact with them. It is an intimate touch not a blaring announcement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 23:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To relax. As a married man I have zero interest in scouting out females. I like juke joints and honkytonks though. Good country music (preferably live) and cold beer helps me soak the stress of the week away.

Places I go everybody knowa everybody. Old guys, young guys, all of us just talk sports, politics and trade tall tales. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 23:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do y'all salute enlisted men? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 18:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I did not know that either.


When we present arms with a weapon we have a distinct movement where we hold our weapons in fron of us parallel to our bodies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 18:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.

Which is why I pegged that answer as Hooah bullshit.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 03:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP to my Brother from the North.

-An American Soldier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 03:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna recommend the obvious; *Starship Troopers*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 02:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! I didn't know that about the Royal Navy. Thanks for schooling me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 01:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agh... FNGs.


Airborne is not just for infantrymen for one. I don't know what the hell he was aiming at with the CID shit. 


Oh well, 3/10 attempt to take down a poser. Nice to see them give a shit though.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about y'alls open handed salute. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 01:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats the real history behind the open handed salute? Senior NCOs over here always say that the unvisible palm salute was reserved for Armies that never lost a war, which I have always taken as Hooah bullshit. Anyway, it got me curious, what is the real deal behind showing your palm when you salute? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 00:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](http://www.flamesofwar.com/hobby.aspx?art_id=4155) hobby site has a very helpful rundown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 00:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess whos car is going on Craigslist? You provided me with all the details I need. Can I just have your phone number? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 22:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, if it works it works. 

Folks who condemn all fighting are usually just folks who don't know what it means to fight for something.

Also, we aren't talking about a disagreement over political parties, choice lf president or the like. We are talking about a group of pricks trying to *ban* the presence of a symbol which has cost far more than any of them can fathom. 


Banning the presence of this symbol does not equal freedom of speech. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 21:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I never disputed that. 


I don't think I would be able to restrain myself from losing my temper in this presence of such asshattery. 


Just because its legal does not mean you won't get your ass kicked for doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 21:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never said I was an asshole. I am very kind to women, because my mother raised me right. I have respect for others. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 20:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luckily I don't attend this school because I am too busy fighting for that flag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 20:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I won't bother. I will just leave a downvote.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 20:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please explain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 20:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the helpful answer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 19:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see where you are coming from.

As a free market libertarian I have never met a socialist who agreed with me on market issues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 18:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you are a socialist who believes in letting the free market solve problems? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 18:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Through the free market? Yes.


Through the state? No.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 18:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Join the Army and have a DS yelling 15 feet up your asshole and you will understand what I am saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you describe yourself as "sensitive"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 18:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not at all.. I have a leather heart and I don't give two flips about what someone else thinks about me. I am a salty veteran who doesn't fit into the parameters of what modern masculinity movements laud as good and wonderful (sensitivity, political correctness, emotionality etc). 


What about y'all? 

Edit; I don't mean I don't care, or have emotions, I am saying I don't spend my time caring whether someone likes me or not, or trying to tiptoe around how to say something. I say what I mean and mean what I say, and if someone does not like it they can shove off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 18:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you really have to check my TA-50? I promise I packed everything... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What makes a good Buck Sgt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 18:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a lot of guys who pick up their E-5 either try to stay "one of the boys" or they get a big power trip and walk around with a chip on their shoulder, still others just sit around as a buck sgt for 10 years not going anywhere.

So I wanted to ask y'all, what qualities make a good buck sergeant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 17:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck it. I am a soldier. I lost my filter in Afghanistan.


Fuck sensitivity. I have a leather heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best advice/anecdote you have recieved from a SNCO? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 17:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What advice/anecdote from a SNCO have you recieved that has stuck with you over the years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 16:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I am aware of the EOD attrition rate and EOD doesn't appeal to me. I like the traditional Army. 

I don't just want to blow shit up (though that is certainly a plus). Engineers have lower points, way more opportunity for career progression, I could feel like I was actually doing something important, I am tired of the dumb bullshit of support units, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 01:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big ones;

WCF advocates baby baptism and a sacramental view of the Lord's Supper. The LBCF is the opposite.


Thats pretty much it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 20:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judging by his comment history he is an American Airman. So you are right, it is my bad.


I doubt the wristband fits the requirements set forth in AFI 36-2903 (6.3.1.2) due to the clause that states bracelets cannot advocate a cause or philosophy.

Granted, EOD units usually don't give a flying flip about regs anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 18:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That wrist band is not authorized IAW AR 670-1 (3-4a). 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 16:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hemingway is hard to misunderstand. He is terse, he is short, and to the point. He says what he means and means what he says.

This does not mean his characters lack depth or flavor, but you don't have to wade through pools of flowery language to get there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 16:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is so Charmin, ultra good at flirting.That dude is smooth, Angel Soft even. He has a Bounty of awesome lines.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 15:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brave Little Toaster ain't so brave when he is served up with hot sauce.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 04:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Afghanistan. 


On a motorcycle? Never been close to death at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 03:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, they do some gear reviews. 

It isn't specific to any sort of bike though. You will get cruisers, dualsports, supersports, they review them all. So if you are a hardcore v-twin devotee you might not care about the rest of the content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 03:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I subscribe to *Motorcyclist*. I would say it is the equivilant of *Car and Driver*. Good bike reviews, good articles, interesting editorials. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 03:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't even gotten your sideways license yet?

I am from Bama too. It is largely conservative, but certainly no bastion of 100 percent religious participation. Bham is a fairly liberal area. USA is a pretty liberal school. There is enough debauchery in my hometown to counteract all the churches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 03:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet. I would love a pm letting me know whats up after you finish! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 02:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for tje recommendation, but I am currently in an aviation unit and I hate it. I loved my old infantry unit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 02:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. Currently at Fort Drum, been here almost 3 yrs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 02:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably better than spending endless hours in a clamshell counting parts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 02:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I hope so too. I am done with the support side, I have had enough. I'd like to see if the grass is greener on the other side haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 01:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because its a lot harder to go EOD than 12b and if I wash out of EOD school I end up right back in my current MOS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 01:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. I realized after I posted. Got it right the second time though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Army--Looking for advice from my fellow soldiers. I am considering a reclass from my current mos (92A- Automated Logistics Specialist) to 12B (Combat Engineer.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 01:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much what the title says. My reup window is open, I hate my job, I hate how our points are always maxed.
How does the reclass process work with 12b? I know those guys have OSUT, what point would I link up with the IET guys? Are reclass guys treated differently than IET guys?
I know Combat Engineers don't really build anything, when I was deployed they mostly blew shit up. What is the day to day life of engineers like?
Any other advice would be appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for advise from my fellow soldiers. I am considering a reclass from my current mos (92A- Automated Logistics Specialist) to 12B (Combat Engineer.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 00:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much what the title says. My reup window is open, I hate my job, I hate how our points are always maxed. 

How does the reclass process work with 12b? I know those guys have OSUT, what point would I link up with the IET guys? Are reclass guys treated differently than IET guys?

I know Combat Engineers don't really build anything, when I was deployed they mostly blew shit up. What is the day to day life of engineers like? 

Any other advice would be appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 21:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The NAM is a socialist movement.. Not to conducive to AnarchoCapitalism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it would be something related to Pooh's search for honeys
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except the ones that are marked "whites only". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is funny because solar panels and wind turbines cannot speak IRL. 

Lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People actually comment on imdb? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found your shit.. in my toilet.. because i reddit on the toilet..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or he demanded they turn over their forks, which he then pawned for cash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She "took" it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I am a fish with fins.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 21:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Following nature's template. Growing things as closely as possible to the way they naturally do.


With regards to animals, replicating a natural environment, diet, and atmosphere for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 06:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can testify firsthand to the corruption of the third world nations...

I have seen Afghan soldiers have to be physically restrained from running away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 06:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not an anarchist. I support a small and decentralized state for the purposes of national defense and courts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 05:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa... No shit. I am stationed at Fort Drum. Bottle Caps is my local beer store. 


Left Hand Brewing's Milk Stout Nitro. The very best stout on the market in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 05:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A libertarian minarchist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 05:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ron Paul did. The Republican Liberty caucus does. Justin Amash does. Rand Paul kind of does. 

Establishment guys like Jeb Bush and John McCain don't, but fuck those guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
