<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject535</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 06:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was over two years ago and from recollection both drivers survived with minimal injuries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 05:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To thank it for allowing me to control the direction of my car.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 05:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Though often misunderstood to refer only to insecticides, the term pesticide also applies to herbicides, fungicides, and various other substances used to control pests.
  
-[EPA](http://www.epa.gov/pesticides/about/index.htm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 05:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is your best one yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 05:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably that 11:00 is when people are going off to sleep? Or maybe it's when we all discuss our plans for world domination.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 03:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems to be a timed exclusive from how they worded it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 03:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that those should work if you digitally purchased/own them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 00:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately IIRC you download the full game on the X1. If space is of an issue it might be worth it to get a [USB3 external HDD](http://www.amazon.com/Seagate-Expansion-Desktop-External-STBV3000100/dp/B00834SJU8) for your X1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 00:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It's emulation, not streaming.](http://www.theverge.com/2015/6/15/8785955/microsoft-xbox-one-xbox-360-emulator-software) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 23:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So were is my paycheck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 23:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They also keep claiming Roundup is 100% safe for human consumption and the environment, because Glyphosate[1] is very toxic to non-human entities. Our environment is just as important.

  
No one is claiming it's safe for human consumption, what is claimed is that it is safe when used as directed. [In terms of herbicides glyphosate is one of the least harmful ones to non-target organisms and soil health.](http://www.epa.gov/ogwdw/pdfs/factsheets/soc/tech/glyphosa.pdf)
  
[Also glyphosate tolerant crops have allowed farmers to use more non-tillage farming practices in order to preserve soil health.](http://grist.org/food/soil-proprietor-do-gmos-promote-dirt-conservation/)
  
They also are the original developer's of Agent Orange (now banned, but you see where the stream goes.)

  
No they are not, they were one of many producers of the chemical under orders of the US government. 
  
Bill Nye, though not a "GMO scientist" has done the basic math and found that USA doesn't "need" GMO's
  
[Actually Bill Nye changed his mind after actually researching and learning about GMOs.](http://www.washingtonpost.com/news/energy-environment/wp/2015/03/03/proof-hes-the-science-guy-bill-nye-is-changing-his-mind-about-gmos/)
  
so why does Monsanto keep pushing it here? Other countries that DO need it aren't getting enough of it.
  
There has been a push for GMOs in many countries from India to the Philippines and in all instances it has shown to be a plus to local farmers from increase yields to decrease pesticide exposure. The issue is that GMOs have unfortunately become a political talking point and many countries that could gain from their use have decided to ban and halt their use. 
  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 22:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, if someone has a different opinion they must be a shill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 22:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MS should have released both Halo 5   6 day 1, it's a joke that we have to wait so long! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 21:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So just a bunch of documentaries?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 21:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most likely it was caught early so surgery was all that was required.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 21:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so exactly?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 21:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This test wasn't done by Top Gear, but yeah I'm sure Ferrari isn't too happy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GMOs are not poison, this is no better than the anti-vac movement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have to have the disk in to play?
  
Most likely, the disk will be used as an authentication key.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 360 emulated original xbox games but not all ran so well and some where unplayable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both the X360   PS3 used different hardware architecture then the current gen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 18:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to download the game, but it's free if you use a 360 copy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 18:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe they will use a pesticide that costs a little more with just as much saftey testing but has less damaging effect on the environment and doesn't give their customers cancer.
  
What one? And there is little evidence that glyphosate is actually causing cancer in humans.
  
  
 IARC's findings are not a risk assessment, they didn't look at the actual risk of getting cancer from glyphosate exposure. Their classification and findings are based off if they believe it can from the available evidence. A chemical could cause cancer in 1:1billion people or 1:10 people and they can be classified under the same group.
  
When you look at human and animal studies the risk of glyphosate is overblown even among high risk groups such as applicators.
  
[Evaluation of carcinogenic potential of the herbicide glyphosate, drawing on tumor incidence data from fourteen chronic/carcinogenicity rodent studies](http://informahealthcare.com/doi/abs/10.3109/10408444.2014.1003423)
  
There was no evidence of a carcinogenic effect related to glyphosate treatment. The lack of a plausible mechanism, along with published epidemiology studies, which fail to demonstrate clear, statistically significant, unbiased and non-confounded associations between glyphosate and cancer of any single etiology, and a compelling weight of evidence, support the conclusion that glyphosate does not present concern with respect to carcinogenic potential in humans.


[Cancer Incidence among Glyphosate-Exposed Pesticide Applicators in the Agricultural Health Study](http://www.jstor.org/discover/10.2307/3435746?uid=2 amp;uid=4 amp;sid=21104202186197)
  
Note that there was a weak but slight association with multiple myeloma that the authors suggest that further follow up is required. Also this was among applicators who inherently are exposed to significantly higher amounts of glyphosate than end product consumers.

  
Also a re-analysis of the AHS data failed to show the same link between glyphosate and multiple meyloma. 
  

[Multiple Myeloma and Glyphosate Use: A Re-Analysis of US Agricultural Health Study (AHS) Data](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/25635915)
 
  
[Epidemiologic studies of glyphosate and cancer: A review](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0273230012000943)
  
To examine potential cancer risks in humans, we reviewed the epidemiologic literature to evaluate whether exposure to glyphosate is associated causally with cancer risk in humans. We also reviewed relevant methodological and biomonitoring studies of glyphosate. Seven cohort studies and fourteen case-control studies examined the association between glyphosate and one or more cancer outcomes. Our review found no consistent pattern of positive associations indicating a causal relationship between total cancer (in adults or children) or any site-specific cancer and exposure to glyphosate.  

[Here is a good article that summarizes a lot of the data on glyphosate and cancer.](http://weedcontrolfreaks.com/2015/03/glyphosate-and-cancer-what-does-the-data-say/)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 18:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where was the car sourced from? Ferrari is known is give the press ringer cars. Perhaps this was a customer car and thus not as fast as expected.

  
It was Chris Evan's car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 11:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spinosaurus or Giganotosaurus, but who really knows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 09:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw Fallout 4, nothing else matters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 09:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of note the IARC's report was not a risk assessment, they didn't look at the actual risk of getting cancer from glyphosate exposure for their classification. A chemical could cause cancer in 1:1billion or 1:10 and they can be classified under the same group.
  
When you look at human and animal studies the risk of glyphosate is overblown even among high risk groups such as applicators.
  
[Evaluation of carcinogenic potential of the herbicide glyphosate, drawing on tumor incidence data from fourteen chronic/carcinogenicity rodent studies](http://informahealthcare.com/doi/abs/10.3109/10408444.2014.1003423)
  
There was no evidence of a carcinogenic effect related toglyphosatetreatment. The lack of a plausible mechanism, along with published epidemiology studies, which fail to demonstrate clear, statistically significant, unbiased and non-confounded associations betweenglyphosateand cancer of any single etiology, and a compelling weight of evidence, support the conclusion thatglyphosatedoes not present concern with respect to carcinogenic potential in humans.


[Cancer Incidence among Glyphosate-Exposed Pesticide Applicators in the Agricultural Health Study](http://www.jstor.org/discover/10.2307/3435746?uid=2 uid=4 sid=21104202186197)
  
Note that there was a weak but slight association with multiple myeloma that the authors suggest that further follow up is required. Also this was among applicators who inherently are exposed to significantly higher amounts of glyphosate than end product consumers.

  
Also a re-analysis of the AHS data failed to show the same link between glyphosate and multiple meyloma. 
  

[Multiple Myeloma and Glyphosate Use: A Re-Analysis of US Agricultural Health Study (AHS) Data](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/25635915)
 
  
[Epidemiologic studies of glyphosate and cancer: A review](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0273230012000943)
  
To examine potential cancer risks in humans, we reviewed the epidemiologic literature to evaluate whether exposure to glyphosate is associated causally with cancer risk in humans. We also reviewed relevant methodological and biomonitoring studies of glyphosate. Seven cohort studies and fourteen case-control studies examined the association between glyphosate and one or more cancer outcomes. Our review found no consistent pattern of positive associations indicating a causal relationship between total cancer (in adults or children) or any site-specific cancer and exposure to glyphosate.  

[Here is a good article that summarizes a lot of the data on glyphosate and cancer.](http://weedcontrolfreaks.com/2015/03/glyphosate-and-cancer-what-does-the-data-say/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 09:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was more then just several scientist sending letters, virtually every major health and safety department from Europe to Brazil wrote up a report highlighting all the faults and errors in the original 2012 study.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 07:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll Meet Again - Vera Lynn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 04:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wanted to read about said problems in a re-analysis of their findings. 
  
Remember?
  
And I hope to read about these problems in a re-analysis of their findings in the scientific literature!
  
So I provided links to several re-analysis by top health and safety assessment groups. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 04:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are some analysis of the 2012 study and its short falls.
  
[Here is the original EFSA report that highlighted short comings and error in the 2012 Seralini study.](http://www.efsa.europa.eu/en/efsajournal/pub/2986.htm)   
  
  
EFSA finds that the study as reported by Sralini et al. is of insufficient scientific quality for safety assessments. EFSA concludes that the currently available evidence does not impact on the ongoing re-evaluation of glyphosate and does not call for the reopening of the safety evaluations of maize NK603 and its related stacks.
 
  
[Here is Health Canada's response.](http://www.hc-sc.gc.ca/fn-an/gmf-agm/seralini-eng.php)  
  
  
Based on Health Canada and CFIAs review of this information [the Seralini study], the authors conclusions concerning the long term safety of NK603 corn and glyphosate are not supported
  
[Food Standards Australia/New Zealand](http://www.foodstandards.gov.au/consumer/gmfood/seralini/pages/default.aspx)  
  

  
On the basis of the many scientific deficiencies identified in the study, FSANZ does not accept the conclusions made by the authors [Seralini et al] and has therefore found no justification to reconsider the safety of NK603 corn  


[Brazil National Biosafety Technical Commission](http://www.cibiogem.gob.mx/Sala-prensa/Documents/CTNBIO-Brasil-Seralini1725.pdf)  
  
  
  
[VIB response.](http://www.vib.be/en/news/Pages/VIB-concludes-that-Seralini-study-is-not-substantiated-.aspx)  
  
[Here is BfR's response and review of the study.](http://www.bfr.bund.de/en/press_information/2012/29/a_study_of_the_university_of_caen_neither_constitutes_a_reason_for_a_re_evaluation_of_genetically_modified_nk603_maize_nor_does_it_affect_the_renewal_of_the_glyphosate_approval-131739.html)
  
[Belgian Biosafety Advisory Council report](http://www.bio-council.be/docs/BAC_2012_0898_CONSOLIDE.pdf)  
  
  
Here is a great quote on their opinion on Seralini 2012  
  
It should never have been accepted for publication in a scientific journal. The process of peer review which is usual before acceptance for publication in scientific journals has clearly failed here.

[High Council of Biotechnolgies conclusion.](http://www.efsa.europa.eu/en/efsajournal/doc/2986ax1.pdf)
  

  Consequently, the HCB Scientific Committee considers that the paper offers no information supporting the existence of a health risk associated with consumption of maize NK603, whether or not treated with a Roundup herbicide formulation. 

[ANSES Opinion](http://www.efsa.europa.eu/en/efsajournal/doc/2986ax1.pdf)

**Conclusion on study Results**
  
[The significant results obtained before correction are not biologically coherent overall. However, biological data on the results would be needed to draw a definitive conclusion. At this point in time, in light of the information provided in the publication, the ECEAGs experts consider that the authors interpretations are not sufficiently corroborated by the study data. 
Moreover, during the hearing, the studys authors admitted that this study was not conclusive by itself and that, though subject to improvement, it had the merit of opening up an interesting line of research. 
From ANSES opinion from their evaluation of the Seralini study on pathologies.](http://i.imgur.com/W0OJGIg.png)
  
[Here is the relevant chart.](http://i.imgur.com/BxD7sAb.png)  


[Monsanto's response to the study](http://www.monsanto.com/products/Documents/ProductSafety/seralini-sept-2012-monsanto-comments.pdf)  
  
   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 02:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.princeton.edu/~ota/disk3/1981/8104/810406.PDF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 02:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The EPA is currently re-evaluating its classification of glyphosate with regards to recent findings for example
  
Kind of, the EPA is going to take into account IARCs findings but the current review isn't due to the IARCs findings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 02:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I was paid to browse and post on reddit, but alas I'm not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 02:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you don't have any quantifiable evidence that the sources I've linked to are falsified? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 02:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are paid to do this! and we are here because we stumbled upon this thread and want to discuss it, or read how other people wanna interpret it.
  
[Citation Needed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 01:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do such as Bt-crops. Glyphosate is a herbicide and so it kills plants not insects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 01:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they are a simplified model and shouldn't be used as the sole evidence for determining if something poses a significant risk in humans, especially when you have animal studies along with human studies to draw from.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 00:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of the studies that I have linked to what ones are falsified or have been disproven by more recent research? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 00:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 00:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cell cultures are not the only way to asses toxicity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 00:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it does, but it classifies glyphosate as probably carcinogenic which is a completely different category.

  
They are not completely different categories as they are merely in different subcategories of Group 2 classification.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 00:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In cell cultures.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 00:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The organization is mentioned in the article and is the reason for the current ban.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 23:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same group (IARC) classifies cellphones as possibly carcinogens. 
  
  There is plenty of evidence supporting the relative safety of glyphosate to humans.
  

[European Review of Glyphosate finding it poses no significant risk to humans](http://ec.europa.eu/food/fs/ph_ps/pro/eva/existing/list1_glyphosate_en.pdf)
  

[Safety Evaluation and Risk Assessment of the Herbicide Roundup and Its Active Ingredient, Glyphosate, for Humans](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0273230099913715)
  
  
  
[Developmental and reproductive outcomes in humans and animals after glyphosate exposure: a critical analysis.](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/22202229)
  
[Epidemiologic studies of glyphosate and non-cancer health outcomes: a review.](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/21798302)

[Review of genotoxicity studies of glyphosate and glyphosate-based formulations](http://informahealthcare.com/doi/abs/10.3109/10408444.2013.770820#.)

  
  [Here's a safety analysis of glyphosate in many animal studies.](http://whqlibdoc.who.int/publications/2006/9241665203_eng.pdf)
  
  


[Evaluation of carcinogenic potential of the herbicide glyphosate, drawing on tumor incidence data from fourteen chronic/carcinogenicity rodent studies](http://informahealthcare.com/doi/abs/10.3109/10408444.2014.1003423)
  
There was no evidence of a carcinogenic effect related to glyphosate treatment. The lack of a plausible mechanism, along with published epidemiology studies, which fail to demonstrate clear, statistically significant, unbiased and non-confounded associations between glyphosate and cancer of any single etiology, and a compelling weight of evidence, support the conclusion that glyphosate does not present concern with respect to carcinogenic potential in humans.


[Cancer Incidence among Glyphosate-Exposed Pesticide Applicators in the Agricultural Health Study](http://www.jstor.org/discover/10.2307/3435746?uid=2 uid=4 sid=21104202186197)
  
Note that there was a weak but slight association with multiple myeloma that the authors suggest that further follow up is required. Also this was among applicators who inherently are exposed to significantly higher amounts of glyphosate than end product consumers.

  
Also a re-analysis of the AHS data failed to show the same link between glyphosate and multiple meyloma. 
  

[Multiple Myeloma and Glyphosate Use: A Re-Analysis of US Agricultural Health Study (AHS) Data](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/25635915)
 
  
[Epidemiologic studies of glyphosate and cancer: A review](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0273230012000943)
  
To examine potential cancer risks in humans, we reviewed the epidemiologic literature to evaluate whether exposure to glyphosate is associated causally with cancer risk in humans. We also reviewed relevant methodological and biomonitoring studies of glyphosate. Seven cohort studies and fourteen case-control studies examined the association between glyphosate and one or more cancer outcomes. Our review found no consistent pattern of positive associations indicating a causal relationship between total cancer (in adults or children) or any site-specific cancer and exposure to glyphosate.  

[Here is a good article that summarizes a lot of the data on glyphosate and cancer.](http://weedcontrolfreaks.com/2015/03/glyphosate-and-cancer-what-does-the-data-say/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 22:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the video on Kevin Smith.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vgYhLIThTvk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 08:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Security guard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 06:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O'toro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 06:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [HD-DVD had porn.](http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2007/01/8602/)
  
Also, one of the big reasons why Betamax failed was due to it only supporting 1hr recording times early on preventing it holding a regular movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 03:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/dD0H0pk.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 00:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had that exact problem but with a Crucial SSD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 00:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> replaced the superdrive with another 500MB SSD
  
  
Didn't know SSDs came that small.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 22:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just said no pharmacutical companies would pay millions to get a cannabis based drug approved, I just proved you wrong.
  
Also GWPharma Sativex is currently undergoing phase III clinical trials in the US for pain management in cancer patients and Epidiolex is undergoing trails in the US for treatment of epilepsy in children.
  
So even in the US millions of dollars are being spent to get a cannabis derived drug to market.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 21:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Epidiolex is still under going clinical trails and has yet to be shown to be effective. Time will tell if it is a good treatment for Dravet Syndrome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 21:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Why do you lie?](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/GW_Pharmaceuticals) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 08:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is an interesting IAMA from one of the Guards.](https://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/2y5sbt/iwasa_guard_in_the_1971_stanford_prison/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 06:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Something cool.](http://pbfcomics.com/210/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 05:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still waiting for one of those evilutionist to explain the banana or the peanut butter???? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 04:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1:14.2 Slightly damp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 01:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not, Ferrari doesn't control the actual operations on how the team is ran.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 01:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, a single anecdotal account is hardly evidence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a clinical trial going on right now in the U.S. looking at its effectiveness with treating seizures in children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was always asking for strong clinical controlled studies proving mmj effectiveness, the same threshold required for all drugs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The issue with the current research on seizures is that the studies are small and not controlled. Which is fine for supporting further research, but not proving efficacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of those are control clinical studies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you wont because there are very few studies showing efficacy of mmj.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What studies? Please provide links to controlled clinical data showing cannabis effectiveness curing or treating disease/illness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anecdotal accounts are hardly compelling evidence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are these controlled   blinded studies you are referring to? If so I would like a link.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America is not the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 20:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ferrari doesn't actually have a team that competes at Le Mans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 20:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately as long as Ferrari believes F1 is the only important racing series we won't see a Ferrari Ford rivalry unless Ford enters F1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 19:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the evidence that mmj is actually having a positive effect on reducing seizures is weak/lacking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 19:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of shit has been used for thousands of years, but that isn't proof that it is an effective medical treatment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 19:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can still gain exclusivity on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 19:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except there is no Ferrari team at Le Mans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 19:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed the Ferrari reference, but I wonder if Ford knows that Ferrari doesn't actually have a factory team at Le Mans anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Life-span carcinogenicity studies on SpragueDawley rats exposed to -radiation: Design of the project and report on the tumor occurrence after post-natal radiation exposure (6 weeks of age) delivered in a single acute exposure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 08:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 04:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Tesla is fast, except around a track. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 03:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canada doesn't allow research into cannabis?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 03:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's easier to just repurpose a V8 from an existing car.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 02:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The issue with mmj is that for most illness/disease it lacks strong empirical evidence proving its effectiveness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 03:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After seeing a few in person god that car is beautiful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 03:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because a gas car can do it in under 29hrs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 03:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USDA does allow trace amounts of GMO contaminates in Organic crops to remove/minimize this risk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 03:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monsanto has never actually sued a farmer over accidental cross pollination, only for willful and intentional isolation and use of their seeds. Also it's not copyright law but patent law.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 19:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thermite?  
  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 10:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Cars.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_ULm6QrC428) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 10:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll carry on through the dust and the muck and the storm if it's easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 09:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Commonly all playlist are "ranked" it just that they keep the actual figure hidden from you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, but we already got [snake in cow.](http://phenomena.nationalgeographic.com/2013/01/01/how-a-quarter-of-the-cow-genome-came-from-snakes/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same organization declares cell phone usage is probably carcinogenic to humans.
  
Also there is ample evidence for the general safety of glyphosate.
  
[European Review of Glyphosate finding it poses no significant risk to humans](http://ec.europa.eu/food/fs/ph_ps/pro/eva/existing/list1_glyphosate_en.pdf)
  

[Safety Evaluation and Risk Assessment of the Herbicide Roundup and Its Active Ingredient, Glyphosate, for Humans](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0273230099913715)
  
  
  
[Developmental and reproductive outcomes in humans and animals after glyphosate exposure: a critical analysis.](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/22202229)
  
[Epidemiologic studies of glyphosate and non-cancer health outcomes: a review.](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/21798302)

[Review of genotoxicity studies of glyphosate and glyphosate-based formulations](http://informahealthcare.com/doi/abs/10.3109/10408444.2013.770820#.)

  
  [Here's a safety analysis of glyphosate in many animal studies.](http://whqlibdoc.who.int/publications/2006/9241665203_eng.pdf)
  
  


[Evaluation of carcinogenic potential of the herbicide glyphosate, drawing on tumor incidence data from fourteen chronic/carcinogenicity rodent studies](http://informahealthcare.com/doi/abs/10.3109/10408444.2014.1003423)
  
There was no evidence of a carcinogenic effect related toglyphosatetreatment. The lack of a plausible mechanism, along with published epidemiology studies, which fail to demonstrate clear, statistically significant, unbiased and non-confounded associations betweenglyphosateand cancer of any single etiology, and a compelling weight of evidence, support the conclusion thatglyphosatedoes not present concern with respect to carcinogenic potential in humans.


[Cancer Incidence among Glyphosate-Exposed Pesticide Applicators in the Agricultural Health Study](http://www.jstor.org/discover/10.2307/3435746?uid=2 uid=4 sid=21104202186197)
  
Note that there was a weak but slight association with multiple myeloma that the authors suggest that further follow up is required. Also this was among applicators who inherently are exposed to significantly higher amounts of glyphosate than end product consumers.

  
Also a re-analysis of the AHS data failed to show the same link between glyphosate and multiple meyloma. 
  

[Multiple Myeloma and Glyphosate Use: A Re-Analysis of US Agricultural Health Study (AHS) Data](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/25635915)
 
  
[Epidemiologic studies of glyphosate and cancer: A review](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0273230012000943)
  
To examine potential cancer risks in humans, we reviewed the epidemiologic literature to evaluate whether exposure to glyphosate is associated causally with cancer risk in humans. We also reviewed relevant methodological and biomonitoring studies of glyphosate. Seven cohort studies and fourteen case-control studies examined the association between glyphosate and one or more cancer outcomes. Our review found no consistent pattern of positive associations indicating a causal relationship between total cancer (in adults or children) or any site-specific cancer and exposure to glyphosate.  

[Here is a good article that summarizes a lot of the data on glyphosate and cancer.](http://weedcontrolfreaks.com/2015/03/glyphosate-and-cancer-what-does-the-data-say/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To alter the genes of a plant/animal to create an organism that could not normally happen in nature is not the same as updating Windows.
  
Transgenic plants and organisms are 100% naturally occurring.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 00:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually the 208 GTB/GTS Turbo was their first mid engine V8 turbo car back in 82. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 22:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly not sure, but the Core-M has similar [performance to the i5 version](http://www.anandtech.com/show/9219/the-surface-3-review/5). If you are willing to wait I would wait, but you won't go wrong with getting a SP3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 21:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are thinking about the base Surface Pro 3 (i3) then I'd wait until the Pro 4 as Core-M tablets like the Dell Venue 11 are a lot more powerful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 21:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's number one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 08:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you finding these people?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 07:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don Hertzfeldt: End of the World </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 06:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Richard Prince is not presenting someone else's work off as his own.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 06:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, he's not passing their art off as his own and he is making modifications to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 02:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should also strongly consider the SSD upgrade. It will make the computer much faster, and should give it more years of use before it is too slow.
  
The SSD is a must for this thing, for the computer is painfully slow without it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 00:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God you're dense, he is not passing off their work as his own. What Prince is doing is classic appropriation art.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 22:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not passing their photos off as his own.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They might start caring about more important issues, they might also start caring about less important issues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if they will ban cell phones, for the IARC classifies those as possibly carcinogenic to humans. 
  
**Edit:** Here are a handful of safety studies on glyphosate.
  
[Safety Evaluation and Risk Assessment of the Herbicide Roundup and Its Active Ingredient, Glyphosate, for Humans](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0273230099913715)
  
  
  
[Developmental and reproductive outcomes in humans and animals after glyphosate exposure: a critical analysis.](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/22202229)
  
[Epidemiologic studies of glyphosate and non-cancer health outcomes: a review.](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/21798302)

[Review of genotoxicity studies of glyphosate and glyphosate-based formulations](http://informahealthcare.com/doi/abs/10.3109/10408444.2013.770820#.)

  
  [Here's a safety analysis of glyphosate in many animal studies.](http://whqlibdoc.who.int/publications/2006/9241665203_eng.pdf)
  
  


[Evaluation of carcinogenic potential of the herbicide glyphosate, drawing on tumor incidence data from fourteen chronic/carcinogenicity rodent studies](http://informahealthcare.com/doi/abs/10.3109/10408444.2014.1003423)
  
There was no evidence of a carcinogenic effect related toglyphosatetreatment. The lack of a plausible mechanism, along with published epidemiology studies, which fail to demonstrate clear, statistically significant, unbiased and non-confounded associations betweenglyphosateand cancer of any single etiology, and a compelling weight of evidence, support the conclusion thatglyphosatedoes not present concern with respect to carcinogenic potential in humans.


[Cancer Incidence among Glyphosate-Exposed Pesticide Applicators in the Agricultural Health Study](http://www.jstor.org/discover/10.2307/3435746?uid=2 uid=4 sid=21104202186197)
  
Note that there was a weak but slight association with multiple myeloma that the authors suggest that further follow up is required. Also this was among applicators who inherently are exposed to significantly higher amounts of glyphosate than end product consumers.

  
Also a re-analysis of the AHS data failed to show the same link between glyphosate and multiple meyloma. 
  

[Multiple Myeloma and Glyphosate Use: A Re-Analysis of US Agricultural Health Study (AHS) Data](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/25635915)
 
  
[Epidemiologic studies of glyphosate and cancer: A review](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0273230012000943)
  
To examine potential cancer risks in humans, we reviewed the epidemiologic literature to evaluate whether exposure to glyphosate is associated causally with cancer risk in humans. We also reviewed relevant methodological and biomonitoring studies of glyphosate. Seven cohort studies and fourteen case-control studies examined the association between glyphosate and one or more cancer outcomes. Our review found no consistent pattern of positive associations indicating a causal relationship between total cancer (in adults or children) or any site-specific cancer and exposure to glyphosate.  

[Here is a good article that summarizes a lot of the data on glyphosate and cancer.](http://weedcontrolfreaks.com/2015/03/glyphosate-and-cancer-what-does-the-data-say/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It's flat and it is also 180^o, but it's not an actual boxer engine.](http://www.aircoolednut.com/erkson/personal/ferrari_boxer_flat_crank.htm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It is a 180^o V12, but that also makes it a flat 12 cause it's you know flat. But it's not a boxer engine which is the common flat type engine arrangement. ](http://www.aircoolednut.com/erkson/personal/ferrari_boxer_flat_crank.htm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 16:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 11:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going the way of the factoid...makes me sad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 10:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly do, and would be shocked if Prince would lose in court over this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 10:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But this isn't parody a more relevant chase would be the more recent [Cariou v. Prince.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cariou_v._Prince) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 10:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Prince Rupert Drop.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xe-f4gokRBs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 10:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Electrocuted means death.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Electrocution) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 10:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Randy - That 70s Show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 10:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assure you it's a real thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 09:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also here was the [response to her response.](http://www.geneticliteracyproject.org/2014/09/02/new-yorker-editor-david-remnick-responds-to-vandana-shiva-criticism-of-michael-specters-profile/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 09:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you watch the video? The thing flew like 100 meters before crashing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 06:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It's legal](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nussenzweig_v._DiCorcia) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 06:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He already had a [case](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cariou_v._Prince) that he won over making very minor transformations to photos by a different photographer. I'd be shocked if the courts classify his work as copyright infringement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 06:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You either have the creative urge or you don't. 
  
So it's the "urge" that make it art? So if Richard Prince had the "urge" to take comment and take photos off instagram then he's an artist right? Cause he had the "urger" right? So if someone who paints or takes photos purely to make money like a wedding photographer or a portrait painter then cause they lack the "urger" they are not true artist?  
  
So to reiterate, this crappy excuse of art is just some guy downloading other people's work, making insignificant changes that change absolutely nothing about the main focus of the piece
  
Why are they insignificant changes and how is the main focus unchanged?
  
nor that he only just doesn't violate copyright
  
Is he actually violating copyright? How is this work not protected under fair use as appropriation art? 
  
That'd be like me taking a photo of the Mona Lisa and putting a caption on it, and trying to act like I did something artistic.
  
Well by your reasoning if you had the "urge" wouldn't it be art? 
  
There's better "art" than this dude's in /r/photoshopbattles[1] .
  
Wait, is making art a competition? Is only good art "art"? What makes something good? And who decides this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 04:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hardware stores and the like, acid has many uses such as cleaning. Even in the states buying high concentration acid is relatively easy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 04:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if he took the pictures himself would his work still be an "embarrassment to art"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 04:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not stealing, what he is doing is protected under fair use as transformative art.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 03:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a myth.
  


[Here is a very simple graph on suicides in India.](http://i.imgur.com/FovwdC0.png) 
  
  
[The largest comprehensive review on the data failed to find sufficient evidence that GMO bt-cotton was a major contributing factor to suicides of Indian farmers.](http://www.ifpri.org/publication/bt-cotton-and-farmer-suicides-india) 
  
We first show that there is no evidence in available data of a resurgence of farmer suicides in India in the last five years. Second, we find that Bt cotton technology has been very effective overall in India. However, the context in which Bt cotton was introduced has generated disappointing results in some particular districts and seasons. Third, our analysis clearly shows that Bt cotton is neither a necessary nor a sufficient condition for the occurrence of farmer suicides. In contrast, many other factors have likely played a prominent role. Nevertheless, in specific regions and years, where Bt cotton may have indirectly contributed to farmer indebtedness, leading to suicides, its failure was mainly the result of the context or environment in which it was planted.  


[Here is the 2011 Version](http://www.ingentaconnect.com/content/routledg/jds/2011/00000047/00000002/art00007)
  

  
  
[And a more recent report.](http://www.geneticliteracyproject.org/2014/03/05/new-research-paper-gm-cotton-in-india-has-probably-reduced-farmer-suicides-not-caused-them/#.UxqR46hn8Uu)
 
The analysis reveals considerable variation in trends in suicide rates across the nine cotton-growing states. The data, although not ideal, and the modeling do not, however, support the claim that GM cotton has led to an increase in farmer suicide rates: if anything the reverse is true.
The Indian farmer suicide story has become received wisdom for some anti-GM
campaigners. In fact, we find that the suicide rate for male Indian farmers is slightly lower
than the non-farmer rate. And Indian suicide rates as a whole, although contested, do not
appear to be notably high in a world context. The pattern of changes in suicide rates over
the last 15 years is consistent with a beneficial effect of Bt cotton for India as a whole
albeit perhaps not in every cotton-growing state.

  
  
Overall in terms of increase yields and decreased pesticide use Bt-cotton has been a significant plus to farmers in India. 
  
  
Edit: Here is a New Yorker article on [Vandana Shiva.](http://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2014/08/25/seeds-of-doubt)
   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 03:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're just photos he stole off instagram. With a ridiculous price tag. It's laughable.
  
It's hard to take you serious when you don't even know what you are hating on. The work that Richard Prince created was not merely "photos off instagram".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 03:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you saying that I just have to understand the process to be an artist?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 03:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So that's the F-35? No wonder everyone is pissed about it, damn thing can barely fly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 03:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably not the last Enzo produced, Ferrari has a habit of making more then they claim. IIRC there are actually about 450 produced Enzos out there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
