<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1598</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 18:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mentioned it in a way which suggests you thought it was happening in Portugal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 17:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is illegal to do cosmetic testing on animals in the EU.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 15:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pendulum - Voodoo People (Prodigy remix)
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BKXKWBcaV3A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Insidious tactics of animal rights groups in Portugal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 15:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 14:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worst part of the film </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 14:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> unzipping </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 14:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oxford University is older than the Aztec Empire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 12:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Opening doors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 12:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of newer books, I loved We Need to Talk About Kevin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Those who or are involved in animal research, do you tell friends/family what you do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 12:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 11:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Passport photos seem designed to provide the worldwide media with a convincing mugshot if you turn out to be a terrorist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 12:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the entire whip system - some votes are important and you are expected to vote with your party. Otherwise you'd be left with the US system where nothing can get done because there is no party control and everyone has to bribe each other with amendments left and right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 18:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Islamic State has been gaining thousands of followers just through its own successes - doing nothing is not much of an alternative. 

I agree that bombing Iraq, and civilian casualties that result, will create some extremists, but I think doing nothing could be worse. If the Iraqi government can regain control of the country it is the best chance to reduce the number of extremists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 18:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting perspective, but makes sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 18:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No ground troops - only air strikes in Iraq </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 18:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very unlikely, though no doubt a handful do. 

The parties have been urging MPs to vote with them and support intervention in Iraq. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 18:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We hope that through airstrikes we can support the Iraqi ground forces enough that they can regain the territory lost to the Islamic State in the past few months. 
Given that the Islamic State is encouraging terrorists in countries around the world, we feel the world would be better without a strong Islamic State (IS) movement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MPs support UK air strikes against IS in Iraq </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 18:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British parliament votes to back air strikes in Iraq by 524-43 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 18:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 14:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? You might have an 8 week course in the cold war, just as PPEists might choose to do 8 weeks on cold war politics. 

No subject can be "mastered" in 3 years - you're always just on the tip of the iceberg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 14:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Economics, Maths and Chemistry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 17:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm also an Oxford PPE-er

PPE does teach a kind of short-termism bullshitting. I say I know about the economics of carbon exchange because I spent 3 days writing an essay on it.

Then again it does teach you to deal with a lot of different topics in a short space of time, which is common for cabinet positions (PPE is much more overrepresented in cabinet than just in the commons). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 13:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you try and do university without a student loan or something?

The reality is people pay less than before! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 12:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People pay less up front than they did before. And most people never need to pay off their whole debt. Where's the issue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 12:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I will. 

I think they have moderated the Conservatives well (obviously as the minority party they have limited power, but they have done well). 

My concerns are:
- Labour - I don't trust to run the economy and the concept of Ed Miliband being the statesman in charge of the UK TERRIFIES me
- Conservative - I worry about the power of their far right MPs who want to leave the EU, pull up the drawbridge and bring back social conservativism
- UKIP - Oh Jesus, No!

Lib Dems have:
- Raised minimal tax thresholds to 10,000 
- Brought in the pupil premium
- prevented some nutty policies by conservatives on green energy, immigration etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 12:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they have a smaller than average bike then I'm screwed if I get new tenants. Or if friends bring a bike over etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 01:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi thanks for answers so far.

My house has 6 steps down to a lower floor door which is around 2.5' below ground level. It's a very small space below my bins which I need to raise. I really need the lowest sensible height I can get away with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 17:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are not the only person who will live in the house in the future. I need a future proof height. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 17:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tea man ... he goes round making cups of tea in an emergency, He's a British national hero.

Oh, we claim Judge Dredd as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 17:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Done (says the British first, English second person) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Building a bike shed - what is the minimum sensible height it should be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 17:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't ride a bike, but housemates do. I'm building a small bike locker. What is the minimum height it can be to allow most bikes to be easily stored? I.e. what height are most bikes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 15:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's too long, but I really wanted to call my Wifi, "If you connect to this your children will be next" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 15:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is nothing I **own** that I would not give away for a billion dollars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 15:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First I had to microwave it, then I eventually got a rice cooker, before finally getting a proper kettle from home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 15:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I moved to Washington DC (from London), no one knew what a kettle was (the electric kind) or where I could buy one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 13:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More information:
http://www.understandinganimalresearch.org.uk/news/2014/09/this-week-in-animal-research-w-e-19-september/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Week in Animal Research - 19th Sept </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 13:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Week in Animal Research - 19th Sept 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 13:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 12:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you prepare pork well there will be no ill effects. Done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 13:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SPEAK go out once a week with about 5 people. The Pro-Test movement pretty much finished off SPEAK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 16:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forget the "testing" - it's the animals used in the development of the medicines that matter. Take Zmabb, it is a combination of three mouse antibodies, and the efficacy was discovered in monkeys. No mice or monkeys, no Zmabb.

You are right we could do it in human (not always faster - we simply couldn't not study the role of genetics in slow growing humans as effectively as some of the work that is done in genetically modified mice), but most would consider this unethical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 16:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also the only we will develop new medicines which save millions of lives. The moment you start equating human and other animal lives you start to create all sorts of moral issues - do you have a moral obligation to prevent a lion killing an antelope (you would stop a lion killing a human).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is British Animal Rights Extremism Back? New group targets student scientists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 15:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 15:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well in the situations of hyperinflation the government tends to print money and use it to pay its debt. 

In quantitative easing the government buys debt or government bonds from banks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 13:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money is just a medium of wealth used to assist bartering. If one person has all the money it ceases to play that role. Alternative currencies would set up (e.g. gold standard, where there is some intrinsic value). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 13:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inflation is defined two ways (both mean the same thing):
- The rise in the general price of goods
- The fall in the value of money

If you print money, there is more money in the economy yet the same amount of goods. So the nominal prices of those limited goods rises.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 12:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you print a large amount of money the value of currency decreases (inflation), and people's wealth decreases... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 11:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're British until you vote otherwise (j/k) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 11:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the London Underground.

- Only the Western part of the district line goes down (where it splits past Earl's Court), when I lived in Stepney Green the District line was an unstoppable force.
- Really? Haven't noticed any problems recently. When the train judders on startup, that's because someone is leaning on the doors and therefore causing the automatic brakes to kick in.
- Yes, I hate them too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 11:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *tips hat* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 11:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm more concerned that the technician filming saw the monkey vomiting (which isn't unusual after surgery), and rather than getting a veterinarian, decided to sit there and film it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is British Animal Rights Extremism Back? New group targets student scientists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 11:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 10:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When someone brings in an accordion and decides that now is the time to use it to call a demon God into the theatre, and then when they finally manage to summon the damn thing they have a FIFTY MINUTE CHAT about some occult crap. The invites the fucking demon to dinner and ask members of the audience to be waiters.

I HATE that .... and I always say no to being a waiter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 10:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Age of Empires II </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 10:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Living in the UK, normal policeman don't carry guns so they can't fatally shoot people even if threatened. Seems to work here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 21:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, no substitute for the feel of a book </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 13:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's in the pile there's an 80% chance I've read it and will remember I own it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 13:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The range of answers widens dramatically </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 12:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hmm, could possibly send a book </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 12:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will count today or tomorrow, so keep guesses coming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Books glorious books (Can anyone guess how many?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 12:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All my books in a pile waiting for new shelves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 11:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 11:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just put on boxee+, but didn't work before upgrade either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 03:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I tried that originally, had the same problem - which is why I bought the hub (I read something online about boxee not able to power two usb HDDs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 03:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both work individually, but if both are plugged in, one will not function properly. Surely that can't be a formatting issue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boxee won't recognise second hard drive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 19:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have two unpowered 2TB HDDs. I plug them into a powered USB hub, so that boxee need not power them. One has Films, one has TV shows.

Boxee can read both drives fine if only one is plugged in. 
Boxee cannot read both, if they are both plugged in - it just reads one and assumes the second drive has identical information. If I try and play a file from the "unrecognised" drive, then it merely says it cannot access the file or directory.

Help!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 17:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A rather cynical view. By the same is the motivation of a Doctor seeing a patient to get paid and hopefully get a promotion? No, it's to try and help people. 

Yes, there are profits involved, just as there is in healthcare, education and most other positive endeavours, but that doesn't make it the primary motivation of the people involved. Most researchers I know working on diseases in animals, really want to find a treatment - not for the profit, but for the patient. 

Very little animal research is done by the military, but the bit that is is almost all for treating war injuries e.g. the best treatment on site for someone who has been shot to ensure they survive, or studies into PTSD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The power plug is bigger than the bit of technology it powers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 17:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 16:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might think that, I couldn't possibly comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 16:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do colourless green ideas sleep furiously? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shattering DNA may have let gibbons evolve new species </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 16:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time for a change? A Scientists View of Public Interests in Animal Research and Welfare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 16:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 18:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It changes the meanings of words. 

In the UK, you might be a Conservative (voter of the Conservative party), or a conservative (one who prefers less change). 

If you watched the girl next door, were you referring to the film or your neighbour?

If your favourite band is ratm, is that a band you haven't heard of, or initials of a better known band (Rage Against the Machine)

etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 16:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite literally everything - I've got all the time in the world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Activists force Maastricht University to cancel important study into pacemakers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 16:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Promising monkey results in Ebola trial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 14:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a word? The Economist helps confuse the question. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 15:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 18:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 17 different meanings expressed by the word "sorry" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 14:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they were sensible they'd sell umbrellas in the winter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 14:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The optimal sleeping position is the one discovered the moment your alarm goes off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brain stimulation in mice 'helps in stroke' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 12:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help turning 2.0 into 5.1 system (I have 5.1 Amp) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 17:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Sherwood RD-6106R 5.1 amp

I have a pair of Eltax Symphony 6.2 speakers

I NEED a pair of rear speakers, a centre speaker, and maybe a sub (the Eltax have a reasonable amount of bass). If I bought another pair of Eltax Symphony speakers, would they work as rear speakers or should O get something else? What should I buy as a central speaker? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help turning 2.0 into 5.1 system (I have 5.1 Amp) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 17:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Sherwood RD-6106R 5.1 amp

I have a pair of Eltax Symphony 6.2 speakers

I NEED a pair of rear speakers, a centre speaker, and maybe a sub (the Eltax have a reasonable amount of bass). If I bought another pair of Eltax Symphony speakers, would they work as rear speakers? What should I buy as a central speaker? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 17:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except they haven't. Students might be paying a bit longer (hello graduate tax) but they aren't paying any more. They're in LESS debt than before, because they pay nothing up front (I had to pay my fees up front many years ago). I say this as a former teacher who had to explain the new system to students.

The fact they said they'd do one thing, and did another, is a fair frustration - they should have abstained - they're paying the price for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 17:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there is a strong group of "The Economist Liberal Lib Dems" - which is economically just right of centre, but socially much more progressive. It's these "bluer" Lib Dems who have always tended to make up the elected top of the party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leading UK scientists warn against cloning pets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 12:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Instructions on how to make your own homeopathic ebola remedy... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 11:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 11:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Frankly, my dear, I don't give a damn" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Pregnancy Kits to Ebola Treatment: The animal research behind the invention </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 19:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 16:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pick up a second hand TD-10 e.g.:
http://orangecounty.craigslist.org/msg/4594120842.html

Frankly I reckon your kit sold in bits could raise around $1000 or more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 16:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have sold a lot of drums online (mainly ebay).

Sell

* each cymbal separately
* the snare separately
* the shell kit with only stands for any floating toms
* Bags separately
* stands separately

I also would go with the Roland e-kit over the Alesis, better bang for your buck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 00:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't original - it's a wiki picture, and copied from my post:
http://www.reddit.com/r/StarWars/comments/2c1lpd/this_library_looks_like_the_jawa_sandcrawlers/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 13:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would this do:
http://www.acoustic-foam.co.uk/products/Pro-Acoustic-Home-Studio-Kit-AFHS--%28-24x-AFW305-12%22-Panels-%252b--4x-AFBT200-Bass-Traps-%29.html
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheap sound dampening </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 12:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Library that looks like the sandcrawler from Star Wars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 17:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This library looks like the Jawa sandcrawlers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 16:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WSIG] Fairly new board gamer looking for some new games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 14:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Games I enjoy/own:
Game of Thrones - Strategic, cutthroat, changing fortunes
Carcassonne - Relatively fast, easy to learn, 3 player as good as 6 player
Coup - Great, short game, I can carry with me



Number of Players: Up to 6, but preferably those that can be successfully played with 3-4 as well.

Game Length: Either 4 hours, 2 hours, or 20 minutes

Complexity of Game: Quick to pick up for new players - not many people I know will know these games

Your Budget: 10-40 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 17:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure I understand what "cover out" means.

2cm is a fairly thick piece of wood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 12:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ex-research dogs really shouldn't be aggressive, or something is going wrong with their socialisation programmes. 
Usually ex-research dogs are not adopted because:
- concerns of any medical side effects that are yet to show
- the dogs are used to a lot of routine, and they are used to a lot of human contact time (vets, technicians and researchers are around a lot of the time), as well as tending to be group housed - so a family looking for one dog, who will leave alone it for hours on end (when at work) would result in a more stressed dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 00:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The books will generally fit on the 24cm shelves - but I don't know if it is aesthetically better to have shelves all getting smaller? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
