<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2006</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 18:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This may not be what you're looking for if your problem is just seasonal - but I have pretty dry skin and this used to be a big issue for me. And I found that getting your skin in as good shape as possible is really key to making it look good. I make sure I wash my face really well - I just use a basic cleanser but I use a clairsonic - I think it really works wonders. Next use a chemical exfoliant. I'm addicted to Dr. Dennis Gross Alpha Beta peel (aka Black Magic Face Pads) but they are NOT cheap. If this is not a constant issue I don't know that you would find the investment worthwhile. There are other peels that have some of the same ingredients though. After that, I then moisturize giving time for it to sink in well, and then I follow with primer - also giving it sink in time. Then I use my Bare Minerals foundation that I use all over followed by the tinted mineral veil. I'm using the compact formula now which has a bit more coverage than the loose powder - when I used that I would use a powder concealer to touch up any red still shining through. This way it was easy to blend it into my overall foundation.

I sometimes find with blemishes and nose dryness liquid concealer can often get cakey especially as the hours pass on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 22:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would afford the same control the pill gives to women - having personal and discreet control over your re-productivity. It was probably more revolutionary when it was made available to women because the other methods are often complicated, unreliable, or unavailable to women of social status. [Try getting  getting your tubes tied or even getting an IUD as a woman who hasn't had children *now, much less 53 years ago]. 

Men do have the option of condoms, though I understand many men don't like to use them, and relatively easy access to vasectomies (which can be reversed). The pill however is a discreet and simple way for personal control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 23:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a well-meaning and legitimate question: why did you take your kids with you to Ikea?

We live near one and my husband and I go fairly often just to eat meatballs and stock up on tealights and crab paste (KRABBA!). But I see kids swarming all the time; I almost stepped on one when it divebombed in front of me. But I've *really* always wondered why they are even there. And if they are, why they aren't in Small-land? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 21:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tend to blend my Milk base out, especially around the edges, with my fingers. I don't typically wait terribly long, but a minute or two, and then I just apply my eyeshadow with brushes as normal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 16:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was in high school my mom gave me a few Bobbi Brown lip palettes. I never really used them - but I wasn't very into lipstick or very serious about my makeup. Luckily I saved all the things (and they held up) and now  ten years later I use them pretty frequently!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 20:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know of at least a few stores where it has nothing to do with my perception - these gendered sections are in fact *labeled* as such. I was at a chain store specializing in scrapbooking materials that had a labeled "BOYS" section, where the Star Wars stickers and paper was located, and the "GIRLS" section - no Star Wars. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 18:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look fantastic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Artist Coco Layne - a photo series called WARPAINT explores gender presentation within the masculine and feminine spectrum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 17:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 16:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a lifelong (female) Star Wars fan I get super mad when there are stores where things are categorized by gender and Star Wars are under the 'boy' section. I have to restrain myself...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 15:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES! This was my first time using it and it was instant love! Prior to getting on MUA, I had really only used pencil liners. I picked up a liquid liner a few weeks ago (Loreal Lineur Intense) but wasn't too pleased with it - didn't really have the opacity I wanted.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 02:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 00:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I uploaded this on my tablet and didn't have a chance to write up a product list, but here it is:

* **Face:**
* Olay Fresh Effects BB Cream (light to medium)
* Bare Minerals (Medium Beige)
* *Contouring with:*
* Bobbi Brown Bronzing Powder (1 Natural)
* Bare Minerals Eye Brightener (Well-Rested)
* *Blush:*
* Bare Minerals (the Aphrodisiac)

* **Eyes:**
* NYX Jumbo Eye Pencil (Milk)
* Elf Geometric Eyeshadow Book (Glam - used some of the green shades)
* Maybelline Eye Studio Gel Liner
* Maybelline MegaPlush Mascara

* **Brows:**
* Benefit Browzings (medium)

* **Lips:**
* NYX Soft Matte Lip Cream (Sao Paulo)

edit: formatting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Target Haul and First Ever B A - CC very W! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 00:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 00:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I missed it too! ALAS :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 23:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so BADASS. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 17:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Delivering something warm? Or perhaps with catnip? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 15:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not Python related, but Michael Palin, I adore your travelogues. Pole to Pole is probably my favorite - I love the vastly different cultures you encounter but I have to imagine that passing through the USSR just as it was on the brink of collapse was shocking. I was amazed that it did not seem at all imminent to many of the people you met. What has been your favorite trip so far? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 15:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was in elementary school I was home sick and my mom rented me Holy Grail. She said she thought I would like it and went out to run errands. I loved it, and when it got to the end I actually sat through all of the music after the film ends. I sat there waiting for the movie to come back before I realized that it wasn't. Then I sat and laughed my ass off realizing it was actually the best way it could have ended. 

To this day, I still watch it when I'm home sick. I'm convinced it has healing powers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 15:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The part of "The Universe" when Eric and Terry are in space and the big green grid comes up is where I always conceived of all maths happening. Thank you, it makes maths much more enjoyable. 

It starts at 1:35
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JWVshkVF0SY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 04:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Document everything and GET A LAWYER!! Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 18:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [ugh](http://imgur.com/y1hV9pt) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 05:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depending on how old grandma is she may not know the neighbor girl's age. When I visit my grandparents' assisted living home some people ask when I'm graduating from high school and others attempt to set me up with their sons who would be my father's age. I'm in my late 20s. I've just realized that at a certain age, you stop caring or being capable of determining young people's ages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 20:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad (an engineer) has always said that "big ass" is a technical term.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 15:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In high school we read the play "'Master Harold'...and the Boys" by Athol Fugard - a play that explores institutional racism in apartheid-era South Africa. People were so uncomfortable calling the characters black (or white), that my teacher had to routinely tell people to stop calling the black characters African-Americans. I recall him yelling, "THEY'RE JUST AFRICANS." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 05:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The beer shampoo  interesting... my (American) mother used beer on her hair when she was growing up. I think it was supposed to increase shine. She wouldn't really drink beer until she was in her late 40s because for her it was akin to smelling like soap! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 21:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would highly recommend you talking to a counselor or administrator of some kind to get *something* on the record. Also, keep all those texts. Given his aggressive behavior, it would be wise of you to have a record. Since he is your professor, he is in a position of power over you, and he could use that to your great disadvantage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 19:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SWEET SWEET PEARLY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 18:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband and I have played through TTAODK two or three times and I have cried EVERY DAMN TIME.

But then Butt Stallion makes it all betta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 21:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess is that someone Axebombed the place. When I was in college, Axe would send a lot  of the frats boxes of sample sizes. The bros employed them by duct-taping the sprayer down, threw them into suites, and held the doors closed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 15:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I enjoyed it because while the plot could be understood, it did put faith in its audience and put some challenging ideas out there. Also, the way the stunts were done (largely without CGI) were incredibly and really added to my enjoyment of the film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 15:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will say, while the plot, dialogue, and characters were as thin as Chinese gymnast, the reason to enjoy that movie is the incredible set design and costumes. But then you should probably watch the 'making of' videos instead of the movie itself... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
