<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3761</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 22:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like single lane roundabouts. Once you add more lanes, the idiocy of the population kicks in. Most people just ignore the lanes in those.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 22:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What should I use to clean it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 03:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/wtf has actually been making me say wtf. Thank you, reddit, for finally putting out weird shit again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Age requirement for suspensions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 05:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suspensions have interested me since I first saw them, and I'm interested in doing one (or more if I like it), but I'm wondering if there's an age requirement (or an age you'd suggest) for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 05:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [These are probably what you're looking for.](http://www.sickplugs.co.uk/product/blue-snowglobe-plug) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 05:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think 15-16 is the minimum. At that age, you have an okay scope of a job, college, and the rest of your life. At 10, you're hardly out of elementary school (if that). I also think that piercings should be fully the decision of the one being pierced. Pierced babies always frustrate me. I understand that the school and parents are okay with it, but I hope she was given a talk about how future employers might not be okay with it. I've wanted stretched ears when I was younger, but I didn't even know how people wanted to do it; I thought you needed some type of surgery, which my parents would never allow. Once I got a bit older and a bit more educated on it, along with showing responsibility, my mom allowed it. I definitely think 10 is too young to start stretching, but I don't think there should be any laws or regulations on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 05:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With my first piercings, the 18-14 jump wasn't happening at all. My second piercings, however, went from 18-14 seamlessly. It ultimately depends on your ears/piercings. If it feels like you have to force it through, it's too big of a jump for your ears.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 05:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep my stuff in a transparent blue lock box (from Walmart, so it's not far from pickable; just enough to keep it from popping open) and I have each pair in a labelled 'drug dealer' baggie. I would do the tackle box system (which I really like) but I don't quite have enough plugs to have a system for that, and I find the labels a bit easier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 05:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'll be doing that. I'm diligent about keeping only steel in fresh stretches, and I'm planning on getting mostly glass, steel, wood, or other non-acrylic plugs and tunnels in my goal size. I have one acrylic pair, but I'd only be wearing them for a day at most. The spirals I would wear over night and such, so sleeping on them probably didn't help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 05:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Morgan Joyce/ilymorgannn is pretty reputable when it comes to piercings and the advice that comes with them. I would give that link as advice myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 05:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BAF has fossilized mammoth tusks for over $1000. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 05:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From my experience, Wal-Mart does better piercings than Claire's. My first holes were done by Claires, and I needed a taper to go to 16g, but my second holes could go up to 14 right away. My first holes have also been extremely sensitive. This is also problematic for me because I want to stretch to 2g, but I don't want my ears funny looking with the outside being the larger hole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 04:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bodyartforms.com all the way. I've had completely good experience with them, and you get free o rings and a sticker along with a gauge card with every order, and who doesn't like free things? They also have a huge selection (with decent prices) and excellent service. Their shipping rates are also decent, and it's only $1 to add insurance to the order.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 04:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read on BAF that Kaos is discontinuing their o rings. Is there anywhere else that sells clear silicone? With my recent BAF orders, I've been choosing the clear o rings as the freebies since they're not like the standard black ones that come with everything, but since they're being discontinued, I might need a new source.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about acrylic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 04:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I started wearing some 14g acrylic spirals in a healed stretch, and I noticed that a really small area around/in the piercing was a reddish pink. I didn't know if this was just dye coming off of the spirals, or a reaction to them. My ears don't feel irritated while wearing them. I clean the spirals with rubbing alcohol and a q tip and they usually turn the q tip pink which is why I thought it was maybe the dye.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 04:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In what way does the stretching speed effect the shrinking? Does faster stretching mean faster shrinking? I'm kinda in the same boat as OP with stretching, and I'm only at a 12 so not too worried yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 03:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pictured the entire scene when I saw that. Bomb jacket and everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 00:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Accept my selfie.](http://i.imgur.com/3ObI9oY.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 03:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Build underground. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 03:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> klol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 03:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't the period stuff get taught in 5th-6th grade? Or at least health classes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 02:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to download the game and it's stuck at 0%. I don't know how to get it to download or if it's just a really big download, but it's been stuck for an hour or so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 03:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why mannequins exist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 04:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After looks amazing!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-16 20:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever heard of camera phones? They're these awesome new things that are phone, but they have a camera on them too. It's really neat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 23:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TI Calculator Program Help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 13:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have some programs for my TI 84 Silver that I want to convert to my TI 84 SilverC. I want to know if this is possible. If I can't convert it, can I just write the program straight into the 84C? I'd also like to know if there's a pc program that can read calculator programs to display the code and allow editing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 00:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legal pads. Although it's understandable why most people aren't exactly passionate about them, I just love them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 00:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not alone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-10 20:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I spent $10 on a roll of toilet paper with Mitt Romney's face printed on it. It was funny for about three seconds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 23:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to use Meeko as a follower so bad but I'm afraid of losing him :/ I'm hoping one of my kids will want to adopt him so I can keep him and he won't die. I wish I was on PC so I could console him immortal or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 22:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine was a battle axe with a pretty good enchantment too. I have a feeling it was frost or shock. I always want to destroy every other holds' special weapon out of spite. I wouldn't be able to just let Lydia go. I always make sure she's at home with my kids so she's out of danger. I refuse to have them live at homes away from Breezehome, because the walls of Whiterun are rather safe. Losing Lydia would crush me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 02:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I found out I sold the axe of Whiterun. I'm attached to Whiterun, so when I found out I sold that axe because level 8 me was scraping for money, I was pretty sad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 02:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no getting out of these downvotes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 02:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Janessa in Whiterun. I hardly enter the Drunken Huntsman or hire followers, so it didn't affect me in the slightest. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-20 19:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just kind of his thing. In pretty much all of his videos, he's shirtless. Davey just embraces his nudity. He always wears pants in videos, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is just fun to stare at. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 16:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 15:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like it would be smarter to carry around a cheap smartphone (or at least not shitty looking phone) to avoid OP's classmate's situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Place to visit- Ancestor Glade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 04:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Dawnguard Spoiler](#dg "If you haven't been to (or found) Ancestor Glade yet, I definitely recommend it. It is by far, one of the most beautiful and mysterious places in the game. It's just south east of Peak's Shade Tower in a mountain near Falkreath. There's a few spriggans, but after getting past those, is a large cavern similar to the Gildergreen Sanctuary. There's odd trees with unharvestable bark (unless you have the proper tool) so bring the nettlebane if you have it in case that will work. This is one of those locations that I probably wouldn't have found if I didn't climb mountains a lot, so it's easy to miss but worth the travel. If anyone knows any more about it, sharing is great!") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 02:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 02:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does Dawnguard make you a vampire regardless? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dawnguard or Dragonborn? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 01:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which should I get first? Does it matter? I want the best experience, and I don't know if having both at once will be good, or if it will even be noticeable. Any help is appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 22:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you react to the more extreme fans/fan art? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 00:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should only take 3 sheets with 2 ply.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I get a whole number while working with chemistry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 03:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 22:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought that if I had a blanket covering my body, I would be safe from the world's horrors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 02:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Just typed them in the wrong order. The rest of the letters I can only justify by the cat walking across the keyboard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 02:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's just a universal tradition thing now and one of those pointless etiquette rules. I went to a summer camp that made you run around the mess hall as everyone chanted if you had your elbows on the table. When I got home I slammed my elbows on the table and embraced the freedom.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 21:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd stay off the subreddit if you're worried about spoilers... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 00:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have porn on my computer and I'm still too paranoid to put my laptop on the tv. You get some bravery points.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 17:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't hate Justin Bieber. I'm not a fan, but there's no reason to hate him. He probably makes more in ten minutes than I will in a lifetime, and it's just immature to hate him for songs he released years ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 17:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only time I will cosplay or get even the slightest bit weird with my interest in anime, is at an anime con. It's a designated place and time for people that like anime to be a bit more open about it and it's a bit more accepted to let loose. I still refuse the weird noises.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't know where they're going wielding tiki torches... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 04:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 02:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do my best not to post unless it's in a subreddit for teens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 02:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played that once. It destroyed my processor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 23:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [My gloriously fangirl drenched, possibly triggering, and quite unoriginal blog.] (http://mikovargas.tumblr.com/)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-29 21:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the actual fuck is that purple _ ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-29 20:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember finding the lyric book for my band in 4th grade. Even made a dvd of one of the songs. Snapped the cd and disposed of the lyrics. Never again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 23:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The third and fourth ones kind of look like the models on packaged Halloween costumes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 22:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm afraid there would be many crusty sleeves without tissues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 02:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I haven't. Only a few other ones a while back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 01:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any shaders kill my computer. It's not worth the FPS drop for me. I use a regular laptop, so that might be the problem. But I'm not getting a gaming pc just for shaders.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 01:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They *are* a thing with the new snapshots and upcoming 1.7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 01:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That link is purple _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wrong. It leads to the inevitable, "Mommy, why does Daddy's dick get hard when shoves his fingers down my throat?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 01:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-21 03:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made the decision that if I purchase any over priced clothing, it had better have the brand name emblazoned on it for justification.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 01:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only confirmed gay character is Sweden. The rest is just speculation (based off of consistent hints).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 01:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It could be worse I guess.](http://www.deviantart.com/art/Commission-Erica-rose-the-hedgehog-318004653) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 01:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering why the picture of America was included until I remembered most redditors aren't Hetalia fans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 01:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That one makes much more sense than the other pictures, since the character represents America. The Sonic ones are agreeably where it gets weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 01:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Philosopher was changed to sorcerer so that American children would know it was about wizards and be more likely to read the book.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 19:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might want to tag that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 19:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a repost from the list of top posts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 01:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any way to get her armor besides killing her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 01:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It always feels good.](https://gs1.wac.edgecastcdn.net/8019B6/data.tumblr.com/c21cd83ea070204a95e981d633063e86/tumblr_mig1e8Okmz1s51zjyo1_250.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 02:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well fuck. I guess that time I looked up pork recipes really screwed me over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 06:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He posts tweets like this regularly. That's a pretty dedicated 'hacker'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 21:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP might not be drinking age but still on their own.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 19:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Breezehome, I would organize my potions and such on shelves and get everything nice and neat down to the last cup. Save and go off to do a quest. Come home to a disaster. I always blamed Lydia for having a party while I was gone even though it's just an annoying glitch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robin Thicke </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 18:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 19:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another reddit legend dug up at least once a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 18:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thomas isn't that bad. Not everyone will pick up on the train reference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 18:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not teal. It's *marine*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-06 19:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shouldn't have clicked that. I should *not* have clicked that. [Eyewash time -very SFW](http://kittiesntitties.tumblr.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-02 05:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/popping Would love to have a go at that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 07:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this on facebook too, but I can never really tell if TF4 is a thing or its just heavily rumored. There hasn't been much official word that I've seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 03:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...wrong subreddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 03:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> .....I'm damn adorable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-26 18:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's in the depths of the sidebar. http://www.stickermule.com/products/snowboarding-sticker
There you go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
