<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6216</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Pug Mid-Sneeze </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 18:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 18:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking to stock up on this stuff so if anyone else sees this and has some used or unused bottles, please let me know!!  
I can't believe how helpful people on reddit have been  :)   you guys are awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 18:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes!! Thats exactly what Im looking for!! :)  
I will happily get you $5. Do you have paypal? I'm not sure the best way to get you the money but I will message you.  
I'm completely ok with the bottle not being completely full. We know how difficult these are to find and shes just going to be excited to get it! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] A Discontinued Lotion. Breathe Romance, Bath and Body Works </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 01:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if this is the best subreddit.
I'm looking for a discontinued lotion from bath and body works called Breathe Romance. My friend wants it for her Birthday but I can't do $60 a bottle. I was hoping an awesome person on Reddit here would sell me a partially used bottle for a little cheaper.  
  
Please let me know if you guys have any ideas!!! My friend really loves this lotion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 01:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ill take a look at that subreddit as well, Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 01:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bath   Body Works Breathe Romance 24/7 Moisture Boost Body Lotion - Sensuous Amber Myrrh 8.4 fl oz.

So something close Amber Myrrh maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Closest Scent to Breathe Romance Lotion? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 01:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone remember the Breathe Romance collection from bath and body works? Its been discontiued for a few years and my friend was really wanting it for her birthday. I really didn't want to do the $60 on ebay for a small bottle :/  
  
Do you know of a scent that would be really similar to this lotion? Preferably also in another lotion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a Discontinued Lotion. Breathe Romance, BBW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 01:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 01:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, Ill try posting there as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 01:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
