<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9584</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 19:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's some serious tint on those windows. Something's going down in that truck that's making him have to repent so hard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 17:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Raccoon Cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 23:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Apparently yes and no.](http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=761122).


They say he's been fined 3 times prior. Apparently you only get 1 game per number of instance. What a joke. 

And it's a joke that the NHL takes into account injury. Players get injured in totally legal plays. Why don't those legal plays get suspensions if injuries are reasons to suspend? And plenty of players are incredibly not injured, like in this instance, or others like countless boarding penalties that could have resulted in devastating neck injuries. It's the ACT, not the result that merits the suspension.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 22:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should not be playing hockey right now. The suspension for his crosscheck to the neck should have sidelined him for the season, not 4 games. And Byfuglien only got 2 minutes for that. And no further action after the game. NHL discipline is an absolute joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 20:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aggressive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 18:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so you just quote that whole thing to people in conversation, huh?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 22:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You are the father.](http://24.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_lgisjjDXUM1qcgjnyo1_500.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SALE - Prosperity at Miniature Market for $12 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 15:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 15:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Top 24 Hardwood Floors Found Under Carpeting: #14 Will Blow Your Mind! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 15:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Owls love playing floor-sock. Entertainment for months and you don't have to shell out a dime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 22:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF = Wow That's Fuckingawesomeasfucknatureiscool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 15:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was me every time the Sabres looked like they were going to win a game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 23:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually pretty impressive. Have you ever watched TBS/TNT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 21:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ew. I would never. Gross, dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 21:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen that either? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 21:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jurassic Park came out before you were born. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 18:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think my boss will mind? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 18:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone please direct Corey Feldman to the burn unit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 18:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty cool. A local theater near me does that every once in awhile. Caught Rear Window there a couple weeks ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 17:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a question or a statement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 17:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/epFSELK.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 17:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So...a muffin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 17:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry. I also murdered two people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A true confession. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 15:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 14:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's probably why he was able to get the steals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 01:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right?? I guess they're only doing solo efforts as top goals because he passed that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 21:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shipping from **Buffalo, NY**

**[H]**

* **Fortune   Glory** Like new - only played once. $60 + shipping

* **Settlers of Catan** Like new - only played a few times. $20?

**[W]** Cash/paypal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 19:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> verizon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 18:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wi-Fi is turning itself on. I have Wi-Fi off, and then it just turns on by itself and connects to networks around me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 18:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I much prefer Mona Lisa Smile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 17:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I can't tell if you're just fucking with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 17:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 16:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He hasn't read it yet


From the article: "Musk is a constant reader, and this represents just a small selection of books he has publicly spoken about reading" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Note 4 keeps turning on and connecting to wifi automatically. I can't get it to stop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 16:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the Wi-Fi advanced settings I've unchecked "always allow scanning" but it's still doing this. What else can I do to stop it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 16:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that Elon Musk included the Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy in the books he frequently touches on. Amid all the deep, philosophical and intellectual texts, it's often just as important to laugh and be silly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 15:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd put Tarasenko, Ovie and Ennis in the top 3.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NHL's Top 10 Goals of the Year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 15:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 22:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if Fanduel has a player's name in grey font in the lineup, what does that mean? Are they tentative? A subsitute? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should share your analysis with everyone so we can tell if you're on to something or not. For science.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My work has very strict restrictions on software downloads and I can't get f.lux at the office. Does anyone know of a settings for the monitor colors/brightness that will mimic the f.lux software? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can I tell if my monitors are "flicker-free" or not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 16:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would just like to thank you for saying RBI and not RBI's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heading To Rogers Centre next weekend - where to sit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 16:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be heading up for the weekend stand against the Braves. I'm looking at either the 200 infield level, 1st/3rd baseline or behind home plate. Does anyone have preferences for views? Are there any perks with the 200 level; is it considered 'club' or just higher up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 15:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started DFS earlier this year with NBA and NHL and have been pretty successful. I do a fair amount of research and it's worked out. Through two days of MLB (and I've played regular fantasy baseball for years and follow the sport closely) it's been a disaster. I've scored 14 and 11 points respectively between Monday and Tuesday. How are people consistently successful at MLB DFS? What are people doing to build good lineups day to day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 00:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it looks like Scott is listed as the starter, but from what I've read, it looks like Muscala should get more minutes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 22:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With Cousins out and the terrible defense on both ends, how about Payne as a punt at PF? I'm looking at either him or Muscala/Scott. Thoughts on Payne or which one of those guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 20:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was going to downvote you until I read your edit. Good point for the illustration...it might work better, and be more reflective of reality, if the money stairs were barricaded by glass walls or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 18:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why's it named Puzzles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 18:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fans of ??? will be very excited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 14:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my first MLB day ever, I scored 14.5 points on FD. So yea...I guess it's all up from here... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 14:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're around college age, people rent out rooms in houses to students, or people look to sublet their room that's in a house with their friends. I've been on both sides of the subletting arrangement and it's totally fine. You can go, meet the people first and decide if it'd be worth it. You can easily find some spots under $500/month for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MLB TV issues going fullscreen on mac </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 00:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone else have this problem? It happened on my older macbook and on my new one now, no matter the browser. If I go fullscreen in MLB TV, it only fills like 2/3 of the screen. Any fix to this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 00:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been refreshing it, I saw one post about an hour ago that had him in the lineup  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 00:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Paul Pierce starting/playing tonight??  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 22:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not even mad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 22:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. I was gonna brag about starting fanduel 4 weeks and going from $100 deposit to $191 with NBA/NHL $1-$2 GPP's   H2H's but damn that's some money. 


Also...can I borrow some money? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 22:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> great advice. taking pictures of my bike's serial number when I get home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 20:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, Murphy thinks he's being pinned against something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 18:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thaddeus Young or Ilyasova tonight? Vegas has Nets at 10 more points than Bucks tonight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 17:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thoughts on loading up with Anthony Davis and Cousins?? Big price tags and playing each other, but both teams give up a lot of points to those positions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Foggy morning in my hometown - can someone photoshop Pyramid Head from Silent Hill into the photo?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 17:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 21:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't decide between Parsons and Ariza tonight. Any thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 21:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any thoughts of C Parsons v T Ariza tonight? I'm torn on them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend filmed this video for a high school student's poem - This Is Genius </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 22:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 02:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yea, that's the name </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 23:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Sabres fan, this has me a bit worried. Let's say we lock up last place, then lose the lottery getting 2nd pick and Eichel...I'm worried that Murray throws some insane package out there to trade the 2nd pick, Reinhart other prospects/picks for McDavid. He seems to be one of the few that think the gap between McDavid and Eichel is pretty big. I don't think it's that huge...at least not bigger than what it would take to trade for him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any cooking classes around Buffalo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 15:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 13:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that an actual Arnold quote? Do you know from where?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 17:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or drink the water.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 17:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't tell if this is a joke or not... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 17:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in WNY and it's always taken about a week to get to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> S Pen smart select question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 15:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I take a screen grab with the smart select and share it, if there's any text, the note 4 transcribes all the text from the image into the message. Kind of redundant and can make the message really awkward to send. Is there any way to remove this feature?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 02:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are those? I'm running NHL mostly. I only see 20 man league entries that pay top 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FanDuel - what is the difference between Tournaments and Leagues? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 15:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 15:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started The Gunslinger a couple days ago and my only problem with it is I can't put it down and my girlfriend wants me to "talk to her" during dinner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 14:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Sabres fan, I'd be offended if I wasn't rooting for them to lose every game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 13:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a Feldian sales day. Too bad the AquaSphere and La Isla sales aren't on the same site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> La Isla on Sale at Miniature Market - $19.99 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 13:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 13:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fantastic. I picked it up a month or so ago when it became available on Amazon at $35. Worth every penny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 16:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but seriously...how much do you vary up your lineups when you put in 100 entries? Do you put in 10 each of 10 different ones? Hope a couple of them hit big? try to do as many different ones as possible?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 16:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Word. I put in two entries in the $2 tournament and won $12. So, yea...I'm upgrading it to a meal at Subway for lunch today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 15:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all very true. good points. just stands out when they're the first ones I've done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 14:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea it's just crazy...the one guy I keep noticing has easily cleared $10k in this week from the entries that I've seen. He's won two tournaments ($3k each) finished 2nd ($2k) and a bunch of other top 10's). I know people play head to heads for big money and what not, so it's not the money that sways me, it's just how someone can consistently do that out of 20,000 people. Especially in something that can be as random as hockey with butt bounces and deflections etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just started on fanduel...question on how some people do in tournaments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 13:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started on fanduel and, as a big hockey fan, have done some of the tournaments the past week. I've noticed one user has won at least two of them and has had several entries in the top 10 every time. I don't get how this is possible. Up to 20,000 entries per tournament, and this one guy can regularly win the whole thing? How many entries do people put into these tournaments? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 19:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is possibly the most Canadian joke I've ever heard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 14:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not if you buy $75 of more games :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 13:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Also available on Amazon](http://www.amazon.com/Asmodee-LIBT01USASM-Libertalia-Board-Game/dp/2914849877/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 qid=1425991169 sr=8-1 keywords=libertalia) for $33.41 with free shipping if you're a prime member (US) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Libertalia on sale at Miniature Market - $25 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 13:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the weirdest thing you can buy on Amazon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 21:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 17:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Truly understand their needs

Drugs   alcohol is their needs? Systematic humiliation? Are you kidding me? You know you can actually talk to these people right. You can ask them what they need. Who in here is promoting the humiliation of homeless people? If someone is begging on the street with the sole purpose of extorting money for free booze   drugs, than they're systematically humiliating themselves. If you got off your inane libertarian pedestal you'd see that. if you asked someone what they want, and they said 'cigarettes,' ask why. Chances are if they're that honest, your perfectly picked exception, is probably accurate. If they say food, then you offer to buy it for them, and they say no, then they're lying and want drugs, not something helpful. Your argument isn't controversial. It's short-sighted and lacks any thought of actually engaging the person in conversation. You're just lazy and don't want to be bother finding out what the person needs, you just want to absolve yourself of any responsibility while up on your pedestal of moral disposition.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 17:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! And if you live somewhere that gets cold...scarves, hats, gloves, etc. Lots of cities are popping up with scarf trees or poles, where people tie scarves (or hats) to trees so the homeless can anonymously grab whatever they need. Donating these warm items and other daily essentials are some of the most important donations to shelters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 16:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Just move on. Dude was just looking for money for drugs/alcohol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 16:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I'd rather attempt to give sustainable nourishment to someone that is rock bottom than worry about their dignity and just say yes to enabling drugs and alcohol dependence. So would everyone else with a conscience. Please see your downvotes as evidence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 16:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely this. It doesn't ever have to be a surprise. Ask them if they'd like food and what they would prefer or anything they need to avoid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 16:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because you're likely enabling a substance dependence/abuse disorder and not actually helping them get nourishment they may need? Because most chronically homeless have some sort of mental disorder; roughly 1/3rd of the homeless have very severe mental disorders. They're often not in a mindset to differentiate between what's good and bad for them. You may not give a shit if someone drinks themself unconscious or uses heroin, but don't act like you're doing it out of some sort of moral principle. You just don't care. Which is the problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 16:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use your words. Say hey, I don't have any cash, but is there any food I could get you from the store? If they say no, then all they likely wanted was cash for drugs or alcohol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 14:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or get off your cynical ass, and do volunteer work or check to make sure you're donating to a worthwhile charity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 14:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't WTF. This is actually helpful information, albeit posed in a very dramatic manner. I've worked for NPO's focused on aid to impoverished and homeless, and done volunteer work for like organizations in my city. Do NOT give cash. The vast majority of the chronically homeless have mental disorders and substance abuse issues. Maybe they do want food, but when they walk into the 7-11 with your $5, you're damn right they'll see those 40's and buy a couple instead. If you want to do something right there for them, go into the nearest convenient store and buy them a hot meal or hot cocoa. Or find a local organization and volunteer or donate to them. and if you want to make sure the charity you're donating to is worthwhile, visit www.charitywatch.com, www.charitynavigator.com or www.givewell.com. 

Edit: I'm not sure if a lot of these responses saying 'homeless guy said fuck off or threw my food away when I offered' are trying to prove my point or argue against me. You are allowed to talk to them, and ask if they would like food and if so, what they can eat (being aware of allergies). If they say fuck off or no, then just keep on moving, they were only looking for free drugs/alcohol anyway.   ....   and thanks for the gold anonymous stranger! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 14:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Obviously the picture is blurry

*"and I refuse to take a new one"*

Also, that is zero **Splendor** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 19:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Now accepting questions](http://i.imgur.com/Fgsukcg.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 19:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dungeon Lords: Happy Anniversary - on Sale at CoolStuffInc - $64.99 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 17:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 15:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know...I'm not picking up a newspaper that is 3/4ths info on Rochester, Syracuse and Albany. I just don't care that much about their local goings on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 02:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever seen a goalie jump?? When the shit has a goalie ever jumped? The crossbar isn't 8 feet high.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coyotes are now literally dodging pucks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 15:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 14:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. I was annoyed at other people saying he was deaf etc. /u/excelius was the last I saw and did offer it as a suggestion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 04:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Person was high. It was only the first question he asked. He literally just forgot to speak out loud and then laughed and spoke normally the rest of the time. Reddit fuckin loves jumping to conclusions without any questions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 04:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, he wasn't deaf (you asshole). It was only the first question. He talked normally after that. He literally just forgot to speak out loud. He also giggled after he realized it and his eyes were bloodshot. I'm not a moron, I know the difference between a deaf person and high person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Customize the lower left menu button </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 20:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just switched from Galaxy S4 to the Note 4. On my S4, the menu button brought up a settings menu. In the Note 4 it brings up the multitasking pane of all the open apps. Can I switch this to the settings pop up menu option? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The guy who made my sandwich at Subway today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 20:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 17:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mesothelioma 

Yea, those damn asbestos dandelions are getting out of hand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 19:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are local Patterson reps with offices on Filmore in Tonawanda and in Crosspoint Pkwy in Getzville.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 14:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he said "we have two cars." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 07:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This current war I know we were matched up in a couple minutes. It's usually pretty quick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 06:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd think at some point we'd be the overly strong clan at some point by accident or something  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [War] Clan Wars - my clan is always outmatched </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 06:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My clan of 30 has been getting killed on wars. I don't get how we're being matched up. We are consistently being put against clans with much higher bases than any of us. I don't get it. Why could this be happening?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 01:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Thumbs Up](http://i.imgur.com/sn3Brky.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 22:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell yea. Keep up the fight! Just [keep reaching for sticks](http://d24w6bsrhbeh9d.cloudfront.net/photo/a2NXEze_700b.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 22:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you pick the Sabres now no one will call you a bandwagoner! Worst team in the league! But there's oodles of young talent in the pipeline and we're on the inside track for McDavid or Eichel, so we'll have a superstar (hopefully) and contender (hopefully) for years to come.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 22:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that's a draw for you then more power to you. I couldn't think of a more boring team than the Devils for in terms of pure style...the Devils are responsible for ruining pre-lockout hockey with their trap. Made games unbearably boring and clogged up. Give me an open, exciting game every time please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 22:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs more explosions, eagles and dinosaurs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 22:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Walter's money is just to the right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 22:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember kids: if there's one instance of something it's true all the time. Someone has clorox wipes on their desk? Office is always dirty! Someone works everyday? Probably no vacation time! 


How about instead of drawing bizarre conclusions from random observations that could have a million different causes, you just ask to see the company's benefits package. That seems reasonable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 21:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *"and that wasn't my penis"* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Less than a day left. Are you backing Trickerion? Why or why not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 19:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
