<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9876</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even adults would be caught unawares.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How could you focus on work when you have that kind of interruption? I always love cats, but it would be unfair to get one when I know I won't have much time to spend playing with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 10:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe there are some window films with various designs that you can use to cover the lower part of your window, so you can keep your privacy which is available in Purlfrost. As for having more of natural light, you can use mirrors or reflective surfaces in your home decor and place them strategically to fill your home with brightness and natural light. If you put mirrors close to your windows, it will bounce light into your space amplifying natural light, and it will make your windows seem bigger and brighter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 10:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if an experiment works, something has definitely gone wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 09:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we put more consideration to individuals rather than the species, arent we disregarding the fact that all elements of an ecosystem are important to the functioning of that ecosystem. We think only from a human standpoint, but we cannot look at nature only from a human standpoint because ecosystems are so complex that we wont be able tot totally understand all the connections and actions and interactions happening within them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Booming World of Architecture That Only Exists In Pixels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 09:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Architect and Interior Designer Build Their Fantasy Home in Tropical Paradise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 09:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 50 Surprising Photos From The Past That Show How Different Life Used To Be </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 09:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Centennial Tree House / Wallflower Architecture + Design </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 08:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 08:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe to drive away ruffians and evil spirits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 07:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should be a member of Rick's restoration team with that kind of skill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paint against the clock festival raises enigmatic smiles across London </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 17:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 17:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand, and thank you very much for reminding me of the rule. I will be very cautious on my posts when I do it next time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 16:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a can of beer on my desk now as I am writing this comment. (But hey I am not a binge drinker! I sound so defensive here, don't I?) But yes, I think binge drinking is bad especially when people deny it to themselves that they do. Like in another case of being alcoholic without admitting to yourself that you are indeed an alcoholic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evolution of sneakers explored at Brooklyn Museum exhibition, 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 16:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
