<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject138</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Civilians trapped in a Palestinian refugee camp in Syria's capital have fled to safer areas amid intense shelling and clashes between Palestinian armed factions and the Islamic State of Iraq and the Levant (ISIL) fighters who took over most of the camp, Syrian activists said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 22:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraqi Prime Minister Haidar al-Abadi told a German magazine that armies in the region around Iraq had no chance of defeating Islamic State (IS) if the militants continued to recruit ideologically indoctrinated foreign fighters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 22:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> City officials like Department of Public Works director Rudy Chow claim that residents using water without paying are to blame for the $40 million in overdue water bills. In fact, the Baltimore Sun found more than a third of the unpaid bills stem from just 369 businesses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 22:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uhuru Kenyatta, Kenya's president, has said the al-Shabab assault that killed 148 people at a university is an "attack on humanity" and vowed to take harsh measures against what he called "extremists". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 22:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Georgia Legislature Just Pulled the Plug on Electric Cars - But it gets worse for electric vehicle (EV) boosters. Legislators are adding a $200-a-year annual fee for owners to offset the loss of gasoline taxes that drivers would otherwise pay to maintain roads. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 03:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ansas Gov. Sam Brownback (R) signed a bill into law on Thursday that allows Kansas residents over the age of 21 to carry concealed weapons without any permit or training requirements, as long as that individual is not prohibited from possessing a firearm under either federal or state law. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 02:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As part of President Obamas plans to combat climate change, the White House announced a program on Friday for the U.S. Department of Energy to train 75,000 people to work in the solar power industry by 2020 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 02:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 01:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the correction in spelling and the funny pun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Iraqi forces take Tikrit, a wave of looting and lynching - The vehicles were crammed with refrigerators, air conditioners, computer printers, and furniture. A young militia fighter rode on a red bicycle, gleefully shouting: "I always dreamed of having a bike like this as a kid." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 01:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 02:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> McConnell is married to the daughter of a Chinese shipping magnet. I believe McConnell is playing both China and the US for personal gain. He has a foot in each country, and his Chinese father-in-law has financed McConnell's past elections. I don't trust the putz one bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democracy v Psychology: why people keep electing idiots - And the archetype George W Bush was the president. For 8 years. The man whose idiotic musings managed to sustain businesses had a nuclear arsenal at his command. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 00:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans need to get away from the religious freedom debate. Now. - The more that Republicans talk about social issues, the harder it will be for the eventual nominee to portray him or herself as a different kind of Republican to the undecided voter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 00:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democracy v Psychology: why people keep electing idiots - And the archetype George W Bush WAS the president. For 8 YEARS. The man whose idiotic musings managed to sustain businesses had a nuclear arsenal at his command. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 23:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Artificial Sweeteners May Change Our Gut Bacteria in Dangerous Ways - In other words, artificial sweeteners may favor the growth of bacteria that make more calories available to us, calories that can then find their way to our hips, thighs and midriffs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 22:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yemeni Houthi fighters and their allies seized a central Aden district on Thursday, striking a heavy blow against the Saudi-led coalition which has waged a week of air strikes to try to stem advances by the Iran-allied Shi'ite group. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 22:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Governor Christie Told This Man To 'Sit Down And Shut Up' But He's Running For Office Instead - If the governor wants someone whos going to sit down and shut up, then theyre his guys because they have just been yes men for the governor, and not just on the Sandy issue but on a range of issues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 02:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A plan to salvage RadioShack Corps RSHCQ.PK business by co-branding most of its 1,740 surviving stores with cellular phone provider Sprint Corp (S.N) earned U.S. bankruptcy court approval on Tuesday, ending four days of contested court hearings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 02:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraqi troops aided by Shi'ite paramilitaries have driven Islamic State out of central Tikrit, Prime Minister Haidar al-Abadi said on Tuesday, but the fight to retake all of Saddam Hussein's hometown continued. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 02:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Statistics released on Tuesday reveal that the rebranded private security firm [Blackwater], known since 2011 as Academi, reaped over half a billion dollars from the futile Defense Department push to eradicate Afghan narcotics, some 32% of the $1.8bn in contracting money </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 01:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. President Barack Obama on Tuesday vetoed a measure by Republicans in Congress that would have blocked a government labor agency's rules designed to speed up the time it takes to unionize workers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 01:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The political war over gay culture is over, and the gays won - I mean, NASCAR opposed the bill. Being anti-gay is bad for business, and being bad for business is bad politics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 00:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Istanbul prosecutor died from his wounds after security forces stormed the office where members of a far-left Turkish group took him hostage on Tuesday, killing his two captors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 00:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 03:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A golden retriever is artificial selection; a tiger is natural selection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 02:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Believing one book holds all of life's answers is like shutting your mind to the entire universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 02:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ecstasy is the romance novel. Take it with acid and you're now "candy tripping", at least that's what we called in the past.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 02:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The answers to this have a truthiness quality that reflect the cuteness of a polar bear while ignoring it will gladly eat you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The two youngest people killed by the Boston Marathon bombing were torn apart by one of the blasts that ripped through the crowd at the finish line, medical examiners testified on Monday as prosecutors wound up their case against accused bomber Dzhokhar Tsarnaev </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 01:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two people tried to run their vehicle through the National Security Agency's gates near Washington on Monday before guards at the spy agency fatally shot one of them, said officials, who added there was no evidence of a link to terrorism. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 01:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The team operating NASA's Mars Exploration Rover Opportunity learned Thursday that the long-lived rover experienced a brief amnesia event related to its flash memory, the first since a reformatting of that nonvolatile type of memory a week earlier. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 00:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Supreme Court on Monday declined to hear a new challenge to President Barack Obama's healthcare law that took aim at a bureaucratic board labeled by some Republicans as a "death panel" because it was designed to cut Medicare costs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 00:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vulva artist transforms Colorado women's vaginas into body-positive art - He said one of the main messages of his work is simply: Youre normal. Whatever youve got down there, leave it alone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 00:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two bodies were found on Sunday at the site of a gas explosion that destroyed three New York City apartment buildings last week, injuring 22 people, and officials were working to determine if they were those of two men unaccounted for, police said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 00:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Governor Becomes Frustrated When Asked If Religious Liberty Law Will Be Used To Discriminate - Pence had said he was going to appear on the Sunday news show to clarify the intent of the law. Instead, he refused repeatedly to say if the law would greenlight discrimination against people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 00:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indiana Gov. Mike Pence (R) on Sunday defended the religious-freedom bill that he signed last week, saying the growing outrage over the legislation stems from a tremendous amount of misinformation and misunderstanding. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 00:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 21:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dire Straights - *Love Over Gold* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 18:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely agree that most people don't understand a god that asked Abraham to kill his kids just for kicks. You know, the religion that says it's okay for their followers to consider themselves morally superior to unbelievers. If Islam takes over the US, we'll be ready for sharia law because it's been forced on us by "christians." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 00:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching morbidly obese people try to act dainty while eating a really fattening desert. You just know that at home the person vacuums that desert right up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Italy's top court on Friday annulled the conviction of American Amanda Knox for the 2007 murder of British student Meredith Kercher and, in a surprise verdict, acquitted her of the charge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 23:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The spokesman for the Arab coalition bombing Houthi targets in Yemen has said the kingdom and its allies will do whatever it takes to stop Yemen's second largest city from falling to the Shia rebels. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 23:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The American astronaut Scott Kelly and his Russian counterpart Mikhail Kornienko have blasted off to begin a year away from Earth. Gennady Padalka of Russia is also riding in the Soyuz spacecraft; he is scheduled for the standard six-month tour of duty aboard the International Space Station. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 23:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. economic growth cooled in the fourth quarter as previously reported and after-tax corporate profits took a hit from a strong dollar, which could undermine future business spending. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 23:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israel has announced that it will release tax funds to the Palestinian Authority that it has withheld as punishment for its move to join the International Criminal Court. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 22:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 22:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this different from the sharia law that conservatives are always screaming in fear about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 8 Entities Protesting Indianas New LGBT Discrimination Law - Technology professionals are by their nature very progressive, and backward-looking legislation such as the RFRA will make the state of Indiana a less appealing place to live and work, the letter said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 22:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dynel Lane, the Colorado woman accused of attacking a pregnant woman and removing a 7-month-old fetus from her body, was charged with eight felonies by the Boulder County District Attorneys office on Friday, including attempted murder and the unlawful termination of a pregnancy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 22:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate Minority Leader Harry M. Reid (D-Nev.) has endorsed Sen. Charles E. Schumer (D-N.Y.) to succeed him after he retires at the end of 2016. "I think Schumer should be able to succeed me," Reid said in a Friday morning interview at his home in Washington's West End. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 22:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An interest rate hike by the Federal Reserve may be warranted later this year, with a gradual path expected to follow, although a downturn in core inflation or wage growth could force it to hold off, the central bank's chief said on Friday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 22:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Senator Lisa Murkowskis (R-AK) amendment to Congresss budget resolution passed by a vote of 51-49. The legislation would support and fund state efforts  which many argue are unconstitutional  to seize and sell Americas public lands. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 00:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antarctica's Ice Shelves Thin, Threaten Significant Sea Level Rise: The ice shelvessome of which are larger than California and tens to hundreds of yards thickare the linchpins of the Antarctic ice sheet system, holding back the millions of cubic miles of ice contained in the glaciers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 00:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Video Allegedly Shows Cop Planting Drug Evidence After Beating Unarmed Man - A new video released Thursday morning appears to even show Melendez pulling a plastic bag out of his pocket during the incident, although its difficult to discern. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 00:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA's Low-Density Supersonic Decelerator (LDSD) project will be flying a rocket-powered, saucer-shaped test vehicle into near-space from the Navy's Pacific Missile Range Facility on Kauai, Hawaii, in June. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 00:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An apparent gas explosion caused two residential apartment buildings to collapse and burst into flames, and two others to catch fire, injuring 12 people on Thursday in New York City's East Village neighborhood, authorities said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 00:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have raised the alert about an antibiotic routinely prescribed for chest infections, after linking it to an increased risk of epilepsy and cerebral palsy in children whose mothers took the drug during pregnancy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Afghanistan's new president, Ashraf Ghani, warned U.S. lawmakers on Wednesday of the "terrible threat" the Islamic State poses in Asia, and said the militant group is already sending fighters to his country. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 23:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Supreme Court sided with a woman who was faced with the choice to either work her labor-intensive job during pregnancy at the United Parcel Service or go on unpaid leave without benefits. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 23:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Humans are evolving more rapidly than previously thought, according to the largest ever genetics study of a single population. Scientists reached the conclusion after showing that almost every man alive can trace his origins to one common male ancestor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 23:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Galileos on climate change are, like Galileo, the scientists. The people pushing back on the science are, like Cruz, those who favor the status quo. Cruz's comments, from start to finish, are simply not correct. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 23:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Female polar bear raises hopes of birth in captivity - On Wednesday, she will be introduced to an enclosure purpose-built to encourage the delicate, potentially deadly, process of polar bear breeding. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 23:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clarkson left the BBC with no choice but to drop him - Clarkson, with his laddish humour and dodgy jeans, appealed to a demographic who feel left out by calls for diversity  angry white men who somehow believe this fabulously rich, white, privately educated man made it against the odds at the BBC. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 22:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A majority of Americans disapprove of the deal that freed Bergdahl from his Taliban captors, and nearly three-quarters think he should face criminal charges if he deserted his unit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 22:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There was no tape draped across a finish line, but NASA is celebrating a win. The agency's Mars Exploration Rover Opportunity completed its first Red Planet marathon Tuesday -- 26.219 miles (42.195 kilometers) - with a finish time of roughly 11 years and two months. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 23:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The World Social Forum has kicked off in the Tunisian capital with a march in solidarity with the victims of last weeks Bardo museum attack that left 21 people, mostly foreign tourists, dead. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 23:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A sweeping ocean conveyor system that ushers warm tropical waters into the North Atlantic appears to have partly recovered from a near-collapse around the time that the Beatles were breaking up, but the system remains weaker than it had been </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 23:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Katharine Jefferts Schori, presiding bishop of the Episcopal church and one of the most powerful women in Christianity, said that climate change was a moral imperative akin to that of the civil rights movement. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 22:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A California lawyer says he wants to legalize the execution of gay people, and there may be nothing the states attorney general can do to stop the proposal from moving forward. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 22:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Securities and Exchange Commission Chair Mary Jo White told lawmakers on Tuesday the agency would not try anew to craft rules to make it easier for shareholders to nominate corporate directors but that she was closely watching activists' attempts to do just that. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 22:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Tuesday, President Barack Obama dismissed Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahus efforts to walk back his rejection of a Palestinian state and warned that the Jewish leaders comments could empower extremists and lead to violence in the region. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 22:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United States will maintain its current 9,800 troops in Afghanistan through the end of 2015, the White House said in a statement on Tuesday after President Barack Obama met with Afghan President Ashraf Ghani. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 22:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The X-Files is set to return to television screens for the first time in 13 years, with David Duchovny and Gillian Anderson resuming their roles as Mulder and Scully. The US broadcaster Fox has confirmed that a six-episode series will begin production in the summer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 21:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How The Supreme Court Could Repeal The 20th Century - Scalia is, in many ways, a microcosm for the conservative movement as a whole, which has grown increasingly comfortable with aggressive judicial activism as the Supreme Court has moved to the right. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 00:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China's Top Meteorologist: 'Serious Threat' Of Climate Change Could Have 'Huge Impacts' - As the world warms, risks of climate change and climate disasters to China could become more grave, Zheng said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 00:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United States will keep funding Afghan security forces at the targeted peak personnel level of 352,000 at least through the 2017 fiscal year, extending a financial commitment that has cost about $4 billion annually, U.S. officials said on Monday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 00:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Jesse Helms Sink Ted Cruz's Presidential Campaign? In the 1960s, Helms supported apartheid. He was elected to the Senate in 1972 as an opponent of integration, interracial marriage, and civil rights laws. Cruz said his first political donation was a $10 donation to Helms when he was a kid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 00:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Ted Cruz jumped into the 2016 presidential race Monday in the same way he intends to run his campaign: upstaging rival Republican candidates with a splashy, impassioned speech that sought to drag the national conversation further to the right than many in his own party want to go. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 23:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Ted Cruz Is Trying To Appeal To Millenials And Why He Will Ultimately Fail - So I want to encourage everyone here to be arsonists and spread the flame of liberty. There arent any three year old girls, are there? They did card people at the door, please tell me that? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 23:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 23:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to argue against willful ignorance so I won't make any further attempts on that part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everything you need to know about the Ted Cruz birther movement - But birthers weren't making a legal argument about Obama; they were arguing the facts about where he was born and accusing him of perpetrating a massive fraud. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 23:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robert Durst, the real estate scion awaiting extradition to California to face a murder charge, was denied bail on Monday after a judge deemed him to be a potential danger to others and a likely flight risk. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 23:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Cruz Launches White House Bid By Appealing To A Voting Bloc That Doesn't Exist - Cruz might also run into trouble with many evangelical ministers over the issue of gun violence prevention. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 23:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate Bill 101, known as the "Religious Freedom Restoration Act," was approved by the Republican-controlled House by 63-31. A version was previously passed by the Republican-controlled Senate, and Republican Governor Mike Pence said he will sign it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 22:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Cruz Responds To Gov. Jerry Brown Calling Him 'Absolutely Unfit' To Run For Office - While Cruz is trying to steer the discussion about climate change even farther away from reality, in California Gov. Brown is taking immediate measure to confront the very real challenges his state faces. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 22:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 22:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's one from the [General Accounting Office](http://www.gao.gov/assets/670/665966.pdf) that provides the relevant numbers. Again, conservative ideology runs away from empirical evidence, so put on your running shoes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The latest victim of Florida governor Rick Scotts unwritten ban on state officials using the words climate change is his own disaster preparedness lieutenant, who stumbled through verbal gymnastics to avoid using the scientific term in a newly surfaced video. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 22:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 22:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The number is literally in the millions, but conservative ideology largely ignores evidence based arguments. Faced with empirical evidence, conservative ideology falls apart in relation to voter fraud so they fight back by making disingenuous arguments that appeal to fear mongers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forays by Islamic State, which is strongest in the northeast and east, into the provinces of Homs, Hama and even Damascus pose a fresh challenge for Syrian President Bashar al-Assad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 22:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could Oslo's decision to divest from coal inspire bigger cities to do the same? When Oslo sells the coal investments in its pension portfolio next month, it will set a historic precedent: the first capital city in the world to divest itself of that most polluting of fossil fuels. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 22:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 22:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the US's political lifetime the numbers are in the millions. The reports from the justice department on the number of illegal voters, however, said their numbers are minute. For a democracy to work, it requires the participation of the entire population. It still pains me that people believe the US is a democracy when for most of its existence it kept African Americans from voting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Political Football over Climate Change Rattles Windows of Ivory Tower - Their target is not science so much as a slew of U.S. EPA regulations meant to clean up the nation's coal-fired power plants and reduce the levels of smog in the air. Democrats support the regulations, most Republicans do not </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 21:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Battle Over Science Funding Gets Fiercer In U.S. Congress - Science advocates and researchers that depend on government grants are particularly worried now that Republicans control both chambers of Congress. They fear that science budgets will be cut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 21:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yemen's top factions are squaring off for battle after months of skirmishes, turning respectively to neighboring Saudi Arabia and its regional rival Iran for help in what may become all-out war. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 21:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Wake-Up Call for US Liberals - Todays conservative intellectuals arent even bothering to offer irritable mental gestures which seek to resemble ideas. Instead, theyre making calculated attempts to undermine our democracy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 21:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 21:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Driven by conservative ideology that relies on nonexistent fears, in this case over voter fraud, to mask the true goal of limiting voter turnout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Cruz Imagines the White House - But we shouldnt pretend that his is a serious campaign with a shot at success. It isnt. At best, Cruz will win a Fox News contract. He wont win the Republican nomination, and hell never be president of the United States. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 21:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 21:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as the SC is dominated by conservative ideology American voters will continue to lose access to voting rights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Supreme Court on Monday rejected a challenge to Wisconsin's Republican-backed law requiring voters to present photo identification to cast a ballot, a measure Democrats contend is aimed at keeping their supporters from voting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 21:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu has said he regrets remarks he made during last week's national election offending Arab-Israelis. Netanyahu drew accusations of racism in Israel when he warned that "the Arabs are voting in droves," just a few hours before polling stations were to close </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 20:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 00:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd watch the "masturbators", "balls", and "backdoor" movies. I could just see bilbo stabbing an enemy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 00:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Intergalactic Knitting*  
  
*Knitting Guardians of the Galaxy*  
  
*Taken 3: Knitting*  
  
See what I did there? Add knitting to any movie title and it's instantly boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McConnell Declares War On A Livable Climate, Aims To Stop National And Global Action - McConnell wants governors to ignore the laws requirement for them to put forward a state implementation plan to meet the EPAs proposed Clean Power Plan standards. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 23:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am one of the final 100 candidates for the Mars One mission but it is unlikely that I will ever land on Mars. As much as I would love to be one of the first interplanetary scientists, a potential mission to Mars remains, for the moment, beyond our reach. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 23:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seven children from an Orthodox Jewish family died early on Saturday when flames ripped through their Brooklyn home in one of New York City's deadliest fires in years, officials said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 23:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Juan Barros has been ordained bishop in the Chilean city of Osorno despite being widely accused of covering up crimes of a Catholic reverend who the Vatican sanctioned for sexually abusing young boys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 23:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State has posted online what it says are the names, U.S. addresses and photos of 100 American military service members, and called upon its "brothers residing in America" to kill them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 23:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 21:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow...I didn't know the bible was so explicit describing the rape of j. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Ashraf Ghani publicly acknowledged for the first time on Saturday that Islamic State was gaining influence in Afghanistan, as he prepared to leave for the United States to seek to slow the withdrawal of American troops. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 21:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 19:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree...religion has no place in politics. J freaks need to keep their ignorance in relation to science and morality to themselves. Where does the religious interference end? Do we allow islam and jewish law the right to formulate policy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Secretary of State John Kerry said on Saturday talks with Iran had made genuine progress and the time had come to make hard decisions in reaching a deal to curb Tehran's nuclear program. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 19:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Al Qaeda fighters captured the capital of a province in southern Yemen, killing about 20 soldiers, before they were driven out by the army late on Friday, local officials and residents said. The fighting came hours after suicide bombers killed 137 people in the national capital Sanaa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 19:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 01:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's see how many religious nuts I can offend by providing evidenced based proof about J's marital status:  
  
When the Romans crucified an individual, it was usually done by the book. However, since J's crucifixion was politically motivated, the Roman soldiers tasked with overseeing his execution would be far more attentive to the rules. A major rule the Romans wouldn't have bent for anyone was that only family was allowed to view the body while it remained in their custody. One of those allowed to see j's body was Mary Magdalene. This means that she was either related to j or she was his wife. 
  
Looking at the whole ordeal from the contemporary Roman POV, j was just another jewish idiot claiming to be important, and there were a lot of those during the period. A good example is j. the bapt., who claimed to be a prophet and healer sanctioned by g to dunk people in water. It is only time that has provided the event with any importance, especially for the Romans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Wisconsin state lawmakers have proposed a bill that would roll back the states requirement that companies give workers at least one day off every seven days. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 23:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet The Wiccan Witch Who Took On Scott Walker - In addition to considering eliminating the funds for Witchs post, Walker also suggested he might consider a likely unconstitutional idea: allocating chaplain positions in proportion to the religious faiths of the prison population. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 23:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mystery of Darwin's "Strange Animals" Solved - The scientists behind the work also think that ancient proteins could revolutionize the study of long-extinct species, revealing the secrets of fossils millions of years older than can be studied using DNA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 22:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia described "sanctions rhetoric" as destructive on Friday and said it would do what is in its national interests after European Union leaders kept economic sanctions in place over the Ukraine crisis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 22:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To present his case here Friday that he is the kind of leader Republicans should rally behind as its next presidential nominee, Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker put on his political scientist hat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 22:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Claiborne Countys sheriffs department and the Department of Wildlife, Fisheries, and Parks found Otis Byrd, a 54-year-old identified by the NAACP, hanging from a bed sheet half a mile from his home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 22:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran and six world powers suspended negotiations on a nuclear agreement and were set to meet again next week to break a deadlock over sensitive atomic research and lifting of sanctions, Western officials said on Friday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 22:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Friday, President Obama called for the release of four Americans detained or missing in Iran, arguing that the start of the Persian New Year offers an opportunity for the Iranian government to reunite these individuals with their families. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 22:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What It Feels Like to Be a Demographic Threat to Israel - This is why a Jew from anywhere in the world can come to Israel and live in the house of Palestinian refugees who are barred from returning precisely because theyre of the wrong ethnicity and religion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 21:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State claimed responsibility for suicide bombings in the Yemeni capital Sanaa that killed 126 people during Friday prayers at two mosques used by supporters of Shi'ite Houthi fighters who now control the capital. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 21:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Katharine Viner has been appointed the editor-in-chief of the Guardian, the first woman to run the newspaper in its 194-year history. Viner, currently deputy editor of the Guardian and editor-in-chief of Guardian US, will take up the role in the summer from incumbent Alan Rusbridger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 21:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 02:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the people I know who dislike Bibi say it's because he doesn't keep his word, and is very sneaky. They point to a television show that visited Bibi's home to highlight that the PM lived in a modest home, but were shown instead the servants' quarters. I believe that if he were assassinated, the peace process would make greater progress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Despite Hillary Clinton promise, charity did not disclose donors - But in a breach of the pledge, the charity's flagship health program, which spends more than all of the other foundation initiatives put together, stopped making the annual disclosure in 2010, Reuters has found. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 23:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tunisia said it would deploy the army to major cities and arrested nine people on Thursday after 20 foreign tourists were shot dead in an attack on a museum which Islamic State militants called "the first drop of the rain". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 23:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> t an event in Cleveland on Wednesday, President Obama endorsed a system of mandatory voting, a policy that would penalize eligible voters who don't make it to the polls on Election Day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 22:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An unidentified warplane attacked the presidential palace in Aden on Thursday after rival forces fought the worst clashes in years in Yemen's second city, an official and residents said, in a sharp escalation of the country's months-long conflict. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 22:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 01:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the course of my day I visit a number of Star Bucks and in some areas of Seattle people routinely refuse to flush the toilet in the coffee shops. It seems like a cultural thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Dow support from 300 lawyers: Petition to Texas Supreme Court to overturn suspension of death penalty defense attorney - Or, as one lawyer quipped after the piece was posted: Apparently Texas finally found one lawyer to be incompetent: the one who is actually good at his job. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 00:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Dow support from 300 lawyers: Petition to Texas Supreme Court to overturn suspension of death penalty defense attorney - Or, as one lawyer quipped after the piece was posted: Apparently Texas finally found one lawyer to be incompetent: the one who is actually good at his job. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 00:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The White House on Wednesday scolded Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu following his re-election victory for abandoning his commitment to negotiate for a Palestinian state and for what it called "divisive" campaign rhetoric toward Israels minority Arab voters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 00:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The amount of carbon the Amazons remaining trees removed from the atmosphere fell by almost a third last decade, leading scientists to warn that manmade carbon emissions would need to be cut more deeply to tackle climate change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 00:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With little fanfare, Sen. Barbara Boxer (D-Calif.) has thrown her support behind a historic Senate bill to comprehensively reform medical marijuana at the federal level. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 00:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservatives Say $15 Minimum Wage Is Killing Seattle Restaurant Scene, Restaurateurs Disagree - Frank reportedly asked one conservative writer who had picked up the wage-menace red herring to not make assumptions about our business to promote your political values. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 00:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A gunman opened fire inside a motel room in the Phoenix suburb of Mesa on Wednesday, killing one man and wounding two women, then shot three more people as he sought to elude a manhunt that ended in his capture, police said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 00:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 01:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Japan refused to surrender in WWII, forcing the U.S. to drop the bombs on Hiroshima and Nagasaki. Declassified records revealed that Japan repeatedly attempted to surrender eight days prior to bombs being dropped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. House Republicans on Tuesday proposed higher defense spending and deep cuts to social services including healthcare for the poor in an aggressive new budget plan that seeks to eliminate deficits by 2024. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 22:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rep. Aaron Schock (R-Ill.), who in a matter of weeks went from a fast track to national prominence to beset by numerous reports of spending misdeeds, announced his resignation from Congress on Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 22:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Activists working to address the rates of sexual assault among college students dont want gun enthusiasts to co-opt their issue in order to push for more weapons on campus, and have launched several advocacy campaigns to fight back. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 01:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UTexas-NASA Study Sees New Threat to East Antarctic Ice - If Totten Glacier were to collapse completely, global sea levels would rise by at least 11 feet (3.3 meters). As in the West Antarctic Ice Sheet, complete collapse of Totten Glacier may take centuries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 01:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than 16 million Americans have gained insurance coverage as a result of President Barack Obama's health care law, the administration said Monday as the White House prepares to commemorate the fifth anniversary of the law's signing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 01:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oregon Will Start Automatically Registering Voters. Is Vermont Next? Officials estimate the new policy will add about 300,000 more voters to the rolls right away, and could eventually reach cover nearly all of the estimated 860,000 people currently unregistered but otherwise eligible to vote. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 01:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers out of San Diego State University found that the United States is becoming more tolerant than ever of communists, atheists, LGBT people and more. The only groups for which Americans didnt become more tolerant were of people who believed black people were genetically inferior. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 01:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Criminal Defense Lawyer Told Us Robert Durst's 'The Jinx' Confession Is '100 Percent Admissible' in Court - "I would think it's admissible unless they could prove somehow it's not him talking or it was somehow spliced together." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 00:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Kurdistan Region Security Council (KRSC) said in a statement on Saturday that EU-certified laboratory tests showed that soil and clothing samples collected from the remnants of a suicide blast in northern Iraq in January had levels of chlorine that indicated the substance was used as a weapon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 22:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flagging in opinion polls before Tuesday's election, Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu is trying to rally Israeli rightists by casting his center-left challengers as tools of a global campaign to usurp power. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 19:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraqi forces besieging dozens of die-hard fighters of the Islamic State of Iraq and the Levant (ISIL) in Tikrit will have liberated the city within three days, a spokesman said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 18:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. government is appealing a federal court ruling that reduced the potential penalty BP Plc must pay for the 2010 Gulf of Mexico oil spill by almost $4 billion. The appeal, which was filed on Friday in U.S. District Court in New Orleans, challenges a January decision </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 18:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Oklahoma University chapter of Sigma Alpha Epsilon, which was shut down and had some members expelled following revelations they led a racist chant that celebrated lynching, has just hired high-profile attorney Stephen Jones to look into whether they can sue the university or its president. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 22:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia on Friday rejected U.S. concerns about its use of a former American base in Vietnam for the refueling of Russian bomber flights around U.S. territory in the Pacific, dismissing recent U.S. statements as "puzzling" and "strange". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 22:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cockroaches could inspire superheroes if they weren't so repulsive...Recently researchers discovered another superpower: the nocturnal creatures can see in nearpitch black by pooling light signals over time, like time-lapse photography. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 21:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swedish prosecutors want to question Julian Assange in London over allegations of sexual assault, potentially ending an impasse that left the WikiLeaks founder holed up for almost three years in Ecuador's embassy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 21:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 02:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abraham from the bible. That prick tried to kill his kid and blamed it on the voices. He also kept slaves and probably raped one. Noah was a pretty big asshole, too, as his daughters were killed by bears because he fucked them.  
  
Edit: Bring it on god-squad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 02:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I watched Katie Holmes in *The Giver* I wondered if she drew on her times with Tom Cruise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 02:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you worked for Edison, he got to keep all your research. This included any experimental processes the worker did during the home hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 01:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the kids, an upside-down christ on a cross. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 01:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why stop at dead bodies when zombies are so much more fun? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Easter Bunny has rabies. What gifts does it hide this year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 00:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 00:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can just imagine her spitting out some folksy "double-speak" that defends Iran's right to "drill-baby-drill" while demanding it be wiped off the earth's face for its nuclear policy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Big Oil Finally Entering a Climate Change World? - This meant that no fossil fuel reserves, no potential source of supply -- no matter how remote or hard to reach, how far offshore or deeply buried, how encased in rock -- was deemed untouchable in the mad scramble to increase output and profits. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 00:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 00:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just think, McCain could have been our president and this is the level of intelligence he would have brought to our foreign affairs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Senator John McCain said on Thursday that Republicans stood behind a letter to Iran's leaders threatening to undo any nuclear deal despite an outpouring of criticism from the White House, U.S. allies and Democrats. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 23:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The FCC has just released the full text of its Open Internet Order, which lays out its contentious vision for how the internet should be managed, along with each commissioner's affirming statement or dissent on the issue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 23:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA's Curiosity Mars rover used its robotic arm Wednesday, March 11, to sieve and deliver a rock-powder sample to an onboard instrument. The sample was collected last month before the team temporarily suspended rover arm movement pending analysis of a short circuit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 23:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Secret Service agents suspected of driving under the influence and striking a White House security barricade disrupted an active bomb investigation and drove directly beside the suspicious package itself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 23:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Major world powers have quietly begun talks on a U.N. Security Council resolution to lift U.N. sanctions on Iran if a nuclear agreement is struck, a step that could make it harder for the U.S. Congress to undo a deal, Western officials said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 23:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 23:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Justice in the U.S. is distributed unfairly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Obama administration is investigating allegations that two senior Secret Service agents, including a top member of the presidents protective detail, drove a government car into White House security barricades after drinking at a late-night party last week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 23:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Utah lawmakers and Mormon Church leaders celebrated a landmark moment Wednesday night, when a bill banning discrimination against lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender people passed the states Republican-controlled legislature. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 22:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Villagers in eastern Ukraine have told Reuters they saw a missile flying directly overhead just before a Malaysian airliner was shot out of the sky on July 17 last year, providing the most detailed accounts to date that suggest it was fired from territory held by pro-Russian rebels. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 22:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 01:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's that sound you hear? It's the door to the presidency slamming loudly shut in Christie's face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kurdish and allied forces battling Islamic State militants have severed cross-border supply and communication lines between Iraq and Syria, according to the US-led coalition. The report comes after the IS suffered a series of defeats in both Iraq and Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 00:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.N. torture investigator accused the United States on Wednesday of stalling on his requests to visit its prisons where 80,000 people are in solitary confinement and to interview inmates at Guantanamo on his terms. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 00:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Secretary of State John Kerry told Republicans who control Congress on Wednesday they would not be able to modify any nuclear agreement struck between the United States and Iran. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 00:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The embattled police chief of Ferguson, Missouri, is to resign a week after his department was accused of racial bias in a scathing report by the US government. Chief Thomas Jackson will announce he is stepping down at a press conference on Wednesday afternoon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 23:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A bipartisan bill aimed at aiding victims of human trafficking is in peril now that Democrats have learned it contains an anti-choice provision to restrict funding for abortion. Democratic lawmakers say they were not aware of the abortion-related language </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 23:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Catholic Church Claims It Can Refuse To Pay Victims Of Sex Abuse Because Of Religious Freedom - This would undermine the compelling interest of the Code by allowing a debtor who has made preferential, fraudulent and avoidable transfers to intentionally harm its creditors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 23:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United States has asked Vietnam to stop letting Russia use a former U.S. base to refuel nuclear-capable bombers engaged in shows of strength over the Asia-Pacific region, exposing strains in Washington's steadily warming relations with Hanoi. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 23:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The International Monetary Fund has agreed to pump $10 billion into Ukraine's troubled economy over the next year, providing swift assistance for the country's struggling finances as part of a larger four-year bailout. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 23:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The State Department's internal watchdog has found that many department employees are not preserving emails for the public record as required by the government. That could mean a substantial amount of lost government information. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 23:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 01:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bankers, politicians, executive management, police, movie stars, Kanye, are good examples of this phenomenon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 00:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I immediately signed the petition because I consider these 47 senators cowards whose irrational dislike of the president lead them to sabotage the negotiation process. Republicans literally fear just about everything: gun control, the FCC, banking regulations, the minimum wage, non-existent voter fraud, immigrants, unions, taxes, paucity of religion in government, the EPA, American history, birth control, abortion, health care, and....well, you get the idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Cotton Tries To Offer Alternative To Iran Talks, Gets Almost Everything Wrong - The newly-minted senator argued that a credible threat of force should be on the table, adding Israel struck Iraqs nuclear program in 1981 and they didnt reconstitute it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 23:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25 Years Later, This Simpsons Episode Still Hits Too Close To Home - Burns makes a TV ad where an actor playing Charles Darwin explains that Blinky the three-eyed fish is really a more evolved miracle of nature. Its a perfect analogue for present-day Republican efforts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 23:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Muslim college received formal academic accreditation this past weekend, making it the first officially recognized Islamic institution of higher learning in the United States. On Sunday, Zaytuna College, a liberal-arts school based in Berkeley, California, announced that it was formally accredited </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 23:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. solar power grew by 6.2 gigawatts in 2014, a 30 percent increase over the previous year and representing nearly $18 billion in new investment, according to data released this morning by the Solar Energy Industries Association and GTM Research. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 23:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why couldnt Hillary Clinton have two e-mail accounts on one phone? - The standard appears to have been (and in some cases still is): a secure phone provided by the government plus an unsecure phone for your personal use. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 23:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia said on Tuesday it was halting its participation in a consulting group on the Treaty on Conventional Armed Forces in Europe, ending one of its last modes of participation on the 1990 security treaty. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 23:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraqi government forces and their allied militia have entered parts of Tikrit, as they continue a major offensive to recapture Saddam Hussein's hometown from the Islamic State of Iraq and the Levant (ISIL). Iraq's defence ministry said on Tuesday that its forces have surrounded the city </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 23:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A video posted online by Islamic State militants on Tuesday showed a boy killing Muhammad Musallam, an Israeli Arab accused by the group of having signed up as a jihadi to spy for Mossad, with a bullet to the head. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 23:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Rodham Clinton acknowledged Tuesday that she had erred in using only a private e-mail server for work correspondence at the State Department, saying that she sent about 60,000 e-mails from her private account during her four-year tenure as secretary of state. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 22:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forty-seven Republican senators are seeking to undermine the international negotiations aimed at containing Irans nuclear program with an open letter to the government of Iran </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 23:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Merchants of Doubt about Global Warming Hope to Strike Back - The wider discussion is viewed by some as a window into the network of skeptical scientists, bloggers and conservative think tank scholars who often raise objections to mainstream climate science. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 23:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are standing on the edge of a new world where warming is poised to accelerate at rates unseen for at least 1,000 years. Thats the main finding of a paper published Monday in Nature Climate Change, which looked at the rate of temperature change over 40-year periods. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 23:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Supreme Court on Monday revived the University of Notre Dame's religious objections to the requirement for contraception coverage under President Barack Obama's healthcare law, throwing out a lower court decision in favor of the federal government. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 23:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 22:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know and understand the long history of the united states, but I don't believe a past political party has shown such contempt for a president. It's sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican U.S. senators warned Iran's leaders on Monday that any nuclear deal with President Barack Obama could last only as long as he remains in office, an unusual partisan intervention in foreign policy that could undermine delicate international talks with Tehran. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 22:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United States on Monday declared Venezuela a national security threat and ordered sanctions against seven officials in the worst diplomatic dispute with the oil-rich country since socialist President Nicolas Maduro took office in 2013. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 22:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In what advocates describe as an historic first, a trio of senators plan to unveil a federal medical marijuana bill Tuesday. The bill, to be introduced by Senators Rand Paul (R-Ky.), Cory Booker (D-N.J.), and Kirsten Gillibrand (D-N.Y.), would end the federal ban on medical marijuana. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 22:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Barack Obama and Hillary Clinton exchanged emails during her time as secretary of state, the White House said on Monday, confirming the president was aware that his potential successor used a private email address for government work. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 22:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Ron Johnson (R-WI) preemptively dismissed the Obama administrations effort to reach a negotiated deal that could contain Irans nuclear program on Sunday and instead suggested that the United States and Israel may need to take military action </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 23:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
