<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5015</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 18:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a common missconception. The security lies in the pilots being told *to* fly into the tower, and the ATC's relying that the pilots training is completely shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 14:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took me about a week i think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 00:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly why I wish I trained Amarr first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 00:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it then? On second look you're right, absolution is *a lot* shinier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 22:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolution looks dank. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 20:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad burnout paradise made that list, love that game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 18:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably be better off asking in the staff directly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 19:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Small note, TorrentShack invite channel has been down for maintenance (AFAIK) for almost a week now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 14:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it apply less or more stacking penalty than intended?

Edit: Answer: https://www.reddit.com/r/Eve/comments/2spdua/manymost_pos_fitting_tools_not_to_mention_the/cnrnm6j </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 00:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UK here, anyone not calling it a duvet/duvet cover is a wierdo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 00:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of all these flavours you chose to be salty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 23:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What information do you collect for internal analytics? Is that information tied to the IP address you have that created the account?

Cheers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 00:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "So I hear you're looking for a cheap guardian-vexor?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 17:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably? PROBABLY?!? You're fucking dead kid, i'm sending my tiger buddies round now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 10:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I did, it's still under maintenance then. Cheers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 20:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I doing something wrong or is TSh's invite irc channel still down? Heard it was under maintenance but that was like 4 days ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 18:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your license is getting stale

Better throw it out OP, no one likes to eat stale licenses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 00:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It means your account won't be shutdown/disabled/banned if you do not login for a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 19:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can use reddit you can use a VPN. It's not hard at all as long as you go with someone that has a client. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 19:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can use reddit you can use a VPN. It's that easy, NordVPN has a really user friendly client. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 19:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> does nothing to help protect your IP from the swarm. 

see: https://www.reddit.com/r/trackers/comments/kibgc/to_users_of_private_trackers_dont_use_peerip/

https://www.reddit.com/r/torrents/comments/17gold/can_we_have_a_new_rule_regarding_peerblock_please/

http://www.peerblock.com/docs/faq#p2p_disclaimer

use a vpn or private trackers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 08:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biggest problem you can see with a modular phone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 08:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can preface any statement with 'sudo' and they're contractually obligated to perform it. For example, I once had a tech come over and make me a turkey bacon sandwich. Definately one of the better sandwiches i've had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 06:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except he won't, because this didn't happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 03:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're just messing with you dude. (sorry guys) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 16:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to say I agree with him. Your post comes off as one: making a very reasonable point about respecting other peoples opinion, which 99% of rational people will agree with. Two: arguing against minors being able to deny potentially life saving treatment, which is without a doubt a much more controversial opinion. The first is generally agreed upon by all rational people, and the second is up for debate until the world explodes.

It's also one that both me and him (and the votes) agree detracts very much from your first point.

I personally see your first point only being made because of your second point, i.e., although I can appriciate how the first point is unrelated and still relevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 14:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unintentionally deep title? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 13:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I think it means link to profile pages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 12:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> huehuehuehue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 23:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent job dodging the question, and 'enhancing the discussion'. Don't expect a reply unless you can actually support the existence of this imaginery myth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 23:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so say they don't google it. Where exactly do they hear this myth? The only reason i'm still replying is because I don't think you can find a popular website where people don't completely disagree the second that's posted, educating anybody reading it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 23:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, you keep claiming it's a myth, but 9/10 results on google say otherwise (http://lmgtfy.com/?q=Are+private+tracker+safe%3F). As well as anyone that's done 1 minute research on the subject. You haven't even posted a link or a screenshot of anyone saying that, and people agreeing with them. 

Edit:  here's an article by the largest copyright and privacy website where they analyse the OP: https://torrentfreak.com/are-private-bittorrent-trackers-safe/ The only myth here is the one you're inventing, it's pretty hilarious you can't see that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 22:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You agree with 99% of rational people that use private trackers. This is the most pointless thread i've read in a long while. Congratulations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 12:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 16:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having recruitment threads on trackers that require you to get to a higher user level (e.g. elite) is a pretty good incentive. Other than that, free invites and immunity from getting disabled for being away is pretty nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 07:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took me way too long to notice it was the same person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 16:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EvE Online is a space based, player driven, persistent world MMORPG. This is the age of the people playing the game. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eve_Online </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 16:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome video, thank you. Would love to see more like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 23:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LACK LEGION </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 15:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even in 'ask me anythings', it's never 'i'll answer everything'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 07:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asshole looking to be an asshole. Downvote and move on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 09:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, you're not wrong. Here, I even have proof autism is real: http://puu.sh/e3eHJ/01c44f7d9b.png

Edit: please mods don't delete this thread. this is gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 08:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their hats are the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 01:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmao. what was your post that you got banned for?   [also.](http://www.caption-of-the-day.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/08/041-internet-forum-moderator1.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 00:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright video, but the music is seriously cancer. Seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 03:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah thats cool, I can understand that then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 01:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice video.. Why they stayed in t1 ships when they saw you were rekting them no one will kniow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 12:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fine, I saw on an API key that they got an alliance mail telling them to delete them.

Wait a second... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 11:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could just buy him a PLEX and give him the Activation Code they give you. AFAIK Amazon might ask you for an account name, but places like http://store.markeedragon.com/?cat=4 and https://www.g2a.com/ (make sure you use G2A shield) are trusted, and they both should give you an Activation Code. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 12:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Yes they can. People don't because they prefer not to be in jail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 09:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could have done so much more with that title OP. You failed us damnit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 22:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Becuase they have to make other people feel bad to make themselves feel good. Welcome to reddit, where the circlejerk is too real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 17:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a title I thought i'd ever see. Did BRAVE stop PL from dropping supers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 16:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most useful piece of software you use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 16:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is this for this http://www.capitalfm.com/london/win/nye-fireworks-tickets/ ? or what are the tickets actually for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 15:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Homebrew apps according to the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 14:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daughter better hope so, or maybe one day she'll find out she's adopted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 11:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah? 4 minutes? What a scrub. http://www.destiny.gg did it in one and a half. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 11:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This video looks straight outta 1990. Amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 14:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Says who?

Edit: found a source, https://www.vehicleenquiry.service.gov.uk/ , H982 FKL PORSCHE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 12:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't you buy personalised numberplates? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 07:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Shit, a heavy! Time to take it out. Biggest, slowest target in the game. No problem!" *miss*...*miss*...*die*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 06:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't even seem to hit heavys with the LnL. I can hit scouts though, it's wierd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 02:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant be the only one that thought you were talking about the soft drink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 16:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were just straight up assholes. No excuse for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 08:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No context? How is this justifce porn if we don't know what happened before? Skater dude could have been the cunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 08:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way he says that picture is photoshopped, and the whole conversation, leads me to believe he's a troll. I just can't believe someone can be that dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 08:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought my car in the US, and it dosen't have that written out on the mirror. Or are you referring to the actual level of maginification? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 08:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, thanks for this! Really beautiful food   video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 07:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get your head out of your arse. Not everyone is a native english speaker, and not everyone has good linguistic skills. Assuming so makes you look like an asshole, and rightly so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 07:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not everyone is a native english speaker, or even if they are, have you ever heard of dyslexia? Sometimes I forget how much reddit can be arrogant douchebags. Thank you for reminding me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 14:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP Santa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 22:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read what I said in the very next sentence: Anyone that hears the -bro terms being used in context enough knows that to be true. 

If you go to assumptions the first few times you hear something said, in a community you're completely new to, then it's not the communitys fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 21:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmao b8/8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 21:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I racially identify as a helicopter, can I still join? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 21:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're *really* reading too much into it. I think in the context that -bro is used in EvE it seems like a more blanket term, that isn't meant to include gender politics, but is used to connate a role that attracts friendship. It's not implied that your female or male, because no one actually knows what you are behind the screen. Anyone using the term like that does not represent the majority, and their defenition should not be taken as fact.

Personally i've only ever heard of logibro (when a logi saves someones ship) and newbros (because the game needs new players to survive) being used widely. Wormbro is a name of a corporation, and not something that fits the majority of the -bros. 

It's not hard to get around the perception of exclusion, because there is none! Anyone that hears the -bro terms being used in context enough knows that to be true.

For some context i've been playing for about a year, and have been in large-very large corps for the majority of that time (so it's not like I play market pvp 24/7 in my 0% tax corp). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 20:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they set the drives on fire to test them!? Also you can be damn skippy those workers don't take as much care when the cameras not on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 20:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's something about the combination of that cheesy music and the titles, i'm guessing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 19:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Louis looks straight out of the Beatles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 18:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peal my orange, bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 15:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Homie gotta get their orange pealed one way or another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 15:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That fucking pink shirt. Lmao. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 11:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you zoom in enough, you'll actually find dickbutt is made of rectangles, proof: http://puu.sh/dGgMi/34a06a1fad.png

Amazing work Dr.unproperNoun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 11:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You some sorta mathey-maticks nerd?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 21:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kappa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 20:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe not to you, but if they get upvoted and reach the top then a lot of people do find them funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 03:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All those industrial ships. I automatically assume if I read/hear a ship name i've don't know its an industrial. Works 99% of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 02:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got 200mill from a question game channel when I first started. Thank you rich drunk person! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 00:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even more beautiful with that handsome ECM boat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 23:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://wiki.eveuniversity.org/Scams_in_EVE_Online#Trade_Window

Jita is a hub for scams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 22:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you see this being used in hisec ganking or? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 22:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you mind linking me that skill plan? Cheers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 21:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, they're still up for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 11:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Widow because fuck yeah ECM bonus'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 09:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I understand of it, the code in the second picture shows the app downloading something silently, and encrypting and sending usage statistics of the user to Viber. This shows a blatent lack of respect for their users privacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Viber smartphone app calls out ESET as being a bad antivirus. ESET responds with code proving Viber secretly sends its users usage statistics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 09:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 13:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost forgot. Why would you ever trust battleclinic for a 1.9bn fit? Some of their fits are really really bad.  Please say you cross checked the fit with a trust corp mate or smth like that. 

That 4th BCU gives you 300dps increase vs 30k EHP with a DCU. Is that really worth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 13:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming there was no such thing as eve-survival, wouldn't you just warp in, not bastion, align out, and warp if you can't tank it? Or do the frigates reach you too fast?

If there wasn't anything like eve-survival, people would just setup a channel and do it that way instead. And you would still have probably died because you wouldn't have read the comments there. Or even if the guide was made by CCP, can you honestly say you would have read the comments?

Seems like you're trying to blame this on the game, when it was pilot error plain and simple.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 22:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if he is 'biased', which any opinion is by the way (at least by your defenition) his point still stands, they were obviously looking to make the cops look bad on camera. Stating that he's biased dosen't even begin to refute his point, and just makes it looks like you can't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Possum has an existential crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 12:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 03:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what i've heard all the races are equal (or one might be a tiny bit better) so train what you think looks cool. And AFAIK you can use both torps and bombs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 01:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kappa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 00:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [He seems like a nice guy. (comments)](http://evewho.com/pilot/Roggle)	 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 07:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a monstrosity! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 23:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hisec shitters, nothing new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 07:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AFAIk zkill prices bpc's correctly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 03:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, you should warp in a blackbird and a griffin too, complete the family! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 03:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious, do you put ECM on that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 03:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn you have a Widow *and* this.... how rich are you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 00:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IN THE BUT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 18:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I *wish* i was a widow pilot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 18:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [Widow is the best blops, why would that be a joke?!](http://img1.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20140606005500/iwbtb/images/8/84/Kappa.jpg) (realtalk solo dropping on ratters and ecming them straight off the bat is awesome) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 05:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take my advice with a grain of salt, as i'm not a wormholer.

1. Probably not. It can be scanned down by multiple peole 

2. You're in a wormhole system, it's not on the world map because it can only be accessed through scanning it down, not throguh stargates.

3. They're selling the loot they get from the sites, and I think people do sell wormholes too if they're empty and valuble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 02:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nevermind, I missread the article. Where the hell does she even hide 200$ worth of items?!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 22:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww yeah bby, Widow represent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 20:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nicely done, some drop shadow would make it look nice IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 10:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've played with the worst of players in League of Legends, this is much much worse, simply because people can completely destroy your EvE experience, and you cant just leave a game like you can in League and forget about it. 

The 'bonus room' was a 'service' created by a scammer. Once he scammed someone he would have them go into his teamspeak and make them degrade themselves IRL, or completely devalue their character (imagine making someone lose rating from diamond to bronze), just so they could get their assetts and money back (he still wouldn't give it back 9/10 times). He and his buddies were eventually permanently banned from EvE. 
http://jestertrek.blogspot.co.uk/2014/03/the-bonus-round.html

There really isn't any permanence of meeting a troll in league, apart from maybe losing some rating and 40 minutes of your time. In EvE, the scumbags can kill your ship which you've spent actual days farming for. To be fair, if you're smart about it you probably will only be scammed once, it's the people who are ignorant of what's encouraged (scamming) that get bit the worst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 04:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 04:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Esteemed community

Eve brings out the worst and the best in people. I have met the most vile people on EvE, that I wouldn't dream of finding anywhere else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 04:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> autism incarnate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 04:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bui is literally autism incarnate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
