<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject889</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 22:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a big difference between liking a girl and liking her boobs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 13:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad was a stay-at-home dad, and my husband and I have decided that since I earn over double what he does, that he will be one too.

I have nothing but respect for men who make that sacrifice for their family; challenging gender roles and all that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 13:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OoooooOooooOoOoooOooOooOooOOOoOooOOOOOoOoOoOOoOO. Fuck yeah.

Bitch, at least try to make it believable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 13:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phew! Just in time to miss the GOT season! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 13:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They really do! I thought my friend's tree had herpes or something when I saw them. Turns out, they are really good and totally don't taste like STD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 13:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi neighbour! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 13:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, read the damn post then post criticism! You're playing with fire here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 13:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Telling girls that the only reason boys pick on them is because they like them.

Wrong.

Boys pick on girls because they like their *reactions*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 12:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make an elephant head (or other cute animal) and sew it in the middle. Snugglers don't need to be flat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 12:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That one did come up in my searches. That sounds so tasty! Is it like a custard apple? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 11:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are. I had one the other day. They are waxy on the outside which leaves an odd feeling in the mouth, but the crunchiness and juiciness makes up for it. I would liken them to a Nash pear in texture and flavour.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 8 Fruits You Probably Have Never Seen Before </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 11:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 11:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I laughed it off, he laughed it off. We avoided eachother for the rest of the evening... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our new lab coats have press-buttons down the front. How I feel every time I take mine off. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 10:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They have the same first name. Awkwardness ensued. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 10:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 11:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just booked my American holiday! We plan to cram as much as we can in 3 weeks, but we organised internal flights everywhere, so hopefully we don't have tok much trouble </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 11:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/R8EMU5Z </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't think I have ever once completed a full game of Monopoly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 10:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 10:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me wonder...you know when you see those parents chasing a laughing toddler all over the place desperately trying to catch them? I wonder if you would be able to train your child to freeze on command by constantly playing that game where you yell FREEZE! and everyone has to stop in their tracks? They would eventually get used to freezing when you yell and would do it when you are trying to catch them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 10:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For flowers, I would suggest finding someone crafty to make you some if you are into that sort of thing, or even just looking into store-bought bouquets. Some quite pretty little bunches can be bought for under $10 each </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 10:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "This one has purple in it. Purple's a fruit." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 09:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would just ask for someone to bop me on the head, then wake me up when the morphine kicks in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 09:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well...good for you, I guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 08:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. Also married with a healthy social life. 

Gotta keep up appearances though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 08:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure? You aren't a murderer or anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 08:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I've *heard* of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 05:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jokes aside, I wish Unidan was here to tell me fun biology facts about what this little guy is doin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 03:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully not to the one of Wendy and Tink... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 03:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 03:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did we expect a fabulous, expensive log cabin to look fabulous and expensive on the inside? Yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 02:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because human interaction confuses and frightens us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 02:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ["Dad? Dad wake up!"](https://3.bp.blogspot.com/-IeHhr1mq064/VSqJuKTbyCI/AAAAAAAAH68/ooj6znB9lZ8/s1600/Simba%2Bcuddling%2BMustafa.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 00:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm lying in bed right now with my two. They are really confused as to why I just pulled them in for a big bear hug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 00:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband was at the Dept of Transport (aka DMV) one day when a car pulled into the carpark, swung into a spot and just kept going. The car hit the concrete barrier, went over it and got jammed up on it. The wheels were off the ground, but the driver still chucked it in reverse and floored it. Funnily enough, nothing happened. The guy got out of his car and husband said he was the tiniest, most feeble old man he had ever seen. He stood there scratching his head for a moment then went inside for help.

It turns out he was there for a renewal.

My husband didn't stick around long enough to see if the guy got it. He valued his life too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 00:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the time she probably couldn't tell the difference. Fuck broken ankles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 00:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Touche. 

But then, if by commenting, someone stops commenting "shitpost" then maybe I will have made a difference and maybe it is worthwhile.

Edit: Also, looking at the votes right now, I would humbly like to point out that people do seem to agree with me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 00:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at your history OP, you seem to make a habit of reposting, then complaining that you didn't know it was a repost.

Well, either you are new to this game and have much to learn, or you are a dirty rotten liar.

I am going to go with liar, as you just tried to claim that Reese Lightening was just adopted by you. A lie.

So! I will just pick up my pitchfork here ---E and go stand with the gathering mob </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 23:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand why people feel the need to comment "shitpost" on stuff they don't like. 

Don't like it? Downvote it. 

Just coz you call it a shitpost doesn't make it one, and doesn't mean other people agree with you. In fact, given the amount of upvotes, I would say your opinion is in the minority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 23:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister has copped a lot of criticism for piercing her daughters' ears but honestly, if pierced ears are the worst thing she has done to her children, then they will still have had a pretty great childhood.

It bothers me how much people object to it in our society when there are larger issues to deal with. My nieces are happy, healthy and loved; people need to quit telling her she is a bad mother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 16:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somehow mine managed to come together...even after the celebrant had a heart attack 2 days out, my husband crashed his car a week out and my bmaid of honour forgot the ring in the limo.

Mind you, I was drunk for most of it, so not much could phase me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 11:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, being both married and a woman...not really the issue :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 11:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing as I am a lady and all my tackle is always in the box.....no, it doesn't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 11:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 21:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got that constantly this weekend. Most of them hadn't seen me since I was a baby and yet they expected me to cry out with joy at the very sight of them.

"Lady, you could have easily walked in off the street for all I know!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 21:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now he ded </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 21:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Example: We were staying at my cousins house who I thought I knew pretty well. Turned out he had a son from a previous relationship that I never knew about and people were pissed he wasn't there.

Also, I met my Uncle's first child fr another marriage...who I never knew existed. He knew me though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 21:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, no...Australia. But hey, our family breeds like rabbits, so.I might have family in Maine I don't know about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 21:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, I always have the same job-related questions. I am one of the few to go to uni so I seem to be some kind of mythical unicorn to them that must be studied </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 12:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 12:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She wanted to be a merman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When my massive family gathered for a reunion on the weekend... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 12:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 13:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how it says "Australians" as if we all did it as a collective.

We did it Australia! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 04:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sorta see what you want to get across but wanting to maintain a lifestyle because you enjoy it is not the "definition" of childish. 

On the flipside, having children and changing your lifestyle does not make you an adult </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 23:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that the need to fly with children may arise, but for the love of everyone's sanity, be prepared! 

These parents had no toys, no snacks, no medicine, nothing. They spent the whole trip just shushing the kid and trying to reason with him. He looked no older than 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 23:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but I got to immediately enjoy the wine in the Airport bar during my stopover, while I watched all the parents sit in the McDonald's chairs getting fries thrown at them. 

One day I might want kids, but it is not this day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 23:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it based on then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 23:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 21:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did tell him to open the box, just not what inside. He knew </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmm maybe, but not on-hand. School was 9years ago now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 11:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The seats on this airplane have coat hooks in them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 09:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 09:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. I love that song/episode. 

This was my art, inspired by it:

http://i.imgur.com/6IiBHFD.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 09:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was my normal teacher. He was really weird though. Several times he would gush over my worst work and then completely miss the point of my best. It wasn't until a year with him that I realised I could argue my case for a better grade and he would usually change his mind. Got mostly A's after that.

But thanks. I did work hard and I was really proud of the subtle (and more obvious) symbolism I had put into it. Ohh well...luckily I never wanted to be an artist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 09:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got Elsa. Blue-eyed, white haired Elsa. I have dark hair and green eyes.

So close. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 09:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have just met you and I love you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 09:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *You're* not! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 09:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You heartless monster! Pick her up and snuggle her at once! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 08:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a fence-sitter also...but right now, after sitting through a 2 hour flight with someone's screaming child beside me the whole time, I am definitely on the childfree side of the fence.

It's nice here, we get wine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 08:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did an art project a lot like this in high school. The topic was Power, so I made a male torso out of metal, wood and clay, a female torso made of tissue paper and lace, and a cross. I made a box with a padlock and put it in the male's chest and hung the key around the cross. Inside the box was a bunch of stuff meant to symbolise the strength of women (pictures, quotes, etc).

It was meant to symbolise that men seemed to have power over women, but only through the power of the church.

I was so proud of my sculpture but my art teacher claimed he didn't "get it" and never even bothered opening the box or trying to understand. I got a C+.

He was Catholic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 08:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister has 3 kids and 3 step kids, aged 3, 6, 7, 8, 9, 9 so visits to her house are....noisy. Everyone either hates eachother and won't shut up or love eachother and won't calm down. I was lucky to just be on holiday with the youngest this week. I don't think I would have survived the hoarde.

But she was pretty vocal alone. Any question you asked her was answered with "No" until she realised what you were asking...and then it was a little whinge for not getting the thing she just said No to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 23:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you *like* apple juice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 23:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I'm glad not everyone has filth on their minds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After spending the week with my 3 year old niece </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 13:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 09:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is definitely behind the 8 ball when it comes to IT. Dad often says the only thing he knows about computers is how to pay for them. You should have seen his face when we explained MP3s to him

"You mean I can get all my music on this tiny stick."

"Yes Dad."

"*All* of it?!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't own a cat, but my cousins do. I followed him around the house trying to get a cute photo for you people, and this is the best I could get </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 11:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 23:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd be like a walking philosophy lesson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 23:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting a tatt, huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 13:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also posted a pic of a hermit crab...did you see that? I thought it was pretty cool... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 10:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dad is just the same. He gets so excited when he finds a thing that he searches for...as if is surprises him that the internet would have it. 

"But it is a really rare bike!"

"The Internet has everything, Dad." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 10:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In his words "Why look at tits on a screen when I can't touch them?!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dad recently learnt how to use a computer. This is him excitedly showing his granddaughter all the motorbikes he found on Google. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 10:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 08:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer it to be preceeded by "U wan sum..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 08:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on holiday right now and not in reception all the time, so when I finally get some and come on to find all this going down...I was confused to say the least </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 07:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Transplant Scientist, I know all too well the kind of desperation that leads to stuff like this. Unfortunately, I also know all too well that it is very unlikely to work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 06:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somehow he looks real pleased with himself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 06:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for potato </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I'm King of the world!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 06:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Soon...hopefully </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 06:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 05:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so confused. I am on holiday and just checked in for a minute, as much as my limited reception will allow, only to find WW3 going on on the front page. Might just put my phone down and go snorkelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 23:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work in a lab that does genetic testing for coeliac. It is now the *most* requested pathology test.
 I get so mad every time I see the clinical notes and all they say are: Diarrhea, ?coeliac </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best part of my day! 100% recommend it to every couple. We aren't a super romantic couple but we do have that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 07:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband and I often fall asleep holding hands. I love it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 22:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was very lovely. It was sugarcane country too, so as the sun was setting we got some nice views of the [cane fires](http://imgur.com/mbERXQF) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our car broke down in the middle of absolute nowhere. Oh well, may as well get a few stitches in while we wait for a cab to come get us </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 09:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 20:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been married 4 years and with my partner for 3 more before that...always used a condom.

Babies are *not* part of our plans right now. I am on the pill too, but it isn't 100% foolproof </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No spoilers] Someone seems a little confused here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 09:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 12:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They had an empty cage from another parrot, which came in handy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My sister was washing her car today and this friendly little guy landed on her roof and said "Hello!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 10:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 03:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are all wrong.

It is a pencil with wheels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 03:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> K </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 07:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know! I just imagine this adorable shamozzle of a line up where everyone is playing chasey and sniffing eachothers' butts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 01:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> K </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dog saved from Death Row by DNA test after he was falsely accused of attacking someone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 00:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 23:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thus making them the only two animals in the Monotreme group </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 23:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is one character who sounds like Barry Weiss...that douchecanoe from Storage Fisticuffs or whatever show. I can't unhear it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a phoney. A big, fat phoney. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 23:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 14:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need a better bouncy-ball related memory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 14:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't think it is misleading. I am saying it is uncommon to hear about female vs female domestic violence.

I guess if people are feeling misled, they coild just read all these comments and know the facts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 14:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geniuses, duh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 14:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I don't think I will. It is still uncommon in my society to hear about a case like this. Like I said, this was the first I had heard of a case like it...in recent news at least.

These are the kind of stats often quoted:

http://www.aic.gov.au/publications/current%20series/rip/1-10/07.html

There seems to be disagreement with numbers tho. Some say it is mostly male vs female, but others say it is about even </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 12:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel it would be less subtle if they had a guy out front who punches you in the face then gives you a flyer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 09:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I was not aware of those stats. In our news lately, there has been massive coverage of particularly violent domestic abuse cases (a handful of women have died recently). New measures, task groups, charities and workplace allowances seem to be springing up every day to help. To help *women* escaping their abusive *male* partners. I have not once heard mention of a female being an abuser until this article, which is why it struck me as uncommon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 08:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aand now you are on a list </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 07:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to get a niece

I sure hope you mean "you need your sibling to make you a niece".

You can't just pick up a kid from the street and call them your niece. There are laws </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 07:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say genius. More like pure mischief </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 06:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 06:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Off the side, to go hurtling 2 storeys down and cause pandemondium as they bounced all over the place below.

He *loves* telling me this story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 06:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here in Australia recently there has been massive talk about domestic abuse, but when they talk about the offenders they always talk about men. It is definitely portrayed as a Men vs Women issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 04:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah my bad, I forgot it didn't do it for titles. I just wanted to highlight that it was a woman and she was charged with rape. Not trying to cast aspersions or anything, just an interesting piece of information </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 03:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say so, yes. A lot of anger needed for that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman stabbed in eye and genitals by her *female* partner. Her attacker was also charged with rape. An uncommon case of domestic abuse, but no less important </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 03:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 02:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am a wife, so can say that I think honking is crucial in the success of a marriage.

A honkless marriage is a doomed marriage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 02:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I like you...in a totally creepy way

 (   ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 02:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband's favourite memory of his teens (and one he always brings up when he sees a bouncy ball) is when he went to an arcade and got 100+ of em, went to the top of the carpark and let them loose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 23:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geez, my husband won't leave me alone! I can't get changed in the mornings or afternoons without him leaping out from behind a wall and honking them.

You need to up your honking game. Make your wife *afraid* to get changed. So much so that she has to look over her shoulder every time she takes off her bra.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 23:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He knew his time had come and walked into the afterlife with courage, leaving the ones he loved behind to spare them the heartbreak </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 23:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, that cheerleader puts our school's cheerleaders to such utter shame. Our school didn't have a football team, so we didn't need cheerleaders, but that didn't stop all the chubby uncoordinated year 8 girls from grouping together and doing shitty dances to "Blow My Whistle" in front of the whole school.

Maybe if they had of pulled of these sick moves they wouldn't have been booed so loudly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 14:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you seriously not know the difference between a metaphor and an insult?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 13:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buddhism is huge in my hometown, Eudlo. It is a tiny speck of a town but it hosts a massive temple. The Dalai Llama has even visited

http://www.chenrezig.com.au/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 09:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand what not talking about the issue would achieve, except maybe closing the door on any people who might *need* to talk about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 00:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No shit it's a repost. He is trying to find his friend by making the story as visible as possible in as many subs as possible.

You are an asshat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 23:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That depends..are you my husband? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 23:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another Redditor posted [theirs]( https://www.reddit.com/r/crochet/comments/34ocwe/im_really_loving_this_sweet_little_ice_cream_coin/) and you will find the pattern in the comments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 22:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get lost nigga, you din wiin! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 21:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. I have seen them everywhere but I haven't seen the movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And it's all the way on the other side of the house! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 13:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
