<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9737</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 02:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude. /r/Tulpas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 02:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa. I read this out of context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 22:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blood libel (to what OP is referring to here) is a tactic of antisemitic theory. Hundreds of years ago Christians began spreading rumors that rabbis were using the blood of Christian babies in religious rituals. Of course, this was used to denounce Jewish people/culture and to further alienate Jews from Christians. This theory, if it can even be called that, is still alive   well in modern times.. The media is just out there to soil the minds of people willing to absorb these ridiculous things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 01:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eating out without a single cell phone in the perimeter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 00:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I didn't know Asia was a country!"

Her name was Asia.

And country, really?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 14:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dumb question: Can I use this in coupon in stores on my phone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 15:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *And women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 17:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SPECIFICALLY for supporting an addiction, ya know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 14:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article brought me back to dark moments in my Early Irish Literature class. Now all I'm gonna think about is Cu Chulain, shitty cows, and honor price. Thanks a lot, OP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 14:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as money, religion, and discrimination still exists, we're pretty much fucked.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 23:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate games like this so much, but hand painting this makes me respect you even more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
