<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8250</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The picture doesn't do it much justice. Its the roof of a parking garage that is caving downward in multiple areas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Around 730-8! I was looking at it and realized that it would be perfect for this subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is the Galleria! And yes, the picture really doesn't do it justice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not complaining, just very, "WTF."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The parking lot on top of the parking garage at my local mall. It's already collapsed once. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 13:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You'd probably never say in public, "I've got a bad back from my pipe laying days," even if you actually laid pipe for a living. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 22:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 22:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought a new 200C 2WD and I love it as well. I really don't see the problem with this. If anything it removes clutter from the climate control and arm rest area. Honestly, if you have a problem with it then you're just not paying attention. I've never had an issue distinguishing the difference between this new knob and the climate control. Great car overall so far!

Edit: problem with the parking knob, not the electronic brake, I realized I sounded kind of like an asshole to you without addressing what I was really talking about. Sorry! Directed towards the picture not you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 05:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an awesome comment. It is definitely much appreciated, those are the exact feelings that were derived from that exact place and time. I am glad some one received so much enjoyment from a photo that I was able to take!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
