<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1909</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 05:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is Soul Level? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 04:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not 100% sure what Soul Level is. Is that just your normal level? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 03:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy crap that would be so great! Thanks! SL is 13436
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 03:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is legitimately the first time I have said aww outloud from a /r/aww picture. "Awww" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PS3] Solair Armor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 03:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Solair. I want his armor. I would never *kill* Solair. If anyone has a character on PS3 where they wouldn't mind giving me the armor I would be forever grateful. If you do I will give you my Dark Sign! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I swear one of those fuckers was Dory. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 03:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Misleading title, I know. This may have been posted before, but this [video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-XPAdlkQYYA ab_channel=REACT) makes me want to run into the room and show these kids how to play. Especially the two girls who were bitching the whole time. At least this gave some more people a chance to see dark souls, even if it was through some shitty perspective. (I am very salty about this video) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 02:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any Animal Crossing fans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 05:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> indeed. Keep the same villagers, add more shit so we can sit and play for an hour plus. Loans for PWP would be gr8. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 03:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some say he's racist... others treat him like a god. Adolf Hitler has done some crazy things, but you won't BELIEVE what he did to these Jews! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one who thinks the next AC should be on 3ds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 03:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taking the time to use the Wii U to do animal crossing would be a strain. The game would sell 100% better on 3DS as well. Anyone else with me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 02:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 18:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try, thanks for the help! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 17:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never been to the Depths. I went to blighttown through the valley of drakes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 17:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By the "gaping dragons tail" do you mean drake sword? Like I said it's my first run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 17:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( Do I at least get his armor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 16:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ed the guy with the eggs on his back at the spider lady as well.

I may have... I will check. oh... that means I have to go back to blighttown... rip me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 05:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D: Is there no other place to get pyromancy's flame. I know there is some way to get it if you get egg headed, but idk if that requires the daughter of chaos to be alive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 05:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I killed him :/ I raged and went on a murderous rampage. Alot of NPC's died that day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 05:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is he located at Firelink Shrine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 05:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where could I get a Pyromancy Flame? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 04:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8chan, hitler, isis, nazi, north korea, patriarchy, piccolo, satanist, stalin to name a few.
lul. Fucking Dragonball Z offends feminists :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need Solair help. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 04:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not a member of the Chaos covenant or whatever. Solair is my favorite NPC and would hate for him to go insane. I killed white daughter of chaos after the Quelaag fight. Any way to save him? (I am at Anor Londo, so I don't think he can go insane yet, I just want to make sure) also first play through.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 01:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am wanting to figure that out myself. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 00:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the *fuck* Danny!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barry's desktop from the Smash episode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 23:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 18:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm. DAMN YOU MODS! D: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 22:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, more salt in this comment than in that entire video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So much salt in this video. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 21:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 20:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an idea for the use of the clothes hanger after the ring extraction! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1 new comment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 19:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] Crypt of the Necrodancer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 18:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 16:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha, thanks. :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 02:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AC for the DS emulator. You can use cheats and spawn all the bells you need! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 02:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 00:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 22:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 19:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, the only thing I got to take pics is a 3DS. If you are fine with that I will post a pic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 19:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> frontyard* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 19:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just woke up. What the hell have I done. :P NOT a fig tree though. No fruit. Also, found a way to make this weed related. Weed won't grow under it either! (oohh noes!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 21:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously didn't know. Was brosing /r/all and saw /r/trees. Didn't click the photo but I thought, hey, maybe they will know. Why not /r/weed or /r/marijuana? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 20:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAMMIT TREEMAN! I thought a man of trees would know this. :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 19:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> on a scale of 1/10 the amount of grass surrounding my tree. That does not mean pelvic hair. It means that my tree hates grass. I am not saying I hate weed. I am saying... dammit... I give up. You get what I'm trying to say right!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 19:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just realized this is a weed subreddit... *facepalm* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What type of tree is in my yard? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 19:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a camera to take a photo of it. It is gray and has green leaves. The leaves have 3, idk, prongs(?) It won't let any grass grow within ~3 foot radius of it. Do any of you guys know what it is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 19:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Semi-off topic. From my experience, Acer is not too reliable. I have had their products often breaking and messing up. Not sure about their monitors though. Just a thought :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 19:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fuck is that pic? I am very confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Older video, still can't get enough attention. Robin Temple </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 18:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 16:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I laughed at this way too much... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 05:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you spamming copypasta? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hugh just moved in. I believe he is a failed clone... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 04:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 03:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the majority do. There are always a few exceptions, but most Christians do. Most Christians avoid talking about the Old Testament because of all the "Why did God kill everyone?" and the "Don't shave your sideburns" comments. :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 01:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, thanks for the info. Since I am not planning to buy more cards with the money should I go with TCGplayer or ebay? Which one have you had better experiences with selling cards? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 01:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess after you buy it take a vid of you scratching the marks in and save them all in a folder. Lots of work but when you are working with expensive equipment it is prob worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 01:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you ask him if he was Robin Williams? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP Saiyan Build. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 01:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ultra OP build. All you need is Super Saiyan, SS Goku's Z-Soul, and Crusher Volcano. Charge, go SS, spam Crusher Volcano, for every kill ALL your ki fills up again. 2ez4me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 00:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old Testament and New Testament for Christianity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 00:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will. You are the only person to respond so far. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where to sell cards? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 23:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing for a little while. Never needed to sell cards because I like to collect them. Then, I pulled a Voice of Resurgence foil which is supposedly worth some money. Where would I sell it? Online? Local game shop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 23:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah, I see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 23:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Do as I say, not as I do." -Linus 20?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 23:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it is just a generation of every book ever randomly? Wouldn't that take an infinite amount of time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 23:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain what this is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 22:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, speaking of PC accounts, lets exchange our PC account names. My account username is: XxX69PotatoCrusher69XxX. Also, I have PC Gold so I can play games with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 22:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Islam should have 4, Christianity should have 2, and Atheism should have a Kindle. :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 22:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh, I see. Thanks for the info! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [META] How do you guys get screenshots of the game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 21:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know how to take them, but how do you get them to your PC? Do you use an adapter and a SD card reader? Seems like a lot of work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 04:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want to go on a salt filled rant about all these fatpeoplehate idiots that would get on bestof and I would have gold for 10 years. Instead, I only have 2 words. *Fuck you.* I have been a fan of Boogie for years now and it sucks how these assholes have no respect for him and what he has been through because he weighs "too much". I have been following boogie for a while and it astounds me how he gets all this hate and keeps going, keeps trying, and continues to inspire people. This dude is amazing. His fan base is just as great. He has the best community, who fucks up every asshole in the comments section who is a dick. Every time Boogie makes a video, I click it, and watch it. I will laugh, or cry. This dude has brought so much joy, and courage into my life there is nothing I can say to these pea brained bigots who don't look at *him*, but his *weight*. Also, I realize this is exactly what I said I wouldn't do earlier on in this comment... fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 03:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are we supposed to be seeing? A potato-quality Burger King drive-thru?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 03:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, Unpopular Opinion Puffin was banned a while ago. Que butt-hurt mods in 3... 2... [deleted] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 02:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think she knows exactly what she said... (   ) ( ~  ) ( o  o) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 02:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't this banned? Also, how are you expecting this dumb generalization to not be downvoted into oblivion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 02:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think she knows exactly what she said... (   ) ( ~  ) ( o  o) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
