<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject800</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wordreference translates it as fortress, palace, or castle. I guess it's a mix of palace and fortress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never implied that. I was answering to your blatant assertion that we don't know about a part of our history that lasted for 8 hundred years and makes a part of our culture. Maybe you think we have something against muslim history and culture, that in the school they lie about it or silence it, telling us we were better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 12:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, the same country were Al Andalus stayed for 8 centuries doesn't know about it. We don't have experts, teachers, historians, museums, archeologists, historical centers, investigations, books, touristic routes specialized in the matter.

Yeah, sure, mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 11:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Unfortunately we have to deal with media that are eager to find shocking news and don't give all the information and even distort it. The best thing to do is read articles from different sources to get all the different details, even reading independent people that have investigated and gathered all the info and maybe wrote some post in his blog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 11:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But... He's not a clown. I win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 01:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if she went crazy, there is still the question about how impossible it was for her to close the tank lids from the inside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 23:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you learn about "pre-Spain" era? Are you some kind of expert or made some specialized studies about that matter? Not trying to be sarcastic, I promise. Just want to know who I am talking to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 22:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, you still didn't provide any source using the "pre-spanish" term. I googled it and only found stuff about Philippines and Chile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 22:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I guess you are better informed about Spain history than the spanish educative system itself.

We are taught about Al Andalus since primary school. Nobody denies it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 21:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those aren't proof

The Iberian Peninsula being called Hispania in the year 27 b.c. is not enough proof for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 21:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry but I'm from Spain and I've never heard this "pre-spanish" term applied to Al-Andalus. In fact it would make no sense to a spanish person if you tell it. Could you give me some source where this term is used?

"Pre-spanish" implies that some spanish quality came after the muslim occupation. As /u/SNCommand is explaining you, this part of the world was called Hispania (Spain, Espaa) by the romans before the moors came here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 20:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to know what exactly is considered the "pre-spanish era". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 19:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read about this happening first in France, but the date of [this article](http://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2014/10/clown-killer-quest-ce-que-cest/382092/) and the ones this guy ([1](http://www.reddit.com/r/creepy/comments/38zrih/its_a_creepy_craze_in_california_now_mysterious/crz6oid)|[2](http://abcnews.go.com/US/mysterious-clowns-terrorizing-california-city/story?id=26157014)) posted are the same.

In France clown bands were really attacking people with weapons, provoking the creation of anti-clown patrols. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 19:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... our lord and savior John Wayne Gacy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 14:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  they use to sneak onto the roof all the time with their girlfriend. Apparently the alarms rarely went off.

In the Cecil hotel or another building?

just saying that bipolar can often cause SERIOUS cases of psychosis.

I'm not sure if I got it right because I still have some problems with my english, but I think they say in the video that the family denied Elisa having mental issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 13:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's just one of the many strange things in this case. Even the elevator behaved in a weird way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 13:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [In case anybody is interested](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VXM6OgrZl3U) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 13:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are gorgeous. The true definition of "androgynous hottie". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 22:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a very interesting case. It seems to be very famous, but I didn't know about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 21:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very useful for graffiti artists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 15:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly were you trying to communicate with this video?
What what it's objective? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 14:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't said "the universe itself is the product of their minds". What I mean is that there is a team of people that had to addapt the content of the books to the screen, and in that process they created some things. New events, new dialogues, sometimes new characters (who immediately die, lol). But, of course, the world that Martin created in compare to what we see in the show is huge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 14:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course it's derived from his writings but not totally. Some part of it came from other creative minds. Let's say 10%. I don't even know what I'm talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 14:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, yes, of course, all the characters and this world and stories and places came from Martin's mind. He is a genius, I admit it. But there are a some more writers creating memorable dialogues and plots that aren't included in the books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 14:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  everything we discuss on this subreddit and everything in the show and books

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 14:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably it came from the minds of a whole team of writers. I don't think Martin is writing the whole tv series by himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 14:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can that guy eat his spaghetti while watching to this horrible creatures? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 13:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh. This is the kind of shemales I don't like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 13:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I have started liking shemales recently. I prefer traps. I need them to be cute. I don't like guys with long hair, fake cheap tits and a dick. Bailey Jay and Natalie Mars got me into this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 13:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't realize it has an age restriction because of boobs. Sorry. Thanks for the link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 13:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because pretty chicks with dicks are hot. Not this one, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Masked crossdresser (not porn, I promise) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 03:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 02:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Soundtrack](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uUaXI3YXasE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 20:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt so sorry for him in season 4 that I could barely stand the scenes he appeared on. It made me feel uneasy. I felt like they were extending his suffering and humiliation too much for no reason. But that's just how I felt. I guess I empathized too much with him. This is partially due to a great acting, no doubt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 19:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 19:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It's magic](https://fedgeno.com/its-magic-i-aint-gotta-explain-shit.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 18:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Current 93 - I have a special plan for this world](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lxZpEFJhO6k) (22 min long)

[Penderecki: Threnody for the Victims of Hiroshima](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dp3BlFZWJNA)

I can't recall any particular song, but I heard some creepy songs by Diamanda Galas.

And here you have some albums:

[The Residents - Commercial Album](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MdSlFl5H76A)

[Diagnose Lebensgefahr - Transformalin](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VIQNUVTfKQM)

This album was made as a therapy by an ex-depressive-suicidal-black metal artist while he stayed at an asylum. I know this sounds like bullshit. Actually there are many fake rumors about this guy, but this asylum fact seems to be true.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 17:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You hold your pop in a box? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 16:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? Aren't you afraid that one day you will... Ooooh, I see... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 16:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it will be more like a new ice age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 15:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen all kind of serious shit in the internet, and it usually doesn't affect me. I even considere myself quite a pervert with some fetishisms, but the fact that this kind of material exists always unsettles me. People aroused by drawings of anthropomorphic animals swallowing things... It's just too much for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 15:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He died because of a cerebral edema while the filming of "Game of death" wasn't still finished. In that movie there is a scene where Bruce gets shot. Maybe that started the rumors. Some people still believe that's the scene where he died by accident, when a fake gun was actually loaded. I guess this rumors originated after his son died this way in the filming of "The Crow". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 14:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Death knows this and tries to not having any major celebrity in her list on April fools. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 14:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe this, from "The taking of Deborah Logan"?

https://33.media.tumblr.com/df7a7f89dc0e179dbe580a11e7ed9dfd/tumblr_ne5dc0N4Bt1tsy6uyo1_400.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 14:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eating like, with fork and knife on a plate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 13:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you hurt yourself or other people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 13:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you and your girlfriend ever played swapping gender roles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 13:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually they are scared men might find out they are actually aliens in human disguise.

wtf man? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 13:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this cultural appropiation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 13:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does he manage poop? Does he do it in plastic bags and later throw them in the garbage? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 13:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that_is_the_joke.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 02:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those beers look tasty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 02:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.thisiscolossal.com/2015/06/bruce-shapiros-mesmerizing-kinetic-sand-drawing-machines/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 02:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A huge simulator </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 20:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew I had seen this somewhere else before.

http://www.timecube.com/

But, what has this to do with the Lunchables trademark? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 15:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until now I was living in a deception, believing Reddit and 4chan were enemies and separate worlds. I believed that redditors were kind and civilized people that ocasionally posted dank memes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 12:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could expect this from /b/ but not from redditors. I am dissapointed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 05:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All you people signing this should feel ashamed. You are just hurting one person just for the sake of hurting.

Just let people live in peace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 20:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a day! What a mathematical day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 19:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know about bootlegs, but I don't trust in their sound quality, and I don't want to give my money to somebody stealing the artist's work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 23:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! You are right. I spent a lot of time there. I haven't visited it for awhile, though. I guess I got tired of going through all the memes and reposts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 23:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a reference to that article about the size of the printed version of Wikipedia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 23:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work in a public library. It has a big press section. Sometimes they throw away useless or old stuff and sometimes I pick up some magazines or books I can later use to make collages. One time I was attending this section and had a look in the recycle bin. I found a thick old magazine celebrating the anniversary of the death of Francisco Franco -Spain dictator for 30 years. I leafed through the magazine and found inserted in one of the pages a very thin and flexible disc. It turned out it was a compilation of recordings of speeches of Franco through history. National speeches, victory speeches, militar speeches. His galician accent, his special voice pitch and the particular way public figures used to spoke at that time of history makes listening to this a very special experience.

It's the rarest piece of my collection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 22:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Death Grips - Ex-military](http://www.discogs.com/Death-Grips-Ex-Military/release/3267383)
One of my favorite albums by one of my favorite bands. Can't be reissued because of copyright problems with the samples they used, so now it's kinda rare. Some copies are being sold for 150-200$.

[Moondog - Moondog (1969)](http://www.discogs.com/Moondog-Moondog/release/926533)
One album I love by a very special man: poet, composer, instrument maker and blind. They are even making a documental film about him. Was re-released last time in 2001. It's 35-75$ now.

[Have a nice life - Deathconsciousness](http://www.discogs.com/Have-A-Nice-Life-Deathconsciousness/release/6024716)
I love this album and it's quite common, but since the original recordings were destroyed by accident and only 128 kbps files were left to use for re-pressings, I'm only buying this when I have a lot of money and can afford it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 21:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a shame that they had to disable the comments in the video. Probably it was constantly bombarded by hateful messages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 20:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol dinosauers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 20:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, Dave.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 19:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 16:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: Kate 'vesner' Redesiuk
http://society6.com/product/popcorn-hsa_print#1=45
http://www.redesiuk.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
