<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8959</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dexter Morgan vs. The Joker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 16:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dexter Morgan wants the Joker on his table. Can he pull it off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 16:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *I think* Truck tire came off a truck going the opposite direction. Truck tires are about three feet tall and it is probably in a tree after bouncing off 3 cars at a combined speed of over a hundred miles per hour *but do not have any evidence to support this at this time.*

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 16:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was her make and model? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cars smashed by mysterious object </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 08:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Deathmatch] Nancy Grace with a sword vs. Stephen Colbert with facts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 05:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Times Square showdown, only one can survive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 19:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want a pet Michael Caine now. I didn't think about it one time in my life but now I can't stop. I'd feed him tiny plates of fish and chips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spiderman with a bleeding papercut vs. 3 bloodlusted great white sharks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 16:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spidey is dropped in the middle of the ocean with a tiny bleeding wound, three sharks all hungry for human blood attack him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible for internal organs to fossilize/petrify? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 05:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to find out whether or not a fossilized animal organ has ever been found or if it is somehow impossible for this to occur. Thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The sun slightly changes spectrum and humans, completely dependent on vision developed in the current UV spectrum, go completely blind. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 05:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 05:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trans-species surgery. South Park nailed it. Someone will be born human but know deep inside they want to be a Giraffe, and science will make it happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25 years ago, it was 1990. In 1990, someone saying "25 years ago" was referencing 1965. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 04:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 03:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmmm batcowburger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 21:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mac = Bruce Wayne </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arya Stark gives Jaqen H'ghar the name Bruce Wayne. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 17:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arya is an orphan girl in Gotham, angry that Bruces attention whoring is making orphans look bad. After saving Jaqen from a band of murderers and receiving his pledge, Arya asks him to take out Wayne. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Record Store Day Mixup Leaves U2 Fans Holding Tool Vinyl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 10:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DEA Chief to Resign Following Sex Parties Scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 10:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three Xenomorph Aliens are loose on Captain Piccards USS Enterprise. Does the crew survive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 10:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star Trek The Next Generation Enterprise crew only. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 08:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now I know that is a real thing that can happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 07:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ate one quarter cup of cinnamon. Frankly, it sucked goat ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the stupidest thing you have ever done? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 07:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 07:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forget the vocab, this has gone primal. The only way to gain his respect now is to piss on his leg while thumping your chest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 07:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mass compromise of systems renders encryption worthless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homeland Security Secretary Begs Silicon Valley to Stop the Encryption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 03:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Deathmatch] Yoda vs. Incredible Hulk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 03:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> City street fight, movie abilities only, no prep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Golden Girls Deathmatch: Sophia vs. Dorothy vs. Blanche vs. Rose </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 01:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The battle is in a city park at sundown. Only one can survive before sunrise or all die. Each contestant is given a bag with a weapon and additional item.
Dorothy: Taser and nightvision goggles
Blanche: Katana and Tracker displaying general location of other contestants, margin of error 10 feet
Rose: 1911 .45 caliber handgun with 2 rounds loaded in magazine and high powered flashlight
Sophia: Blowgun with 2 fast acting poison-tipped darts and a camo outfit
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congressmen to NASA: Stop Wasting Money on Global Warming Research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 09:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a feminist who buys gas that directly funds Saudi Arabias oppression of women. How many Tumblr posts do I need to make to balance this out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 08:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unarmed Bruce Wayne vs. a Velociraptor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 04:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bruce is completely unarmed, having a morning stroll in the woods when a Velociraptor appears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every male over 5 years of age suddenly turns into a zombie, hunting the living. Do the living have a chance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 20:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A single event changes all men currently over 5 world wide, the event does not reoccur (ie 4 year olds will grow up without changing if they survive). Zombies display '28 Days Later' speed and aggression. Once bitten, victim has 24 hours before change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 16:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Society doesnt support social security. It is your money, you paid into it. This isnt welfare, its money you earn your entire life specifically to collect when you need it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 16:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Show me some stats on successful newly hired people pushing 70.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mysterious group stakes claim for high-profile murders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 15:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 05:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By doing this, they just helped her afford the best defense attorney in the midwest at the rate the donations are pouring in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 05:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this mean GWB wouldn't be able to collect his post-presidential retirement pay until he hits 69? Or any congressional rep? 

Hello? Mr. Bush?

Is this thing on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bush: raise the retirement age </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 05:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 05:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can tell you graduated at the top of your class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frank Underwood, Dexter Morgan, Petyr Baelish (Little Finger), Tony Stark and Sarah Connor sit down to a game of poker. Who wins? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 18:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Each player has 100 thousand dollars to start. Texas Hold Em. No outside assistance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gregor Clegane (The Mountain - GoT) vs. Bane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 22:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fight in an open field. Demonstrated abilities on film/television only. Each fighter has one katana and one shield. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 18:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so old it was written in DOS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 07:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 06:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone blinks and suddenly dies but Superman as he flies around the room forcing water down their throats before they have a chance to react. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martin O'Malley Goes After Hillary Clinton For Leading By 'Polls,' Not 'Principles' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 06:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a straight Christian man, married to a woman with six beautiful children. Why do I keep wanting to put penises in my mouth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 06:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How does the US Federal Reserve know when to introduce more money into the economy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 05:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Luke Skywalker vs. Gandalf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 01:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 17:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You get one wish, but it can't benefit you in any direct way. What do you wish for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 17:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ixnay on the wishing for more wishes." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 16:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always preferred "Mind if I follow you into a dark alley and make you scream 'No, don't stop!' ?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 00:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That links to a youtube video of how qr codes work.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could anyone in Westeros stop Akuma from taking the Iron Throne? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 21:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 16:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My money is on Shlorpian. He should handle it without a problem. Cabtain Umerica may be abe to pull it off if he can get close enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Al Pacino vs. Robert Deniro vs. Christopher Walken </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 05:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Each man is at their prime health and age. Fighting at a mountaintop Buddhist temple in a raging storm at night, each man armed with a katana. Only one survives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fever Ray - Triangle Walks [Electronica/Alternative/Experimental] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 03:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dads been super depressed lately so I want to pull a joke on him for his birthday tomorrow. How much ecstasy should I put in his coffee before we go to my mothers funeral? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 03:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Genie from Aladdin is free. Who could defeat him? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 18:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The person you lost your virginity to suddenly kicks in your door right now and challenges you to a fight to the death. Will you survive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 13:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada and Mexico launch coordinated attacks against the US. How far do they get? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 23:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a T-1000 Terminator was sent back in time to kill Batman, would it succeed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 02:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 02:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posting a repost of a claim that "this is a repost". The circle of life continues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 20:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much are you paid to say this? I don't believe anyone could honestly believe that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it Really Going to be Prince Jeb vs. Queen Hillary? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 19:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom. Wait...

No, that's right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thom Yorke in an old appearance on Space Ghost Coast to Coast. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Incredible Hulk vs. a team consisting of every cartoon, TV show and movie version of Batman fighting together. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 10:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> City street fight. Current movie Hulk. Movie Batmen limited to one per actor playing the role. No implied or comic powers for either side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All racecar drivers are racists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 08:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bruce Wayne vs. Bruce Lee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 19:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No weapons, fight takes place in open field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 19:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a mental disorder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 16:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this, had no idea it was remade. Am definitely adding this to my list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 03:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the catch :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Suggest] 13 Sins (2014) A brutal thriller about a desperate man drawn into a twisted game show. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 03:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you consider to be a "perfect" day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 00:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama: Netanyahu 'misjudged' in demanding Iran recognize Israel as part of nuclear deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 09:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 09:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, I suggest you give it a shot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 09:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 07:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom Cruise was a samurai. The last one. That is also worth noting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 03:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why has no one mentioned Junior? Arnold in Junior would HORMONE RAGE. That has to be worth something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most disturbing thing you have ever personally seen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 00:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 21:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 20:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One city growing as dozens of towns die out. Bragging. #texanlife </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 20:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duh, Jesus will make it rain when we have a Christian president, didn't you read the manual? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 20:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you don't. Texas is already importing water and tapping into aquifers that they barely have access to. They've been sued for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 20:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Abundant water" compared to California, perhaps. But water is growing increasingly scarce in the Midwest and the aquifer is drying rapidly. This is not a California problem. This is a "Fuck, it's really affecting me personally" problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 19:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you a wizard? How the hell did you know that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 19:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you ask if my feet are phones? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every character Tom Cruise ever played forms a team and fights a team consisting of every character Arnold Schwarzenegger ever played. Who wins? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 18:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> City street fight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (SUGGEST) Beyond the Black Rainbow (2010) A dark, psychological thriller set in 1983 about a young girl with a special gift held captive in a medical facility by a psychotic, obsessed doctor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 05:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 02:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twenty first century. Still trying to prove Bible accuracy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every animal, reptile, amphibian, fish, insect and adept plant on Earth suddenly turns on humans and begin attacking us. Can humanity survive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 01:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finn and Jake (Adventure Time) vs. Ash and Pikachu (Pokemon) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 04:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I get a diet soda every day with my McDonalds but I'm not losing weight. Can I sue Coca Cola? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 03:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could Galactus create a being so powerful he cannot defeat it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 21:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A cure for aging/dying is discovered but it completely erases our ability to feel enthusiasm, joy or happiness. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 18:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Live the average lifespan feeling occasional happiness and joy or live forever without ever feeling happy again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good vs. Evil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 11:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every naturally good person in the world, alive or dead, bands together in the western North American region against a team consisting of every naturally evil person alive or dead occupying the East. Assuming the resurrection was a one time instance that can't be repeated, who would win if the two sides went to war? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 08:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you basing this on? Will you personally fight in a war with Iran? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran nuclear deal: Can the US Congress sabotage it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 07:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> V (V for Vendetta) vs. Batman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 05:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Batman visits London to help the police kill the terrorist known as 'V'. V targets Batman as an agent for an oppressive government. Only one lives through the night. Who survives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fred Flintstone vs. Barney Rubble </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 02:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fight to the death, cage match.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A weak minded person who is all powerful versus a weak bodied person who is all knowing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 15:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cage match. 24 hours to prepare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superman vs. Yoda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 07:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mountaintop fight to the death </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Mark Mothersbaugh, the lead singer of the band Devo, composed The Lego movie soundtrack including 'Everything is Awesome' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 16:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In light of the new Spiderman/Avengers announcement, could Spiderman take Ironman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 05:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Humans evolve in real-time in response to environment and needs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 20:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Blues Clues' was just a guy living by himself, talking to his dog, his mailbox, his salt and pepper shakers and an invisible audience. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 03:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every single time I tell my girlfriend she badly needs to start exercising, she starts crying. How can I get her to understand crying is not an exercise? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 01:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superman is actually a powerful Agent program in the Matrix. Can Neo beat him? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 22:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm supposed to speak at my mothers funeral but I am having nightmares every night, reliving what I've seen and now I'm scared it could happen to me. How can I be ABSOLUTELY SURE Kanye West doesn't take my mic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 07:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chun-Li, Akuma, Ryu vs. Wonder Woman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 07:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> City street fight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 01:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eventually? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 01:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully they do. AIPAC is disgusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superman vs. Justin Bieber in an Iron Man suit lined inside and outside with kryptonite </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 01:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superman is in the middle of an appearance on 'The Daily Show' when Iron Bieber crashes on to the set and challenges him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feeling guilty causes our thoughts to broadcast, allowing others to read them. All other times, we function as normal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 21:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists successfully photograph light acting as both a wave and a particle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 18:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every time you feel genuine happiness, a person you do not know dies a painful death. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 09:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All women around the world launch a coordinated surprise attack to wipe out men. Would men survive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 02:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My 97 year old grandmother has Alzheimers disease and I think she was born the wrong gender because she likes watching football. Who can I call to schedule her sex change operation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 15:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 21:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ted Cruz is a genius. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Words have flavor. Speaking positive or kind words tastes sweeter while harsh or negative words taste foul. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 18:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When people try to pass me on the highway, I speed up but slow back down when they get behind me again. What else can I do to let everyone know my penis is absolutely not microscopic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 18:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
