<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6188</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new satirical ad goes viral with a controversial jab at white privilege. It was released by "Look Different," an MTV campaign that seeks to undermine prejudice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zambia's President Edgar Lungu on Thursday reduced the sentence of 332 prisoners awaiting death by hanging to life imprisonment to ease maximum security prison congestion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I feel like a plan to kill 2 million feral cats by Greg Hunt is likely to involve something like importing 5 million feral dogs.

And then they'd have to import 5 million feral wolves to kill the feral dogs... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekend working ultimatum to hospital doctors: Health Secretary Jeremy Hunt argues the lack of a seven-day service costs lives, but he is accused of a "wholesale attack on doctors". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A long-term study of a large puffin colony on Fair Isle in Shetland has caused considerable concern after showing that breeding numbers have halved to 10,000 individuals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australian government declares war on feral cats in bid to save native animals: Greg Hunts plan to cull two million feral cats and create native animal safe havens receives cautious welcome from environmental groups. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australian government declares war on feral cats in bid to save native animals: Greg Hunts plan to cull two million feral cats and create native animal safe havens receives cautious welcome from environmental groups. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australian government declares war on feral cats in bid to save native animals: Greg Hunts plan to cull two million feral cats and create native animal safe havens receives cautious welcome from environmental groups. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> State wins millions against dialysis company. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kanuha accepts Tobacco Coalition gifts while sponsoring bill. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Darkode: FBI shuts down notorious online forum and cracks 'cyber hornet's nest of criminal hackers'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who live near fracking sites suffer higher rates of heart conditions and neurological illnesses, says research. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowboy welfare: Private profit from public Alberta land. Auditor general's 'bombshell' focuses on ranchers charging for access to public property </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veteran died and lay undiscovered in his house for 4 months, says sister: Retired corporal Shawn Brumsey died of a heart attack and wasn't discovered until mid-May. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colombian President Juan Manuel Santos confirmed Wednesday that the FARC guerrillas' latest cease-fire will last four months, allowing time for government and rebel negotiators to try to work out a definitive end to the hostilities. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japans atomic regulator on Wednesday said falsified documents at Chugoku Electric Power Co Inc related to radioactive waste showed the countrys nuclear industry still lags on safety more than four years after the Fukushima plant meltdown. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It is not fall yet, but Ontario teachers are starting to make good on their threat of back-to-school strike action, with English public high school teachers withdrawing from extracurricular activities on Monday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Vancouver city sanitation superintendent was shot and killed in Burnaby Wednesday, triggering an extraordinary police presence at city hall and a number of city work sites. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British Columbia's Forests Minister says soaring temperatures and paltry rainfall have pushed the province's most heavily populated region to the highest alert level on the drought scale. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 07:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British Columbia's Forests Minister says soaring temperatures and paltry rainfall have pushed the province's most heavily populated region to the highest alert level on the drought scale. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 07:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Old Montreal business owners angered by sidewalk repairs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 07:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Obama administration task force is expected to make recommendations on how the federal government do more to fight wildlife trafficking, a trade that largely revolves around elephant tusks and rhino horns, by the end of the month. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 07:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No, the Earth Is Not Heading for a Mini Ice Age. Sorry, climate change deniers: We're still warming the planet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 07:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for kenilsin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for eze2fine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for wendyjohn2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for privateMR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for cutpricemattresses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for JackWallner2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for wondershaper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for revolutionplussize </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for ksmit5a </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for MylottoApp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for marketingpirata </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for entroy45 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for hoianprivatecar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for Denvzla </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for saywutttut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for masbatgg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 04:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for helaliahelalia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 04:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A major Japanese corporation, Mitsubishi Materials Corp., will offer a landmark apology this weekend for using U.S. prisoners of war for forced labor during World War II. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 03:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new interactive map that was developed with the help of Canadian researchers at the University of Toronto is monitoring air pollution exposure during the 2015 Pan Am Games: Dubbed "AirSensors," the map shows the air quality health index at Pan Am sites across the Greater Toronto Area. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 03:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new interactive map that was developed with the help of Canadian researchers at the University of Toronto is monitoring air pollution exposure during the 2015 Pan Am Games: Dubbed "AirSensors," the map shows the air quality health index at Pan Am sites across the Greater Toronto Area. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 03:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-police officer who mocked paid suspension in email says hes a scapegoat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is kale making people sick? The dark side of everyones favorite superfood: A California-based researcher has been detecting unusually high levels of heavy metals in the leafy green. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 13-year study combined genetic and demographic data to determine that even though hunting mountain lions is prohibited in California, humans caused more than half the known deaths of mountain lions studied. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analysis: How much does the UK spend abroad on 'climate finance'? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The leader of Afghanistans Taliban insurgency has endorsed political negotiations with the Kabul government and foreign countries to seek a peaceful end to the 14-year old war. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Air pollution is an economic aberration that is costing France some 100 billion a year, according to a French Senate report published Wednesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Air pollution is an economic aberration that is costing France some 100 billion a year, according to a French Senate report published Wednesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost 7,000 sardines have died over the last two days in a reservoir in northern Puerto Rico due to the drought that has been shrinking the water supply for two months, making this the third massive dying off of this fish species in less than two weeks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the first time ever, coal has been unseated as Americas largest source of fuel to generate electricity. As of April 2015, natural gas is now number 1. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Animal rights group PETA said SeaWorld Entertainment Inc, known for its dolphin and killer whale performances, sent an employee on secret missions to infiltrate events organized by the group in an attempt to undermine its work. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Animal rights group PETA said SeaWorld Entertainment Inc, known for its dolphin and killer whale performances, sent an employee on secret missions to infiltrate events organized by the group in an attempt to undermine its work. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A team trying to fly a solar-powered plane around the world said it is suspending the journey in Hawaii after the plane suffered battery damage during its record-breaking flight to the islands: will continue the attempt to circumnavigate globe, but irreversible damage has grounded the flight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraq's antiquities minister says the Baghdad National Museum has gotten back nearly 500 artifacts recovered by U.S. Army commandos during a recent raid in Syria targeting the Islamic State group. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japanese automaker Honda has agreed to pay $25 million to settle U.S. claims that it discriminated against minority buyers by overcharging them for auto loans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Members of the Ossington Community Association are taking issue with a city zoning bylaw change that they insist provides a loophole for developers intent on building mega houses and condominiums on residential streets. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman receives 9 months probation for indecent act on Halifax-bound flight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A law prohibiting the sale of a service in British Columbia that preserves human bodies at ultra-low temperatures after clinical death is being challenged in the province's courts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Could you introduce yourselves?**

Hey there, I'm /u/train_subject6188! I've been on Reddit for almost two years now.

**How did you get involved here?** 

To be honest, there were three reasons I started the sub, one of which /u/carmabound has already covered. The second was that I joined the Mod Squad at /r/worldnews about a year and a half ago and thought it would be a good idea to learn how to do mod stuff without accidently tripping over the wires and unplugging a default. The third reason was there really isn't a sub out there that will allow me to post my jabberwocky.

**How would recommend your sub to new users**

If you're looking for a place to chill out and hang, pour yourself a drink and come talk story.


**Aims for this subreddit?**

Haven't the slightest clue.

**Favorite posts?**

All of them on /r/train_subject6188, of course! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 07:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay and thank you to /u/handicapreader and /u/carmabound!

As well as the fine folks at /r/TinySubredditoftheDay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 06:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They should consider Vancouver over Toronto if nature is what they're after.

I've never had the pleasure of going over to Vancouver. Have been through Toronto twice, when I drove from Chicago to New York through Canada...talk about taking the long, scenic route!

I really liked the drive and Toronto too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Lower House special committee on July 15 approved security legislation amid shouting, heckling and signs raised by opposition lawmakers that criticized Prime Minister Shinzo Abe: committee sent the legislation for a vote by the entire Lower House, possibly as early as July 16. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 06:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sightings of magpies, laughing kookaburras and willie wagtails are on the decline in some regions, a report tracking the health of Australia's bird populations has found. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 06:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sightings of magpies, laughing kookaburras and willie wagtails are on the decline in some regions, a report tracking the health of Australia's bird populations has found. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 06:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best and worst cities to be a woman in Canada, according to the annual study by the Canadian Centre for Policy Alternatives. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 06:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dozens of workers at a wildlife charity in Toronto have set up a makeshift triage unit as they try to save dozens of ducks covered in oil that spilled into a city creek. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 06:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beachgoers help save stranded great white shark: The great white was kept wet by people who splashed it with buckets of water until rescuers arrived to help it into the ocean. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 06:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colorados ambitious renewable energy standard will remain in place thanks to the 10th Circuit Court of Appeals, which on Monday shielded the law from a legal attack by a right-wing litigation group. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 06:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for MARKETING_PRODUCT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for rkmitinstitute </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for khimjistravel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for makinresidential </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for slipsafetyfloors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for loosyoswal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for elocations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for onyxsystem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for huntingsgrgau </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for snowyyang2001 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for gamesfreaky </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for completegarden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for Wholesalediamondsusa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for stellacott </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for berniesanders4pres </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for Minkmeapp12 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for jasmynroi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for arredocasa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for eenes150 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for DentalDesignProducts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for thaijobonline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for ozzietel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for thomaskertscher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for Jordan97k </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for michaelgusman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for bloggyleaks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lot's of positive vibes coming from these kids and it's good to see that they really do want to venture out of Japan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A $2.8 million project at Maalaea Small Boat Harbor begins this week as crews start removing and replacing a badly deteriorated pier adjacent to the harbor's new ferry terminal building. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your government on weed: Health Canada to spend another $1.5 million on anti-drug ads. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran's nuclear ambitions remain a major threat to peace despite Tuesday's agreement by Tehran to curb its nuclear program, Canada said, declaring that it would continue to judge Iran by its actions and not its words. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alberta faces growing backlog of abandoned oil and gas wells: Millions needed to clean up sites and mitigate environmental risk. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alberta faces growing backlog of abandoned oil and gas wells: Millions needed to clean up sites and mitigate environmental risk. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Japanese think of Canada  () (xpost from /r/Canada) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A pair of golden eagles have defied the odds to raise a rare set of triplet chicks. The birds usually lay just two eggs, which makes the hatching of three healthy chicks all the more unusual. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Planned Parenthood - claims director offered to sell fetal body parts are false: After a video, taken via hidden camera by an activist group, began to circulate the organization said there is no financial benefit for tissue donation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can Germany protect the wildlife havens on its former military bases? 62 former military bases have been turned into nature conservation areas, but they face challenges from careless motocross bikers and unexploded ordnance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The family of a black man who died after being placed in a white police officer's chokehold is holding a news conference Tuesday to discuss the $5.9 million settlement it reached with the city days before the anniversary of his death. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three more people have pleaded guilty in Miami for their roles in a $64 million mortgage fraud scheme, bringing to 25 the number of guilty pleas in the case. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Iranian nuclear deal shows the U.S. willingness to engage even countries "with long-standing differences," the State Department said Tuesday, stressing the U.S. is ready for negotiations as long as Pyongyang is serious about denuclearization. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Iranian nuclear deal shows the U.S. willingness to engage even countries "with long-standing differences," the State Department said Tuesday, stressing the U.S. is ready for negotiations as long as Pyongyang is serious about denuclearization. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Iranian nuclear deal shows the U.S. willingness to engage even countries "with long-standing differences," the State Department said Tuesday, stressing the U.S. is ready for negotiations as long as Pyongyang is serious about denuclearization. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German Chancellor Angela Merkel said on Tuesday that although she favoured measures to curb discrimination against same-sex couples, and that the case of LGBTQ+ rights had been advanced greatly, she did not think that marriage licenses should be offered to homosexual couples. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This story should be used in the travel brochures for Norway because after reading this, I really want to hop on a plane to the Historical Museum in Oslo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Viking Sword Discovered in NorwayBattle ax with shaft coated in brass also in grave. Charcoal dates to AD 1030, coinciding with coins found. Its quite possible the dead man was 1 of King Canutes men for battles with King Ethelred of England. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's always me, isn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
