<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9503</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gross Domestic Product, Indeed | Hurricane Sandy, divorces, malpractice suits, the BP spill - each of these involves cash transfers that get booked as adding value to the economy, but they clearly do not. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-10 16:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkified: Why I Can Never Be a Proper German | Marvellous first-person essay on growing up Turkish in Germany. However hard you try, you will never fit in; you are, at best, an object of curiosity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-10 06:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corralling the Loners | The truth is that, no matter how shocking or heinous a given crime, the perpetrator is one of us, and intelligent social policy cannot begin until we acknowledge this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 16:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Cut Poverty in Half in Ten Years | The War on Poverty contributed to cutting poverty by 43 percent between 1964 and 1973, to a historic low of 11.1 percent. We know how to do it, and we can do it again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 17:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plutocrats vs. Populists | The plutocrats have managed to seize control over politics in the United States and elsewhere. There is no lack of good answers, the problem is that the plutocrats have power to stop them from being put into practice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 17:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Great Austerity Shell Game: Here's How the Capitalist Scam Works | A remarkable two-step hustle. (1) massive borrowing funds stimulus and bailout programs. (2) austerity pays for the borrowing. This shifts most of the costs of capitalist crises onto the backs of middle- and lower-income people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 16:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Economic Growth Has Become Anti-Life | The peasants of the world, who provide 72% of the food, do not produce; women who farm or do most of the housework do not fit this paradigm of growth either. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 16:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Naomi Klein: How Science Is Telling Us All To Revolt | There is still time to avoid catastrophic warming, but not within the rules of capitalism as they are currently constructed. Which may be the best argument we have ever had for changing those rules. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 20:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five Reasons Why Cutting Social Security Would Be Irrational | 'Entitlement' means that people who have paid into a program all their lives are entitled to a reasonable return on their investment. A better definition is a "mandated retirement savings plan." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 17:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obamacare is a Republican Construct (So Why Are They So Upset?) | The Democrat's version of health insurance would have been cheaper, simpler, and more popular </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 16:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dont Even Talk About Cuts | Here is what people want: Jobs. Infrastructure. Higher taxes on the wealthy   corporations. City transit. Environmental protection. Bank regulations. Jobs. Fund the Post Office. Rebuild our cities. High-speed rail. Jobs. This list could go on for a very long time. Jobs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 20:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Triumph of the Right | The real triumph of the right has come in shaping the national conversation around the size of government and the budget deficit -- thereby diverting attention from whats really going on: the increasing concentration of the nations income and wealth at the very top. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 19:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Road from Here: What About Medicare and Social Security? | Social Security was not projected to run a deficit until 1, an enormous amount of our income moved above the current payroll tax; and 2, the financial crisis left 22 million un- or under-employed, depriving it of even more revenue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 19:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lets Get This Class War Started | The inability to grasp the pathology of our oligarchic rulers is one of our gravest faults. We have been blinded to the depravity of our ruling elite by the relentless propaganda of public relations firms that work on behalf of corporations and the rich. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 19:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Food Stamp Corporate Welfare | If you think the SNAP food stamps debate is about poor peoples need to eat, youre wrong. Its about big corporations need to profit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-20 18:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worse than Watergate | If the Supreme Court ends all limits on the campaign cash the super rich can throw at their candidates, American politics faces dangers far more troubling than anything Richard Nixon ever imposed upon us. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-20 18:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charter Schools and the Future of Public Education | In too many places, charters function more like deregulated enterprise zones than models of reform, providing subsidized spaces for a few at the expense of the many. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-20 18:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Water: Canada's Most Valuable Resource | Bulk water deals have nothing to do with global need and everything to do with global greed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 22:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans Are Delusional About US Spending and Deficits | Contrary to the widely repeated stories of out-of-control deficits and spending, deficits have plunged in the last four years falling from 10.1% of GDP in 2009 to just 4% of GDP in 2013. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 18:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Perfect Epitaph for Establishment Journalism | If the government tells me I shouldn't publish something, who I am as a journalist to disobey? Put that on the tombstone of western establishment journalism. It perfectly encapsulates the death spiral of large journalistic outlets. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 00:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Big Business Could End the Shutdown Overnight | So if business groups really became determined to end the government shutdown and the standoff over extending the federal debt ceiling, declaring a moratorium on campaign contributions ought to do the trick. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 19:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress and the President: Just Because You Were Bullied, Dont Take It Out on Our Seniors | Social Security contributes nothing to the deficit, is fully funded through 2033 and can easily be strengthened for even longer by raising the ceiling on payroll taxes above the current limit of $110,000. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 18:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are Americans Dumb? | The dumb ones are not the poor minorities or low skilled adults who fared badly on the OECD tests, however, but a certain privileged and selfish elite, who seem to think that denying millions of struggling Americans an equal opportunity to get ahead is a sensible way forward. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 18:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Subsidizing Economic Inequality | The federal government, we ought to keep in mind, already denies our tax dollars to companies with employment practices that discriminate on the basis of race or gender. Why should we subsidize economic inequality? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 18:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Rationality Shutdown | This is the sly, primitive, irrational part of government: its reptile-brain function. Thats still in full operation. Bizarrely, the irrational functions of government are usually called security, though of course they have nothing to do with rational security. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 17:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Debt Default: It Can Happen Here | One way of forestalling such a crisis would be for Congress to require that bills breaching the budget resolutions revenue floor or spending caps would have to include an increase in the debt limit equal to the increase in the deficit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 18:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican Crazy Talk About the Debt Ceiling | The President has only one option: He must ignore the debt ceiling and order the Treasury to continue to pay all the nations bills. If Republicans disagree, let them try to impeach the President. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 18:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Voice and Hammer | Harry Belafonte's unfinished fight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 22:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rich People Just Care Less | Though the more powerful pay less attention to us than we do to them, in other situations we are relatively higher on the totem pole of status -- and we, too, tend to pay less attention to those a rung or two down. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 17:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Id rather be dissected | There are never enough whole-body donations to science. Why dont more people want their death to help the living? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 02:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 07:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it possible that James Burke's series Connections would be useful for some of these older kids?  Not especially sciency but there's a lot of fascinating stuff about inventions in their historical context. Maybe for 8 years old and up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There Are No Significant Facts About Human Beings | I say that I have views and desires, but I have no way of saying whether they are really mine, rather than parroted. Its immensely unlikely that Ive ever had a remotely original thought. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 05:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Shutdown and He Said-She Said Reporting | Framing everything as a standard-issue partisan fight is almost a professional imperative for many journalists. But there are three reasons this is wrong. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 07:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Prion Love Story | I am writing to introduce myself and my wife and our quest to cure fatal familial insomnia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 21:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoreau 2.0 | You Can't You Won't You Don't Stop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 20:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They're Back! And Rich as They Ever Were | Together with the rest of their compatriots in the top 0.1%, the Forbes 400 capture half of all capital gains income in the country. We need to "tax wealth like work" and end this special tax break that disproportionately benefits those at the top. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 18:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inequality for All | We need a robust inheritance or estate tax that would limit intergenerational transfers of wealth larger than $50 million-and the elimination of offshore tax havens, which enable trillions of dollars in income to escape taxation and accountability. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 18:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which issuers of secured credit cards report them to the credit reporting agencies as just credit cards, not as secured cards? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 18:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Memento Mori: The Death of American Exceptionalism... and of Me | The question Why cant I live forever? assigns the custody of ones death to powers that make it their business to promote and instill the fear of it -- to church or state, to an alchemist or an engineer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 19:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Comedian (Louis C.K.) vs. The Smart Phone | Sadness is a big part of life. Kids need to get used to it, be at home with it. Its part of price of being human, of living in the truth. Its part of growing up. We want kids to laugh and cry for the best possible reasons. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 23:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exploring the Psychology of Wealth | Experimental evidence that rich people are more likely to break the law while driving, help themselves to candy meant for children, cheat in a game of chance, also to lie during negotiations and endorse unethical behavior, including stealing at work. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 02:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Making money is the easy part | A former director-level fixed-income banker exposes the cut-throat world of creating instruments for investment banks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 02:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Real Reason the Poor Go Without Bank Accounts | The banking industry needs to develop different fee and service structures designed to accommodate lower income depositors in much the same way banks currently provide VIP treatment to high-net-worth individuals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-21 21:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Case Against High-School Sports | The United States routinely spends more tax dollars per high-school athlete than per high-school math student-unlike most countries worldwide. And we wonder why we lag in international education rankings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 19:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Play Deficit | The rise in mental disorders among children is largely the result of the decline in childrens freedom. If we love our children and want them to thrive, we must allow them more time and opportunity to play, not less. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 01:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Letter to an Unknown Whistleblower | You are the perfect double agent. Until you become a spy for the American people, for the old democratic system in which those we elect were supposed to let us know what they were doing in our name, you arent just masquerading as one of them, you are. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 18:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We tend to be patronizing about the poor in a very specific sense...we tend to think, 'Why dont they take more responsibility for their lives?' And what we forget is that the richer you are the less responsibility you need to take for your own life because everything is taken care of for you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 06:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ditto Boys | On Westmont College, a feeder school to the upper ranks of the Christian conservative movement. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 21:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 04:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Challenge" is a completely normal word in English.  It's just not used in this way -- "try to challenge."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Repetition Compulsion for War -- and How It Might Fail This Time | Theres an antidote to the repetition compulsion for war. Its called democracy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 22:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Our Neighbors Wish Us Dead or Broke, We're in Trouble with More Than Our Health Care System | "When someone gets sick or hurt and lacks insurance or cash to pay for care, should they just die?" He didn't answer in words, just shrugged his shoulders again and smiled. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 18:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Work Is Undervalued in Societys Obsession with Stuff | If workers were truly valued as people, wouldnt there be at least some semblance of democracy at work? Instead, the master-servant relationship is the legal framework that dominates under our current economic system. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 18:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Organized Labor's Decline in the US is Well-Known. But What Drove it? | To escape the label of "special interest" unions must work for far more than their own members. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 20:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its a Myth That Entrepreneurs Drive New Technology | A quick look at the pioneering technologies of the past century points to the state, not the private sector, as the most decisive player in the game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 17:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Appeal to Gen. Dempsey: Resign If Obama Orders Attack on Syria Without Congressional Authorization | "As seasoned intelligence and military professionals, we have long been aware that - from private to general - it is ones duty not to obey an illegal order." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 17:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fraud, failure and bankruptcy pay well for CEOs | Over the past 20 years, nearly 40% of the top-paid executives were bailed out, booted out or busted. [x-post from r/business] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 06:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fraud, failure and bankruptcy pay well for CEOs | Over the past 20 years, nearly 40% of the top-paid executives were bailed out, booted out or busted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 00:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the Assault on Whistleblowers Has to Do With War on Syria | Countless deaths and unfathomable suffering have resulted from the failure of potential whistleblowers to step forward in a timely and forthright way--and the failure of journalists to challenge falsehoods in high government places. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 16:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tutor reveals Ivy-admissions madness of rich penthouse parents | This is the biggest secret to success in the college applications madness: Its not about getting kids in. Its about allowing them to grow up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 01:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want to Win a Political Debate? Try Making a Weaker Argument | Information is more likely to have the desired effect if, on net, it doesnt lower a persons self-worth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 00:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA and GCHQ: the flawed psychology of government mass surveillance | Indiscriminate intelligence-gathering presents a grave risk to our mental health, productivity, social cohesion, and ultimately our future. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 18:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Leveraged Buyout of America | Giant bank holding companies now own airports, toll roads, and ports; and store and hoard vast quantities of commodities of all sorts. They are systematically buying up or gaining control of the essential lifelines of the economy. How have they pulled this off? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 18:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cynicism is Corporate Americas Greatest Weapon: Disarm It | Were not saying the situation isnt dire. Were saying weve overcome dire situations before. The forces arrayed against the publics interests are frightening. But its worth reminding ourselves: Theyre frightened of us, too. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 16:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 23:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And is 'mid drifts' an affectionate Briticism?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Internal Clitoris | It wasnt until as recent as 2009, French researchers gave the medical world its first complete 3-D sonography of the stimulated clitoris. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 20:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ben Nelson: The Man Who Would Overthrow Harvard | Can the Minerva Project do to Ivy League universities what Amazon did to Borders? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 02:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Wiz (Washington Post 1993) | Navigating life as a brilliant teenage girl. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 04:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Power Goes To Your Head, It May Shut Out Your Heart | The good news is an emerging field of research that suggests powerful people who begin to forget their subordinates can be coached back to their compassionate selves. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 19:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Are Seniors Changing? (Take A Look At Who They Are) | Theres no doubt in my mind that boomers are going to change this cohort in many different ways over the next few decades just as they changed everything else in their (our) lives. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 18:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spending is Not Growth: The Case Against GDP | Economic disasters like the BP oil spill and Hurricane Katrina demonstrate the inherent limitations of GDP as a measurement of economic growth, health, or the well-being of citizens in an economy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 17:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 21:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now rarely, next seldom, then often, eventually usually.  I believe it gets easier when you see the benefits of sharing a vulnerability.  Also there are good opportunities for humor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Punishing Kids for Adult Failures | If the nation judged Duncan as he thinks teachers should be judged - by the rise or fall of student test scores - then he would be fired for presiding over a disaster. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 18:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keep Your Identity Small (2009) | If people can't think clearly about anything that has become part of their identity, then all other things being equal, the best plan is to let as few things into your identity as possible. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 04:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 23:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever tried being up front about your hearing difficulties?  Like, 'Sorry, I don't hear well, it sounded like you said gerrymandering.'  I once took a Hearing Society class that helped me a lot with being up front. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Strengthens and Weakens Our Integrity - Part I: Why Small Choices Count | Once you commit one dishonest act, your moral standards loosen, your self-perception as an honest person gets a little hazier, your ability to rationalize goes up, and your fudge factor margin increases. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 18:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 8 Ways Privatization Has Failed America | Health Care; Water; Internet; TV, and Phone; Transportation; Banking; Prisons; Education; Consumer Protection. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-05 19:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The $4 Million Teacher | South Korea's students rank among the best in the world, and its top teachers can make a fortune. Can the U.S. learn from this academic superpower? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-03 21:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Extradition Theories Collide: Snowden's Whistleblowing vs. CIA Kidnappings | There was not a single editorial, outraged or otherwise, anywhere in this country questioning the administration's decision not to allow a convicted criminal to be brought to justice in the courts of a democratic ally. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 18:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antibiotic resistance: The last resort | Perversely, the rapid advance of resistance and the consequent need to use these drugs sparingly has convinced pharmaceutical companies that antibiotics are not worth the investment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-27 23:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Brief, Tragic Reign of Consumerism-and the Birth of a Happy Alternative | The guardians of the consumer economy are not stupid. They will not permit the wholesale introduction of happiness metrics absent necessity. But, as weve seen, necessity is coming. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-27 19:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Detroit's Decline Is a Distinctively Capitalist Failure | The auto industry Big Three were loyal only to shareholders, not the people of Detroit. The city was gutted by that social choice. Capitalism as a system ought to be judged by its failures as well as its successes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 19:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> J.K. Rowling and the Chamber of Literary Fame | Rowlings spectacular career is likely more a fluke of history than a consequence of her unique genius. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 18:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal Research Suggests New Approach to Teaching Fractions | The typical American approach to teaching fractions can overemphasize procedures at the expense of understanding the relationships among numbers, which is needed for higher math. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 21:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Physicists offer new theory on cancer | The new theory claims that cancer is actually an organized and systematic response to some sort of stress or physical challenge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 02:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Life-or-Death Situation | As a bioethicist, Peggy Battin fought for the right of people to end their own lives. After her husbands cycling accident, her field of study turned unbearably personal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 01:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Cop's take on the Zimmerman Verdict | I am sure that my old department would not have hesitated a moment to prosecute any off duty police officer if they had done the same thing that George Zimmerman did. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 19:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spanking in Childhood Tied to Adult Obesity and Heart Disease | Children who were punished physically had higher risks for cardiovascular disease, arthritis, and obesity in adulthood. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 18:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Do Americans Live Lives So Short? | Americans now live shorter lives than men and women in most of the rest of the developed world. And that gap is growing. The more unequal a society, the more unhealthy most everyone in it -- and not the poor alone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 18:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Special Deal  The shadowy cartel of doctors that controls Medicare | Allowing a small group of doctors to determine the fees that they and their colleagues will be paid not only drives up the cost of Medicare over time, it also drives up the cost of health care in this country writ large. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 06:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Cant Offline-Borns Tell Difference Between Voluntary And Forced Actions? | Just because somebody chooses to be open about some parts of their life voluntarily in ways that the offline-borns wouldnt, that gives them no right whatsoever to take the rest of the net generations privacy by force. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 02:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Culturalism, Gladwell, and Airplane Crashes | Perhaps we focus so much on a plane crash for the reason that it is a rare deviation from perfection...Like racism, culturalism distracts away from asking more meaningful questions, and obscures pertinent facts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 21:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is to be done about the banks | In their current condition our banks are an existential threat to British democracy, a more serious one than terrorism, either external or internal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 00:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blowback from the White House's Vindictive War on Whistleblowers | Everything Adolf Hitler did in Germany was "legal" and everything the Hungarian freedom fighters did in Hungary was "illegal". Obedience to the law should not be absolute. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-06 18:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Roots of Social Rebellion? Social Movements | Like the American Dream, there is now a Brazilian Dream, a Chinese Dream, and an Indian Dream--all featuring hopes of individual car and home ownership and expansion of the automobile market, at the risk of immobilization of the poor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-04 18:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For Journalism, Objectivity vs. Subjectivity Is False Dichotomy | Everyone is an activist of one kind or another. The distinction should rather be drawn between conscious activists and unconscious activists. Those who fail to reflect on their own commitments are sometimes the most vicious. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 17:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No Self-Mockery, Please, We're American | One of the gravest moral defects of Americans is that they tend to be straight, honest, and plain-speaking. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-02 07:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Evidence That US Middle Class is Sliding Toward the Third World | As a sign of the distance between America's middle class and its national wealth, the ratio of median to mean in the U.S. is lower than in any country except Russia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 17:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Color Of Law | Voting rights and the Southern way of life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 07:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Believe It or Not!13 Mindblowing Facts About Americas Tax-Dodging Corporations | Serious politicians and pundits are demanding that ordinary people sacrifice earned benefits, while at the same time allowing corporations to avoid more than ten times as much in taxes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 17:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Fallacy of Human Freedom | Enthusiasts for reason have not noticed that the idea that humans may one day be more rational requires a greater leap of faith than anything in religion. Outside of science, progress is simply a myth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-26 18:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Connecting the Dots, Missing the Story | The supertool Big Data is made out to be is a rather feeble instrument that tackles problems quite unimaginatively and unambitiously. Worse, it prevents us from having many important public debates. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-26 06:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does life have a purpose? | Is biology basically different from the other sciences because living things do have purposes and ends? Or has biology simply failed to get rid of some old-fashioned, unscientific thinking? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 06:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Physics Behind Traffic Jams | Here's how to dissolve a major interstate traffic jam. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-24 20:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paris Air Shows Slowest Plane Could Have Biggest Impact | By using the electric motors on each of the main gear to move the airplane, the main engines dont need to be switched on until the airplane is close to the runway and ready to take off. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-22 21:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Technical Interview Is Dead (And No One Should Mourn) | "Stop quizzing people, and start finding out what they can actually do." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-22 20:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Are Americans So Passive? Get Pissed Off and Break Things | The appropriate, intelligent and self-preserving response to mass theft is rage, demands for action, and decisive punishment of political and economic leaders who refuse to change things. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-22 18:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finding women who can write is complicated at the London Review of Books | "Based on the tedious regularity with which you ignore female writers and female reviewers, I have to assume that my lady-money is quite simply not welcome in the man-cave of LRB." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 20:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another Brick in the Wall: Supreme Court Shields Corporations From the Law (As Usual) | The Court established a legal Catch-22. A process to resolve disputes has been established that effectively can never be used. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 20:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Cities Should Use Public Banks Instead of Big Banks | A different paradigm should frame the issue of access to credit for the public good than that which governs credit for private investment. Rather than a utopian dream, public banking is an option that actually works. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 19:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lochnerized: Corporations have Constitutional Rights. Unions? Not So Much | Corporate Personhood is a farce, a facade conceived to subvert the rights of real people, a fictional idea imagined to ignore democracy in the name of enriching plutocrats. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 19:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Science of Why We Dont Believe Science | It would seem that expecting people to be convinced by the facts flies in the face of, you know, the facts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 00:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Know What You Think of Me | We dont give other people credit for the same interior complexity we take for granted in ourselves, the same capacity for holding contradictory feelings in balance, for complexly alloyed affections, for bottomless generosity of heart and petty, capricious malice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 04:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> America Feeds the Rich | A food stamp applicant must prove poverty to qualify for government aid. But not big business. Not agri-business. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-17 18:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> America's Private Prison System is a National Disgrace | An ACLU lawsuit against a prison in Mississippi is the latest to detail flagrant abuses at a private correctional facility </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 17:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Two Centers of Unaccountable Power in America, and Their Consequences | Both the political left and right are worried about the encroachments of the NSA on the privacy and civil liberties of Americans, as well as the depredations of too big to fail or jail Wall Street banks on our economy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 17:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the NSA Trusted Edward Snowden With Our Data, Why Should We Trust the NSA? | The more badly Snowden is depicted, the more rickety the governments case for surveillance becomes. After all, they hired him. They gave him unrestricted access to their systems. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-10 18:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edward Snowden as Conscientious Objector | US members of Congress ought to be seeking the earliest opportunity to learn what this brave whistleblower is saying. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-10 17:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its the Corporations, Stupid | My hypothesis is that whereas the gun manufacturers clearly make big bucks off their weird absolutist interpretation of the 2nd Amendment, there is no set of corporations that would lose billions of dollars if the government snoops into your phone or email traffic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-10 17:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Minimum Wage: Putting Some Myths to Rest | If minimum wage had kept pace with productivity, it would be approximately $22/hour. If it had grown at the same pace as the income to the one percent, it would be around $33/hour. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 18:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mass Incarceration USA: How a Broken System Perpetuates Itself | Jerry, who is a black man, wasnt simply stopped. He was arrested for riding his bicycle on the sidewalk. After all, he had committed a crime. He was handcuffed, put into the squad car, taken to the local police station. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-06 17:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-06 04:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is a fairer way to get the full quote under 300 characters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On the Moral Grounds of Economic Relations (2010) | In the immediate wake of great disasters people tend to revert to a kind of rough-and-ready communism. Hierarchies, markets and the like become luxuries that no one can really afford. Communism is the foundation of all human sociability. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-05 20:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Landays lilt internally from word to word in a kind of two-line lullaby that belies the sharpness of their content, which is distinctive not only for its beauty, bawdiness, and wit, but also for the piercing ability to articulate a common truth about war, separation, homeland, grief, or love. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-05 18:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Darwin, the Greatest Psychologist | The fundamentals of our conception of human nature can all be found in Darwins notebooks, written 175 years ago and before his thirtieth birthday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-05 17:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you pay them money, partisans will tell you the truth | Democrats and Republicans may diverge in their survey reports of facts, but such responses should not be taken at face value as sincere expressions of partisan worldviews. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-05 03:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does France insist school pupils master philosophy? | The purpose of the philosophy Bac is not to understand the history of human thought but to leap into the stream that is the actuality of human thought. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 19:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lets Talk Taxes; Lets Talk Trillions | Americas deepest pockets, a new report shows, are saving big bucks from the U.S. tax codes wide assortment of income tax breaks. Theyre saving even more from the absence of a wealth tax. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 19:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The notion that a radical is one who hates his country is naive and usually idiotic. He is, more likely, one who loves his country more than the rest of us, and is thus more disturbed than the rest of us when he sees it debauched. He...is a good citizen driven to despair." -- H.L. Mencken </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 18:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We Must Not Accept This Economic 'New Normal' | Yes, the economy is improving, but too many Americans are being left behind, while the rich keep getting richer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 17:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Graeber: On the Invention of Money--Notes on Sex, Adventure, Monomaniacal Sociopathy and the True Function of Economics | Homo Oeconomicus is an almost impossibly boring person--basically, a monomaniacal sociopath who can wander through an orgy thinking only about marginal rates of return.2011 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 22:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Problem Is Capitalism | Only radical reforms will solve neoliberalisms crisis of democracy. Socialists need to teach the liberals to fight once again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 17:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 'We Steal Secrets' Documentary on WikiLeaks Is Incredibly Biased | We live in such a perverse moment in society that a film is portrayed as "balanced" when it paints whistleblowing as deviant behavior. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 21:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elusive Entropy | An unfortunate conflation of the concepts of entropy and disorder has resulted in widespread misunderstanding of what thermodynamic entropy actually means. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 18:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beyond Personhood: Why Corporations Love the Constitution More Than You do | The Constitution is more of a flow chart for how decisions are made that currently is a set up to ensure the financially wealthy win and that real power is out of our grasp. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 17:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corporations Cozy Up to Judges | Perhaps the silver lining to the corporate storm cloud, which brought us the economic crash of 2008, is that most Americans have awakened to the fact that our democracy is suffering under the weight of corporate personhood. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 17:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doubting Obamas Resolve to Do Right | He has now been unusually candid about the dilemmas he faces. But lacking is any real sign  there is just hope  that he will change character. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 17:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Radical Kleptocrats Anxious to Stop Disclosure of Corporate Money in Elections | The great majority of Americansincluding Republicansagree that, at the very least, the shareholders who own the corporation have a right to be told how much of their money is being spent on behalf of which candidates. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 17:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Unexotic Underclass | When I look at the bulk of startups today, it doesnt seem like weve aspired to something nobler: it just looks like weve shifted the malpractice from feeding the money machine to making inane, self-centric apps. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 02:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Future Shlock | One day Google, too, will fall. The good news is that, thanks in part to this superficial and megalomaniacal book, the companys mammoth intellectual ambitions will be preserved for posterity to study in a cautionary way. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 18:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fire School | If you train as a West Texas firefighter, and your boyfriend is an emergency medical technician, you come home with quite a few stories to share. Heres a selection. How to section a car with hydraulic tools. More on the West factory explosion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 17:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Chained CPI Is Bad for Seniors and for Accuracy | Reducing benefits is neither right nor necessary to avoid the projected shortfall in Social Security payments starting in 2033. Lifting the payroll tax cap would eliminate the entire projected shortfall in one easy step. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-27 00:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Liberals Need Radicals | "Without radicals pushing deeper and bolder critiques, liberalism will struggle to achieve real change and easily devolve into a technocratic project, which is pretty much where it is today." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-25 20:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Biggest Criminal Enterprise in History | "To destroy our planet with malice aforethought, with only the most immediate profits on the brain, with only your own comfort and wellbeing (and those of your shareholders) in mind: Isnt that the ultimate crime? Isnt that terracide?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 19:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tax-Avoiding Corporations Siphoning Billions from World's Poorest | "Almost half of all money invested in developing countries is channeled through tax havens, stripping developing nations of the chance to benefit from the wealth generated by multi-national firms inside their borders." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 19:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Globalization of Hypocrisy | "Major corporations have ignored all the problems they've caused, choosing instead to cut their taxes in half despite doubling their profits, hold 60% of its cash offshore, eliminate workers rather than create jobs, and reduce the pay of their remaining employees." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-20 18:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fighting Poverty Through Wall Street Accountability | "The banks created a disaster, and economists and politicians said, Thats terrible for the economy, lets give them trillions. And then the folks who were actually hit the hardest were forced into poverty." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-18 04:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Upside Down Economy | If profits are rising while revenues flatline, and if employees from temp agencies are putting in longer hours than anybody else, its chiefly because American workers have lost the capacity to defend their interests. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-14 18:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 05:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whew!  Let us know how it turn out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-11 22:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shyness, fear of being wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
