<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5173</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will, if possible  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great! waiting for your new movie and good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, so will you choose to watch it again if you get any chance?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, word of mouth can make every movie successful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this mean we have no more 007 series? What a pity! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see~ So have you ever thought of the things about your second movie?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ant-Man tops U.S. box office with second-lowest opening for a Marvel Studios movie, earns $114 million worldwide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you choose Suspicion to be your Directorial Debut? I mean you must have had some choices and why you finally chose Suspicion?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But creating heroes in the movie doesn't mean creating the heroes in our real life. In my opinion, in order to fulfill people's desire of heroes we need to make our nation stronger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 08:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't agree more. And this kind of films are popular outside America, which enlarge the market and gives the film maker more profit to make. But now I want to know what things they will make into hero in the future. So far we have iron, spider and so many things. It seems that children and boys are more addicted to this kind of films.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 08:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, so I mean there won't be so many women who want a guy at their father's age to be their boyfriend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 06:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, the monster on the cover is very cute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 06:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ant-Man has arouse heated discussion recently but I haven't seen it. Do you think it worth watching? I am thinking about finding a time to watch it with my friends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Latest movie list, which one do you like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 05:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 05:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 16 maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
