<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4367</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 06:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mirror scene in 25th hour and the "Dead N-Word storage" scene in Pulp Fiction.

In both scenes, our awareness of the directors' personalities breaks immersion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 04:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just watch the Directors cut. It adds some excellent scenes that are missed in the theatrical. it also adds some silly bits, but overall its the better version of the movie. 
The ultimate cut is neat, but don't watch it for your first time. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duly noted.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 02:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, 
It does bug me that he cites "too dark" as his reason for distancing himself from Temple. When I think it is more likely the other, like you said.
the movie is just a case of Spielberg sticking a bit too close for comfort to the adventure serials he loves so much without finding a way to subvert or update their more questionable tropes for modern sensibilities.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 00:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't drastically change or improve the film. But it's nice to watch if you want to see more mutants doing mutant things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 23:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it strange that people seem to have more of an issue with the silly bits in Crystal Skull than the troublesome xenophobia and sexism in Temple of Doom.

I think they're all varying degrees of good, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 21:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He falls out of a plane in an inflatable raft and doesn't get hurt.
You go try that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 08:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wes Anderson

Organized Crime film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 07:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simple Plan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 03:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I'm remembering right.
Yojimbo was sort of a response by Kurosawa to critics saying he was too "western" in his filmmaking.
Kurosawa was "I'll show you western!" With yojimbo.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 01:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like it is going to be similar to Jumanji or Zathura </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 01:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your use of "boring" confuses me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
