<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5136</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why on earth is this on /r/askreddit?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the WSJ thing I want to get working with or without the root. Was asking how to get that 'gift' in the first place. 

Also, when you say warranty, do you mean Samsung's warranty? I have t-mobile's stupid warranty for $8 a month.

And what about this site? 

http://galaxynote4root.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lenovo design chief wants to build a retro-styled ThinkPad laptop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 18:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is the aspect ratio so lame? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 18:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is the aspect ratio so lame? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will help the GOP.

"Senator, what is your position on gay marriage"
"Why is that significant? That issue has already been decided. My stance on gay marriage, pro or against, would have no bearing on how I will govern. Next question". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2 questions - rooting my phone, and Samsung gifts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. I want to root my phone. I have a T-mobile SM-910T. Will this help with my battery life? My battery life SUCKS after the lollicrap update (can we start calling it **Lollicrap** please?).
So can I root this phone? I know for some phones you can't. I also don't know/care what KNOX is.

2. I remember I got a Samsung gift for 6 months free of WSJ, but I never did anything with it, and kind find any info. Anyone know what I need to do? I've had the phone for 7 months already - but I never activated the subscription, so I should still in theory be able to use it.

EDIT: this second question is completely unrelated  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok cool thanks. I'm not sure if I personally see value in that, but that's a good distinction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 05:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, not bootstrap paradox. It's the **'Predestination Paradox'** - which is not actually a paradox.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 05:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why should I use Atom instead of Sublime Text 3 (other than $$)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 05:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Obama </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 05:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have it, and it's my favorite. It's awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 23:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Probably because they didn't think of it first

This. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 21:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Come, and journey into the mystical forest of the elves..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 21:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. Love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 20:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing color. It almost doesn't even look real. Great stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 20:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an amazing reflection </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 20:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All those people who killed themselves after watching Avatar should have just come to /r/earthporn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 19:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait but you only get the 1% back if you spend it as credit - which you can't do when loading redcard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah I see. So you just don't like the naming convention. That makes sense - especially since Vegeta went from SSJ2 to SSJ4 - which doesn't make sense if that's how you name it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 17:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I don't plan on doing more than $500, maybe $1,000 a month. I really just want some points and to pay some bills using REDcard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Loading REDcard with Paypal Business Debit Masterdard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 17:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Paypal Business Debit Mastercard. I'm wondering if I can use it to load my REDcard account. Has anyone tried this? The CVS by me allows me to buy Paypal cash cards with a CC - which is great, because the fee is only $3.95 for a $500.00 purchase.

For the record, there are 2x such CVS that I know do this.

* CVS on Howard and Western (Chicago)
* CVS in Ogilvie Train Station (Chicago) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 16:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wondering what /u/shewdz would say. He complains that SSJ4 isn't an advancement from SSJ3.

 but it kind of muddles the SSJ line as theoretically you could achieve it after only achieving SSJ1

By that logic, SSJG is even worse. You don't even have to become an SSJ to become an SSJG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 16:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you did there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 01:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean like SSG? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 01:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then how do you feel about SSG? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That response was way too PG-13. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judgemental. Very judgemental </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. This deserves more upvotes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vox. A very, unbaised, legitimate news source...

Not saying they are wrong, but posting a liberal blog to outline a Republican is just kind of stupid and couldn't possibly lead to an objective analysis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a neighbor who has a sign on his lawn that says, "black lives matter". I want to put a sign next to his saying, **"white lives don't"**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Banning in general? No, it's idiotic and goes apart from the 1st Amendment. Banning from official public properties, and issued material? Yes.

Agreed. That's an important distinction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am pretty pro-gun for the most part. But honestly, the two day waiting period seems pretty reasonable. I mean, if you order a gun, it might take a while before you get it. 2 days? I think it's more than appropriate.

EDIT: you guys are right - if you already own guns, then the waiting period makes absolutely no sense. So what about the woman who needs a gun to protect herself **now**? We make her wait? Good point. we don't want that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't we see the same thing about another state recently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am nano offended by your micro offendedness of micro aggressions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 22:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm coming from windows/Linux, and the Finder has been infuriating. I know you posted a month ago, but I hear you. Finding the path, opening a terminal from the finder, or moving up one directory should not require research. Very frustrating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 22:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was absolutely infuriated with the finder last night. Same of the same complaints. It's really shit, honestly. Shouldn't have to do a Google search to figure out how to find the current path or how to move up a directory.

And how about opening the terminal from the finder? No? I need an app for that? FU Apple.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 22:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That Illiana bullshit needed to die. Leftovers of spending hungry Democrats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 22:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not baffling whatsoever. Look at the shape this city and state is in.  As /u/TheJPdude says, people voted *against Quinn*, not *for Rauner*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIT - Illinois Institute of Technology. It's a private school on the South side of Chicago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two games for Christmas hardly classifies as "Richie Rich". I know you are being sarcastic and making a joke btw.

Anyway kids nowadays, even kids in middle class, get brand new phones for their bdays - you know, $700 phones. I know there is inflation, but holy crap that's a lot of money compared to 2x N64 games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The word *could* is used over and over again. But is it practical? It sounds a little bit like fear-mongering. I'm not educated on this topic, I'm just telling you my impression from that info-graphic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 06:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You had a second one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 06:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, got it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If you think there job is to tell the truth and the honest news of what's going on, your bullshitting yourself.

If you think **their** job.

EDIT: another typo for you:

 your bullshitting yourself

**You're** bullshitting yourself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, he does *talk about news*. I mean, he makes fun of it. but really most of the time he has a political undertone, and has quite the bias. I would say it's closer to a political talk show than news or comedy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man I hope they make at least one of them kosher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personal story here. 

**I used to steal the little caps on the tires of cars.** Some crazy ass kid got me into it. I would go to parking lots and look for cars with tire caps that looked shiny. The best were the special ones like [this from a Porche](http://img0083.popscreencdn.com/105230619_agt-aluminum-silver-valve-caps-tire-cap-stem-for-porsche.jpg). I had about 60-70 of these cool tire caps until I got caught around the age of 15. I didn't even actually arrested. They took me to the local police station and called my parents. That was enough to scare me straight.

Yea, I'm white. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tumblr comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Local college (Chicago) near me started a Facebook group for Bernie. This is significant, because this school has rarely had any political movements on campus. Another sign that Bernie is stirring things up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rafael Nadal. Such an amazing player, and has made tennis so much fun to watch the past 10 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -Barack Obama </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they don't think it's satire, what do they think it is?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do, it's just their rating are horrendous compared to FOX, and most mainstream media has a heavy liberal bias, so no one sits and scrutinizes MSNBC like we scrutinize FOX.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That were going fucking broke.

Chicago/Illinois. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 00:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had to read that story in french class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 00:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are most welcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 23:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little? I'm 5'8, somewhat muscular, and 200 lbs. But even when I was 170 lbs I had the same problem. It doesn't seem to be about the weight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 22:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who overshare, and only the share the best parts of their lives. Not only that, but they always make it look like they are the shit. It's like their entire Facebook page exists to make them look like a douche. Good job, you did it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 22:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You came here to be a grammar nazi? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 21:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not a word.

That's like saying "I'd'like" is normal. It's not, but "I'd like" is. No such conjugation "J'm'apelle" exists in the French language. It's simply incorrect, and I'm quite sure you have no idea wtf you're talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 21:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And... So because he shouted during the state of the Union he is racist? Are you serious? How does that help your ridiculous claim?

 Nobody claimed that. That's just a cheap trick on your part

You said the idiot who shouted is from South Carolina, whose state capitol is racist because it has a confederate flag, and because that racist mass-killer killed people.

Now that you've established that area to be racist - (because of the flag and one person), you go on to say...

 Now, it could very well be a coincidence that a congressman

wait for it...
 
 from a racist state happened to shout during the State of The Union

You literally obtain your conclusion from the fact that the shouter is 'from a racist state'. 

1. Not all people in SC are racist. Making such a claim is ignorant and devoid of any factual evidence.
2. You conclude that A) because the shouter was from SC B) He shouted during the SOTU, and C) Obama is black, that it *must be because of race*.

And then you have the audacity to tell me 'nobody claimed that', when in fact, **you did**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 21:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So anyone from South Carolina, who says the President lies, is racially charged? 

Wow. This is the type of thinking that fuels racial tensions. 

 I think there's no way he would have done it to a white president

I'm sure there would be no difference, as long as the President is a Democrat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 20:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Je m'appelle Unidan is proper.

J'm'appelle is just plain retarded. I didn't notice what I had typed initially. 

 I didn't think I was correcting you. I did correct you.

No. No you didn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 20:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  less likely to get divorced even if it's a shitty relationship

Kind of an unproven statistic. Many people who are not religious stay in terrible marriages for their children. Or just cheat. 

It's not about moving in together necessarily, but that people tend to move in together for necessity. The relationships progresses in a sense, but not for a good reason - it could be to save money/time, someone needs to move anyway, etc. It's not a properly thought out decision - and when big decisions like that are made out of convenience - that usually ends in divorce. 

Think about people who get married because the girl got knocked up. Those marriages rarely work out. They made a big decisions in regards to their relationship for the wrong reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 20:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you think you are correcting me, you are a moron, and quite lazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 20:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Bernie Sanders stood for LGBT Equality long before it was acceptable.

This shows his sincerity, whereas Clinton only came out as pro-gay when the polls were in her favor to do so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to get notifications when someone Tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 18:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I favorited someone (@buysellshort). I also made sure my phone gets notifications from Twitter. However I still don't get notified when @buysellshort Tweets. The message popped up on my phone that I will now get notifications when he tweets. Anyone else have this problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PCworld article here:

http://www.pcworld.com/article/2939321/google-finally-makes-undo-send-an-official-gmail-feature.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gmail Formally Adds Undo Send Option </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This could be the greatest addition to email in the history of the world, err, internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> J'mappelle unidan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also floss, and use mouthwash.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Don't marry someone before you've lived with them.

Disagree with that one, but that's just me. A lot of studies show that those who move in together too quickly, are much more likely to get divorced

 Don't commit to the first pretty girl that comes along because you don't think you'll ever do better.

For sure

 Looks are not everything, a nice pair of tits does not compensate for a lack of personality.

Yup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This.

And the only people that would believe they were the first to find out, are probably the same type of people who have already called for the 'rapture' in the past. 

No one would believe them. Basically, nothing would happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ask Xavier from X-Men.

[CALM YOUR MIND] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JBRlM9hN0GQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sweat waay too much for a normal person. I am hot when everyone is cold. I sweat just from walking, even when it's 60 degrees out. Battling my sweat/heat is a daily grind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you don't have a soul, ginger - so you don't apply to this thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In school, 8th grade. Some kid in my class came up to me with this super-excited face and said, "Dude! Someone just bombed the Pentagon!". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The deserves to be at the top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's a Jewish supremacist group?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of when Westboro said the V Tech shootings happened because of gays. It's almost not even worth responding to such things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 15:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate my focus. I'd rather be driving something else. Only have it because of the wife.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 15:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can do all that, but I'll never give up my Nespresso. Nespresso, by the way, is recyclable, unlike Keurig (read like, 'tastes like ass'). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 05:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do wah. Do wah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 05:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/James_Horner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 05:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where were these teachers when I was in school?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 05:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Good

Good ^thing you **didn't** quote him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 05:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I hardly think this is genuine concern for civil rights at its best.

Since politicians are generally never sincere, I'd say you are probably right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 05:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Good thing you quoted him.
 Good thing you quoted Him
 GoOd quOTEd thing you *him***

**Good** ^thing you *quoted* him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 05:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Never heard of the CTS, CTS-V, or Escalade?

Yeah I have. They are crap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 04:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can you put BMW and Cadillac in the same sentence?
And BMW has some of the highest residual value in the industry. Not as much for the other two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 04:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Good thing you quoted him.

Good thing you quoted him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 02:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might need to look into taking some medication... or getting some help... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 02:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If he likes to lift, he should probably start lifting more.

OOOOOHHHHHH! BURN! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 02:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8 inches. Around. Think about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 02:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also, OP forgot the serious tag.

Good call. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 02:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think it's safe to say that people who fly the confederate flag are probably too credulous

Kind of a douchey comment honestly. You've already made up your mind about someone who hasn't even verbalized their opinion yet. It's quite closed minded, and doesn't yield to an open discussion. I have downvoted your comment accordingly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 02:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'll do it later" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 02:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I simply don't have time for video games right now" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 02:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually really liked that movie. It felt original in a sense of the general set up of the alien movie. They weren't invaders, but 3rd class citizens in our own world. It was pretty neat. 

With that said, I'd love to see those aliens come back and take vengeance for all the crap the humans put them through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 02:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, my Mom taught me great eating habits my entire life - and I still eat like a fat kid. 

I'm 5"8, 205 lbs, slightly muscular. When my metabolism slows down even more (I'm 27), I'll gain weight very quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 02:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Selfie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 02:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Direct violation of rule 3:

 Questions with a single correct answer, that can be researched elsewhere, provide a limited scope for discussion (yes/no, DAE, polls and surveys, etc.), or limit discussion are not appropriate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 02:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No then we'll all be singing "Seven seven three, two-oh-two, LUUNAAAA!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 02:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jaywalking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 02:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Raw chicken left in the garage. There were 50 maggots.
2. A dead squirrel that was partially decayed and stuck to my porch. Had to scrape it off. It was half eaten already.
3. The women's bathroom at Staples. The little garbage in each stall - it was horrifying. Every combination of yellow red and brown was in there. Truly disgusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 00:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a scene from a samurai movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 00:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repost. 
And we all know it.

Jerk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 00:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they have special skin that is always pristine. They also never die, age, or need to eat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 00:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to disappoint you, Aquaman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 00:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 00:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That got more and more funny.

Thanks for this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
