<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5807</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Would Aliens Actually Look Like? Seven Experts Respond. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 01:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 01:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard this incredible story first on This American Life. Here's the [link](http://www.thisamericanlife.org/radio-archives/episode/522/tarred-and-feathered?act=2#play) for anyone who'd rather listen than read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study finds that antiperspirant deodorants alter your armpit bacteria and may actually worsen body odor as a result. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 18:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Physicists create water tractor beam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 23:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Neil deGrasse Tyson was asked for his thoughts on GMO foods, he responded with this brilliant answer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 05:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For a "Boring Billion" years of Earth's history, evolution basically stopped and life consisted of slime. 3 recent studies try to explain why. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 15:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stanford researchers achieve a stable lithium anode, a tremendous advance in battery technology. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 00:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How should men pee? Study examines the "urodynamics" of sitting versus standing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 21:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 30% of U.S. clinical trials do not have their results publicly disclosed within four years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 17:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is the vehicle that astronauts will use on Mars. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 01:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tractor Beam Created Using Water Waves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 18:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientific review of randomized, controlled studies finds that weight loss from low-carb diets is almost entirely from caloric restriction. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 22:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A first direct glimpse of photosynthesis in action. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 02:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Large study finds organic produce contains significantly higher levels of antioxidants than conventional produce, contrary to prior research. But there may be methodological flaws and selection bias. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 03:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Environmentalists Almost Killed My Friend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 17:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the Mind Affect Quantum Mechanics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 16:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Many zoos have elephants paint as an "enrichment" activity and often sell the art to the public. But a new study finds little evidence that painting reduces stress behaviors or benefits the animals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 16:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 15:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So true. He has that big (mostly) liberal blind spot on GMOs and vaccines. I watch his show every week and bite my tongue when he goes on one of those rants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comedy vs. Anti-Science: Comedians are using humor to combat everything from climate denial to anti-vaccine BS. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 03:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study finds that most people don't enjoy sitting and thinking quietly by themselves. Some actually prefer receiving electric shocks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 20:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 20:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The full scene is much longer. The build-up is like 3-4 minutes. It's perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 17:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, probably The Ring.

One of the best constructed horror scenes came from [Exorcist III](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zH8ynu0jRvY), however. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study finds that half of pet cats in Europe are infested with a parasite. Parasites were most prevalent on cats in Italy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 17:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People Who Wear Glasses Really Are Smarter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 04:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3 big problems with the new paper showing that pesticides are linked to autism. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 17:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Casual sex is commonly considered negative, but a new study shows that amongst people who like it, casual sex is linked to higher self-esteem and life satisfaction as well as lower depression and anxiety. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 21:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10 Reasons Why You Can't Live Without a Particle Accelerator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 22:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doses of the hormone oxytocin cause old rats to regenerate muscle at levels comparable to young ones. Researchers suggest oxytocin could be used to prevent age-related muscle loss in humans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 17:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One out of every eight American children are maltreated by the time they are 18, not one in 100, as has previously been reported. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 22:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first vertebrate sexual organs evolved as an extra pair of legs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 05:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA funds feasibility studies for 12 futuristic proposals, including a submarine to explore the methane lakes of Titan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 03:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 8 Common Health Tips That Aren't Supported by Scientific Evidence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 18:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even if you travel at the speed of light, there are some galaxies you can never reach. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 22:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers identify a new type of procrastination: sleep procrastination. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 15:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astronomers Find a New Type of Planet: The "Mega-Earth" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 19:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists can alter primates' preferences by stimulating the ventral tegmental area of their brains. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 22:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Learning Early in Life May Help Keep Brain Cells Alive," new study in young rats suggests. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 23:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New review article concludes that there really wasn't anything anatomically special about Einstein's brain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 21:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chemists find a way to turn a troubling contaminant into a harmless sugar. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 05:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "How did the Universe begin?" A beautiful answer to a complex question. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 03:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Science writer Peter Gwynne wrote the now-famous global cooling article in Newsweek in 1975. He's now urging people to stop citing it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 00:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 05:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like it could be a quality movie, but I don't think I'll never be able to accept Michael C. Hall as any character but Dexter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
