<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7619</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 03:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might need to watch First Blood again; it's brilliant, and the only death is accidental. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 03:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It works both ways: it's better to live for something than to die for nothing just as it's better to die for something than to live for nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 03:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't think of a lot of movies I've seen in the theater where people actually stood up and cheered. When Rambo went HAM toward the end (spoilers?) the whole audience was going nuts. There was way too much testosterone in that room... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 03:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He literally helps the ~~Taliban~~ the Afghan people

FTFY

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 03:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was better than Rambo: First Blood Part II ***and*** Rambo 3 but failed to top First Blood.

I just realized what a bizarre naming convention this series had:

1. First Blood

2. Rambo: First Blood Part II

3. Rambo III

4. Rambo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 03:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not arguing a single thing, but lots of citations needed here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 03:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm appreciating this novel with each reply such as yours. Thank you for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 01:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  knowing the context of the book is important

I'm beginning to get that, and that's exactly why I posted to begin with. *This* is why I love /r/books. I get so much more out of reading by having this kind of post-reading discussion. 

It's like being a member of the world's biggest book club without anyone giving me a reading list.

Thank you sincerely for taking the time to write. I really appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 00:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  he made me fall in love with Brett

Then I am spectacularly your opposite and this is the kind of thing that makes reading fun. It is so interesting to me that this book had that effect on you and quite the opposite on me. I loathed her. I couldn't understand these foolish men and boys fawning for her. Maybe that's a big part of the reason I didn't get it. I didn't like Brett. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 00:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of the actual events that transpired, I found the bullfighting descriptions somewhat interesting albeit appalling, but little else of consequence. Their conversations seemed asinine, although I'll give Hemingway tremendous credit for capturing perfectly the way drunk people actually converse. 

I felt constantly wanting for more drama. When Cohn finally threw a punch, I was ecstatic! It felt like the most exciting thing to happen in the course of the novel. Perhaps there's some disconnect between a man of 2015 and values and ideals of a generation a century past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 00:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a wonderful explanation and I am grateful for it. What perplexed me throughout the novel was what seemed to be a lack of any explicit conflict in need of resolution, but you seem to be saying the conflicts were, in a way, the characters themselves. They all were in pursuit of something and failed at attaining it.

I suppose I didn't connect very well with these characters. I found Brett absolutely awful, Cohn pathetic, Mike an ass, Jake spineless, and Bill... well, I suppose Bill was alright. I didn't understand why Brett was so sought after, why Mike seemed downright amused by Brett's affairs, or at least tolerant of them, or why Jake was so whipped by her that he loved her and yet stood by her as she was drawn to every man like a moth to flame. 

Why *was* Brett so sought after? Was it her title? Was she really that attractive? It seemed every man wanted her and would put up with her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just finished The Sun Also Rises (Ernest Hemingway) and would love to hear from someone who liked it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 21:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read this because I recently read and quite liked his Old Man and the Sea. I left it impressed as Hemingway could take such a simple story and have me riveted even though I have no interest in fishing or old men and only a glancing interest in the sea. I read it in a single sitting.

The Sun Also Rises seemed amysmally dull from the start, and I would not have finished it had the author not been Hemingway. I always felt sure it would get better, and when I read the final sentence, it was like a kick in the teeth. Really? That's it? All that for that?

I don't get the title either. I might have titled it "Drunks Repeating Themselves." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 02:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and no. When they first created their Captain Marvel, they did so in a vacuum. Fawcett couldn't use their Captain Marvel anymore (Billy Batson) because DC sued claiming their Captain Marvel was a knockoff of Superman. Insane as that was, they won. Until Fawcett was bought out by Charlton Comics which was then bought out by DC, Marvel had the one and only Captain Marvel.

Once DC decided to incorporate the old Fawcett/Charlton character into their own lineup, they couldn't release anything with the title "Captain Marvel" because Marvel now owned that publication title, but because the character preexisted and predated Marvel's, they were allowed to keep the character and the name. Hence the series title "Shazam!". 

After skirting this issue for decades with the odd "his name is Captain Marvel; his comic books are Shazam!" scheme, they finally just gave in and officially named him Shazam with the New 52 relaunch. 

As for Marvel's Captain Marvel, Carol Danvers as Captain Marvel has become one of their top properties over the decades and has a movie coming out, which means Marvel's Captain Marvel will be far better known as *the* Captain Marvel to most audiences. Funny enough, the current release date for her movie coincides with the Warner Bros. film "Shazam!". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 02:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thunder God by himself should be able to handle all of them at once with the exception of Darkskull, and that's only because Darkskull is half Darkseid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 13:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're still wrong. As I said, Captain Marvel *has* appeared outside of a DC Comic, Marvel Comics has had numerous Captain Marvels of their own, and DC's Billy Batson has not been known as Captain Marvel since 2011. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 02:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're still talking about SHAZAM! as in Billy Batson, you're still wrong; he was created in Fawcett Comics and was quite prolific there for 33 years before ever being integrated into DC. For a time, Fawcett's Captain Marvel was more popular than DC's Superman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 01:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It didn't close either door. You can clearly see the arm of the person inside close the door before the tire gets to it. The same person then opens the other door. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 19:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what happens when I'm involved in too many conversation threads. I apologize. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 19:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want a good discussion on this but don't want to wait for responses, check the threads of the other 52,000 times this quote has been posted on /r/batman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 19:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the fans voted for Wolverine, so they had no idea how to have Wolverine win

You're right about that. Lobo was (I don't know anything about [New 52 Lobo](http://static.comicvine.com/uploads/original/11113/111135277/4084955-9940480525-lobo_.jpg) and I'd prefer to keep it that way) functionally impossible to kill. Legend has it that Czarnians can only be killed by other Czarnians, and since he killed all the other Czarnians, there is no real threat to him. Heaven and Hell literally won't take him anyway.

Unfortunately, the bar cop-out made it look like they hid a sex scene off panel and Wolverine found the Rogering so satisfying he required a smoke immediately after... the cigar Lobo was smoking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 19:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For context, I have to explain that I am a "white" person and that one of my best friends is "black."

I went over to his apartment one time, and when I walked in the door, he was sitting there eating watermelon. I burst out laughing, and he realized what was up, we both had a good laugh.

Another time we were out and I suggested we get something to eat before we move on to another bar. He suggested KFC, which again, provoked a laugh out of me and then him. He punched me in the arm and said something like, "Don't act like you don't love KFC. I was suggesting it because ***YOU*** like it." Which I do. It's a silly stereotype, because most people I know enjoy fried chicken, regardless of race.

None of this is bad, and none of it is racism. At all. This is basically what people these days would call a "meme," a popular thing to reference that goes way back to some sort of basis in reality. 

Truthfully, I don't know why nor do I especially care about how black people came to be associated with things like watermelon or fried chicken, but we all know of the association, and it's not exactly a cruel or insulting stereotype. 

And what possible agenda could it serve? Who benefits from these stereotypes? Who suffers?

No one. So fuck it. Let's just have fun and be cool to one another. It's not hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 19:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can be anything you want to be! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 18:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/Unexpected 

/r/UnexpectedThugLife  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 18:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The world really is shitty and the world really is wonderful depending on what you focus on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 18:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but there's a very negative connotation to the word "prejudice" even though it's really just pre-judging, which is a sensible thing to do in a lot of situations...

We need a word that's for non-racists to have fun with stereotypes, like black people can dance/white people can't dance, white nerd culture versus black gangsta culture, etc. all while keeping a friendly, tongue-in-cheek tone about the whole thing.

Somehow both of these subreddits do this expertly with only a rare asshole downvoted straight to hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 18:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humorous Stereotypes  Brainwashing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 18:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> S'all yours bro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 18:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the FF might be my least favorite Marvel property as well.

Of course, we don't *have to* watch the new movie... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 18:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do have collected volumes, at least 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Though my art style was basically a carbon copy of Phil Bourassa's work on Young Justice. 

If you're going to copy an artist's style, at least you chose wisely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to be an adventurer like you until [I took an arrow to the eye](http://www.1066online.co.uk/hastings-photos/battle-of-hastings/photos/arrow-in-the-eye.jpg)... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I want to see Grodd in Thor's getup, helmet and all, wielding Mjlnir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vandal Savage: And that, my legion of supervillians, is how we are going to take over the- ***CRASH***

Randal Savage: Saw-wee...

Vandal Savage: God damn it Randal... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on the history of the shield in canon, I would say no, neither Hulk nor Superman could break it or rip it apart. [It has absolutely withstood a direct blow from Hulk more than once,](http://i.newsarama.com/images/i/000/093/888/original/Capt-America-Shield-Block-Hulk.jpg?1364317923) and, as you can imagine, Hulk attacking Cap means Hulk has completely lost his shit.

As for Superman, the only circumstances in which the shield has been broken has been by literal gods or those endowed with all the power of god, and once by a guy who literally controls all matter at a molecular level. All Superman can do is hit it, and the shield just deflects force. Adding more force is useless.

Basically, consider the shield a force multiplier and the multiplier is zero. Hitting with a force of 1 results in 0. Hitting it with a force of 999,999,999,999 results in 0. Anything times zero is zero.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which raises an obvious question... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Promethium is fairly significant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard there was once a Cable fan who was so dedicated that he actually understood Cable's origin and powers. 

He's now committed to an insane asylum, but good on him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's also how Youngblood happened; he was working on a reboot of Teen Titans, got canned, and then started Image with a bunch of guys who actually had talent. Instead of scrapping the work he did on Teen Titans he changed some names and presto. He made shitloads of money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yes?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SJUhlRoBL8M) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I think the SHAZAM!/Thor mashup is the most overpowered of this bunch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not the artist, but you can always ask him: http://ericguzman.deviantart.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As of 2011, his name is SHAZAM!, not Captain Marvel. All rights to the name "Captain Marvel" have been relinquished to Marvel Comics, a subsidiary of Disney. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greenova Corps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would take an amalgam of Sentry   Superman to even strand a chance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joker + Goblin = Mark Hamill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. I liked it for what it was. I still have the full collection of both series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. It's entirely possible, [though not always attractive...](https://shechive.files.wordpress.com/2011/02/body-builder-29.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's really cool is both characters are rare in that they've both displayed knowledge that they're comic book characters, i.e., they both have been shown to break the fourth wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Dat Grayson ass...](https://36.media.tumblr.com/379420b3a9834bb6f739151909f0b64b/tumblr_ni65gyAmIG1rtprkqo1_1280.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It gets so much worse than that. Dr. Otto Octavius turns into Dr. Octopus? A guy is legitimately Dr. Doom? As in that's his fucking birth name? Really? Kyle Nimbus becomes Mist? Seriously? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but Captain Krypton was a much different interpretation than Super Soldier. There's really only so much you can do to combine Darkseid and Thanos considering how similar they are to begin with.

Now mixing Darkseid, Thanos, Apocalypse, and Mongul might be interesting.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct; I am not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but Captain Krypton was a much different interpretation than Super Soldier. There's really only so much you can do to combine Darkseid and Thanos considering how similar they are to begin with. 

Now mixing Darkseid, Thanos, Apocalypse, and Mongul might be interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's too bad Wolverine VS Lobo was the weakest fight of the whole series. If they had done it in a post-Comics Code Authority world, it would've been insanely bloody and lasted a good four or five issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr. Diddle is *not* approved by the Comics Code Authority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I just linked to... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to know what you're talking about before you try correcting people.

In the article you just linked to: Captain Marvel is now officially named "Shazam" because of this

Read more: http://tvtropes.org/pmwiki/pmwiki.php/Main/IAmNotShazam#ixzz3crEh3DSI
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then get Marvel VS DC because [they totally did that already](http://static.comicvine.com/uploads/original/11/111539/2116739-dc_s_thor.png). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been frequently surprised by the amount of users on /r/comicbooks  that are completely unaware Marvel VS DC exists, let alone Amalgam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the crossover I've always wanted to see.

Instead I had to settle for the crappy Daredevil/Batman one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carefully? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season three lives on in my heart... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also he's missing an eye now, so there's that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'd agree with that assessment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, [it was a great moment.](http://static.comicvine.com/uploads/scale_super/11/113883/2164436-deadpool_vs_deathstroke.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Captain Marvel as in Marvel's Carol Danvers, not SHAZAM! formerly known as Captain Marvel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tangent Joker is so boss. I'm surprised she didn't reach Harley Quinn levels of fandom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Oh man, the 90's were ~~AW~~**FU**~~L~~**N**

FTFY

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good guess, but no; it's a combination of five different robots:

Marvel: Destroyer + Galactus' Punisher robot + Machine Man (X-51) 

+

DC: Ultivac + Ultra the Multi-Alien.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine if both were indirectly his fault.

With great power comes... enormous, crushing guilt and depression... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found the writer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should happen to Batman at least occasionally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [As powerful as Superman.](http://i.imgur.com/W4ZmfTp.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Offering the entire Justice League their own asses on a silver platter. 

And then he kicked back and enjoyed some milk and Oreo cookies.

[Here he is kicking Superboy Prime's ass.](http://static.comicvine.com/uploads/original/11112/111126230/3402638-8623363798-qx7v4.jpg)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Loved* Dr. Doomsday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only after Joe Kelly made Deadpool different when he got his own series. Before that, Deadpool was an elite assassin who brandished a sword and had enhanced superhuman abilities with fast healing and a mysterious origin. 

He was Marvel's Deathstroke. The silly Deadpool we know today didn't come until his own self-titled monthly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Green Arrow is a Robin Hood Rip off.

Technically Green Arrow is a Batman rip-off with a Robin Hood gimmick, but all good points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Doom Patrol/X-Men is more debatable because their timelines were close

That actually seems more like evidence that X-Men *did* rip off Doom Patrol than didn't. X-Men came out three months later, which is enough time to see Doom Patrol and copy it.

Superhuman misfits, led by a paraplegic in a wheelchair, dedicated to protecting a world that shuns them, The Doom Patrol debuted in My Greatest Adventures #80 in June 1963, three months before The X-Men #1 with near-identical cover taglines and the names of their arch-enemies with The Doom Patrols The Worlds Strangest Heroes! versus The X-Mens The Strangest Super-Heroes of All! and The Doom Patrols Brotherhood of Evil versus The X-Mens Brotherhood of Evil Mutants.

They're nearly identical. I don't believe in coincidence in general, but certainly not to the degree of a damned near carbon copy just three months after the original. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All good points, and let's not forget copying Marvel's mutants with metahumans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rob Liefeld's entire career is "accidentally" ripping things off. At some point, you begin to doubt the "accidental" part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Mr. E. Nygma (Mystery/Enigma) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 02:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are: http://en.m.wiktionary.org/wiki/Category:English_double_contractions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 21:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fanfic. The actual Amalgam was Batman + Wolverine = Dark Claw and Lobo + Howard the Duck = Lobo the Duck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 21:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cautioning parents against creating a horrific fate for their children does not equal hating fat people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 21:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lex needs the suit if he wants to throw down with Superman; [Kingpin ain't afraid to scrap](http://static.comicvine.com/uploads/original/10/104794/2122102-kingpin.jpg), and he damned sure ain't worried about what he's wearing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 21:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well then [here you go.](http://orig14.deviantart.net/eccc/f/2014/191/e/7/amalgam_comic__wolverine_and_lobo__by_alexbadass-d7q5zzr.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 21:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Ultimate CA's shield indestructible?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 21:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Pretty much](http://fc06.deviantart.net/fs71/i/2014/079/c/3/armored_daredevil_colors_by_ginmau-d6uozw1.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 21:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  giving the invincible guy a shield

To be fair, [it's been done](http://dc.wikia.com/wiki/Clark_Kent_%28Amalgam_Universe%29).

Also, as of the New 52, Superman wears [Kryptonian armor](http://media.comicbook.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/03/super-change.gif).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 21:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [K](http://dc.wikia.com/wiki/Logan_Wayne_%28Amalgam_Universe%29) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 21:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure about the original series, but DS9 and Voyager certainly did.

Also, if you rather feel like pretending you're on board, there's always [this.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZPoqNeR3_UA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 21:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like anything it has its ups and downs. I am a fan in general and a big fan of The Next Generation specifically, but keep in mind that this is a highlight video taking the best 15 minutes of Picard's edifying over the totality of 176 episodes and four movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 21:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not at all necessary and the tone is so completely different that you might love one while strongly disliking the other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you really didn't care you wouldn't keep posting.

I think maybe you *do* care.

Just a little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear they're the same person on different ends of the diet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I don't *like* big-chested Captain America.

I ***LOVE*** [big-chested Captain America](http://loltrap.com/pictures/c32efcb7f667f6c5def39db8eda2e6ce.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But does Deadpool x 0 = Deadpool? 

Because you're going to break math. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew what you meant ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone really been far even as decided to use even go want to do look more like?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are a genius. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't get the respect they deserve. I still wonder how The Incredibles got away with Elastigirl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lex Fisk or Wilson Luthor. 

He'd basically just be a bigger, stronger, Lex Luthor, which would look just like Wilson Fisk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like Deadpool was a direct rip-off of Deathstroke that a talentless hack named Rob Liefeld "created" until better, more talented people came along and gave us the Deadpool we all know and love today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny that the Batman VS Spider-Man's villains things has already been done (Batman Beyond).

Blight = Green Goblin

Shriek = Shocker

Drek = Kraven

Spellbinder = Mysterio

Inque = Venom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Batman actually has a suit that allows him to go toe-to-toe with Darkseid, so I don't think he has any use for Tony Stark's tech, money, or resources. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inertron, Promethium, and Radion come to mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, [read this.](http://www.popmatters.com/post/176291-thor-who-its-beta-ray-bill/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. It's not the density of the bullet; it's the force with which it's projected. 

Also, The Hulk has been so ridiculously overpowered in recent years that nothing surprises me anymore. I'd totally expect a story where he's tossed into the sun and he eats his way out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You probably would've gotten it if it had been:

     (Bane's real name) + Venom = Bane

Unfortunately, no one knows Bane's real name... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rob Liefeld never "accidentally" ripped off anything; he just ripped shit off wholesale because he's a talentless hack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And isn't Deadpool supposed to be a ripoff of Deadshot?

Deadpool *is* a rip-off of *Deathstroke*, not Deadshot, and no, he's wasn't "supposed to be." Deadpool was initially "created" by Rob Liefeld, a talentless hack who is notorious for ripping off characters and art. Fabian Nicieza was the first to realize it and he's the one who gave Deadpool his real name "Wade Wilson" as an obvious parody of Slade Wilson. In his early outings, he was a lethal assassin with enhanced abilities and healing with a mysterious past. He was Deathstroke in Spider-Man's costume.

Joe Kelly is probably most responsible for the Deadpool we know and love today. What started off as a total rip-off turned into one of the most original and fun characters in comics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually prefer vanilla, but I'm not going to get all upset about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eyeball muscles is the best superpower I've heard of since [Arm Fall Off Boy](http://static.comicvine.com/uploads/scale_small/1/15659/3097751-arm-fall-off_boy-edited.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always felt like Marvel missed out on "Doctopus." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scarlet Red Spider Hood! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like the device nullifies anti-life though, which would mean it's really a life equation. The double-negative bothers me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I underestimated the potency of 2CE once and that's the only time the kind of psychedelic experiences you see in movies ever happened to me. At first it was the usual abstractions, geometric patterns, animations, but as the intensity turned up, I went out on the balcony to smoke and I watched a tree across the street turn into a fire breathing dragon. When I went back inside everything was way too animated and out-of-control. I decided to go to bed and try to sleep it off, which eventually kind of worked. I had never had a bad trip before and wasn't eager to start.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Don't act like there wasn't any superiority implied with your constant insistence that "well, yeah, maybe but Marvel still does it more"

There wasn't, but you're more than welcome to continue thinking there was.

I said Marvel has ripped off DC more than DC has ripped off Marvel, which is true. I went on to cite examples. Not once did I say or imply either brand is better than the other. That would be akin to saying chocolate is better than vanilla. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anti-Life Gauntlet could've worked though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but SHAZAM is a straight up wizardry not to mention a ridiculous powerhouse in his own right. I really think a SHAZAM/Thor hybrid would destroy Superman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Bucky/Jason Todd is an even more obvious parallel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're reading a lot more into what I wrote than what is actually there.

Relax? I couldn't be more relaxed.

Admit that there's more than I think? I'm pretty sure I just did since you were able to think of a few DC rip-offs of Marvel that I didn't.

Stop waving around my big dumb DC-is-better flag? I was never doing that to begin with so I can't very well stop now can I? 

Saying Marvel has ripped-off DC properties numerous times and has done so more than DC has ripped-off Marvel is not the same as saying DC is better, although fantastic arguments as to which brand is better can certainly be made either way. I don't claim one is better; it's a matter of a taste. Personally, I prefer DC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, but Deadstroke is new; Thanoseid has already been done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get their reasoning in adding the Ultimate Nullifier. That device is most strongly associated with Galactus and Reed Richards. 

Finding the Anti-Life Equation by itself would make sense to impress Death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Batman/Spider-Man team-up against Riddler   Mysterio has great potential for exactly those reasons.

Too bad we don't get Marvel/DC crossovers anymore since the buyouts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It really is.](http://th01.deviantart.net/fs70/PRE/i/2014/060/7/e/the_scarlet_speedster_by_robertmacquarrie1-d78ikq1.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Truly.](http://orig14.deviantart.net/eccc/f/2014/191/e/7/amalgam_comic__wolverine_and_lobo__by_alexbadass-d7q5zzr.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Probably.](http://40.media.tumblr.com/c095c474a0f6aa64209f5d125c521917/tumblr_nicsefdDri1r811rmo1_1280.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Working onomatopoeia into a character name.

I like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right; I thought /u/lovers_acid was asking about something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In an ideal world, Disney and Warner Bros. would say, "Hey, Marvel VS DC and the subsequent Amalgam Comics was a pretty big deal in the 90s. That was *before* blockbuster summer comic book movies were a thing. Imagine the riches..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Like this?](http://orig06.deviantart.net/2ed8/f/2009/078/b/6/b61d7b68b5c17f9ff2f62217a106d916.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean I'm not the only one who thinks [this](http://img1.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20110710044111/marvel_dc/images/f/f4/Supergirl_Vol_6_1_Textless.jpg) look ridiculous? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a tough week for Peter Wayne.

Or Bruce Parker.

Thank goodness for Aunt May Pennyworth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could probably add the modern version of [Despero](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Despero) as DC's rip-off of its own Mongul which was a rip-off of Marvel's Apocalypse which was a rip off of Marvel's Thanos which was a rip-off of DC's Darkseid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll always have [Iron Lantern](http://static.comicvine.com/uploads/scale_small/6/67663/2169758-iron_lantern.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Hyperion is part of Squadron Supreme/Sinister which is an intentional send-up of the Justice League in response to people accusing the Avengers of ripping off the Justice League.

Which is hilarious on Marvel's part and a perfect response.

In return, DC Comics has "[Earth 8](http://dc.wikia.com/wiki/Earth-8)" as part of its 52 world multiverse, which is a blatant [Marvel parody](http://www.dccomics.com/characters/earth-8). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with Flulk?

You wouldn't like Barry Banner when he's angry.

Or Bruce Allen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Amalgam Universe](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Amalgam_Comics), the result of [Marvel VS DC](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DC_vs._Marvel). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under Warner Bros and Disney ownership, I doubt we'll ever see anything like that ever again. 

It was cool coming of age in the 90s... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of these are pretty good, but some are way off.

Swamp Thing   Man Thing debuted within weeks of each other and there's no possible way one creator could have been aware of the other's creation. Call it a cosmic coincidence.

Black Mask is nothing like Red Skull. For one, he wears a mask as opposed to Red Skull being a deformed freak. The first word that comes to mind when I see "Red Skull" is "Nazi." The first word that comes to mind when I see Black Mask is "gangster." Red Skull is basically Hitler whereas Black Mask is basically Al Capone. Red Skull does things as lofty as attempting world domination and even cosmic conquest. Black Mask concerns himself with organized crime in Gotham City.

I get the Blackest Night/Marvel Zombies comparison, but they're really quite different. For one, MZ was an out-of-mainstream continuity story and everyone was zombies. Blackest Night was in-canon, did a lot to further expand the Green Lantern mythos, created a top villain out of a forgotten B-side villain, and the only "zombies" were already deceased DC Comics characters.

The Jason Todd/Red Hood   Buck/Winter Soldier thing is superb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might as well say The Flash + The Hulk = God. There'd be little practical difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moon Knight + Midnighter = Moonighter?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought Batman and Moon Knight were the most obvious mashups, but they combined Moon Knight with Nightwing to make [Moonwing](http://www.marvunapp.com/Appendix/moonwing1.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It's been done.](http://amalgamfanon.wikia.com/wiki/Iron_Bat) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fixed it; thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bit on-the-nose, but yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but that's not a comic book company ripping off their only true rival. Also, DC's Batman and Superman both had a number of inspirations, neither was a direct rip-off of anything else. That's patently different than two major companies existing as direct competition to one another and one far more often than the other ripping off its rival and doing so blatantly.

Bumblebee is really the only DC Comics character that I've noticed who was just outrageously obvious a rip-off of a Marvel one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Creeper has been around since the 60s. I last saw him in an issue of Katana within the past year or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, but Thanoseid already exists as part of Amalgam; Deadstoke didn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Pow Wow Boom Boom Smith

By far my favorite name to come out of the whole event.

Also, I absolutely loved the way [Magneto](http://i.imgur.com/Q7kZaSU.jpg) looked.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but Thanoseid is a thing and Deadstroke isn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, just in the Ms. Marvel and Captain Marvel styles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but you can't blame Marvel   DC for combining their two best-selling characters at the time (Wolverine + Batman = Dark Claw). 

Plus, combining The Creeper and Nightcrawler made visual sense. Still, Wolverine   Creeper's powers are fairly similar and they do have a nice visual complement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't, but when you say this:

 I am positive I could identify a counter example to each one listed, thus showing that it is much more even.

and then don't, that's pretty weak.

You're basically saying, "I can totally prove you wrong, but I don't feel like it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He could positively wreck Superman. Thor is already on threat level to Supes, but add magic? Might as well give him a pocket full of Kyptonite while you're at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Steel.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Steel_%28John_Henry_Irons%29) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Party, yes. Clark Kent is based on Harold Lloyd and his name comes from Clark Gable and Kent Taylor. Inspiration for Superman was drawn by stories of Samson and Hercules, Flash Gordon, Philip Wylie's novel "Gladiator," and Doc Savage. Metropolis is so-called because of the classic Fritz Lang science fiction film. 

Funny you mention the "Biblical" aspects; Superman is an easy parallel to Moses as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here.](http://dc.wikia.com/wiki/Thanoseid_%28Amalgam_Universe%29) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, [everything is a remix](http://everythingisaremix.info/), but I disagree that it's pointless to debate. Actually, it's downright interesting in many cases. If anyone really cares about a character, it's worth noting what inspired said character, rip-off or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To fair, Amalgam had some terrible names too.

Skulk

Winterstick

Abominite

Two-Faced Goblin

Bizarnage

Shatterstarfire

Ra's-A-Pocalypse

Aurora Trigger

M-Parasiteplate

Northstar Trigger

Pow Wow Boom Boom Smith

Shaggynaut

Thunderchick

Fin Fang Flame

Medusa Moonrider

Ultivac the Multi-Robot

Mandarinestro

Chemodam

Paste-Eater Pete

Scavulture

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the entire collection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they say Superman is overpowered... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but Deadpool looks kind of cool with a half-mask and pirate boots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Link](http://www.amalgam.wikia.com/wiki/Super-Soldier) for the lazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not Eric Guzman, but it's funny you bring up Apocalypse because Apocalypse is a rip-off of Thanos is a rip-off of Darkseid. To get even weirder, DC ripped off Thanos, a rip-off of their own Darkseid, to create Mongul.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and kinda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No argument here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because [Thanoseid](http://dc.wikia.com/wiki/Thanoseid_%28Amalgam_Universe%29) is already a thing and because [Thanos is a rip-off of Darkseid](http://comicsalliance.com/knockoff-characters-comics/), hence the similarities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but if you go all the way back to DC's earliest stuff, they weren't ripping off Marvel of course, but Batman and Superman both take their inspirations and some vital characteristics from other works of fiction.

For example, the original Batman was a mix of Sherlock Holmes, Zorro, a Leonardo da Vinci sketch of a bat-winged flying machine, The Shadow, and even a pulp fiction serial called The Bat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem. If anyone knows of any other times it has been broken, feel free to correct me, but I'm pretty sure that's it. Marvel has been pretty good about sticking to "the shield is indestructible" canon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yes I have and it was one of the happiest comic book moments I've ever had.](http://static.comicvine.com/uploads/scale_super/11/113883/2164436-deadpool_vs_deathstroke.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. I've been following both brands for three decades and I can think of way more examples of Marvel ripping off DC than the other way around, as I've shown.

2. Please do.

3. Exactly right. For example, although Deadpool *was* a blatant rip-off of Deathstroke when Rob Liefeld introduced the character, Slade and Wade are nothing alike and the characters have much less in common now than they did then. Plus, things like The Avengers being a rip-off of the Justice League are fairly superficial. Whether DC thought to combine a bunch of their A-list heroes or not, someone would have thought to eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now we just need to combine Riddler and Kingpin...

...oh, yeah.

[The Big Question.](http://dc.wikia.com/wiki/Edward_Fisk_%28Amalgam_Universe%29) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not wrong, but more often-than-not, it's more fair to say Marvel rips off DC.

Deathstroke - Deadpool

Green Arrow - Hawkeye

Darkseid - Thanos

The Penguin - The Owl

Suicide Squad/Checkmate/Secret Six - Thunderbolts

Deadshot - Bullseye

Green Lantern Corps - Nova Corp

Doom Patrol - X-Men

Catwoman - Black Cat

Superman - Gladiator/Hyperion/The Sentry

Justice League - Avengers

That being said, DC ripped off Wasp with Bumblebee and Namor with Aquaman. There's probably others, but Marvel is much more thieving of DC than the other way around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being that [Deadpool was originally a Rob Liefeld rip off of Deathstroke](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Deadpool#1990s), the similarities are already blatant.

Nicieza contacted Liefeld, saying "this is Deathstroke from Teen Titans." Nicieza gave Deadpool the real name of "Wade Wilson" as an inside-joke to being "related" to "Slade Wilson," Deathstroke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Can't unsee.](http://www.timetravelcostumes.com/images/sci-fi-monarch-henchamn/monarch00.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They are too similar.

[Because Thanos is literally Marvel's rip off of Darkseid.](http://comicsalliance.com/knockoff-characters-comics/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It's been done.](http://dc.wikia.com/wiki/Thanoseid_%28Amalgam_Universe%29) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Thanoseid has been done.](http://dc.wikia.com/wiki/Thanoseid_%28Amalgam_Universe%29) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Captain America's shield is physically indestructible under normal conditions; while cosmic and godly opponents have broken the shield, the shield proves strong enough to absorb Hulk's strength, and repel an attack from Thor's mystical hammer Mjlnir without any visible damage.

It has only been destroyed a few times. 

1. Molecule mean destroyed it, but reassembled it. He has absolute control of all matter, so that's a special exception. 

2. Dr. Doom broke it, but he had the Beyonder's powers at the time, so he was basically a god-like being with limitless power. The Beyonder proper reassembled it like new. 

3. Thanos, already possessing godlike power, was able to shatter it with the Infinity Gauntlet, which is again unlimited power. Nebula fixed it when she used the Gauntlet to undo everything Thanos did.

4. Thor has broken it twice, but required Odinforce the first time and Rune Magic the second time. The first time he fixed it, the second time that particular timeline was undone, so it's like it never happened.

5. Serpent, the Asgardian god of fear and Odin's brother broke it with his bare hands, but he's basically god. It was repaired magically and even stronger now.

So basically, you need omnipotent power and/or magic to destroy it. Due to the enhancements since the last time it was broken, magic is probably useless. Unless you have all the power of god, you can't break it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To see more of Eric Guzman's art, click [here]( http://ericguzman.deviantart.com). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To see more of Eric Guzman's art, click [here]( http://ericguzman.deviantart.com). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To see more of Eric Guzman's art, click [here]( http://ericguzman.deviantart.com). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To see more of Eric Guzman's art, click [here]( http://ericguzman.deviantart.com). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To see more of Eric Guzman's art, click [here]( http://ericguzman.deviantart.com). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To see more of Eric Guzman's art, click [here]( http://ericguzman.deviantart.com). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eric Guzman DC/Marvel Mashups </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 15:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eric Guzman DC/Marvel Mashups </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 15:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eric Guzman DC/Marvel Mashups </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 15:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
