<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1208</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Video made me cringe too hard. Did he actually say that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shut your whore mouth. /u/da_fuhje is an artist.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 20:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're pretty talented at photoshop, so was really hoping this was OC. So... slightly disappointing. Do you ever post your own stuff? I have no issue with what you do, but on a personal note there's no better feeling than having your own original content make the front page. Maybe give it a try? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 20:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got all excited to see what he did for my country of Bermuda.

Nope. Fucker forgot us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Think I may have jinxed today's SpaceX launch. My bad, folks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 18:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 18:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Every time I see one of your comments.](http://i.imgur.com/NQHKSVE.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 17:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The more I know about people, the better I like my dog." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 17:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "Please don't kill butts. In the US, the overwhelming majority of species are non-thundering and completely harmless. Even the ones that do thunder usually aren't aggressive..."

Cloud to butt extension changes this massively... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 10:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOU ARE A BLINKING, SENSELESS CALF, LOVED BY NO ONE EXCEPT THE DROOLING BEAST THAT BROUGHT YOU INTO THIS WORLD. COME AT ME, BRO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 02:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the founder of Black Jaguar White Tiger, a big cat rescue foundation. He just fucks around with awesome beasties all day. (I'm sure there's other less glamorous work he does, but that's what I'm telling myself.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 02:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Appears so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 02:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I know about Filipinos is that they fuck up every time one replaces my toilet paper. THE END FACES FORWARD, MARTA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 01:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Source](https://www.reddit.com/r/Portland/comments/3bckcf/at_a_church_on_se_92nd_when_i_inquired_i_was_told/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Portland wedding (x-post /r/Portland) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 01:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Things Meatloaf Would Do For Love </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This right here is why I fucking love this site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ellipseseses* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DOOT DOOT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "A man who says a thing can't be done is quite apt to be interrupted by some idiot doing it." - Elbert Hubbard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Those who say a thing can't be done are quite apt to be interrupted by some idiot doing it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 23:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were dead serious about that corgi puppy eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 22:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually posted a while in the Bernie Sanders sub asking why more Americans don't just fund candidates online like kickstarter campaigns. Got downvoted to hell and told a million different ways it wouldn't work.

And now I see that's exactly what's gone and been done.

I like Bernie, but some of his supporters are goddamn morons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 20:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Some people have life goals, I just want a god damned puppy.

Well I just found the quote that's going on my tombstone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 20:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry I couldn't provide more detail. I have a book by the photographer who tells that story, just cant be bothered to go find the proper quote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 20:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What IS the goal? Or are you one of those "it's not the destination, it's the adventure" guys... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is your goal to get the most karma on reddit or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot to mention that they're all on fire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Station fire shook me to my core. It's so hard not to imagine yourself being in that position... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WOW that's dumb. I've been using corn starch to "breath fire" since I was 12. How do people not know that it's flammable as fuck???? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 18:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I can tell this is basically just rugby, soccer, and MMA all rolled into one.

Booking my trip NOW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 18:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See the guy between Ali's legs? He was Sports Illustrated's top photographer at the time. The man who took this picture was new on the job, and would have been in the same spot, which was considered the best angle. He was told to go find his own spot on the ring. He did, and he got this picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 16:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it was totally because of his weight. Sleep apnea I think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 15:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if there's a word for it, but my family does this all the time. My mom has started telling some of my stories like she was actually there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 20:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in the slightest. There are far more extreme wings of the conservative party. That's not bias, that's a simple observation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compare it to the NYT, America's paper of record and a proven government mouthpiece... At least their bias is obvious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deadly groove: check.

Soulful white guy: check.

Hand spasms: check.

Joe Cocker 2 confirmed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except their morons are conservative morons, which are just like liberal morons but with an added dash of insanity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm well aware of what they do and how they do it. I've been a journalist for ten years and have worked with them and CNN affiliates. My point is that their "news" is no different to other tv news channels in America. They're all inherently biased because they are all privately owned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly what I was thinking. What I hate about racing sims is not being able to quickly glance around. Oculus would do that perfectly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did... did you ask him to read you a bedtime story? Because I would've asked for a bedtime story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's precisely what I mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is why I said they're no different to any other TV news station in America. MSNBC and CNN are just as guilty of that as Fox is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Al Jazeera is one of the most respected news organizations in the world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly what I was saying. They give airtime to morons. Their actual reporters are sound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time this comes up I defend Fox News and get downvoted to oblivion. It's their TALKING HEADS that are fucking retarded. Their news coverage is no different from any other TV news station in America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH he probably stole it from another writer (I want to say Stephen King?) who used it as an example on how to create interesting short stories. The only difference to the short story example and the Purge is that in the short story idea, people were allowed to commit any crime as long as they compensated those who they committed the crime against. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real life Cooper reporting in. My mom's friends called me Cooper Cooper, because her maiden name was Cooper, which then became my middle name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a character with the exact same name in one of my AP English short stories. C'mon Nolan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 08:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it might just come down to driver preference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 00:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *oooooooo - eeeeeeeeeeeee  - hehehehehehehehe - oooo^O^^O^^^O^^^^oooooooooooooooooooo* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 23:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally just slapped my knee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 23:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doot doot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 22:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what's this from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 21:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went to school with his nephew actually. He got HEATED whenever you brought that video up hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 21:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work with one other full time employee publishing a magazine I can barely get out four times a year, and running a website. So not exactly six figures, although our office IS air conditioned. We run sponsored stories on that website because our audience demands they have free access to our content and advertisers have gotten wise to the fact that slapping a banner ad on a website isn't good business. And yet we get criticized for "duping" the customer.

I certainly don't like Bungie's model either, but I'm not going to criticize it just because they're making money in different ways to their competitors. If the market is willing to purchase those kinds of games, more power to Bungie. Consumers are morons. But I won't be buying it. Nor will you. Hopefully that sentiment is shared across the market and we can disincentivise game dev's from this brand of business. And if it all goes tits up, you can sit calmly on your high horse and say "I told you so." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 20:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The best product on the lowest possible budget. This is basic business.

You're not including deadlines, which play probably the most critical role. An indie dev team with a small budget and no deadline can spend as long as they want on a game. But if something goes wrong for a team working on a deadline, you have to sink more money into fixing that problem in order to meet the mark, putting you over budget.

 ...the rest of the industry has been able to finance their games without selling missions bundled with soft drinks, Bungie should be no exception.

Sounds pretty communist to me. A company finding an alternate source of revenue untapped by their competitors is unfair????

The bottom line of Bungie is not at hand here, the budget allocated to the game is. You don't know what that budget was, nor whether they were able to deliver the product within that given budget. If shit hit the fan, as I mentioned above, that could force the budget to skyrocket in order for them to meet their deadline. Bungie creates value for itself by creating video games, but they can't do that at a loss.

 This is not advertising.

You're definition of advertising is incredibly narrow. Perhaps the best word is "marketing". This is Red Bull. The way they go about marketing is radically different to everyone else. Other energy drinks would slap a COD logo on the can, certainly, but that is not and has never been Red Bull's strategy. Instead of slapping their logo on an F1 car, they created an F1 team. Instead of slapping Destiny's logo on their cans, they have exclusive content. It's pretty genius IMO.

 That's greedy

Is this communist Russia? This isn't communist Russia, is it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So because other developers have done really cool stuff with a tiny budget, other developers should do that too? That doesn't make much sense, but ok. And how do you know it's not about funding the game? Can you provide a source for that, or are you just guessing because it looks like they're money grubbing whores?

If it wasn't for advertising, my industry would be dead because the money we make selling our product is JUST enough for us to make a new product every four months. That pain is shared by a LOT of others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, fuck those guys for finding additional funding for their game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a champ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 05:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bada-buh-ba-bah.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 05:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take your filthy upvote and get out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 05:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should try pronouncing Southwark, or Gloucester correctly. The British pronounce things different to Americans, strange as it might seem  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 02:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure more clever people than I have already figured this out. But it was satisfying as hell when I put two and two together.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 02:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inb4 people get their knickers in a twist. I have nothing against karmawhoring, reposting, x-posting, etc. Just thought I should say... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I suppose I'm one of those fellows my father always warned me against." - P.G. Wodehouse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 01:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It just dawned on me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 00:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you sought counseling? My ex was a rape victim and had the opposite reaction to you, she felt disgusting during sex, like she was debasing herself. We went to therapy together and that helped her discuss and synthesize her feelings, which lead to a much more fulfilling sex life. More than anything the therapy just allowed her to talk about what she was feeling, and hear herself saying it, rather than bottling it all up in her head.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your service  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The small sail at the front of a sailboat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best one yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is. You can judge age pretty well by the dorsal and this one is very small </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Still got dick

I like the cut of your jib </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on down to Bermuda. Our wood is fantastic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried this at least a dozen times. Never worked. You're like an anal loving unicorn...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... how much damage was there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently learned my ex first slept with me because I had the balls to tell her I didn't think child support should be mandatory. The thing is, I don't even really believe that. Neither does she. I think I just said it to be cool and contradictory, and it totally worked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girls of Reddit, what's the most arbitrary reason you've ever chosen to have sex with someone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 13:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 06:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jolly good, old horse.

***blows***

I say! This could knock out a caribou! CARIBOUUUUUU. Lovely woody word, wouldn't you say old beast? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 06:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, is the headline being intentionally dumb by calling rioters "peaceful protesters"? Literally the first line of the story calls them violent protesters. Aka rioters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 06:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Youuuuu lucky ducks you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 00:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come visit Bermuda. Luscious man-calf abound! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my best friends is Christian. I can never argue about the negatives of religion with him because he's grown up in a house that embodies every positive aspect. His mother is a goddamn saint. Church every Sunday, constant community outreach, food drives etc. Grew up with him and his mom my entire life and she's never once mentioned God besides when they have grace at dinner. 

Point being, for many, religion is just a vessel in which valuable, noble traits can be delivered and instilled. If living a life like my friend's mom has lived is done in order to get into heaven, why worry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow this sub is such a circle jerk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Zouma is a captain in waiting. He's been referred to as France's future captain, so I see no reason why he can't eventually be ours. I fucking love the kid.

On another note, I'll be sad to see Mikel go but he could really lock down another team's midfield, and his talents are wasted on the bench. If Schneiderlin leaves Soton, I think he'd make for a great replacement. Obviously not in terms of playmaking, but I've always rated him for his ability to shut down a midfield. He's a beast, and I'd love to see him do well on another team with regular starts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It goes to show you how fickle Hollywood can be though. Here's a girl that has been stunning in every film she's been in since Leon, and yet three shitty but high grossing films nearly derailed her career. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I misremembered the article I read. It was Cold Mountain that gave her career new life. Linked to the article in my original comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Natalie Portman blames the Star Wars prequels for nearly ruining her career. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The films nearly ruined Portman's career, lest we forget. She had faded into obscurity until ~~Black Swan~~ Cold Mountain, and the only reason she got that role was through a lot of connections going to bat for her. Everyone in Hollywood had written her off directly because of Star Wars.

EDIT: Cold Mountain, not Black Swan.

Source: http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/natalie-portman-blames-star-wars-prequels-for-almost-ruining-her-career-everyone-thought-i-was-a-horrible-actress-9933636.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 06:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asking the important questions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 06:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 50 Shades of Shit did it first

"Aro laughed. 'Hahaha', he giggled." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 03:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, that's correct. I was 16 when I first started smoking. *High* school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 02:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a journalist is basically just having good Google-fu and knowing how proper sentence structure works... and interviews... and the stomach to transcribe hour long interviews. But mostly Google-fu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 00:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DING DING ^^^shame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 23:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's play Spot The Reason OP Is An Idiot!

Fuck my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've missed a lot of great moments in sports. Here's why. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 23:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 23:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd have to be a pretty shitty seamstress not to account for movement...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 22:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a journalist, this interviewer is fucking slobbering all over Pao and it's making me sick. Don't hide your bias or anything... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 22:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to agree to share, first off. I live in Bermuda and have a dock. There's a couple that lives on a houseboat in the bay and they use it without permission all the time. I was actually on it flying my friend's drone around and they just walked past me and loaded up their dinghy like it was nothing. I told them it was a private dock, and that they could use it this one time. They've since teared the ass out of it and are using it all the time, disrupting the guests that pay $600 per night for our vacation rental cottage. I've spoken to them at least a dozen times about it and yet they continue to use it, leaving bags of doritos, beer bottles, etc floating in the mangroves by my slip. I've since called the police, had them charged for mooring without a license and trespassing.

In other words, don't use people's shit without their permission. And if you give a moose a muffin, he'll ask you for some milk. Far better to lay down the law and not let people use your shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 22:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This could pretty much apply to everything I do in life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 22:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro. I'm so fucking altitudinous right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 21:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I KNEW THAT! One of the few things I remember from science class. No idea why the name Bernoulli stuck, but it did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I... I dont remember installing the cloud to butt extension... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Dos Equis has its new spokesman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *midly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 18:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My thoughts exactly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
