<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1805</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We genuinely couldn't give a fuck about losing him on a free, keeping him this year would be worth more than what you are offering </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Critters? Sounds similar can't remember the clown but not seen it for a while </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 17:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair play to him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for 20 RVP and for giving Fergie the perfect send off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 00:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck is CMV? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they aren't  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 09:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeh we will definitely sell for a big loss after one season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 16:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He can still be a professional about it instead of act like a cunt, imagine if he was a member of your staff or someone on your team. I'm a united fan so couldn't give a fuck but he's still acting like a prick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus what a little wankstain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 20:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After he has picked a pug and gets asked why

"It's a bulldog innit?"

Kingsman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 21:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watch other leagues and couldn't give a fuck who wins, it gives me true enjoyment as I'm a neutral who gets to watch great games but couldn't care less about specific teams </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 21:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No because it's weird

Haha at bandwagoners downvoting me, I'm sure you support all the better teams in the different leagues because you feel a real "connection" with the teams </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 01:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was only 20 then in all fairness so maybe couldn't adjust that well but since then he's been all over with the national team so he might be ok now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 23:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me mate he's painful at times because you know he can be an absolutely brilliant fucker but instead he just causes you physical pain  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 23:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has but he will never kick on, he will have a game where he looks like a world beater and you think fuck me what a player we have and then he will be absolutely abject for the next 6 games and you'll want him benched and then he will have a great game and then be fucking abject for 6 games etc etc time is a flat circle yadda yada </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right, he is too inconsistent. It's not so much bad work ethics I genuinely just think he has a bit of a mental block when it comes to taking the next step, he always seemingly sabotages himself by doing something stupid/infuriating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've no idea how well he will do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yyyeeessss finally!!!!! Can't believe he is finally leaving and getting off our wage bill.

He was great in 2010-11 and one of the best in the league but fuck me he is probably the most frustrating cunt I've ever had to watch and I've had to watch a lot of them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
