<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7838</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 18:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 00:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is why the Bible verse is "I will remove your sin from you as far as the east is from the west" and not "as far as the north is from the south".  I'd like my sin further away than 7,918 miles, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 09:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last part of Human After All </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 09:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doooo bow ba dowwww... doooo bow ba dowwww

By the way the fuzzy noise in the background always sounds like it is jumping up and down octaves but I can never tell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 08:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must have been capitalized on one of the lists.  My bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 07:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Top grossing all time adjusted for inflation, AFI top 100, Reddit 100 years of cinema, Rotten Tomatoes top 100, and Sight and Sound top 50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Word cloud of top 100 movie lists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 07:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 23:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> X-Iron Steel Hawk Dragon Force </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 23:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try sitting on the far sides of the car </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 21:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are the explicit parts of the voice acting really necessary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I once made a movie, rather tongue-in-cheek, called Psycho. The content was, I felt, rather amusing and it was a big joke. I was horrified to find some people took it seriously. It was intended to make people scream and yell and so forthbut no more than screaming and yelling on a switchback railway (rollercoaster). I'm possibly in some respects the man who says in constructing it, 'how steep can we make the first dip?' If you make the dip too deep, the screams will continue as the car goes over the edge and destroys everyone. Therefore you mustn't go too far because you do want them to get off the switchback railway, giggling with pleasure." - Alfred Hitchcock in a 1964 interview </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 18:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They all set up environments through editing, better than many feature films out there.  Freiheit, 1:42.08 (A Boy and His Car), and 6-18-67 all have very unique environments thanks to attention to detail with vision and sound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 18:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call me crazy but I like Temple of Doom more than The Last Crusade and almost as much as Raiders </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 17:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Temple of Doom raft fall is pretty ludicrous and happens very early on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 17:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What we're doing here, really, is just designing a ride at Disneyland."

Twenty years later it was a ride at Disneyland.  I'm not sure why Spielberg keeps talking about Disneyland because this plot seems far grittier than the other Disneyland rides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 17:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was a great director when he filmed THX 1138 and American Graffiti.  Also the USC shorts he directed are very well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 21:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first movie had a scene with a spooky car "graveyard" but ultimately it got cut. https://youtu.be/Wzkq6UFsEV8?t=59s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Imgur is the world's largest distributor of silent films </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 21:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 01:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of people at my film school don't understand this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are kids more afraid of vacuum cleaners than lawn mowers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 19:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 16:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a lot of thoughts like that.  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U6y7YOlldek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do people believe that it takes 10,000 hours to achieve perfection? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 05:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It is impossible to wash all of your laundry at once without getting naked. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 00:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 23:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried the back seat?  Pretty insane on that first drop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 23:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, watch POV videos online and imagine you're riding it.  Maybe do other activities like biking or rollerblading that involve sudden direction changes.  Learn about the physics of inertia, acceleration, weightlessness, and then maybe the rides will be less threatening if you know what's happening to your body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 23:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start small and work your way up!  Also, keep your eyes open and relax.  If you want a less intense ride, sit in the middle of the train as the front will go faster into hills and the back will get pulled over the hills faster.

I've ridden every coaster at Cedar Point except for Jr. Gemini and they are all great.  Pretty sure everyone here can give you lots of information on the park if you need it.  Try the wooden roller coasters first; they are less sickening than Corkscrew or Gatekeeper or Mantis (rougarou) because the transitions are less intense.

I actually puked last time I went to cedar point because I rode the Skyhawk swing ride twice after breakfast.  Sudden acceleration and deceleration on a full stomach is dangerous... So take time to digest, haha.

What was the roller coaster you puked on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My attempts at leading nobody on have resulted in me leading everybody on. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 10:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 08:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want to experience that turnaround now.  I love specific breakdowns of rides, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 07:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Volume at full blast in my university's student union building.  Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 07:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wouldn't do that, would you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 06:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3deep5me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Endurance challenge! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 08:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long can you survive in FNAF without dying?  Start with a new game file and work your way up from the beginning.  Continue to night 6 and 7 if you make it that far!

My personal record on mobile is Night 6, 2 AM.

If someone was able to complete all 7 levels in one go that would really be something.  If this catches on we should keep a High Score list on the side of the sub for FNAF 1, 2, and 3 on PC and mobile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roller coaster POV [1 min] [Animation] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 19:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 09:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats actually pretty clever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 09:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id like to think its molding a mini planet and no one can see it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 21:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, that's it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 21:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was gonna say that haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 17:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's one scene where Dave plays chess with HAL 9000 and the computer makes a very slight error in its assessment of the game, hinting at the fact that HAL is malfunctioning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 08:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2001 A Space Odyssey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 08:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't wait to hear the rest of Bluescovery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 09:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking about this today.  In the first game, the animatronics get directly in your face only when you die.  In the second game, the old ones are in front of your face almost every time you put down the monitor, and in the third one the hallucinations are always jumping right on you.  So the first one is the only one where there is the legitimate suspense of hoping to avoid that dreaded face to face encounter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 09:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely, best moment in the series </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 23:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now we know how Scott feels when people ask for FNAF 4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 08:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A short comic?  This is pretty elaborate!  Awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am still alive even though I have never laughed at a Funny or Die video. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 08:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone ever seen the 1977 Rollercoaster movie? Is it any good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 08:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 18:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't tried that.  I tried using the YouTube stabilization but I didn't like the way it looked.  Next time around I will try using a lower frame rate and I'll take more time positioning the camera. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 17:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took still frames from a video of me slowly moving the camera along the track.  If I did it again I would use 15 fps not 30 and I would take the pictures on "set" instead of grabbing them in post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
