<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2450</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A British tribunal has ruled that the electronic eavesdropping agency GCHQ violated the rights of two overseas human rights agencies by failing to delete intercepted data on time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Huckabee and Rick Santorum among anti-gay marriage pledge signees: Defend Marriage pledge comes ahead of supreme court decision on same-sex marriage as some conservatives liken fight to that of Martin Luther King </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 01:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iranian lawmakers approved the outlines of a bill that would ban inspections of military sites and require the lifting of all international sanctions under any nuclear deal with six world powers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 01:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 00:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is great that the university agreed to return this historic building to its original home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> College to return barrack to site of WWII internment camp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 00:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Europol web unit to hunt extremists behind Isis social media propaganda: Europe-wide police team aims to find key figures in campaign producing 100,000 tweets daily linked to terror group, seeking to recruit foreign fighters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 00:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Huckabee and Rick Santorum among anti-gay marriage pledge signees: Defend Marriage pledge comes ahead of supreme court decision on same-sex marriage as some conservatives liken fight to that of Martin Luther King </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 23:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Huckabee and Rick Santorum among anti-gay marriage pledge signees: Defend Marriage pledge comes ahead of supreme court decision on same-sex marriage as some conservatives liken fight to that of Martin Luther King </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 23:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $700 million plan to help salmon habitat in northwestern US faces new challenge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 23:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Around 5,000 people joined a Berlin demonstration on Sunday by a controversial protest group which dug mock graves in front of parliament to highlight Europe's deadly migration crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 23:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California inmates are dying of drug overdoses at nearly triple the national rate and it's unclear whether the tough steps state officials took this year to stop illicit drugs from getting into prisons are having any effect, though they are prompting criticism from civil rights advocates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 19:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dozens of women have held a vigil outside Egypt's presidential palace, calling for the release of thousands detained for violating the country's controversial protest law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 19:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of people formed human chains in cities across Spain's wealthy northern Basque Country on Sunday to call for the right to hold a regional referendum on independence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 19:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Somali jihadist group al-Shabab has launched a major attack in the country's capital Mogadishu. A suicide bomb has exploded near the national intelligence headquarters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 09:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 62-year-old man in Guatemala has received a hero's welcome after a 200km (125-mile) march in protest against government corruption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 03:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Federal Election Commission is suing a Utah businessman, saying he made $170,000 in illegal campaign contributions to U.S. Sens. Harry Reid of Nevada and Mike Lee of Utah and former Utah Attorney General Mark Shurtleff in 2009 and 2010 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 03:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Federal Election Commission is suing a Utah businessman, saying he made $170,000 in illegal campaign contributions to U.S. Sens. Harry Reid of Nevada and Mike Lee of Utah and former Utah Attorney General Mark Shurtleff in 2009 and 2010 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 03:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least 140 people were arrested Saturday after violence broke out at an anti-immigration rally in Bratislava, Slovakia, attended by thousands of people in protest at EU quotas on migrant numbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 02:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toby Keith and NRA: What they say about the Charleston shooting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 02:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Hunt for the Financial Industry's Most-Wanted Hacker: The malware known as ZeuS and its rogue creator have been at the cutting edge of cyber-crime for nearly a decade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 01:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 00:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How far the communist party has fallen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China's Xi Jinping says poverty is 'nothing to fear' after pesticide deaths: Chinese president is on a three-day visit to deprived Guizhou province, where four children killed themselves by swallowing pesticide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 00:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iranian vice-president attacks hardliners over volleyball ban for female fans: Shahindokht Molaverdi denounces men whose violent threats prevented women getting into Iran match against the US as sanctimonious </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 00:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iranian vice-president attacks hardliners over volleyball ban for female fans: Shahindokht Molaverdi denounces men whose violent threats prevented women getting into Iran match against the US as sanctimonious </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 00:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Los Angeles police shoot unarmed man in head </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 00:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One man was killed when his trailer home toppled during a storm that brought rain and straight-line winds blowing at more than 80 mph to some Native American reservations in central South Dakota </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 00:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Italian prosecutors are seeking to indict 297 people and the Bank of China in connection with a massive money-laundering investigation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 00:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fears that staging a gay pride parade in Latvian capital Riga would lead to unrest proved wide off the mark Saturday with police saying just three anti-gay protesters had been arrested for minor public order offenses such as attempts at throwing eggs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 20:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United Nations took a step closer Friday toward crafting a major treaty that would protect marine life beyond territorial waters by passing a resolution at the General Assembly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 02:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United Nations took a step closer Friday toward crafting a major treaty that would protect marine life beyond territorial waters by passing a resolution at the General Assembly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 02:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three California irrigation districts sued the state on Friday, claiming officials overstepped their authority by ordering farmers with some of the strongest water rights to stop pumping from some rivers during the drought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 02:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Texas Supreme Court effectively upheld the Austin divorce of a same-sex couple Friday, turning away Republican Gov. Greg Abbott and arguments that the state can't dissolve a marriage it didn't recognize in the first place </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 01:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The world is embarking on its sixth mass extinction with animals disappearing about 100 times faster than they used to, scientists warned Friday, and humans could be among the first victims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 00:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oil and Gas Co's Disposal of Wastewater Causes Sharp Rise in Quakes: Nearly 90 percent of temblors in the central U.S. are now caused by water injected into underground wells </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 22:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oil and Gas Co's Disposal of Wastewater Causes Sharp Rise in Quakes: Nearly 90 percent of temblors in the central U.S. are now caused by water injected into underground wells </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 22:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Rules Would Cut Pollution from Buses, Big Rigs: New EPA regulations for heavy duty vehicles could reduce fuel consumption by 24 percent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 22:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Seeks Multiemployer Pension Reform Act Repeal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 21:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cancer-Causing Chemicals Found In Drinking Water Near Texas Fracking Sites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 21:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cancer-Causing Chemicals Found In Drinking Water Near Texas Fracking Sites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 21:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A top Federal Reserve policymaker signaled Friday that despite a "nearly healed" U.S. labor market, he will not support raising U.S. interest rates until he sees stronger signs of inflation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 20:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cambodia is training an elite squad of rats, imported from Africa, to sniff out landmines and other unexploded ordnance in the once war-wracked kingdom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 20:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cambodia is training an elite squad of rats, imported from Africa, to sniff out landmines and other unexploded ordnance in the once war-wracked kingdom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 20:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poachers kill ranger, 2 soldiers in Congo wildlife park </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 17:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some parts of KwaZulu-Natal, South Africa, could be without water in 60 days. The worst drought since 1991 has forced the government to ration water by introducing a quota system in some areas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 17:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some parts of KwaZulu-Natal, South Africa, could be without water in 60 days. The worst drought since 1991 has forced the government to ration water by introducing a quota system in some areas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 17:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Californian company behind fatal balcony collapse sued over other project: Segue Construction paid $3.4m after being sued two years ago for water damage to balconies and outdoor spaces in 109-unit Californian complex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 16:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of Brazil's leading businessmen has been arrested as part of a major investigation into corruption at state-owned oil giant Petrobras. Marcelo Odebrecht, who heads the Odebrecht group - Latin America's largest construction conglomerate - is in police custody </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 16:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkish news agencies say that authorities have arrested two Georgian citizens who tried to enter the Turkey with radioactive material, including cesium </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 16:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal agencies lose track of endangered species protection measures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 16:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal agencies lose track of endangered species protection measures, research finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 16:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obamacare: What happens if the Supreme Court rules for the plaintiffs in King v. Burwell? The simplest answer is that Republican states get screwed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 15:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 15:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to thank the German government's policy on reusing military bases as bird sanctuaries for this award. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The International Whaling Commission (IWC) on Friday demanded that Japan provide more information to prove that its revised Antarctic whaling programme was for scientific research, saying it could not reach a consensus based on documents submitted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 15:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The International Whaling Commission (IWC) on Friday demanded that Japan provide more information to prove that its revised Antarctic whaling programme was for scientific research, saying it could not reach a consensus based on documents submitted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 15:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Delaware Senate President Pro Tem said that NRA lobbyist Richard Armitage could have faced felony charges for his allegedly false testimony about closed door negotiations involving the gun rights group and the Attorney General's office over language regarding the marketing of firearm safety programs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 15:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Focus On Islamic Extremism Leaves Radical Right Overlooked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 14:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Record Cash Wrung From Bond Market to Cover U.S. Stock Buybacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 14:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shale oil drillers are devoting more revenue than ever to interest payments. In one example, Continental Resources, the company credited with making North Dakotas Bakken Shale one of the biggest oil-producing regions in the world, spent almost as much as Exxon Mobil, a company 20 times its size </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 14:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers at EMBL Heidelberg have solved a question that has puzzled cell biologists for decades  how does the protein machine that allows cells to swallow up molecules during endocytosis function? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 14:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warring forces in South Sudan have carried out horrific crimes against children, including castration, rape and tying them together before slitting their throats, the UN has said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 14:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amnesty International activists say that Cameroonian authorities have been holding 84 children in detention after they raised a series of schools accused of supporting Boko Haram. Some of the children are as young as 5 years old, and have been held for months without any charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 14:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Probes started into potential U.S. spending on ghost schools in Afghanistan: Officials in Washington and Kabul are examining whether U.S. funds were spent for schooling in Afghanistan that never occurred </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 13:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Probes started into potential U.S. spending on ghost schools in Afghanistan: Officials in Washington and Kabul are examining whether U.S. funds were spent for schooling in Afghanistan that never occurred </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 13:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indian Kashmir was largely under curfew on Friday with top separatist leaders detained to halt a planned protest march over a series of recent killings in the restive territory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 13:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black Americans Are Killed At 12 Times The Rate Of People In Other Developed Countries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 08:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black Americans Are Killed At 12 Times The Rate Of People In Other Developed Countries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 08:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mali's warring factions look close to signing a landmark peace deal to end years of unrest after pro-government militia leaders agreed to evacuate a flashpoint town and the government dropped arrest warrants for several rebels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 07:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A group of eight Brazilian senators on a visit to Venezuela to meet a jailed opposition leader say they had to flee after their bus was attacked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 07:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three Hints Yellen Dropped That the Fed Might Not Raise Rates in September </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 02:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. effort to build a moderate Syrian opposition force that can stand up to Islamic State rebels is moving more slowly than expected due to complications vetting volunteers and bringing them out of Syria for training </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 00:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The carcasses of at least nine endangered fin whales have been found floating near Alaska's Kodiak Island </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 00:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian government assets in France and Belgium including bank accounts have been frozen in a row over compensation for shareholders of defunct oil giant Yukos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 23:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox And Friends Say More Guns Would Have Stopped The Charleston Church Massacre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 23:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 21:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The issues of racism and white supremacy are on any progressive agenda that I know of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DNA Links 8,500-Year-Old Kennewick Man to Native Tribes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 20:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC to phone companies: You can stop unwanted robocalls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 20:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five Years of Greek Misery Laid Bare in Five Depressing Charts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 20:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Political profiteers push Ohio's pot vote: Ballot measure mercenaries seek to amend Ohio's constitution to benefit select few </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 20:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Political profiteers push Ohio's pot vote: Ballot measure mercenaries seek to amend Ohio's constitution to benefit select few </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 20:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Political profiteers push Ohio's pot vote: Ballot measure mercenaries seek to amend Ohio's constitution to benefit select few </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 20:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Scott Walker Dismantled Wisconsin's Environmental Legacy: As governor of Wisconsin, the likely Republican presidential nomination-seeker consistently dismissed science and sided with polluters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 20:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Think of Multiple Sclerosis as a Leaking Swimming Pool [Video]: A new way of looking at the neurodegenerative disorder could lead to more and better treatments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 20:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An attack by suspected Islamist Boko Haram fighters in Niger has killed at least 38 people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 20:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charleston church shooting: Without gun control, racism will keep killing black people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 19:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charleston church shooting: Without gun control, racism will keep killing black people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 19:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Palestinians will next week submit their first file to the International Criminal Court in their bid to open criminal proceedings against Israel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 19:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany agreed Thursday to turn more than 60 former military bases into nature preserves, with the aim of creating vast new green oases and sanctuaries for rare species of birds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 19:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany agreed Thursday to turn more than 60 former military bases into nature preserves, with the aim of creating vast new green oases and sanctuaries for rare species of birds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 19:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Health care fraud sweeps across the country have led to charges against 243 people, including doctors, nurses and pharmacy owners accused of bilking Medicare and Medicaid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 19:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charleston Church Shooting Suspect Is Captured </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 18:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hong Kong's legislature on Thursday vetoed a China-vetted electoral reform package that had been criticized by opposition pro-democracy lawmakers and activists as flawed and undemocratic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 08:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Mastermind' of 1982 Jewish cafe attack in Paris arrested in Jordan: High-ranking member of Palestinian militant group, who went by name of Amjad Atta, held over lethal raid on Chez Jo Goldenberg in which six died </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 08:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A white man opened fire during a prayer meeting inside a historic black church in downtown Charleston on Wednesday night, killing nine people in an assault that authorities described as a hate crime. The shooter was still at large </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 08:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient Inscriptions Decoded at the Spectacular Temple of the Mayan King Pakal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 04:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists create computational algorithm for fact-checking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 04:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists create computational algorithm for fact-checking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 04:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists create computational algorithm for fact-checking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 03:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Republicans Propose Stripping Family Planning Services From Millions Of Low-Income Women </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 03:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The junior party in the coalition that runs Catalonia said Wednesday that its three ministers were pulling out of the regional government due to disagreements over its push to break away from Spain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 03:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Honduran soldiers are taking over public hospitals and medicine storage warehouses to guarantee the supply of drugs to patients after a recent fraud and graft scandal rocked the Social Security Institute </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 03:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> West Virginia has the highest rate of overdose deaths in the U.S., according to a report released Wednesday, further spotlighting Appalachia's festering drug abuse problem that is also fueling a rise in hepatitis C in one of the nation's poorest regions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 21:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> West Virginia has the highest rate of overdose deaths in the U.S., according to a report released Wednesday, further spotlighting Appalachia's festering drug abuse problem that is also fueling a rise in hepatitis C in one of the nation's poorest regions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 21:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opponents of legalizing marijuana for medical purposes have long argued that such laws will encourage more youngsters to partake. But that notion may have no factual grounding, according to a new study that shows cannabis use among teenagers didnt increase in states that legalized medical marijuana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 21:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 400,000-year-old dental tartar provides earliest evidence of manmade pollution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 20:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 400,000-year-old dental tartar provides earliest evidence of manmade pollution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 20:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fossilized remains of a new bat species, which lived 16 million years ago, walked on four limbs and was three times larger than today's average bat, have been discovered in New Zealand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 20:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fossilized remains of a new bat species, which lived 16 million years ago, walked on four limbs and was three times larger than today's average bat, have been discovered in New Zealand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 20:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US struggling to recruit Iraqi troops to fight Isis, Pentagon chief admits: Only 7,000 soldiers have been trained, despite goal of 24,000 by fall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 20:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oliver Sacks, Antonio Damasio and Others Debate Christof Koch on the Nature of Consciousness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 20:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former top U.S. officials can be held liable for the abuse of hundreds of detainees rounded up after the Sept. 11 terrorist attacks for minor immigration violations, a federal appeals court said Wednesday, citing the importance of the rule of law even in times of crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 20:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former top U.S. officials can be held liable for the abuse of hundreds of detainees rounded up after the Sept. 11 terrorist attacks for minor immigration violations, a federal appeals court said Wednesday, citing the importance of the rule of law even in times of crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 20:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AT T Mobility has been slapped with a record $100 million fine for offering consumers "unlimited" data, but then slowing their Internet speeds after they reached a certain amount </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 20:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal transit officials said Wednesday they are ordering the inspection of ventilation systems in train tunnels nationwide after an electrical malfunction filled a train inside a Washington tunnel with smoke, leading to a passenger's death </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 20:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Korea's anti-trust watchdog said Wednesday it has launched a probe into alleged foreign-exchange market rigging by global banks, following a report that six lenders were under investigation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 09:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cleaner air worldwide would save two million lives a year and not only in the most polluted countries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 05:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congressional aides say top House and Senate Republicans are ready to brief lawmakers on their plans should the Supreme Court erase federal subsidies under President Barack Obama's health care law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 04:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A high-level panel urged a major overhaul of U.N. peacekeeping operations Tuesday that would make political solutions the paramount goal, speed up deployment of peacekeepers, and require the naming and shaming of countries whose troops commit acts of sexual abuse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 03:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neil Young calls out Trump for 'Rockin' In The Free World' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 03:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal prosecutors in Brazil have called for the authorities to stop the eviction of at least 2,000 families living in an area of the Amazon jungle where a huge dam is being built </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 03:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal prosecutors in Brazil have called for the authorities to stop the eviction of at least 2,000 families living in an area of the Amazon jungle where a huge dam is being built </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 03:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taser Is Charging Stunning Fees to Handle Police Video: One police department is paying nearly 23 times as much for video licensing and storage as Amazon charges for storage alone. Taser says the comparison is one of apples vs. oranges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 02:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taser Is Charging Stunning Fees to Handle Police Video: One police department is paying nearly 23 times as much for video licensing and storage as Amazon charges for storage alone. Taser says the comparison is one of apples vs. oranges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 02:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican leaders in Congress are considering a plan to revive President Barack Obamas trade package by adding a proposal to give him fast-track negotiating authority to an unrelated bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 02:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israel and Hamas have been holding indirect contacts about ideas for cementing a long-term truce in the Gaza Strip </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 01:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nine US privacy groups have dropped out of talks on voluntary standards for facial recognition technology, after failing to agree on a code on how it could be deployed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 01:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nine US privacy groups have dropped out of talks on voluntary standards for facial recognition technology, after failing to agree on a code on how it could be deployed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 01:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An anonymous apparent fan of pigs and fairy tales is offering some shelter for any piglets still loose after a semitrailer crash last week in southwest Ohio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 21:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An anonymous apparent fan of pigs and fairy tales is offering some shelter for any piglets still loose after a semitrailer crash last week in southwest Ohio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 21:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Border Patrol agents who watch over northern Ohio not far from the Canadian border routinely engaged in racial profiling to roundup Hispanics and often used racially offensive terms to describe them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 21:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Border Patrol agents who watch over northern Ohio not far from the Canadian border routinely engaged in racial profiling to roundup Hispanics and often used racially offensive terms to describe them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 21:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Senate has passed a measure aimed at ensuring that the United States never tortures detainees again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 20:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Senate has passed a measure aimed at ensuring that the United States never tortures detainees again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 20:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arsonists torch storerooms with 4,000-year-old artifacts; Irreparable damage inflicted to antiquities salvaged during excavation at Tel Kishon, near Galilees Mount Tabor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 20:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A team led by archaeologists from the University of Reading has just begun an excavation of a Neolithic building at Marden Henge in the Vale of Pewsey. Constructed in 2400 B.C., the earthworks is the largest henge in England, yet very little is known about it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 20:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A U.S. Justice Department criminal investigation into money-laundering controls at Citigroup Inc.s Banamex USA unit has uncovered potential violations serious enough to merit a fine under the Bank Secrecy Act </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 20:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> France's ecology minister, Segolene Royal, has rankled the company that makes Nutella by urging the public to stop eating its irresistible chocolate hazelnut spread, saying it contributes to deforestation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 20:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> France's ecology minister, Segolene Royal, has rankled the company that makes Nutella by urging the public to stop eating its irresistible chocolate hazelnut spread, saying it contributes to deforestation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 20:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran's President Hassan Rouhani received a fresh challenge to his authority on Tuesday when 60 lawmakers filed impeachment papers seeking to sack his education minister </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Office of Personnel Management investigative official said Tuesday the agency entrusted with millions of personnel records has a history of failing to meet basic computer network security requirements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A team of researchers with affiliations to several institutions in the U.S. has found a new way to track import, export and connecting countries in the illegal wildlife trade network </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Team finds 'unprecedented' earthquake evidence in Africa 25,000 years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Team finds 'unprecedented' earthquake evidence in Africa 25,000 years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 09:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know the mass of Mt. Everest? So we can calculate the force needed to move the mountain 3 centimeters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The world's tallest peak, Mount Everest, moved three centimetres (1.2 inches) to the southwest because of the Nepal earthquake that devastated the country in April </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 09:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The world's tallest peak, Mount Everest, moved three centimetres (1.2 inches) to the southwest because of the Nepal earthquake that devastated the country in April, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 09:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Further research into the sophisticated computer virus used to hack into hotels where the Iran nuclear talks took place has found it took advantage of digital credentials stolen from the world's top contract electronics maker Foxconn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 05:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate Change Might Be Destroying This Ancient Peruvian Archaeological Site </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 04:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The leader of Al-Qaeda's branch in Yemen was targeted in a CIA drone strike last week, though US officials would not immediately confirm he had been killed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 04:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smoking is responsible for nearly half of deaths due to certain types of cancers in 2011 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 04:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 44,500 People, Including Two Presidential Candidates, Vow To Defy The Supreme Court On Marriage Equality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 04:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The World Is Facing Its Longest Oil Glut in at Least Three Decades </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 04:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chemists are first to see elements transform at atomic scale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 03:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quantum Technology Probes Ultimate Limits of Vision: Researchers hope to show whether the human eye can detect a single photonand its superposition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 03:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Molecules Reach Coldest Temperature Ever: Physicists have chilled molecules to just a smidgen above absolute zerocolder than the afterglow of the Big Bang </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 03:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An unpredictable, yet scorching and dry climate kept large, grass-eating dinosaurs out of the tropics for some 30 million years after they first appeared on Earth, a study out Monday found </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An unpredictable, yet scorching and dry climate kept large, grass-eating dinosaurs out of the tropics for some 30 million years after they first appeared on Earth, a study out Monday found </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All but four states have either met or are working toward meeting federal guidelines intended to prevent prison rape, the U.S. Department of Justice says. Idaho, Arkansas, Alaska and Utah continue to reject the federal rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All but four states have either met or are working toward meeting federal guidelines intended to prevent prison rape, the U.S. Department of Justice says. Idaho, Arkansas, Alaska and Utah continue to reject the federal rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Obama administration gave conditional approval Monday to Arkansas, Delaware and Pennsylvania to expand their roles in the insurance marketplaces created under the 2010 health care law, ahead of a high court decision that could wipe out federal health insurance subsidies for millions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photos of the pipeline that spilled oil on the Santa Barbara coast show extensive corrosion and provide clues about the cause of the rupture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photos of the pipeline that spilled oil on the Santa Barbara coast show extensive corrosion and provide clues about the cause of the rupture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. industrial production unexpectedly fell in May as manufacturing and mining activity remained weak, a sign that a strong dollar and spending cuts in the energy sector continued to constrain economic growth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 21:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CIA torture appears to have broken spy agency rule on human experimentation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 21:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israel has approved the reopening of around 70 Palestinian shops which it closed 15 years ago in the flashpoint West Bank city of Hebron, its mayor announced on Monday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 21:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pakistan looks to seal Olympic field hockey berth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 21:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker's former aides has asked the U.S. Supreme Court to toss out her conviction for campaigning on government time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 20:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker's former aides has asked the U.S. Supreme Court to toss out her conviction for campaigning on government time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 20:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Authorities say no one was injured after a natural gas pipeline rupture sparked a massive fire that prompted home evacuations in South Texas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 09:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Authorities say no one was injured after a natural gas pipeline rupture sparked a massive fire that prompted home evacuations in South Texas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 09:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's no spill-proof way to transport oil. That means leaks and worse will happen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 03:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As Governor Scott Walkers state budget inches toward passage, parents, teachers and students are taking to the streets to oppose sections of the education budget, which include sweeping changes they say would effectively privatize many public schools while draining funding from others </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 01:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dense mayfly swarm causes crashes, closes US bridge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 01:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dense mayfly swarm causes crashes, closes US bridge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 01:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudi Arabia is opening one of the worlds most-restricted stock markets to foreigners for the first time on Monday. The move comes as the biggest economy in the Middle East seeks to reduce its reliance on oil income and as the kingdom burns through foreign reserves at a record pace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 01:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Libya's recognized government said on Sunday that Algerian veteran militant Mokhtar Belmokhtar, a major figure in North African and Sahel Islamist insurgencies, has been killed in a U.S. air strike inside Libya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 01:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mayor says town full, temporarily closed to outsiders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 00:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US launched airstrike on al-Qaida operative in Libya charged in leading attack on gas plant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 00:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> France bans sale of Monsanto herbicide Roundup in nurseries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 21:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> France bans sale of Monsanto herbicide Roundup in nurseries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 21:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sudan president barred from leaving South Africa: Human rights groups call on South Africas government to comply with the ICC arrest warrant for Omar al-Bashir, but the ANC calls the court unfit for purpose </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 21:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israel's justice ministry announced Sunday it was closing the criminal investigation of the police officer whose documented beating of a soldier of Ethiopian origin set off a series of protests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 21:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israel on Sunday launched a pre-emptive assault on an upcoming U.N. report into last year's war in the Gaza Strip, saying the report is unfairly biased and issuing its own report that blames Gaza's Hamas militant rulers for the heavy civilian casualties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 21:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Argentine federal oral court yesterday convicted the first judge for crimes against humanity committed during the 1976-1983 dictatorship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 04:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exotic Glass Could Help Unravel Mysteries of Mars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 03:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least 11 Iraqi security personnel were killed Saturday in a quadruple suicide car bombing near Baiji that the Islamic State group said four of its foreign fighters carried out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 03:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders wants Elizabeth Warren supporters on board campaign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 02:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders wants Elizabeth Warren supporters on board campaign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 02:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
