<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9585</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 09:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true. Many people are happy to throw away the first amendment when someone disagrees with them but don't want the same to be done to them. This is very common especially as of lately with the political left. They term everything that they disagree with as hate speech that should be banned, sometimes even arguing for jail time for it. They are the arbiters of what is "hate speech", which is very convenient for them because it could be used as a tool to silence anyone that disagrees with their political agenda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 20:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The author discusses the overreach of the administration's powers to force a certain outcome by abusing the "disparate impact" concept.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A key part of President Obamas legacy will be the feds unprecedented collection of sensitive data on Americans by race. The government is prying into our most personal information at the most local levels, all for the purpose of racial and economic justice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 20:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> East Baltimore anti-violence group work suspended after guns, drugs found in raid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 19:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: That fewer than 385,000 individuals owned slaves in the US. That even if all slaveholders had been white, that would amount to only 1.4% of whites in the country. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 23:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man robs 2 sisters at lemonade stand after they gave him free drink </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 22:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
