<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3431</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since college is coming soon, what advice/lifetips do you have for incoming freshmen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 03:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I enrolled in some course already but the lectures clash with each other. Lectures can't be changed so does this mean I will need to withdraw and make amends? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 02:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For instance, my geology course clashes with my reshapping environments class so, I need to make changes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 07:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *GHOOOSTT CALLLOORRRIIEESSSS~~~ OOOO* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For one of my classes, it says there are no more spaces available when I tried adjusting my timetable. Does this mean it's completely full and I will be unable to take it for this semester? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best way to take notes in college lectures/tutes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 00:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should I be using a laptop or my pen and paper? What are the pros and cons of each?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I be taking notes with my laptop or paper? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 00:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 23:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, my college has around 40-50k students which I find baffling! I was in a school with around ~150 students prior and to be thrown into a school with 50,000 students just boggles my mind. I'll definitely be joining cubs but if i'm entering mid-year, will I be at a disadvantage? Will social clicks be formed already?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some of the easiest Environments courses for first years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 23:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starting college next month and i'm completely introverted and somewhat antisocial. Will I really be able to make friends? How? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 21:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wait.. I hear people collecting thousands of relics.. HOW? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing for a month and have 100... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone take reshaping environments and mapping environments? How was it and how hard was it to get a H1? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really want to take Mapping but i've heard only negative things about the lecturer so far :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some not-so-obvious movie plotholes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 13:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! Ex-Foundie here! Don't worry about the first maths exam, it only counts for like what, 25% of the overall grade? You should definitely focus on getting a better score on the other test which is going to count for ~70% so it can definitely pull your grades up.

Also, try to focus on other subjects! Economics especially starts to get significantly more difficult later on when you are introduced to SAQS/LAQS which makes the first MCQ exam seem like a joke. Other subjects like HOI and Lit/Drama are really easy to score in if you follow the guidelines and ask teachers for help and participate (very important, it accounts for grades) in your classes. All in all, just relax and work harder! Good luck. PM me if you have any other questions. 

Finally, while it's awesome to respect your parents wishes and dreams (and I totally respect that and can relate) you should also come to realise that College is a time when you realize that at the end of the day it's YOUR life. Not your dad's, mum's or whatever but YOURS. So think carefully about what you want to really do. It may feel nice to honor your parents wishes in the short run, but after you've graduated it would really suck to be filled with regrets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How exactly are cockroaches able to survive the radiation of a nuclear bomb? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 20:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's just hope that in the future the professor - who's probably backed by the dept.- doesn't start going against you and intentionally gives you unfair treatment in tests and assignments that would mess up your grade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 17:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about constructing environments? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone taken the following courses and has advice/reviews to give? They are: Designing Environments, Natural Environments, Understanding Planet Earth and Introduction to Programming? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 04:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 12:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure it'd dead already </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I want to increase the number of views on a website, will using a ddos like Loic or Hoic work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 07:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's the building next to a church then yes! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Melbourne Central sorry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone heard of the new Urbanest building in Central? What do ya think about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 02:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 21:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I for one really want to study architecture! Advice would be appreciated. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the population? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 00:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Warning:Very very eccentric but beautiful, just listen to the intro] Hahn Bin playing Sarasate's "Gypsy Airs" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 19:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
