<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5276</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> H1Z1 is the same engine as Planetside, thet game aleready has the templates, vehicles, and weapons. The DayZ engine was built from scratch so they have to make all of the base things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the space between atoms? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 02:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In empty space we know it isnt actually empty, there are tons of things in empty space. But what is between atoms themselves? is that perfect empty space? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 02:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PC Specs:
Intel i5-4440s 2.80 GHz
8Gb DDR3 RAM
H81M-A motherboard
GeFORCE GT 640 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> File system error (-1073741819) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 02:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i keep getting this error when i try to install something for give admin access to something, could anybody be any help?
Windows 8.1
i heard somewhere it was a memory issue so i have 8gigs ddr3
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 05:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Step 1: Don't Capitalize Every Word  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 05:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dayz is cpu intensive not gpu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arma 3 / DayZ SA map concept </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 03:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to know what your thoughts are on this and how i could improve it

http://imgur.com/GetrbkJ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 22:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nvm i fixed it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 21:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> now the game wont even launch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> .54 bug fix? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 20:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i launch the game and start playing on a server and after about 5 minutes stuff like this starts to happen and it gets really laggy (5 fps). then my game crashes. does anybody know how to fix this? id really like to keep playing this game.

http://imgur.com/O3DBgq2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 19:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you were a developer you would know that isnt how development works, so i highly doubt you are a developer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 23:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you must know nothing about game development, the people who make models and clothing CANT CODE AI. i dont see how this is still confusing to dumb people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 00:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i guess i just haven't decided yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 23:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes i know, i guess its an easter egg for those who catch it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 23:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i was thinking it could be a really hot desert with nothing in it or really high mountains with no desirable resources  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> fictional country map- any tips for realism? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 04:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i just now found this subreddit from Vsauce3's video:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=160GmnKOeps index=8 list=PLiyjwVB09t5xhhW0IfHke782_PqlLOxU0

and i just wanted to share a fictional map i have created and would appreciate any tips for realistic borders.

image: http://imgur.com/XG8iiSs
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 23:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cry about it until you realize nobody pitties you for being friendly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 23:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By recent do you mean the new patch released a week ago? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 23:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To clarify, yes, I was double carrying. I had a mosin on my back and the ak in my hands, when I stop in a bush to reorganize. I had forgotten I was dual carrying and drank a soda. I then realized that the ak had been lost, and I was too far away to justify going back and getting it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does this still happen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 03:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i just lost my Ak101 when it dropped near a bush, and im just wondering why this still happpens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 22:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we dont need boats as long as we have the V3S submarine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 22:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they are really only useful for distractions because they draw attention to them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 22:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i played today for 3 hours and only saw about 5-6 zombies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
