<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7133</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 01:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems legit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another relapse. Great. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 18:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 02:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here, picking/biting though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 12:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hungover and unable to detect sarcasm through reddit. Eh, I've found myself in solid rock a few times and like I said, I've been in firewater. My music taste is everything from heavy metal to 80s pop. So that's not exactly an issue.. ha..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 11:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't tend to venture into Sauchiehall street too much, been to firewater a few times but other than that I haven't been to the other clubs; I just know of them. The only thing that seems to be appealing to most people about campus is the prices. 

Might check out Victorias and the other you mentioned. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 09:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first and most appropriate use for that emoji </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 08:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I can safely say I, nor my friend have ever stolen a traffic cone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best bars/clubs on Saturday nights? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 02:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friend and I are contemplating campus tomorrow but I've heard mixed stuff about it. Any insight into it would be awesome/other recommendations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 22:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Equally as awesome. Appreciate the effort too :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 21:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome! Much appreciated :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone remove all the writing and the border? (Not by cropping the image) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 20:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Haven't cut my lower left arm since 2012, felt like sharing how it looks now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 03:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 00:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My therapist is aware, she's asked to see my arms (obviously, that was optional) if you do decide to tell them, he/she will probably ask you why you do or other questions. 

The only way they would ever have to take action was if it was endangering your life/you were threatening that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else still choose to hide scars, despite family/friends knowing and have already seen your scars? *possibly triggering* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 15:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still cut, just not anywhere they would see. But I'm curious if anyone else is the same. I don't mind in public, but if I were to see anyone I know; I'd pull down my sleeves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
