<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8771</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-11 03:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good eye! It's probably not a coincidence either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-11 02:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think aquamarine would do well also.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-11 00:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boodles, Noodlin? I especially like Noodlin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-11 00:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed he isn't. But still, that's gross..haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clarification..is that a noodle?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-11 00:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-09 16:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The clothes look really good. Nice job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Making music and making her dreams come true :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-09 05:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Road cut in Maryland showing the inside of a mountain [640x480] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-09 05:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is my kitty, Onyx :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-09 04:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-08 18:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [bending origins](http://www.fanfiction.net/s/3952682/1/Spirals_Beginning) this is a story that had an interesting idea to the origin of airbenders. There was a post here a few days ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sucks to be that guy... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-08 17:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Team Avatar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-01 19:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since in the original series there was a representative from each bending discipline, do you think Jinora might join the group at some point? So far, we have three, all we need is an airbender. Right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-29 06:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you would learn martial arts, but it would be disguised as bending. Excellent! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-26 21:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone love Ikki's response to Tarlock..always count on little kids to give an indicator of whether or not they're good. He seems like a scumbag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-26 04:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to agree with you. I think this is the case because we followed Zuko's progression as much as Aang's, but 1)Zuko went through more change personally which made him more appealing towards the end, maybe? 2) We all knew Aang would fight the Firelord; that was never a doubt. However, Zuko's fight with Azula was more uncertain throughout the series since Zuko's loyalties were in question all the time. So, it was more surprising I think when it came right down to it when it was time to fight her (not to mention satisfying to see her get her ass beat - the crazy bitch...). 3) Last thing is the personal aspect. They were brother and sister. They knew each other and had a connection through their shared past (twisted yes), but Aang and Ozai were not personally invested in their fight (yes, Aang probably was, but Ozai definitely was not).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-26 01:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wouldn't be the first time he was accused of being magical </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks to Reddit, I found these guys...this is an original song by a couple teens in North Carolina </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-25 17:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-25 16:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NOPE. NOPE NOPE NOPE.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-25 16:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tearbending... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-25 04:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is well established that Korra has negative traits thus far. I read some interviews with the creators and they said that Korra was made to be quite flawed. Obviously this will lead to some serious character development. But to answer your question I think her positive qualities are determination and passion for the safety of her friends and the preservation of bending, and her best friend is her polarbear dog..that's gotta count for something, right? While she may be going about things the wrong way right now (three episodes in), I think she has good intentions and will find the right path.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sokka's master </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-25 04:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We know that Sokka lost his sword in the final battle, but in Sokka's Master, he didn't use the whole meteorite when he made his sword, so he could have made another...right? Just speculation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-25 02:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> poor unfortunate soul... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
