<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject896</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 21:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know the lore but here is a [link](http://fallout.wikia.com/wiki/Brotherhood_of_Steel_(Midwest) ) about the MW BoS, of which I would try and be a part of, living in Missouri!:D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 21:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was their fireteam name before(assuming they become S-IV's) they would have joined SpOps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Halo ODST Cosplay (x-post from /r/Cosplay) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 21:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 09:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically, that whole team could actually come back as S-IV's. Rookie would probably be a last choice. Romeo and Dutch would be among the first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick Question about Keyboard+Controller functions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 06:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so I finally got bored of my Xbox Fallout NV so I downloaded a few mods for my PC FNV and it's already 1000x better than Xbox. Now, because I don't own a mouse, I use my Afterglow Wired 360 controller. Alot of the time before I start adventuring, I will tdm for shits and giggles. My only problem with this is, I have to unplug my controller, type it in, and the plug in my controller again. Sometimes however, the controller f***s up and I have to restart everything. I really hate forgetting to turn it on cause of my controller and then dying at an inopportune time and not having quicksaved. Anyone know a mod or how to fix?

TL;DR Is there any way to use keyboard and controller at the same time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 23:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This belongs in wtf or lolwtf haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 22:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to but you called the Forward Unto Dawn the Pillar of Autumn. Pillar went down in Halo 1 there bud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 10:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol you go /u/OpTic_Niko
I work at a small hometown game store and we sell the figurines for Used $3.50 and New varies. I generally wait for people to bring them back in or for my paycheck. And as it stands, my collection is still VERY small being only 4 characters lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 21:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Top Picture: So there I was, saving Deputy Beagle from the Bison Steve on my PC for the first time and BAM, THERES TWO OF HIM?! lol I rescued both and that was even more interesting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well this is just odd... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 21:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 21:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This honestly was the main reason I got Honest Hearts. I saw this one time on my quest to get all of the uniques and I was so excited to get it cause it was lore rich which I love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 05:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Child Killer. Just because. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 03:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **EDIT**:Because the bullet system fails for me changing this up a bit.

**1:**A USB version of the chip Chief is holding in the "Halo 5" teaser (AKA [this](http://pxlbyte.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/halo-5-1000x561.png)).

**2:**A flat-bill hat with an orange or black Mk. VI visor on the front decal area.

**3:**A keychain Monitor with light up center.

**4:**(I know its really far fetched and actually has been produced but) A lifesize Mongoose.

**5:**Nerf Battle Rifle and SMG or Nerf Energy Sword. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 03:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. I had never heard of this till now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 02:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it the first mission or the city? Some people get these confused very easy. The first mission is Dare's crash site. The first "mission" is walking around in the city. If all else fails however, you might have to delete the save. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-04 19:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be getting on later today and I have a few friends and we would be more than willing to help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-03 07:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you finish, please message me. I run /r/ODST and I'd be more than happy to add this on there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 03:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eBay or etsy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 03:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better than anything I could do. Visor center is a bit too far to left but everything else looks fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 03:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which op was it that Lucy and (I can't remember names to save my life) were the only two alive and her last words before PTVD set in where "How do you know we're not dead? Like this is an honest question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RUL/Greenskull rad Halo Giveaway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 03:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 03:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it just a random give? Whoever happens to be chosen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 19:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mid-west= NOT FUCKING MANY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 19:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can imagine the Truman would dry up or be supremely radiated but the woods around would be ingenious to hide it. I agree on the small town raiding but theres not too many small towns I think you could hit and run. I know a few 1000 pop. towns nearby but still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 18:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vault 42. Everyone would fight over glow sticks lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 18:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah! I thought about it for my state as well cause I live near (within 100 miles) of Whiteman AFB which would be a major target considering thats where ALL the Stealth Bombers come out of. But yeah, the enemy wouldn't just attack the populace cause if they forget the military, we can counter. They don't want that. So they wipe out the populace AND the military and they have it pocketed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 18:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Missouri(middle of the US) so I would probably haul ass to either Columbia, a college town no doubt infested with either chem fiends or survivalists, or to St. Louis for survival. I should go to say, St. Louis would probably be a target considering it is a symbol of American progress and freedom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 18:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With Texas having a good amount of military bases in it, It would be the target of at least 1-3 nukes. Mostly in populace centers like Houston, Austin, and San Antonio. I don't think it would have been ungodly damaged but there would be quite a dent in the main places. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 02:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Y'know, it's little things like this that I hate for making me feel stupid. I guess I never noticed the zip. In all my damn days, how I didn't notice that I will never know. Thank you! Now I can start running FNV on my laptop again.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 00:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I download it, its always in the wrong file format. I'll try again with it. And I'll check that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 00:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I HATE NVSE. Everytime I download or try using it, it never works right and its just. Arg.and I run 4 GB of RAM (3.61 Usable) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 00:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I'm sorry. I didn't realize we were having a pissing contest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can I make FoNV run faster? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 00:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so I have had New Vegas on my laptop for quite sometime but never played more than 15 minutes because it is just so ungodly slow. So, being the Fallout geniuses you are, maybe a few of you could help! General stuff about my computer: Windows 7, Dell, I also have Skyrim, Fo1, Fo2, FoBOS, Amnesia, Arma 2 OA and a few other minor games. Running no mods on the game yet.
 Any help would be wonderful! 

UPDATE: Thanks to /u/croock3 suggestion of windowed, I can run as smooth as Xbox.
Also, wouldn't run right because of wrongly installed mods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 23:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marksman Carbine and All American are perfect duo's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 23:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! lol so far it has been. My cake day isn't for another ~7 months but birthday still counts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 20:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it possibly in /r/fo3 or was it for sure here? I will start going back as far as I can!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For my birthday, I present the only good screenshot I have from Reach </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 16:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 16:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to do this! I have a clip of a double kill with spartan laser on my file share!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 07:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get more than agitated when all that litters the floors of the maps are BR's. Literally, the only thing everyone is using. I've had a few deaths I wanted to go back to check just because every shot some people had seemed to always be headshots. Watching a few, you'd swear there were aimbots(I know theres not. 1/15 shots would miss.) Either way, I can't wait till next week when it's not as big a deal that BR is everything cause next week is SWAT which I am okay with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 05:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but having parental permission isn't!:D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 08:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knocked my two long Vidmasters out of the way (Endure and Annual) and both took me 90-120 minutes which was more time then I want to admit I've spent on any video game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 08:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Mentats + Boxes](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IqbGLKUY7J4)
[Vault 13 Flask](http://www.etsy.com/listing/100397387/vault-13-fallout-flask-4oz?ref=sr_gallery_26 ga_search_query=Fallout ga_view_type=gallery ga_ship_to=US ga_search_type=all)
[Dart Gun](http://special-effects.wonderhowto.com/how-to/make-realistic-fallout-3-dart-gun-prop-384911/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fallout Props </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 07:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, me being the gigantic nerd that I am, would some of you kindly post links to how to's or buying spots for any and all props be it Nuka-Cola caps to Plasma Rifles to Super Mutant masks. I will post a few in the comments to show what I mean:) Thanks to all who help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 04:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I formally apologize now. I have honestly never seen nor experienced this but I had heard it before and was also told that it was a glitch. Sorry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 00:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, scoured some forums. Not a mod, not a reward, just a plain ol' glitch.
[Sauce](https://forums.halowaypoint.com//yaf_postsm833620_posts.aspx) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 00:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never heard of this. Now I have something to look into. I'm assuming still that it has to do with bungie day or something of those reaches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 23:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't listen to him. What /u/PseudoArab said is correct because I even have one. There was an ODST one, Halo 3, CE, and Marathon(?). You got them for, as he said, linking with Bungie. Each required something. Quite a few people still have them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 23:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UNSC. Most, If not all of the UNSC's ships were suited for battle. Now I can't talk for Star Fleet so I will let a trekker take that one for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 10:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That just has creepy written all over it. Noping out of that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 10:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you could give me samples for my sub /r/ODST that would be wonderful and I would get back to you as soon as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 09:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was before the Arbiter had turned on the Prophets. Also, before he was even the Arbiter. Most of the Covenant that were left on Reach by the time of Six's death were just there to glass and finish it off. While Six did go out with a bang, it's highly improbable he is still alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 08:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Troop4921 its in the description. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 07:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Says you don't exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 06:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I'll boost DLC doubles cause that requires the least players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 05:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think in about 15 minutes I'm jumping back on and working on DLC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 05:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I vaguely remember the MC+Cortana mission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 00:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the only training exercise I honestly remember. I mean there was the one where Kelly killed her trainer from the Reach LE packet but this was always a favorite. It goes to show that he does have a heart and wouldn't let bad befall any of his troops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
