<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject933</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 23:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you recommend any?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 05:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just was forced out of my OCD closet last week. There are plenty of people that I have not told. There are plenty of people that I will probably never tell about my OCD. 

I hid it from my family and closest friends for four years. Mainly, I thought I was schizophrenic instead of an OCD sufferer. However, I eventually found the courage to tell a friend. 

This is my advice to you: everyone does not need to know. Don't be ashamed of it, but also know that you are taking a risk if you choose to place yourself on public display for OCD. Also, know that there are people who understand. You will meet plenty of people who simply do not understand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 04:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made good money, though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 20:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry but I sold it on Ebay :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Describe your favorite shirt. Why is it your favorite shirt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 20:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite shirt is a button up shirt that is made from jean material. I got it from Levi's. It's very versatile. What about you men?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 20:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Straight flame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 20:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This website is incredible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 22:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can definitely relate to this. I have a sister and she was definitely allowed to be more emotional than myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We all know the stereotypical gender expectation that men cannot show emotion. When your parents raised you, did your parents affirm or disregard this belief? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 22:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (i.e. Did they validate or invalidate your emotions?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 21:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pee on my possessions to mark my territory. Including my wife  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 17:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See Coldplay live. See the Northern Lights. See Salar de Ayuni. Basically, there are a bunch of places I want to travel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 17:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anywhere along the inner thigh. Not even near the privates, just anywhere in the inner thigh region </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 15:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beauty and the Beast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 15:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Allowing another person to see the uglier sides of me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 16:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree. If you do not come forward with an honest answer, the other person is going to spend a significant amount of time thinking of every potential thing that could be wrong with them. The person deserves honesty if they have given you honesty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 17:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The City by the 1975 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 01:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kids by Childish Gambino  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 20:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally this. Many girls on Tinder just want attention  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 17:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had OCD for 6 years now and I just told my parents (not by choice) for the first time, last week. It really is difficult because you never know how they are going to take it. One thing that helped me was printing out some handouts from the website. OCD is really difficult to understand for someone who has no experience with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 04:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see the argument that male affection has declined among men and I think I would agree. However, I try to challenge this stereotype. I'm a heterosexual man and I will hold my guy friends hands or give them hugs. I think those gestures are signs of friendship, more than romantic relationship.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 18:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Step back and shoot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 01:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long did your OCD start before you told them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parents found out about my mental illnesses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 15:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long story short, my parents had no idea that I have OCD   Depression. I had a psychiatrist appointment yesterday and I couldn't drive myself. So, I basically had to ask my mum to take me to my psychiatrist appointment. I had no intentions of telling them, ever. 

Later that night, my parents questioned me about everything. I tried to explain it to them and they are trying to understand, but they just don't get it. 

How did you explain it to your parents? Any advice on what I could do? They blamed themselves and think it's their fault. Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I've just been outed .... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 15:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long story short, my parents had no idea that I have OCD. I had a psychiatrist appointment yesterday and I couldn't drive myself. So, I basically had to ask my mum to take me to my psychiatrist appointment. I had no intentions of telling them, ever. 

Later that night, my parents questioned me about everything. I tried to explain it to them and they are trying to understand, but they just don't get it. 

How did you explain it to your parents? Any advice on what I could do?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone tell me what Drake song this is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 18:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 01:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had similar experiences. It's definitely scrupulosity and it definitely changed my life  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 01:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was delusional for a few years of my life and I thought I was schizophrenic. Then, I was told that my intrusive thoughts were not voices. Afterwards, I was diagnosed with OCD   Depression </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 14:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As soon as you started reminding me of my dad, I knew it wasn't going to work  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 23:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This movie hits me in the heart, everytime I watch it; especially the ending.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 23:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can quote this movie like it's my job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 03:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 23/ 2.5 years with some on and off  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 02:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely forgot about For You. Dang it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 02:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the live Yellow intro was ICONIC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What songs are on your Top 10 Coldplay list? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 20:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This topic hasn't been brought up in awhile, so I would like to hear everyone's opinions. What songs would you include on your Top 10 Coldplay list? 

I had to think about this for a long time. I attempted to include some personal favorites, while simultaneously choosing all of the songs that I believe truly represent Coldplay's best work. Here are my ten: 

* 1) Strawberry Swing
* 2) Swallowed in the Sea
* 3) X Y
* 4) See You Soon
* 5) Yellow
* 6) Trouble
* 7) Amsterdam
* 8) Easy to Please
* 9) Lovers in Japan 
* 10) Charlie Brown 

Alright Coldplayers, let's hear it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 19:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Everyone I know says I'm a fool to mess with you, Everyone I know says it's a stupid thing to do. I had your love on call and yet my day was so full. And I did not know what to do, so I ran away from you."

I Ran Away was reaffirming when I ended my long term relationship.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 19:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a probably a tie between my favorite B-side: Crest of Waves   I Ran Away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 19:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to fall asleep to Warning Sign, every night  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 19:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh I understand. 

Mine is 

1) AROBTTH 
2) Parachutes
3) X Y
4) Viva
5) Ghost Stories
6) Mylo Xyloto  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 17:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the whole 7 minutes of it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 17:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes is so underrated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 17:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand your reasoning. Could I ask your rank of albums, then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 15:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll give you that actually. Ink is very childish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you rank Coldplay's albums? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 15:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This hasn't been done in a few months so let's hear it: how do you rank Coldplay's albums from best to worst? Also, what's your favorite track on each?

For me, it's 

* 1) A Rush of Blood to the Head: In My Place

* 2) Parachutes: Shiver

* 3) X Y: Swallowed in the Sea

* 4) Viva La Vida/ Death   All His Friends: Strawberry Swing

* 5) Ghost Stories: Another's Arms

* 6) Mylo Xyloto: Us Against the World </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 15:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mylo Xyloto was horrible but I strongly disagree that Ghost Stories was a horrible album. I think Ghost Stories is a more mature Coldplay. Not to say that their younger works were immature, but I think AROBTTH is full of young energy. Ghost Stories seemed as if they mellowed out a bit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 15:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I understand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 15:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drop it like it's hot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 15:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 02:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here, except make my depression worse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 01:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried anything else? Just curious  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 21:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not have girl parts but I definitely do appreciate the insight  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 21:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I was going to ask my psychiatrist if I could try Zoloft next. This is good to know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moving from Luvox </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 19:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want to switch from Luvox because of the side effects. Mainly, my sleep schedule has really been affected. Has anyone had any experience with Luvox? Any advice?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 18:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely scrupulosity  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 18:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still have this problem. I used to pee myself and as a result, I have this ritual of keeping a piece of toilet paper in my pants. If I am anywhere in public without the piece of toilet paper, I consider myself done for the day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
