<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8577</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 02:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why you don't propose to someone IN FRONT OF A FUCKING CINNABON </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 06:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that's disgusting. Holy shit. I'm really sorry and I hope you're healthy and happy, and I hope the ignorant shit who said that to you comes to see things differently someday. It's 100% not your fault and I hope you can recover from whatever trauma might have been inflicted on you. You are loved and and strong and you have this entire subreddit's support 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 05:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Created by /u/monkeytits" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 06:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently started liking [Microsoft Yi Baiti Regular's](http://imgur.com/MQLc7wy) collection of lowercase letters. I was messing around in After Effects trying to figure out how to animate text, and I used Yi Baiti's lowercase paired with Gill Sans' uppercase for any words I wanted to emphasize, and I really liked how they looked together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FWD:fwd:Good thing I didn't have GPS back then! LOL!!1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 00:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 16:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A kid in one of my classes does dip but spits it into a clear water bottle. It takes every ounce of effort not to gag audibly in the middle of class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 20:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who suffers from anxiety, I think this is probably the nicest thing I've read all day! You're a great husband for being so caring, supportive, and understanding. I often feel like my anxiety is a huge burden to the people I love because it prevents me from living fully and happily, and I worry that that's troubling to them. But you seem like a really patient person, which is exactly what a person with anxiety needs in a partner or a friend. You go, dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 17:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quote aside, the leading on this is awful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 22:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 19:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 18:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 21:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 21:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking lost it. I've been giggling at that for the past five minutes. Every time I stop giggling my mind wanders back to that sentence and I start giggling again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 00:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think that kind of behavior stems out of insecurity and shame. It's really easy to joke about your flaws to others to make it look like you don't really care </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 00:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 21:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That gets me super bummed, too :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 18:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 18:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brother once used a hockey stick to behead my favorite barbie -- it looked like [this](https://barbiebeauties.files.wordpress.com/2014/09/img_3456.jpg), except she was tan and had brown hair. Unforgivable. I cried so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 05:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'M NOT DRAMATIC YOU'RE DRAMATIC

*flicks cape around and plays an organ

But seriously though, I just really like history/ancestry. Whenever I go to a historical site that holds a lot of meaning I feel really connected to it, so I feel like this act of vandalism is more destructive than if, say, someone were to spray paint the walls of a decrepit building. There are people who dedicated their whole lives to preserving that landmark, educating people about it and the history surrounding it, and I think it's a really big shame that someone could so thoughtlessly destroy it like that. I don't blame the tour guide for nearly crying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 05:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, literally speaking, yes, that would be the climax </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 05:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BBBBBOOOOOOOOOOooooOOoOOO^oooo000^0000 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 05:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, eyebrows like that were super popular at the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 05:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This hurts my heart. That probably meant so much to so many people, and represented a really rich and strong culture's history. How could one even punish the person who did this? I honestly don't think anything could truly make up for damage that severe to something that important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 05:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goats and lambs are two separate things, I think you're thinking of the word "kid" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
