<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7930</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tip for anyone trying to hatch eggs in X/Y.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 03:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lumiose's center can be used as a never-ending walking loop if you just clip down some tweezers and leave it going. 

http://imgur.com/7aC3XDu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 15:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D: Oh, it's you! On my frontpage! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-14 11:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, what a coincidence. I just drove past your restaurant a couple days ago and was wondering what kind of pies were there. Sounds delicious. I'll definitely try it soon. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 18:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just realized.. will steam add the four copies all to my inventory if I purchase or will it automatically add one to my library and only give me 3? I already have a copy and only want one for a buddy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 18:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm willing to purchase the 4 pack if you guys are still looking for people. I only want one copy for a friend. I'm in the u.s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-09 18:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad to see that so much understanding from fellow dog people. :3 I work in a research lab and my own Jake is a study animal that I adopted out. Whenever possible, we try to adopt our animals out. If not, then they are used for training purposes. The dogs are well cared for while they are in our possession. People always tend to give some dirty looks whenever animal research is brought up, but it's easy to criticize others for doing the dirty work that is necessary for everyone else to be able to benefit from medical advances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 22:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would have been nice not to have this spoiler right in the title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-06 18:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this at Battle and Brew the other night. ^^ Nice job. It looks amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Loki decided she wanted to play too </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-16 07:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-14 04:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much for this. I've been flip-flopping about whether or not to buy Tera forever, but this pretty much sealed the deal. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
