<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4879</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 13-14 inch laptop for university 1000 dollars canada </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 03:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> need a laptop for university, as well as some work related stuff. mostly going to be used for word processing, some video/picture editing, zero gaming. Ideally the laptop would have an ssd, or at least a hybrid. I am willing to pay extra for a great keyboard/trackpad and a great screen. I really want this laptop to last 4-5 years. willing to up my budget if need be. thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> at what quality would this laptop be able to run games? (skyrim, bioshock, ect.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 03:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> would this laptop be able to run games (skyrim, bioshock ect.) moderately well? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 20:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> looking for a lightweight, long lasting computer that can also run games-13/14 inches- Canada 1000 dollars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 02:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between work and university I use my laptop a lot, and it can be quite bothersome to carry something heavy. I am looking for something lightweight, with around a 13 or 14 inch screen, solid battery life, and powerful enough components to run games. i dont game so much, but id like to be able to run skyrim, arkham games, ect, and have them looking fairly ok. thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can i join a wait list for a class i am already enrolled in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 17:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hi,

one of the classes I am currently enrolled on has alternate lecture that is at a more convenient time. this other section however, has a wait list. can I join the wait list for this other lecture, without losing my spot in my original one?

thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 02:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shia Labeouf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 01:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 22:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jagers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
