<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3422</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Betty Who - All Of You (cw remix) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 20:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 21:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know right?!  I'll keep my future kids away from the Ram Van. Back in my days we used to download RAM for FREE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 21:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The candyman is safe. Kids these days need to stay away from the Ram Van. In my day we used to download free ram.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 21:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not understand why sliding down an escalator will make you multiply. There is no woman in the picture... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 21:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here m8. [You're not the only one](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nCkpzqqog4k) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 20:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> likes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 20:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> first...... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 20:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how...... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If other male animals emit a smell to attract the female. Do women have a subconscious way of sensing testosterone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 18:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty easy to get men horny but what about women's stimulus? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disney should go back old school and make a cartoon animated movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 18:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be great for the kids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 21:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Childish Gambino - The Worst Guys](https://www.soundcloud.com/yannmasse/the-worst-guys-feat-chance-the)

[Oh Wonder - The Rain(Saje Remix)](https://www.soundcloud.com/sajeofficial/oh-wonder-the-rain) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 07:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mad of now there is no option for that. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 22:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did address the comparability improvements. I just wish I could kinda put a skin on that:( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Unpopular Opinion?] I think Fl Studio 12 is ugly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 21:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So 7 hours ago FL12 was released. I, like probably everyone else here, immediately downloaded and installed it. Unlike the most of you I did not try the beta though, for I was waiting for a stable version. Only after I had installed FL it loaded with a flat yet childish UI that I personally do not favor over FL11's. The font is a impact roundish font that is rather large at times and does not blend with the interface. FL12 looks like a toy to me. I prefer FL11's professional looks.
KUDOS TO ImageLine for adding touchpad usability. Now I can work on the go. Rarely do, but thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 23:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Just got them new. Usually never wore my old ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I listened to music so much my ears virtually did not survive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 23:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So as a 16 year old teen with rather large ears and glasses my helix tore. I LISTENED TO MUSIC SO LONG THAT MY HELIX TORE! It happened because my headphones pushed my glasses to rub and pierce the skin on my ear...that's my best audiophile story. I want to know what you guys have done concerning music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
