<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8022</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 22:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's keep this PG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 01:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is unfortunately a solid military strategy on the part of ISIS. People have seen what ISIS does to those who challenge it, so they will have little choice but to fight alongside ISIS. Now the non-extremists may no longer view the war as them against ISIS, but instead the US coalition against the people of Syria.

This is a terrible development. This is like an Arab version of Nazi Germany. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 11:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get some framed posters perhaps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 10:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on the type of flash memory used and the amount of redundant storage in addition to the flash controller. I would presume Intel used high quality flash memory in this device alongside a much more robust controller than those found on USB thumb drives. Additionally Windows 8 has the ability to run with a different memory/service profile on small storage devices to help limit the amount of writes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 03:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no way that has an mSATA controller, that alone would almost be wider than the entire device.

Instead it has expandable Micro SD card storage (and right now you can buy MicroSD cards with up to 128GB of space). Also in theory you could plug a thumb drive into the USB port (but it'd be ugly). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 02:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a lot of major earthquakes in that area historically. Including one of the largest which occurred in 1089AD:

*"William of Malmesbury writes that "all buildings were lifted up, then settled again as before", which does not indicate any damage. It is described as "very great" and "throughout England" by Roger de Hoveden."'*

http://web.archive.org/web/20110516173115/http://www.quakes.bgs.ac.uk/earthquakes/historical/historical_listing.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 02:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd really take this study with a grain of salt as they say. It only included 16 participants and it wasn't a double-blind study (the researchers knew while taking measurements which kids were in the extended swimming classes).

With so few participants it's difficult to say whether the impact of swimming was significant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 00:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not uncommon in today's world to preserve a piece of a previous structure/building if it had fallen or been destroyed in tragic circumstances. Perhaps an earthquake caused a collapse that killed many important people?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL in 1929 a group of armed men kidnapped and beat the Idaho governor. When citizens found out, nearly everyone in Northern Idaho joined in the search for the culprits. After the criminals were found, they were taken to jail, where over 1500 armed and angry citizens were waiting for them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 08:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 01:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When non-volatile storage nears both latency and bandwidth of the latest DDR* in production. Bandwidth still has a ways to go, but I could foresee it being doable at a commercial scale in the near future. Latency is an entirely different beast, and will require radical shifts from current consumer SSD tech.

Another factor is wear. RAM is nearly constantly shifted, written, and re-written. RAM doesn't degrade to any significant level with writes, whereas current flash memory used in SSDs does. So drive life is also holding today's SSDs back from threatening RAM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 01:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that Agile was originally what companies/groups did to keep things moving quickly with minimal restrictions and form. Now in large corporate environments that switched to "agile", the walls are closing in because so many rules/guidelines are being enforced as to how exactly it must function... which goes against every reason the agile approach worked so well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 00:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not currently believed to be autoimmune related. Something as absolute as saying it's definitely not an autoimmune disease may be a bit too far for a disease with so many unknowns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 04:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that's the case then it's because you allow it to happen. Naturally there is some give and take with marriage, but if you are just dating, why allow yourself to be railroaded?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 04:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work with a lot of Turks, and they are truly scared of this man and what Erdogan is turning Turkey into. When I first started working with them 5 years ago they were happy for the future of Turkey as a secular state, but now whenever they talk about visits back home they tell me how freedoms are fading away and how people now hesitate to criticize the government in public due to fear of retaliation. 

It's a sad series of events, and I too worry that Turkey may be headed towards a path of further backwards "Islamification" of the state. In 20 years we may view the state of Turkey today in the same way we view the state of Iran prior to the Islamic "revolution".   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 03:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just 20 more Facebook likes and the war is over! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 13:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that "pro-ISIS" rallies have occurred and are allowed in Europe boggles my mind. Waving an ISIS flag should be a crime of supporting terrorism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 13:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only a matter of time before Muslim extremists provoke violent responses from masses of people without direct state support. When that moment comes things are going to get really intense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 10:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless I don't think that calls for name calling. You could have just downvoted the post without the insult towards the OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 08:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing is beyond our reach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 03:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oil consumption is beginning to slow down across the world, yet more advanced/complex extraction methods are making more oil reserves available for refining/production. Most oil producing countries are still using older extraction methods, so if they shift to methods like fracking they can get even bigger 'slices of the pie'.

The US is also now the largest oil producer as well as one of the largest consumers. The US is extremely stable, so there is less likelihood of major shortages due to political/military events. This smooths the volatility of the developed world's oil supply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 02:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a long term investment I'd suggest putting funds into BP or Chevron stocks. They normally rise and fall with consumer demand and prices, and in the long term such low oil prices cannot last forever... There is bound to be a disturbance, or eventual supply shortage that causes prices to rise.

Additionally these companies are also working on alternative energy investments, so if the price of oil stays low for a long time they will likely boost their R D and alternative energy production and the stocks may increase inversely with oil prices down the road.

I'm waiting until oil gets towards $30, then I'm going to dump a lot of money into these stocks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 02:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how economical such factories would be... I think they'd pretty much require initial state funding to even become slightly competitive when run by private parties. 

This is cool stuff regardless though, and I could see this LED based 'factory' tech eventually making its way to isolated villages or remote research stations such as those on Antarctica. But another major hurdle to overcome is that many of the places with food shortages also have power shortages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 10:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was preparing to be really really impressed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indeed's "Boxcar: A self-balancing distributed services protocol" slides   video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 07:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High level overview of Twitter's new Tweet Index project </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 07:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> General engineering overview for Netflix's new telemetry platform "Atlas" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 07:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> StackExchange System Architecture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 07:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 04:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does form count for extra points? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 03:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh for sure. It wasn't meant to be a blanket statement.

But that link you provided is about how Russia refused to share space technology with China's space program? That seems to provide further evidence of how many states are well aware and afraid of China's strong tendency to steal engineering plans for their own production. China is smart, and it's a great way for them to advance. But it certainly makes potential state partners very wary of working with the Chinese on anything cutting edge.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 03:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a bit different though right? In the case of Russian spacecraft the US government was paying the Russian's for launch services, or the engines were being purchased directly from Russia. China in many cases will simply copy foreign tech after obtaining details specifications and engineering details via espionage, which is much less civil in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 03:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being cold in general also lowers the body's immune response does it not?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 02:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who has autism and has read countless research papers on the subject, screw that anti-vaccine group. I wish we could somehow temporarily teleport them to the 1940s or 1950s. I imagine if they had their siblings, friends, and other relatives dying around them due to polio they'd change their tune pretty quick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 13:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakthroughs in reconnaissance satellites could definitely make their way into civilian life.

It's a lot of money for the key hole program, but I think aerial/satellite surveillance programs are good investments for preventing more costly conflicts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL each new US spy satellite under the "Key Hole" program is expected to cost more than the latest Nimitz-class aircraft carriers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 12:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 09:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all. But comparing a country's recent actions to another country's actions that took place long ago isn't a fair comparison when it fails to take into account the significantly different geopolitical atmosphere.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 05:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in the lifetime of anyone still alive today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 02:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would burn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 01:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! This was very to the point and now I'm definitely leaning towards 20% down over paying in cash.

Interestingly a few people have PMed me too with some other things swaying my decision. Mainly that if I use most of my funds in buying a house, I lose a lot of liquidity and may have to sell the house and pay rent again anyway if something unexpected sidelines me from earning an income through the workforce for a couple of years. Whereas if I have a mortgage, I still am sitting on considerable investments that could be partially cashed to weather unforeseen emergencies.

Thank you again! And to the others who offered advice =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 01:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the last few years my returns on investments have averaged out to around 20%, but the market is still rebounding from the 2008 recession so I don't expect I'll see such high returns in the coming years. Historically it seems the stock market has been averaging a 6-7% yearly return, so that is what I'm anticipating for the future.

My expected interest for the mortgage is currently around 5% (I have 1 percentage point added on due to having no credit history).

The purpose for buying the house is simply as a place to live and unwind. A place I can call my own, instead of being at the mercy of a landlord. I am not buying the house itself for investment purposes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have investments (mostly stocks) worth ~$300k and want to buy a ~$500k house... Should I wait several years and pay for a house in full to avoid any debt/mortgage, or does it make more financial sense to buy it now with a 20% down payment and leave the remaining money in my investments? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 00:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like the idea of not having any monthly housing costs outside of taxes/insurance/maintenance by buying a house in full. Right now I'm paying $2,300 per month in rent, so having that extra $25,000+ in my bank account each year by buying in full would be significant. However after looking at 'interest tables' for my current investments and average historical market returns I see that over time the compounding interest on those investments can lead to values **significantly** greater than the cost of a mortgage on a $500k house over 30 years.

I'm 28 yrs old and I've never been in debt. Previously I thought buying everything in full was the best approach. Now I'm not so sure. An advice would be very much appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 08:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So basically it's like going back to the old west, minus all the violence and disease =O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 04:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interestingly because guns are so prevalent so is the value of learning gun safety in communities. Gun violence in Idaho is relatively rare considering how many people own guns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 03:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A great way to get IP information for usernames (being people will likely check their username first). Granted I'm sure it's less sinister, but the potential for some intelligence collection is definitely there. =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 22:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idaho is one of the most armed states in the US. It has the county with the highest gun ownership. Almost everyone has a gun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 04:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of flavors too! Kiwi is very popular and delicious. Lemon or Grapefruit are usually despised. For a while there was even a 'sparkling energy drink', but it seems to have gotten pulled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 03:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Second, it is expensive and there is no reason for farmers to adopt these farming techniques as they are more expensive.

Perhaps in less developed countries, but in developed countries like the US, no-till drills like air seeders are becoming very desirable and cost effective. Mostly due to reduced fuel and labor/time costs by removing the need for plowing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I'm getting the recommended amount of daily exercise, but doing it all in one continuous 'session' (say an hour at the end of each day), do the major health benefits still apply if I'm sedentary the rest of the day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 02:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 11:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Apocalypse Now - Ride of the Valkyries](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GKaYOW9zMoY)

Also... pretty much anything in Watchmen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 10:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a dinner just like all the others, except this time it was filled with an aurora of hatred only known to one of the participants. Wally stared across the table at Clint, hoping for some flickering indication of regret of humanity. Wally and Clint had been meeting at this diner for the last 10 years. Best friends since grade school they enjoyed each others company even in silence But that was before Before Wally found out Clint was sleeping with Wallys wife, Bonnie. That was before.

Wally had spent the previous night restless, pacing back and forth contemplating his next move. Occasionally he would glance up at the shotgun hanging on the wall. A shotgun handed down to him through several generations of his family. There it hung, so peaceful, so tranquil. He grabbed it off the wall and went out on the porch. He made up his mind, his beautiful wife was everything, and Clint had taken her from him, so he was going to take Clints breath with the shotgun that lay on his lap. 
But then as Wally sat there, the sun began to rise, casting shades of orange hues across the crisp morning sky. This is beautiful. Clint said to himself. Thinking perhaps there was more beauty in the world to behold Wally walked back into his living room, and hung the shotgun back above the mantle. 

Back at the dinner, Wally wondered if he had made the right decision in sparing Clints life, in carrying on as though nothing had ever happened. He only wished there was some indication of regret on the part of Clint for his betrayal, yet he saw none. So deep within his own thoughts, Wally barely noticed at first the fly that landed upon the table beside his soup. But then it became his focus. This creature, so small, yet so intricate without any worries in the world... 

Look out Clint exclaimed as he eyed the fly and reached for a newspaper resting on the table. No, Wally calmly said as Clint raised the newspaper above the fly. Dont do it. Why, its only a fly? Clint asked. No replied Wally. Its beautiful.  The newspaper smacked down hard against the table. Other diners turned to see what the commotion was about. Then they saw the dead fly and returned to their own lives.

Wally finished his dinner with Clint, without another word spoken. As usual he paid his portion of the bill, and then Wally sauntered out of the diner and drove back to his house. He sat a moment in his idling car, and watched the wind blow across the tall autumn grass. He turned the ignition off, opened his door, and walked into his living room, and lifted the shotgun off the wall... 

--------------------------------

**Note:** Be gentle as this is my first WP. Integrating **first degree** (premeditated versus 'in the moment') murder into a story was an interesting constraint.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 10:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ, this country almost looks like it is on its way to an all out race war. The tension keeps rising and eventually we'll probably start seeing revenge killings on both sides. So sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 11:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has gotta be a remake/model of an original artifact. The base looks modern and there is no way such an ancient artifact would be stood up like that in such an uncontrolled environment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 10:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's difficult to comprehend just how fast and insanely awesome this aircraft is. At its top speed it is traveling over 3x the speed of a bullet leaving the barrel of a typical hunting rifle, or about the same speed as a bullet leaving the barrel of an M16. That's fast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 07:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems to me like it's actually on the decline. I'm in the engineering sector and it's actually "cool" to work in a smart/nerdy field again, and young people are striving for knowledge and education like never before. 

Just look how many people stood up against SOPA and other similar attempts to cull/regulate free information and media. To me that's an intellectual fight, and young people are fully behind it.

I can totally see anti-intellectualism taking hold in older generations, but thanks to the internet and the awareness it provides to young people. I think the future for intellectuals in the US is brighter than ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 07:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really hoping for a Netflix streaming release. It could forever alter how movies are released in the future.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 06:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 04:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's trying to entice you over to touch the forbidden fruit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 04:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who has magically disappeared? 

The only questionable death I'm aware of in recent years is that reporter who died in a car crash after working on leak stories. Even that is very inconclusive.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 03:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When say a rapist is caught, tried, and thrown in prison, that's prevention against future crime. By your logic we should just release all violent prisoners because the cops made things worse by reigning them in. Genius.

Looking at your history I see you're mental and probably want to kill cops too. Get a life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 03:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I hate to break it to you, but if thugs break into your house you won't be able to defend yourself with a keyboard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 03:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes because cops obviously don't help society or people in need... You're an absolute idiot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 09:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's like telling people not to use Facebook and it's easy because they just have to get all there friends to switch too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US restores diplomatic ties with Cuba </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 02:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opponent calls for Putin's exit as Russia slides into crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 02:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some North Korean related websites/interests that may be worthwhile targets for retaliation against recent hacking and threats? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 02:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 01:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Commander sir? There is magic outside of my window again." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 12:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty easy, and it happens and is even broadcast across media on a higher level. All of that support going to the FSA and opposition groups in Syria is partly because they are ruthlessly attacking the bigger enemies like ISIS. Somewhere in Syria there is probably an intelligence agent overseeing "rebels" torturing and killing ISIS members. The thing is... I don't feel too bad for them. People probably felt the same way during the Vietnam war.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 03:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or is it half-side up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US approves future lethal military aid packages to Ukraine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 02:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> United States approves future lethal military aid to Ukraine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 02:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 01:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually no more than a foot in my region. Below that you can sometimes see goldfish swimming around (people dumped goldfish in some of the mountain ponds and amazingly they survived). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crimean leader in India with Putin as India states Russia is it's most important defense partner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 01:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 09:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ice freezes like this in the mountain ponds where I'm from when the wind is extremely calm or non-existent, and the temperature is relatively consistent between day and night (say 21F in the day and 15F at night).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 22:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. Thanks Bud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 07:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can definitely vouch for the black area in central Washington state. There is a town there called Othello that is basically like Mexico. I stopped there this year while travelling and went to a Burger King, and none of the people inside working knew English and everyone was speaking Spanish. I tried to order something in English and got a confused look, and then told them the number I was trying to order and they still didn't understand. That's when a lady nearby stepped in and told them in Spanish, and then they figured it out... It amazes me that a franchise like Burger King doesn't require customer facing workers know English.

After that little bizarre event I drove around town out of curiosity and a lot of the signs were in Spanish as well, and I didn't see a single non-hispanic white outside of the gas station. It was like I was in the twilight zone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 02:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't we just photoshop it closer and save NASA billions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chechen militants attack Grozny, shattering peace as Putin gives speech. Putin blames forces 'abroad' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 02:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 10:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like neuromytonia and stress, which go hand in hand. You should stop googling ALS symptoms and start a health tracking journal. Also I would suggest asking your MD to test for ganglionic achr antibodies. If you have them you can take the immune therapy route and may be cured by spontaneous remission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 04:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this was /r/science, not /r/politics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 07:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Because I'm tired of looking at them down here." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 06:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sponsored by Autism perhaps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 03:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have to be in an organization to help guide it and interact with it. If I provided as little as $200k for equipment and operational costs, did you think they were going to ignore me?

It works the same way for the government. If someone were to give a senator a multi-million dollar donation, that senator then has a responsibility to look out for his/her donation supplier. If she or he does not, then they should not accept the donations in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 17:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are crazies in most forums. I'm not in the organization but I've funneled some funds that way, and the contacts I have had made some great guarantees when it comes to keeping the active members sane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 02:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can almost "hear" the silence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 01:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As depressing as the reports may be, I still have pretty high confidence that a solution will be found when things start getting really chaotic. If all the governments of the UN came together and set up an insanely massive reward for the first organization/government/corporation that can create a scalable CO2 scrubber, I think we'd stand a much better chance.

There aren't that many resources working on CO2 scrubbing technologies, because there is currently not enough economic incentive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 23:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yes I was absolutely making a generalization, but one I still believe to be accurate. As a generalization it certainly doesn't apply to all cases, such as yours and even mine to some degree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 07:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sample size is incredibly small for this study (20 people) so I'd take it with a grain of salt. The other thing I wonder about is whether the researchers provided a work space to the participants (ie: a job specific to the study), or whether the participants were monitored in their real-world work environment. If it's the latter, the study might be polluted by the work hierarchy. In my office building for example, I can tell you the successful people are more likely to have window offices and be less stressed because they generally aren't doing the frustrating "low level work". The lower level workers are more likely to have window-less offices and be more stressed... so I have a feeling if you moved those workers into similar workspaces, you'd still have distinct groups when it came to cortisol/stress levels, regardless of whether they had windows.

**Edit:** I'm not questioning the well known relation between sunlight and mood... Only the methods used in this study and their concluded level of impact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 22:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not accessible via the internet in the browser sense, but for my private projects where I don't want to use VSO/GIT and still want to access them remotely, I just do so via Remote Desktop. It could be a similar option for you if you are using Windows clients. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
