<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6188</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The head of a new organisation set up to tackle international wildlife crime syndicates has vowed to bring down the Al Capones behind the 86bn global trade in commodities from rhino horn to tuna. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and username mentions too, right /u/carmabound!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German FM Frank-Walter Steinmeier has proposed EU border assistance for Tunisia to curb militant movement. The proposal is said to be backed by the UK and France. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian intolerance of gay people and same-sex marriages has grown significantly in the last decade, state-run pollster VTsIOM said Friday. Eighty percent of Russians said they were against same-sex marriages, as opposed to 59 percent in 2005. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't we all:~( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 65-year-old man appeared in court Saturday in connection with a case in which a man had been kissing women and running away in Barrhaven. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 01:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 01:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to be awesome:

"He says the new lands will increase the parks boundaries by 36 per cent, to 79.5 square kilometres once fully established, making it one of the largest urban parks in North America  19 times larger than Stanley Park in Vancouver and 22 times larger than Central Park in New York City." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prime Minister Stephen Harper says the federal government will more than double its initial contribution to Rouge National Urban Park. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 01:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 01:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this happens, this will be a sweet piece of land:

"He says the new lands will increase the parks boundaries by 36 per cent, to 79.5 square kilometres once fully established, making it one of the largest urban parks in North America  19 times larger than Stanley Park in Vancouver and 22 times larger than Central Park in New York City." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prime Minister Stephen Harper says the federal government will more than double its initial contribution to Rouge National Urban Park. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 01:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Farming, not oil, should be Canadas future focus as temperatures rise, economist says. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 01:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 01:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they're more than welcome to join in:~)

*By the way, are you going through Carma withdrawals yet?!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone likes to watch it happen! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 18:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And smells nice too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for a_jaxx </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 18:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 18:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a great feeling! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S.-Canada dairy spat sours trade talks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 17:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 17:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I packed my bags and bought myself a ticket

For the land of the tall palm tree

Aloha Old Milwaukee, Hello Waikiki

I just stepped down from the airplane

When I heard her say,

"Waka waka nuka licka, waka waka nuka licka

Would you like a lei? Eh?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Change is in the air: Lets Talk Dirty In Hawaiian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 17:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawmakers from Japan and South Korea took part in a friendship exchange program featuring the board game of go in Seoul on Saturday, the first such bilateral event in 11 years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 17:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anaheim mayor gets into deep political waters in clash over Disney tax break. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 17:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Community Discussion: Will the world do enough to save the climate? Nations are finally pledging to cut emissions, but only the result is only confusion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 17:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hello, Mayor Robertson? Its Pope Francis calling from The Vatican... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 17:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for gbxvfzc </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 17:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for mingram92 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for heritagehealthcarein </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for TGJKUA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for hopenorthfoods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for garagedoorseo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for manikiran1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for shirin7384 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seven months later, Hawaii fishing rules still not signed: Gov. David Ige is continuing to review rules approved by the DLNR last year that would create the states first Community-Based Subsistence Fishing Area. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exposure to two chemicals widely considered safeand used in hundreds of consumer products including plastics, cosmetics, and soaphas been linked to increased blood pressure, insulin resistance, and other dangerous health problems in children, according to a new study. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chester broke the Internet's heart: An elderly, terminally ill rescue dog who was adopted in the final moments of his life, was treated to a bucket list of dream doggy activities and was followed by more than 78,000 Facebook fans, has died of cancer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice officials in Ivory Coast have indicted about 20 members of army that helped bring President Alassane Ouattara to power during the post-election conflict in 2011: First time president's military allies have been charged for alleged crimes committed during fighting that claimed thousands. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A difficult, intoxicating fight for those taming raging fires: Stakes are high as B.C.s wildfire season grows longer and more destructive. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadas environment minister is reviewing a letter from philanthropist Jim Balsillie raising concerns over misleading information presented in a CBC documentary about the Franklin expedition. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Singapore's waste disposal needs get a boost: With the completion of the Phase II development of Semakau Landfill, Singapore now has the capacity to meet waste disposal needs for the next 20 years and beyond. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Singapore's waste disposal needs get a boost: With the completion of the Phase II development of Semakau Landfill, Singapore now has the capacity to meet waste disposal needs for the next 20 years and beyond. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A recently created supervisory body in Panama will seek to better monitor business sectors generally used by money launderers when they are unable to exploit the financial system. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stay safe all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 10:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why ask why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for FJEKEEW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 10:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A group of aquariums on July 9 shelved plans to establish an organization that would bypass a ban on buying wild dolphins caught in drive hunts in Taiji, Wakayama Prefecture. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 03:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Health and social services agencies reported Friday that 334 people who live or lived in a seniors residence in eastern Montreal will be reimbursed for irregular charges. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 03:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'I need answers': Mother of Toronto teen girl shot dead speaks out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 03:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Criticism against Nestl is picking up momentum once again as drought plagues B.C., wildfires rage in parts of the south coast, and residents are facing water restrictions. Nestl Waters Canada bottles roughly 265 million litres of water from B.C. every year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 03:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what exactly is in the air that we breathe? We can't see them, but the air that we breathe contains a wealth of biological particles which could damage our health. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 03:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The window for limiting climate change to 2C at a feasible economic cost is rapidly closing, but science is the basis for finding the right solutions. That's the conclusion of the Our Common Future under Climate Change conference in Paris this week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 03:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indian marijuana mega-farm taken down by feds: Both federal and state law enforcement officials raided Native American land occupied by two tribes in Modoc County on Wednesday, seizing at least 12,000 cannabis plants and more than 100 pounds of fully-processed marijuana. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Japanese government will set up a joint council of public and private sector parties by end of this fiscal year to develop and utilize technologies for the Internet of Things: will call on more than 100 companies and groups, including major automakers, telecommunications and electronics firms. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> F n': First African team at Tour de France since the 1950s wants rider thrown out for alleged racial abuse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am proud of how brown my lawn is': In Vancouver lawn battle, every drop is judged. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am proud of how brown my lawn is': In Vancouver lawn battle, every drop is judged. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indian marijuana mega-farm taken down by feds: Both federal and state law enforcement officials raided Native American land occupied by two tribes in Modoc County on Wednesday, seizing at least 12,000 cannabis plants and more than 100 pounds of fully-processed marijuana. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than half of the wastewater from fracked oil wells in California is disposed of in open, unlined pits and could contaminate groundwater, according to a state-mandated study of hydraulic fracturing issued Thursday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Geological Survey, in collaboration with the U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service, has released a study that will enable ecologists, managers, policy makers, and industry to predict the bird fatalities at a wind facility prior to it being constructed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Akons ambitious plan to bring electricity to Africa with solar energy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The co-owner of a Gatineau-based skydiving company said it appears there were problems with the way a parachute deployed on Wednesday during an accident that left an instructor and student seriously injured. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The unemployment picture in Canada remained virtually unchanged in June, with the jobless rate holding steady at 6.8 per cent and gains in full-time jobs being slightly offset by losses in part-time employment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 14:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of line is that?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 08:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Go fuck yourself sandiego

Where the fuck is Carmen, Sandiego? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 08:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good idea, but beware, the spuds have eyes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 08:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never leave your gums uncared for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Link between gum disease, Alzheimers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 08:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it me or is there not enough... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 08:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...sub Reddit drama around these daze? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 07:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be more than willing to help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 07:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might surprise me. Every time I've been back, we've pretty much stayed in Town, so I've yet to see this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 06:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought we both agreed to stop drinking, HR!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 06:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing makes me happier than hearing this song and knowing that I'm pau hana! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for prometheus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 06:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for RandU43 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 06:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 06:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Maybe not the right conditions for jumping Spitting Caves

As a flatlander who used to rent a room out in Portlock, there were *never* the right conditions for me to jump there.

I've been swimming off the rocks, but I kinda feel like I'd snap my neck if I ever tried to dive in from up there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australian law enforcement and intelligence services have been in secret talks with an Italian-based surveillance company notorious for helping repressive states like Sudan spy on their own citizens, according to leaked emails published by Wikileaks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 06:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calgary Stampede disqualifies tie-down roper for mistreatment of livestock. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 06:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Representatives from 22 provinces, states, and other regions across the Americas signed a climate action statement aimed at cutting greenhouse gas emissions and developing clean energy in Toronto today at the Climate Summit of the Americas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 06:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Representatives from 22 provinces, states, and other regions across the Americas signed a climate action statement aimed at cutting greenhouse gas emissions and developing clean energy in Toronto today at the Climate Summit of the Americas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 06:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers from across the globe recently teamed up to accomplish what might seem like an impossible (and scary) task: counting as many of the ocean's sharks as possible. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 06:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Volcanoes cooled Earth in the past, constrain warming from excess CO2: A study more precisely detailing how volcanoes affected climate in the past sheds light on how much CO2 will change climate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 06:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 05:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Even mediocre breakfast/brunch places have long lines.

Yeah, I used to like the "Early Riser Special" at Eggs 'n' Things because it used to be dirt cheap and if you went early enough, you missed the lines. 

They're even in Japan now and I'll never understand why people here think pancakes are a Hawaiian "thing." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coming back next month, so what do you think has changed the most in the last 10 years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really earth shattering news, but I'll be moving back to Honolulu after bouncing back and forth between Oahu and Tokyo for pretty much the last 10 years.

As you all know, there's a big difference between living on Oahu and just popping back...so what do you think has changed the most in the last 10 years?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was also [Hawaii Winter Baseball](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hawaii_Winter_Baseball) that started back in the 90's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C'mon.

Be honest.

It's because I'm coming back next month, isn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for GreatGuitarShop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for gaique </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for Sahin14 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for Golam724A </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for avislease123 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for massivelab </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for gjgklkjl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for Crisburgos7 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for DickensSanomi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for buystdtestkit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for MohamedFarag </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for Wald_Real_Estate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for odon362 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for amazoniphone6 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for Lilydawordsmith </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, it's only 9am-ish here and I've got quite the busy day. One good thing though, it's kinda cloudy-sunny here and that's awesome 'cause I haven't seen the sun for what seems like months! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Aloha Friday, no work till Monday! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.N. announces humanitarian truce in Yemen as of Friday: announcement came eight days after U.N. declared Yemen a level-3 humanitarian emergency, the highest on its scale, with nearly half of the country's regions facing a food crisis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Latinos outnumber non-Hispanic whites in California, according to the most recent figures released by the Census Bureau showing that in July 2014 there were 15 million Hispanics in the state compared with 14.9 million non-Hispanic whites. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Court hears KKK's bid to have name on highway: A civil rights group is suing on behalf of the Klan chapter as it seeks to join an Adopt-a-Highway scheme in Georgia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 01:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSW Education Minister Adrian Piccoli has proposed banning international students from Ultimo Primary School to accommodate rising enrolments in inner-Sydney, while similar bans could be placed on students at seven other schools in the city. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 01:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A water district has sued Tom Selleck, claiming the star of the crime shows "Magnum, P.I." and "Blue Bloods" stole truckloads of water from a public hydrant and brought it to his ranch in drought-stricken California. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 01:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teen who swatted Disneyland sentenced to 16 months in custody: Teen whose hoax shut Disneyland's Space Mountain warned by judge to not lead 'life of a loser'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 01:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teen who swatted Disneyland sentenced to 16 months in custody: B.C. Teen whose hoax shut Disneyland's Space Mountain warned by judge to not lead 'life of a loser'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 01:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ottawa police have arrested and charged a woman after a video posted to Facebook showed a gang-sexual attack on one woman. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 01:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Energy companies are making a strategic mistake and could waste billions of dollars of investment by thinking they are immune to climate policy, says IEA chief economist Fatih Birol. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 01:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A contractor clearing land on Virginia Key to make way for the Miami International Boat Show is responsible for the illegal removal of protected mangroves, Miami administrators said Thursday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 01:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we on a 24 hour countdown till your cruise yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 19:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank yov? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 19:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm no legal and human rights expert, but *I* want to know how a Winnipeg girl could have been impregnated by her stepfather twice and had two abortions before she was 13, yet not have been deemed a victim of sexual assault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 19:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's got such a great little body... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 19:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please join us! Let's make it a threesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
