<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1529</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Saudi-led coalition carrying out airstrikes in Yemen has probably used cluster bombs, which are banned by over 100 countries, the international monitoring group Human Rights Watch (HRW) said on Sunday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 01:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudi-led campaign drops US-made cluster bombs on Yemen rebels: HRW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 01:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 23:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Latin American countries are culturally similar to the U.S.? Have you visited either place...?

Also, you've completely forgotten how many asian immigrants we take in on the West Coast.

Stop making uneducated excuses for your ill-informed xenophobia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 04:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you hate me, /u/PrettyIceCube?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington State Auditor Troy Kelley pleaded not guilty Thursday to federal charges of filing false tax returns, attempted obstruction and possession of stolen property. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 01:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An international team of researchers led by the University of Alberta used MRI video to determine what happens inside finger joints to cause the distinctive popping sounds heard when cracking knuckles. For the first time, they observed that the cause is a cavity forming rapidly inside the joint. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 01:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seattle Is Helping Drug Addicts Instead of Locking Them Up  and So Far Its Working </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 01:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seattle Is Helping Drug Addicts Instead of Locking Them Up  and So Far Its Working </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 01:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least five people have died in a wave of violence against foreigners in Durban, South Africa, while thousands more were driven out of their homes in the coastal city ... in the commercial hub of Johannesburg, immigrant shopkeepers fearing copycat attacks have closed their businesses. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 01:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first F-35 jets ready for combat wont be able to protect forces in ground combat as well as the nearly 40-year-old A-10s the Pentagon wants to retire, according to the Defense Departments chief weapons tester. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first F-35 jets ready for combat wont be able to protect forces in ground combat as well as the nearly 40-year-old A-10s the Pentagon wants to retire, according to the Defense Departments chief weapons tester. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Asking people to explain their reasoning is the best way to soften their strongly-clenched belief and win the argument." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 21:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Undocumented Immigrants Pay Billions in Taxes to Fund Programs Theyre Banned From Using </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 21:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 00:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm very much surprised there hasn't been a shoutout to /r/forearmporn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 07:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, there've also been actual cuts to higher ed. In my state, the portion of tuition that was covered by the state has flipped from 66% to 33% in a few years. Meanwhile, we have more students and therefore a need for more bureaucracy.

We can settle for less and argue all we want about who gets the scraps, but the fact is we *need* to raise state funding generally. Both admin and faculty need to get paid, not one or the other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why wasn't Italy a great power at the time of WWI? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 20:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm reading "The First World War and the International Power System" by Paul Kennedy, and he uses several tables and a short paragraph to summarize some of the basic causes of Italy's shitty performance during WWI; its industrial incapability, it's lack of economic power, etc. I'm wondering why Italy was so industrially incompetent and economically weak in the first place, despite having the historical power of the Vatican and having famous traders and explorers, and having such strong allies? Also why it militarily did not perform very well, but that's probably related to the answer to the question above. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 01:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't it be UPS? Brown shirt and all... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The White House is removing a federal regulation that subjects its Office of Administration to the Freedom of Information Act, making official a policy under Presidents Bush and Obama to reject requests for records to that office. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 23:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is attractiveness objective or subjective? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 20:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did Portugal go from being a colonial empire to Western Europe's poorest country? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 19:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll just bet it has something to do with those meddling British and their dumb Navy, but I really have to clue! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edward Snowden, the fugitive whistleblower who has been given refuge in Russia, is willing to return to the United States if he is given a fair trial, his lawyer said Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 18:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The US militarys top-ranking officer has called for Washington to arm Ukraine in its battle with pro-Russian forces, saying he favours doing so through Nato. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 18:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The US militarys top-ranking officer has called for Washington to arm Ukraine in its battle with pro-Russian forces, saying he favours doing so through Nato. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 18:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Justice Department has cleared a Ferguson, Mo., police officer of civil rights violations in the shooting of Michael Brown, a black teenager whose death set off racially charged and sometimes violent protests last year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 18:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraqi Campaign to Drive ISIS From Tikrit Reveals Tensions With U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 18:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The European Union will need radical new policies to reach goals for safeguarding the environment by 2050 after limited progress in curbing pollution and climate change, the European Environment Agency (EEA) said on Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 18:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greece could need a third bailout deal when its current program expires in June because markets may still not be prepared to lend to its government, even with a euro-area credit line, European Commission Vice President Valdis Dombrovskis said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United Nations says the number of people killed in eastern Ukraine since fighting broke out in April now tops 6,000 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venezuela on Monday ordered the U.S. embassy in Caracas to reduce staff from 100 to 17 amid the worst diplomatic flare-up between the two ideological foes since socialist President Nicolas Maduro was elected in 2013. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> S Secretary of State John Kerry on Monday delivered a vigorous defense of Israel before the UN Human Rights Council, urging its members to end what the United States says is its unfair and biased focus on the Jewish State that could undermine its credibility. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 22:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand why this reply from an expert is not being upvoted more than Dr. Amateur up there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington police shoot and kill man throwing rocks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 21:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A rookie New York City police officer was charged with second-degree manslaughter and five other offenses on Wednesday for the fatal shooting of an unarmed man in a dark stairwell of a housing project last November. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 00:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its Hard To Know Where Gluten Sensitivity Stops And The Placebo Effect Begins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 00:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Live Nation exploits low-wage workers to stage its rock concerts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 23:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Puerto Ricos controversial proposal would fine the parents of obese children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 23:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One quote that shows how the media covers mass shootings differently based on race </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 22:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One quote that shows how the media covers mass shootings differently based on race </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 22:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new report from the Federal Reserve Bank of New York sends a more sobering message to millennials: Your first 10 years in the labor market likely shape your lifetime earning potential. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 22:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new report from the Federal Reserve Bank of New York sends a more sobering message to millennials: Your first 10 years in the labor market likely shape your lifetime earning potential. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 22:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas governor removes protections for LGBT employees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 19:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a dramatic show of defiance toward the federal judiciary, Chief Justice Roy S. Moore of the Alabama Supreme Court on Sunday night ordered the states probate judges not to issue marriage licenses to gay couples on Monday, the day same-sex marriages were expected to begin here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 19:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Myth Behind Defensive Gun Ownership: Guns are more likely to do harm than good. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 21:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 08:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And marvel underwear!! Wonder who's on them ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 09:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if I told you...it doesn't matter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 23:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Another* Jobs biopic? Ugh...

But yes to Michael. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 02:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit is: totally avoiding the point for the sake of feeling important by correcting technicalities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 06:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The basic premise that you're communicating is something I agree with, but you could maybe not be an asshole about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 07:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just ran a half marathon on a whim?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 21:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I mean yeah, but certainly the cunts over at /r/worldnews can be a bit cuntier than most, let's not throw ourselves all in their boat.

Edit: although I did use the word "cunt" twice in that sentence, so...maybe I do kind of suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 19:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So did you enjoy it? I haven't read it yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 05:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HEY EVERYBODY!! THIS GUY'S GIVING OUT FREE KARMA FOR ZOOLANDER REFERENCES!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 21:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, from time to time Disney does some fucked up shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
