<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9731</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 10:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm confused on this one..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 10:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You matter to me buddy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 10:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 10:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you strap yourself in and feel the g's? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 10:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not seeing this as a link to your username you've chosen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 10:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indians did 7/11..

FTFY. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your username - Why? How did it come about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 10:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your username is probably used in countless other places on the interweb, how did you choose this alias? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 12:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without even checking the sub, I read that in the accent as soon as I seen the title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 11:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a club with minimal members buddy. 

I'm there with membership as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 02:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a guy, I've been with many girls and so far I'm on a solid 0.

Same thing as anal.. Damn porn, lied to me again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 01:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I checked the profile to see how long its been in action for.. I've never been so scared to look at someone's profile before.

The fact that its a gay guy just made it even more unsettling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 13:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What song is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 23:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sunny D and Rum? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 23:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much of a muchness really, when you're trained to fight in a street scenario it's never about death, it's always based around defusing the situation and making sure you're not in danger anymore. 

This can be by walking away from it, or if you really do need to fight, it's about disabling your attacker as quickly as possible, then walking away.

You're taught which spots can kill, and these are generally the ones you avoid.

Source: Am 30 now, and been training on and off since I was 7 in 3 types of martial arts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 21:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate..

Poor bloke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 14:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paddlin' the school canoe?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 14:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to put my feet up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 13:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sign me up buddy, happy to write full length reviews for you to post as well.

Edit: confirmation email doesn't send.. Haven't received anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 13:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's his story? / was his story.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 10:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beat me to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 22:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the fuck am I on Brain detail?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 22:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It exists.. /r/showerthoughts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 22:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep.. Went really sweaty and cold at the same time.. Next thing I was on the ground breathing heavily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 22:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No Timmy, unfortunately people like this are real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 22:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need a head in your skull!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 13:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All jokes aside, I actually like Dr Pepper.. Shit is rare as hens teeth in Aus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 13:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you go 

Extreme Cheapskates S03E03: http://youtu.be/ho0D7pGJRg4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1 more.. How to treat m'Lady like a gentle-sir. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 13:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 12:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must be new to this guy.. Watch his video about saving a ladies eggs. 

The closest he'll ever get to eggs and a woman in the same sentence.

Edit: here it is.. Enjoy..

 Her Eggs Made Me Feel Like Batman: http://youtu.be/OF2P-hLAZZ4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 12:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He looks like a thimble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 12:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is drinks other than mountain dew? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He's back again.. Magic is all between 0-2min. Rest in peace Menord Neroy, Leroy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 12:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 02:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL.. 

I'm exempt, I'm one of those pains in the ass that resists, so they've let me keep my iPhone 6.

The Nexus 6 is my personal, so I look like a drug dealer with 2 phones everywhere I go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 20:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well.. My work is now pushing windows phones to everyone instead of blackberry as we have now merged over to Exchange and Outlook.

Gone from a shit phone to another shit phone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 19:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats mate, mines coming up on the 6th.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 19:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean by full screen mode? I'm pretty sure it does have it mate,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 19:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had no idea that its an official Reddit app. 

It always crashes when you're trying to edit a comment you've already posted. 

I've found myself picking up my droid device to fix up the spelling errors I did with my ios device. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 19:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will do mate, thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 19:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nexus 6 / 9 type larger screens? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 10:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say "what does the fox say" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 10:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And regrets it - Steve Ballmer on His Biggest Regret (Oct. 21, 2014) | Charlie Rose: http://youtu.be/v9d3wp2sGPI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 10:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having to sync with a PC was another downfall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 10:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use both Android and iOS, alien blue is a heap of shit. Constantly crashes.

Reddit is Fun for Android is probably the best one I've tried. 


Edit: I have the PAID version of Reddit is fun. Supposedly no one buys android apps....
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 06:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the unknown subreddits, I reckon Reddit has probably created a few serial killers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 00:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of gives a new meaning to /r/eyebleach though.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 13:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm as close to being a 5 year old mentally as you can get.. The first 2 paragraphs nailed it perfectly. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 12:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Animals itch for a variety of reasons. This annoying sensation can becausedby dry skin, skin irritation, dirty skin, insect bites, disease, parasites such as lice, or even forpsychosomaticreasons. Researchers believe this sensation came about as a way of teaching us to avoid irritants and preserve the skins health.

Scientists have made progress in identifying neurotransmitters responsible for causing the itching impulses in the brain, a team from the National Institute of Health has been able to identify which of those factors is primarily responsible for driving the sensation. The research was led by Michael Iadarola of the NIHs Department of Perioperative Medicine and the paper has been made open access in the journalMolecular Pain.

Itching is believed to be caused by gastrin releasing peptide (GRP), natriuritic precursor peptide B (NPPB), and neuromedin B (NMB). A study published inSciencein May 2013 identified a significant part of the pathway that NPPBwhich is produced in the heartuses to trigger the itching sensation in mice. The authors of that paper worked on Iadarolas team to make quantitative measurements about the potential role each neuropeptide plays in causing itching.

The current study used a technique called RNA Sequencing (RNA-Seq) to identify where and in what quantity the itch-causing neuropeptides were being expressed in mice, rats, and humans. The results supported the previous study inSciencethat implicated NPPB as a primary cause of itchingat least in mice. As it turns out, rats and humans dont express NPPB in their sensory ganglia. However, all of the tested species expressed NPPA, which acts on the same peptide receptor as NPPB.

NMB was expressed in high levels at sensory ganglia across all three species, hinting that it has been evolutionarily conserved. The results also showed that GRP was not expressed in any of the three species, refuting the long-held notion that it plays a role in producing itching. The misidentification likely came from interactions between anti-GRP antibodies and NMB in the sensory ganglia. This could mean that previous studies based on GRPs supposed role in itching need to be reevaluated.

While scratching acute itches can bereally, really satisfying, certain conditions can trigger the desire to scratch excessively, which can break the skin and haveserious consequences. Understanding the pathway involved in causing the itch sensation would allow researchers to potentially create a way to block those molecules. If the pathway could be altered, it could be used as a treatment and bring significant relief to those suffering from psoriasis, eczema, and other chronic skin conditions.

www.iflscience.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 11:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect for those who lung hit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 11:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope you're ok..

Usually the story goes "if it wasn't for that pole, he/she would still be alive" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 11:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If melb holds a vape convention, I'd fly down for it.

Melb does shit way better than Sydney does.

I was at Steam today when they were discussing attendance at the meet.. They weren't taking anything or doing anything apart from just hanging out.

I don't want free shit etc, but a meet like they have in the US would be awesome.. Something along the lines of a convention. 

With a convention you get to see what people are doing, products that you weren't aware of etc.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 23:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is especially true if your box is running batteries in serial </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 14:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly is this meet?

Will there be anything interesting going on with suppliers etc, or just a bunch of peanuts vaping away in a beer garden? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 09:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to hear mate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 10:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that this is your personal favourite, meaning there is more of his antics to report on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 08:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chinese new year celebrations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 13:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I picked one up last week for $49 from steam e cigs.. Brilliant little unit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 06:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being bald and reviewing balding cures.

Losing my hair at 19+ made me an expert in all the crack pot and medical remedies out there.

Here's the Jazz people, nothing works except for implants.

So get get that razor sharpened and join the dome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 07:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Macedonian and other eastern European languages we have a similar concept.

Directly translated the term is 'babied', as in, the words used are given a slight twist to make them 'cute' and baby like.

E.g -  and  (sock and err.. Socky?) "Where are your sockies" .. Hope this makes sense  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 07:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't concentrate on the finger, or you'll lose all that heavenly glory... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 21:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On Fasttech there are hundreds.

I'm using the Lite version 3.1.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 07:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It shrinks?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 07:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That episode is one of my favourites </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 21:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as it might upset some people, grab a Kayfun Lite from Fasttech, clone or not, I have 2 of them and there is no difference to my real one apart from being 1/10th of the price </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 01:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took what out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 00:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My George isn't clever enough to hatch a scheme like this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 21:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They called Cartwright, no one answered so she hung up. 

Who's Cartwright?

I'm Cartwright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 21:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coco! Hi five. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 21:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But where does the meat go?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 14:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, it's just like a normal salad.. But bigger! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 10:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might have custom protection, but there are only so many cell manufacturers..

I want to open my 30w up and put in a VTC instead  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 10:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What battery brand do you use in the istick 30w? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 09:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was bald Jerry, BALD!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 09:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were floating.. But they were out there Jerry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No topic, just the best one liners you love! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 07:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a 40, now I'm a 42, I'm huge Jerry!


Just let them rip people! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 07:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their should've been a mango in the picture somewhere! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 07:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol - NUT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 03:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got to agree here.. It's just a huge nexus 5. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 13:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is on its way.. With the logo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 13:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate, I'll pass.

Not a massive fan of nut flavours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 12:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you based and what do these flavours actually taste like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 21:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought my Nexus 6 because my Nexus 5 was doing this constantly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 21:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give google a call and see what they say.  Might be worth a shot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 20:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call him Gammy!   (Gammy's getting UPSET!!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 20:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please, from now on call me T-Bone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 20:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at the gym and I saw him.. He 'was huge'  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 20:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry mate, I received it as a an MMS ,  saved it and shared it.. No manipulation of it from my end </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 08:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is a sexy fellow, can't believe Hallmark haven't invested in him for Valentines day cards yet.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 07:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure that burnt cock breath will be worth it.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 07:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I had sex.. With your wife!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 50 Shades of George </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 07:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 21:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Walky has to be one of my most favorite cars. I had to watch the gif twice because I missed the prank the first time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 08:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just went from the n5 to the n6 solely for the camera.. Definitely not disappointed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 10:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate, never read anything so boring yet interesting at the same time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 10:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm guessing you all have it memorised? Seems painful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 08:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All ya'll Muricans' - what the hell is a social security number and what does this club membership get you?

I'm gathering your birth is registered as it is in most other countries, although from what I gather, you're given a SS number, when and how is this number used in life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 23:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a great video. Your voice is so well suited to tutorials as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 23:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like big bird from sesame Street </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 06:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> XXXX Summer Bright 

I hate beer, but this beer goes down so easy.

Now, just to kill the arguments, Yes its a 'girls beer', I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 00:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry mate I didn't finish it until 10pm last night Aus time, 

Its now day time and I'll add a few more pics  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 23:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black Honda Accord Euro / Acura TSX.

Used Nu Finish scratch doctor, then the once a year protection they sell.

Scratch doctor was ok, but not as good as hoped for the bonnet, previous owner had tree sap on it and it's permanently ingrained in the clear, I might try Meguires Ultimate Compound on it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 23:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate! No idea it existed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 12:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6 hours later and it's done. Love how the car and the fence outside blend in together.

2010 Honda Accord Euro / Acura TSX for my US friends  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
