<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9909</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 20:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My reply:

 That is quite a quandary. Opportunity breeding decisions. You can save local businesses by reserving eggs for them or you can use the money to invest in people who follow your model (I know you aren't interested in personally expanding). Either of those takes people coming to you and being honest with their finances and goals - and you have to be sure of their honesty and integrity. I think you will be able to do both by riding the wave for people and places which do not come to you for help (or do not warrant it), but letting some partake reduced prices. The only sour point there is those who see a double standard or are turned away not be humble enough to understand. If that seems insurmountable, take the money and invest it in more farms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polyface Farm - From Joel Salatin | On price increases for eggs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 20:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 17:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about letting people flair blog posts. I just linked one and thought that might be a good idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A good post about the living history town of Sovereign Hill, and looking back on what some modern components of a town came from. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 17:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 06:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tonsil? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 04:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might even say he was... [jammed](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HXKOsajNZY4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 04:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And saws... or hammers... or whatever the hells... Cow tools, y'know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 00:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roomy, [ain't it?](http://stream1.gifsoup.com/view6/3347201/so-much-room-for-activities-o.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 23:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [go, team](http://i2.kym-cdn.com/entries/icons/original/000/013/034/yeahsciencebitch.PNG) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 23:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tastes fine, stop bleeding from your ear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 23:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever try orange juice? Got that one from my grandpa in law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 23:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It said the studies did 3 days, but I don't think it said anything about other lengths or schemes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 22:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like there are air bubbles trapped under a thin film of egg white.

very cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You Get What You Pave For | A look at how one spread out southern city has problems funding utilities. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 21:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The article](http://theind.com/article-20971-You-Get-What-You-Pave-For.html) says taxpayers can expect to pay much more in taxes each year, or the city has to find another solution.

[Strong Towns](http://www.strongtowns.org/) is spearheading this kind of wake-up for towns and cities. The suburbs have not paid for themselves in taxes, it turns out.

Any fun stories about moving to a town before you found out it was in trouble? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 20:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is living and then there is delaying death, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the process an allergic human immune system goes through to eliminate proteins? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 19:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 17:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True.

People eat so much protein at one time that trying something new might mean consuming more that first time than they might on a HC diet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 17:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen Tomorrowland, yet, but I can wonder why there are no bathroom cleaners. Automation relieved society of the need for that particular menial task.

Automation currently removes the demand for jobs like airline receptionists and secretaries, people who just punch tickets and register information. A user interface and networked customer information system automated 95% of the job, so we can do the last 5% by typing in some info and swiping our card. There is still demand because a human touch is still more agile than a human's code.

It isn't like people are pre-destined to be low-skilled workers (not that I think anyone thinks that, anymore). Automation can also make it easier to live independently for people who might fall into those tasks today and the many that did, previously. People both fall into those tasks and life is not made easier through automation for various reasons which we may not entirely disagree on.

Did the movie preclude that in some way? Were there renegade air conditioning specialists? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 17:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How rude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 17:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why didn't you text post these and link this page at the bottom? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You Get What You Pave For | Southern town learns how underfunded utilities are after decades of low-density growth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 13:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 05:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  QSEL

 ENTER

repeat

*sigh* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 05:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not yelling at you or making fun of you or anything, but you know that your comment happens to construct a straw man argument, yeah? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 05:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was that interview from back when Texas was trying to get the Tesla factory in state? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> State, Youre Just the Worst | BadCatholic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 22:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 21:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/NgETaLY.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you get the Civ Eng file and the layer "Any thing else" highlights half the drawing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 21:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 20:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I crazy to think Barclays would make more money in the end by purchasing the watershed above this land and re-greening it on a budget? The value and water catchment in ten years will be worth more than a bunch of empty, unsold, houses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 19:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://forums.catholic.com/showthread.php?t=578046

Looks like no. Fallible yet sometimes binding in that it expands or cements the understanding of a topic through logic, being a work of philosophy or theology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pontifical Spin Cycle | On the upcoming environmental encyclical </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do people say glucose is the preferred energy for the body? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 04:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mean this definition?

 a system of cultivation intended to maintain permanent agriculture or horticulture by relying on renewable resources and a self-sustaining ecosystem.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 04:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough, but that is as hippy-dippy as it gets.

People who engage with this design ethic have increased quality and profits at the same time. Joel Salatin has a well-known example of an extremely successful operation. Mark Shepard documented how he was raking in cash while his plow and corporate seed monoculture neighbors were suffering. There is a good example of an orchard which bucked the norm and did a few things: stopped spraying, diversified cultivars, and increased biodiversity in the orchard; this orchard was a hobby until he did this and it turned a profit. This isn't some get rich quick thing, these are prominent examples which took years to figure out the pieces and fit them together correctly. I can link you to short youtube videos which pertain to each of the mentioned people.

[Here's a big compendium I have](https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLLISQy9l1YUlDY19LDABGMC4I4qjhR4pV) - and a [headliner playlist](https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLLISQy9l1YUkScuUq0l6qUov7tj8Vmt8I)

edit: fixed headliner link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 03:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was watching and I noticed that they haven't stopped consuming, they just compact the inert waste.

The sustainability some people desire (like Paul Wheaton of Wheaton Labs) is to make the supply train as responsible as possible. This prevents permanent contaminants even coming onto the property. He's practical, but he has a goal to not even have synthetic paints and gasoline vehicles at the first circle of habitation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 03:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certainly are an interesting bunch. Ted has spent an awful lot of time thinking, that is evident. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 02:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agriculture has the etymology agri+culture. Agri meaning sky (as in, open fields); culture meaning exactly what we think. Since this is a movement which has found plowing (widely considered a sign of civilization) as detrimental to perpetual habitation, the founders thought a direct challenge and contrast was fitting. Hence perma was substituted for agri. Perma meaning just what you'd expect. All they mean is that this is a design ethic which is meant to find the best way to create a permanent, non-cyclic and non-self-destructive, way of enabling human settlement and life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 02:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think the author refers to the people that founded the movement by name; he mentions Bill Mollison. If you read the article again, you'll see the most astute permaculturists insist that the market is a part of life.

Permaculture is just like applying the ideas of human action to each part of an endeavor. "What behaviors, inputs, and outputs does a chicken have?" Then you give it what it needs and use its behaviors and outputs to their best use. Chickens are omnivores and scratch the dirt, so many systems elect to run cows over pasture and follow with chickens. The chickens eat flies for protein and spread the manure. They also eat different greens that grow in the meadow.

Permaculture is a design system, not a lifestyle or save the planet cult.

If you want to know more, let me know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 02:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One tap no, two taps yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 01:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see him in there, but he ain't movin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 21:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even he has skeletons in closets, and his are under-age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 21:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So he is saying that the government collecting money is not violence, but that money will go to private hands instead of somehow the government doing everything internally down to mining the raw ore and farming is violence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Permaculture, Strong Towns, and American Libertarianism are three of my interests which are intersecting in this article.

From what I know of permaculturists, many are mostly anti-political rather than anti-liberty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Myth of Self Reliance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree.

Permaculture, Strong Towns/ Lean Urbanism/ New Urbanism, and American Libertarianism are three of my interests which are intersecting in this article.

The idea of a responsible supply chain is very interesting. It recognizes externalities of various kinds, empowering journalists and academics to monitor the modern goods and services and supports paying the costs up front which would otherwise be deferred to pollution or human strife.

Come to think of it, /r/keto also intersects, here, because if Allan Savory and Dr. Peter Attia are both right there is a very obvious solution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 18:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woohoo! More Shriners in tiny cars! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 18:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The secret is, we ruined all our beaches a hundred years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 18:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what I like about a parade? Hearing the drums of the band getting closer and closer. The brass and cymbals coming into range and slowly getting more clear. The sound of a band coming changes if you are in a small town, or near a park or pond, or nestled in the canyon of a city center's skyscrapers. The echo and reverberation can confuse the distance. Then the band comes around the corner and you hear the real power of a marching band.

I enjoy the sight and smell of old cars, hot rods, firetrucks, and military surplus rolling down the street. I enjoy seeing the community and trade groups because they show the vibrancy of a town. I enjoy seeing the Shriners race miniature cars to delight children. I'm not a fan of having children ride floats in parades - it isn't where the children want.

You know what I didn't like about a parade, once? I walked in front of the Macy's Day Parade one year and being in NYC before and after the parade was the worst part, everything else was ok. The Macy's freight elevator was filthy (if you haven't been in the belly of an American city, you don't know what I mean) and we were accosted by the unfortunate mentally handicapped who are homeless on the streets.

A parade is a hopeful thing when done right, but it is easy to do wrong. I don't like watching the Macy's Day Parade because it is done wrong. It isn't personable and it isn't for the person on the street. You can't televise a parade - not the real parades. How long can a parade really be?

People don't like parades because some parades are done wrong. Keep it short. One band in front, one near the back. Have marshals to keep the pace; don't rely on stopping and starting. Only kids who are directly involved should be in the parade; no idle wavers, even in float contests. Idle wavers subtract from the audience. The last piece in a parade should always be obvious, and possibly traditional. Cities still have to keep it short and should consider neighborhood or district parades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 17:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You never know *which* tree will grow to be 1000yrs old. Most of them are specimens from forests which grew for thousands of years before the seed from that tree even fell, making a perfect habitat for the future giant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 23:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop. My jaw can only drop so low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 23:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good piece of advice goes:

 Successful people do everyone else's job, too.

This works in most job environments, but doesn't in customer service. *How can you be a good customer so the customer doesn't have to be?*

Isn't that part of product development?

New corollary:

 Successful people do not work in jobs where they cannot perform everyone else's job, too.

Don't work in customer service unless you are fine with no internal advancement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 23:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a difference between Republicans and Democrats you'd like to defend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 22:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sure.

Anyway, in government, management has problems dealing with corruption so the effect would be limited. There is quite a bit of bureaucracy surrounding firing and disciplining government employees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 22:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Because some prospective parents want capable, well-heeled children to add to their family rather than the presumably Annie-type ragdoll basket cases you see coming out of private orphanages.

no imagination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 22:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One previous post which was about the rash ended with OP discovering a macadamia nut allergy. Keto rash looks exactly like when I eat coconut protein (I have to use refined coconut oil - which is a shame because I love the taste!).

Red and slightly puffy, itchy but forgettable, and lasts for weeks. Seems to appear above the diaphram and below or between the pectoral muscles/ adipose deposits. All in all not fun, but I can't say that is what you are experienceing for sure and I have not found a way to end the reaction faster. I also have no idea what a protein allergy can do to your kidneys, if anything.

I can tell you that I survive instances without cortisol because if there is one thing I hate more than an itch it is a smelly, sticky undershirt.

Check your recent diet for new types of dietary proteins you may have eaten. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 22:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wouldn't be impossible to turn that into a nice place to live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 22:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you need to modify that to "*survivable without continued investment.*" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 22:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would rather have my pay up front than promised. That is the trade-off.

Do you think I mean keep the pay the same and take away the benefits? One of the best solutions for healthcare is to end plans tied to employers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 22:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, so you are agreeing with me when I said:

 Well, it might help bad management if they hired someone who would fix the internal issues instead of begging for more cash to throw away.

Cool. Sorry, I thought since you were making the same argument I was you were making another argument. But mine wasn't terribly clear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 21:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A failure is to offer benefits in the first place, regardless whether public or private. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 21:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please, explain how adding money reduces corruption in government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 21:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm not going to write five pages, single-spaced for us to be on the same page so I suppose I'll settle for head trauma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 20:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much complaint over what seems to be a fluid situation, with even the Conservative party agreeing on some faults though not the overall idea of privatization. If one considers the action of privatization a government action (this one certainly was) it can be said the same level of success has been seen as is normally achieved in any other government program. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 19:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   This is the case across the globe.

Only because if any private company pops up it either has to attach itself to government money, serve a segment not able to get government support, or die.

How can anyone compete with endless money, and why would you improve once you get that money? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 19:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can imagine how we have no idea how great security services could be if the sector didn't have to compete with the endless pockets of government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 19:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The take-away from that should be that those companies don't need subsidies. You should look and see who owns the roads, too (government). So let's say almost all methods of major transport accept government money.

Why are we doing that? There are myriad reasons we are in this state, but the effect is to make travel less expensive for the less wealthy because taxes are progressive, right?

Two things to say to that: some people think the tax structure isn't progressive enough and these companies have made their services more expensive because once you get into the pen the trough of government money overfloes.

Cut off the money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 18:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And? If the government is going to do that, then it doesn't deserve to have control of the assets. That is how I treat all government powers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 18:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might call that a failure.

We gonna start evading the Amtrak issue now that I brought up the post office? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 18:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   it is clear that privatization leads to slack rather than efficiency.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 18:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The post office is rather well run.

Sometimes it doesn't matter how well run something is if it fills the demand poorly and I hesitate to call it well run at the deficits it carries yeat-to-year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 17:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't say "close it down and tear up the tracks." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 17:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're just making claims without evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 17:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People wonder what is eating America out from the inside? Infrastructure costs being unresolved by local taxes. Developers not building mixed, truly walkable, communities. Government not giving up on owning something when it fails (post office, Amtrak, etc.).

Amtrak was a corporate bailout from the start. We don't want bailouts, right? So it was a bad decision to begin with!

Now we've got this company that America treats like a toy train set. Grow up.

ninjaedit: I'm not saying "grow up" to /u/crackron </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 17:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giving Amtrack more money doesn't solve passenger trains using the same tracks as cargo, road-level crossings, corruption and overpaid workers, or bad management.

Well, it might help bad management if they hired someone who would fix the internal issues instead of begging for more cash to throw away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you admire America, or do you LOVE HER? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 04:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 02:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However there are cultural aspects and subgroups which are "shitty."

Pickpockets, actual ghettos, and institutionalized corruption and misogyny. These exist - not to say they are always prevalent.

Edited confusing sentence structure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 02:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title legislation itself doesn't care, but the surrounding advisors and succession legislation does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 23:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ######UNDERLINEDLIVESMATTER </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 22:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is complementary legislation which has been set up in states as a mandated prerequisite for Common Core standards federal funding. There is no device usage requirements, but publishers sell counties and states on new and expensive crap all the time, you think they can't sell that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 22:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I don't want them to do it without my express permission, not the permission of my elected or unelected government officials. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 22:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you mean "actively pursue joy through LEGO."

Nobody doesn't like LEGO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 21:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This confirms everything I've ever been told about Marines by my Army friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 21:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your friend must read the Washington Examiner.

[Black is an ideology, not a color.](http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/article/2564146) According to "a study." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 21:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm, am CVS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 20:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Step 5: Profit?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 20:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is terrifying.

Killer whales can be terrifying by themselves. This is terrifying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 19:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better off than me, I haven't seen anything like that in a decade. Last place I saw it was in a ditch near a place my younger brother had soccer practice. Now I know its genus and I had always wondered what plant it is, so thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 19:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> irritating? Infuriating.

Maybe we need a vent subreddit /r/likeitsmyjobtoo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 18:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessarily, unless you can tell by the seed pod. [The whole genus Impatiens](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Impatiens) exhibits that behavior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 17:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My biggest complaint is schools collect data "anonymously" but the companies have access to the list that attaches identities to "anonymous" personal identification numbers.

Data collection is better in aggregate, but certainly not by individual child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 17:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teachers should be involved enough, smart enough, and not over-burdened enough to give feedback to the companies. If they want to put out books students can access via secure app on private computers and devices for homework, that would be fine. Then they could fix errors and typos without reprinting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 17:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a structure called a [*garconniere*](http://en.wiktionary.org/wiki/gar%C3%A7onni%C3%A8re). I know it from southern plantations. Young boys where given a separate structure or semi-detached wing to live in. The most interesting I have seen is a [stone gazebo with a second story.](http://m1.i.pbase.com/u17/septembermorn/upload/42282801.HH_garconierre.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 17:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It won't be tied to 2015, but the owners might be. People hang onto crap houses because of demo costs and sentiment way to much, imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 15:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does that race have rules about not being able to officially retract candidacy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 14:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Homeless man looks on at incoming competition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 14:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahead of her walking past one, explain your situation and tell him to ask how she is. Then when he does you say she lost her job and we can barely make rent. Make sure beforehand the guy will say something like "You need this more than me" or "Take care of yourself before you take care of others."

If she cares about these people so much, maybe she will listen to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 14:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [wiki page for Dust Bowl](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dust_Bowl) supports this view. I think one of the more accessible (and short) works which gives more detail is [*Dirt: Erosion of Civilizations*](http://smile.amazon.com/Dirt-Civilizations-David-R-Montgomery-ebook/dp/B007V2D4JO) by David R. Montgomery.

If there had been record rains instead of record drought, the dirt would have washed away. Just like Boston received red snow, the floods would have been red with soil. Montgomery has good information on how early American farming practices caused massive gullies in the Carolinas and northern Georgia around the time of the Civil War. Thankfully, the seed drill and cover cropping has resolved the most extreme negative effects of agriculture on soil. - it is still odd to think that the plow has probably killed more people than the sword through instgating droughts, floods, and famines.

Montgomery has a few lectures on youtube. In at least one, [he includes material left out of the printed book because it was too data-centric for the intended audience.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sQACN-XiqHU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 14:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you want ads where your kid is picking up new influences and ideas?

There are good places for ads and bad places for ads.

^^^Which ^^^is ^^^my ^^^second ^^^biggest ^^^complaint ^^^against ^^^common ^^^core, ^^^which ^^^would ^^^eventually ^^^have ^^^children ^^^using ^^^electronic ^^^devices ^^^owned ^^^by ^^^the ^^^school. ^^^These ^^^devices ^^^would ^^^send ^^^back ^^^usage ^^^info ^^^to ^^^publishing ^^^companies. ^^^Then, ^^^tailored ^^^ads ^^^would ^^^be ^^^made ^^^automatically ^^^when ^^^that ^^^info ^^^is ^^^sold ^^^to ^^^other ^^^companies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 02:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm mostly commenting to read later, but I'm really sure the reason is that the fine soil being held together by plains grasses blew the hell away after being plowed by new steel plows and tractors.

Edit: As expected, they didn't discount the human mismanagement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 22:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> precisely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 21:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is where somebody makes a GIF of Craig getting 00 status by killing Jar Jar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 20:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, how the hell were you downvoted.

Second, The title is certainly a spoiler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 16:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/Hammocks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 16:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it this kind or did it have spreader bars and did you recline strait in the hammock along the ropes or diagonally? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 14:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  People try to say stuff like "it needs to be privatized", but they seem to miss the big picture. The US's infrastructure is simply not conductive toward two forms of ground transportation.

Putting on my amateur urban planning cap, I will agree with your second sentence.

However, car transport is bankrupting America. Small towns and cities alike cannot impose the taxes necessary to provide adequate upkeep for suburbia's low- density sprawl. It is taking a long time to make people realize this (mostly because they haven't needed to care). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 14:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, we'd have to use an even cooler word. It would go right along with "incarnate," "consubstantial," and such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 05:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It s a shame state-run eminent domain has made a bad precedent for private rail companies looking to add extra lines and high-speed options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 05:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, seriously, some people have reported that their 4pm drop in awareness and energy is avoided on the Keto diet. The thinking is that since the body is not running on carbs there are no blood sugar waves. The liver can generate glucose for the brain (and some other organs) but it does not usually do this outside ketogenisis. Having the liver generate brain food on demand smooths out the swings.

I have a hard time staying awake all day even with distributed meals (in a sedentary job), so this is something I want to try some day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 05:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not excited. We have no way to control what might happen if the convention proceeds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 03:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definately misremembered that. Sorry. I was on mobile and shot a quick reply.

[Their webpage states the situation](http://drakesbayoyster.com/)

It also links to a Newsweek article which exposes the data falsification the NPS engaged in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 18:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, those scientists and land managers just lost a case against them concerning an oystering company they put out of business by falsifying records. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NPS Ecological Mismanagement at Point Reyes: By Design? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [National Park Service] Ecological Mismanagement at Point Reyes: By Design? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article is not the original, but I was unable to locate the original on the West Marin Citizen website. There seems to be no way to access the article from [archives](http://westmarincitizen.com/2015/04/), [search by author](http://westmarincitizen.com/?s=sarah+rolph), or [tag](http://westmarincitizen.com/tag/elk/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [National Park Service] Ecological Mismanagement at Point Reyes: By Design? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [We all know what needs to be said.](http://i.imgur.com/ihF13ie.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 14:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is where you were supposed to say mountain *climber* goats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 03:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Like this?](http://i.imgur.com/1RuhJQ9.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 03:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Some recent posts here ave been good. Duany was in the Carolinas, recently.](http://www.reddit.com/r/urbanplanning/search?q=duany sort=new restrict_sr=on t=all)

[There is a website.](http://leanurbanism.org/)

[I find this to be a very level-headed group which respects the same things and has good goals.](http://www.strongtowns.org/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 19:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  At least I haven't crossposted between here and /r/kotor[1] yet.

Although I can't imagine what you would post right now, I think I would upvote that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Andres Duany has kind of had a turn of heart on New Urbanism - since being one of the founding designers! He now touts Lean Urbanism.

The difference is how change is brought on. NU used political structures and developer relationships to modify sections of the built environment (or build them from scratch, more often); LU tries to fix existing areas (not precluding redevelopment) by relaxing and eliminating regulatory and zoning ordinances. There isn't supposed to be a difference in community involvement, but instead of the process in NU being driven by the town or city, in LU it is driven by developers big and small. the idea is to set up a system of [guidelines](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jl0hMfqNQ-g) which everyone can use to build a cohesive and healthy town or city rather than the NU way of master-planning everything. The small business owner isn't squished quite as much this way and the process becomes an opportunity for good design and planning principles to take over in a town or city, rather than political squabbling and cronyism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 00:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only do that when [I think people](http://www.reddit.com/r/maryland/comments/34z4mb/crazy_maryland_laws_youve_probably_violated/) would want to [read up on it.](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatCheapAndHealthy/comments/1xprd7/20_cheap_hearthealthy_dinner_ideas_under_3/cfdquj7?context=3) Since it is a bunch of bland language it didn't seem worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Canadian work safety PSA 

[I don't know why you reminded me of this gem.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q-lDtCHFmvg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 22:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was this, by chance, a *fist* argument? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 22:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as our bartenders are from Taiwan

Ah, a secret republican hideout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 22:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An article suggestion: [link](http://www.libertarianism.org/publications/essays/how-laissez-faire-made-sweden-rich) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 21:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, pray tell, is a twoonie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't even need to let him into the really cool labs. He could be placed in a more basic, less secure, research office. SHEILD can't do all the work in-house, the cost benefit of covers and parking don't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is more to the story of clean clothes, namely, why they are [dirty.](https://mises.org/library/why-everything-dirtier) 

I've used TSP in my whites for months, now, and am very pleased. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 13:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Y'all are being so polite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 22:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ingenious, if depressingly off-camera. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 22:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Permaculture definitely is a massively-libertarian/anarchist movement in disguise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Wound in West Baltimore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 22:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Wound in West Baltimore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 22:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 22:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "... while you're here, you wouldn't mind putting a few rounds through the tach just to be safe, would you?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Governor Larry Hogan To Sign "Uber Bill" and "Tesla Bill." Removing resistance at state level for transportation networking and direct to consumer car sales. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 22:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 21:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the people in the system for gasoline and diesel vehicles would have a fit - or, rather, a bigger one than they already will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 21:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The list of hobbies my aunt and uncle have i slonger than my list of interests. A pair of pharmacists in New Jersey... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 21:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without a band or ribbon around the cap, a felt hat may stretch. I found blanks from a company I like (though pricey, you can choose a head size, it may have a larger brim, and you can get actual customer service from them) and from Amazon.

* [Jas. Townsend and Son, Inc.](http://jas-townsend.com/standard-wool-felt-blank-unlined-p-249.html)

* [Random secondary seller. Many similar options.](http://smile.amazon.com/Fashion-Vintage-Bowler-Fedora-Floppy/dp/B00JJJLTTE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 21:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you really want to do sugarcane and like permaculture, figure out a way to make sugarcane grow in healthy competition with some helpful plants and animals. Then find a location where you can try this out for some time while making money doing other things. Once you get it right, buy your land and work hard!

But I don't know anything about sugarcane. I may be the plant won't tolerate the methods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
