<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9503</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Banks Win Mortgage Fraud Settlement, Borrowers Lose | "The $8.5 billion and other settlements are not comparable to the trillions of dollars in wealth sucked from communities." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 18:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AIG Investors Break the World Record for Arrogance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 18:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even a Military Judge Recognizes What Many Progressives Deny: Bradley Manning Was Mistreated | The ruling is but the latest repudiation of claims from Obama supporters that Manning was treated fairly and justly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 18:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How To Make Trillions Of Dollars | You will have to be unusual. I hope you already are. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 01:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first word in mangled meanings | You have to appreciate that the milestones we have set in these swim lanes provide a road map for this flow chart. When we get to toll gates, well assess where you sit in the waterfall... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 22:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Hoax of Entitlement Reform | Two possibilities that entitlement reformers rarely if ever suggest, but are the only fair alternatives: raising the ceiling on income subject to Social Security taxes (in 2013 that ceiling is $113,700), and means-testing benefits so wealthy retirees receive less. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 18:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tax Avoidance On the Rise: It's Twice the Amount of Social Security and Medicare | The system of loopholes and deductions is a statement by the rich that they don't have to pay for their lopsided share of benefits. If tax avoidance is legal it's because the people with money have redefined 'legal.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 18:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Years in Solitary, an Austere Life as Uruguays President | If there is any country in South America where a president can drive a Beetle and get by without a large entourage of bodyguards, it might be Uruguay, which consistently ranks among the regions least corrupt and unequal nations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 01:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let your security blanket slip | Our woes have their roots in security-chasing to begin with: politicians wanting to feel safe, bankers wanting to feel safe, voters wanting to feel safe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 01:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Profits over your dead body | Health regulatory and advocacy groups are deliberately corrupted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-05 21:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guns and Drugs: We Can Curb Gun Violence by Ending the War on Drugs | What should truly alarm us about guns in America is the banality of the drug-war-fueled violence that enforces profound racial, economic and social divides.  Were all endangered by laws that erode humanity instead of securing it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-05 18:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Save Social Security: Paul Krugman for Treasury Secretary | We need a Treasury Secretary who can stand up to Wall Street, not a Treasury Secretary chosen by Wall Street. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-05 18:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why We Wont Stop Mass Killings: We Like Them Too Much | A couple of dozen people died, and their friends and families will never be the same. But on the other side of the ledger, hundreds of millions of people around the world spent a few hours wallowing in some wonderful emotions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-05 08:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats Inside Americas Banks? | First, there must be a straightforward standard of disclosure: describe risks in commonsense terms that an investor can understand. Second, there must be a real risk of punishment for bank executives who mislead investors, or otherwise perpetrate fraud and abuse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 20:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Truth Behind the Fiscal Cliffs Reality TV Show | Bush tax rates beat Clinton's. Nobody in Washington cares about deficits. Corporate welfare is sacrosanct. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 18:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Schools Used To Be Better | Authorities in Michigan require a kindergarten teacher to give more than 27,000 grades or marks to her 4- and 5-year-olds. That number, evenly distributed over the school year, would require her to take a data-related action every two minutes of every school day! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 17:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Delhi Gang-Rape: Look Westward in Disgust | In Delhi 625 women are raped in a year. Yet in England and Wales, which has a population about 3.5 times that of Delhi, we find a figure for recorded rapes of women that is proportionately four times larger: 9,509. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 17:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I Fell in Love with a Schizophrenic | No doubt there's a lot of hard work ahead, for both of us. But you know what? I never saw anything in this life that was worth a damn that didn't involve hard work. The idea is not to shun the hard work but to embrace it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-01 18:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deficits Were On Purpose To Cause This Crisis | Bush said it was incredibly positive news when we went back into deficit spending because it continued the plan to use debt to force the government to cut back. Now we are seeing how things work out when the 1% dominate everything. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-01 17:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americas Deceptive 2012 Fiscal Cliff | Holding the bottom 99% in debt, the top 1% are now in the process of subsidizing a deceptive economic theory to persuade voters to pursue policies that benefit the financial sector at the expense of labor, industry, and democratic government as we know it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 22:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Top 12 Political Fallacies of 2012 | If austeritys so good for us, why are they trying to terrify us with the afiscal cliff? Their Monster In the Closet is austerity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 18:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Radical Mental Health in an Era of Mass Shootings | The circumstances of each of these shooters indicate the social character of mental illness, and the need for a social response to it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-30 22:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best Way to Prevent Rare Massacres: Focus on 'Routine' Violence | Americans' access to guns leads to thousands of deaths each year in accidents, suicides, fights and crimes. So getting a national handle on our gun problem, if effective, will mostly be about preventing those mundane kinds of deaths. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 23:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the Fiscal Cliff Bores the Snot Out of Me | The fiscal cliff has been a tiresome charade, and it disguises the fact that both parties are taking us down the path of austerity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 02:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philanthropy: Youre doing it wrong | Remember, in philanthropy, youre meant to be the humble one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 19:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Claiming US Has 'Best Health System' Is a Sick Joke | Every other industrialized country provides better care to more people for less money.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 19:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Laws of Physics Cant Trump the Bonds of Love | Kids are very spiritual - they want a bigger purpose. I think thats where this story gives them something to think about. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-26 19:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Self-Made Man Looks At How He Made It | I know that what work I have done and what I have achieved doesnt exist in a vacuum or outside of a larger context, or without the work and investment of other people, both within the immediate scope of my life and outside of it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-25 18:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not Another Wall Street Puppet | After three decades of a Wall Street Treasury, thats the last thing the country needs or voters want. Whats now needed is a secretary who can answer Obamas convention-speech call for bold, persistent experimentation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-23 18:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-23 07:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First post I've seen where I upvoted most of the comments.  The extent of the sexism is not only dismaying/enraging but as old as I am it's really weird and not really understandable.  And I don't even see any jailbait, creepshots, or gonewild.  TwoX is mostly respectful and thoughtful.  And I'm sometimes blown away by the quality of bestof posts and comments in cogsci, science2, foodforthought and others so I keep coming back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Banks and Persons | Banks dont go to jail even though they are persons and even when their offenses involve billions of dollars... $1.92 billion is a lot of money and it means that instead of HSBC having a 2011 profit of $22 billion it will only have a profit of about $20 billion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-22 19:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bolivia's Morales Calls for New Era of 'Peace and Unity' to Break Greed of Capitalism | "The Mayan calendar's Dec 21 is the end of the non-time and the beginning of time. It is the end of selfishness and the beginning of brotherhood, it is the end of individualism and the beginning of collectivism." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-21 18:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Engineering Pornography (2002) | Skip this if you don't care about megawatts, bus bars bigger than your wrist, things that cause ground loops out to Hawaii, or big hairy construction projects. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 20:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breaking the Hold of Corporate Welfare on America's Incarceration Industry | Because certain corporations are profiting handsomely from the incarceration binge that has been in place for the past few decades, the reduction in prison populations and prison closures is being met with huge resistance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 19:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should Tax Payers Subsidize Charitable Contributions? | A few surprises about giving in America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 19:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What If All the Worlds Debt Just Went Away | Debt is created when a powerful group of people impose scarcity upon another group of people who have been conquered.  This is the root cause of poverty.  It is the destabilizing force of unequal societies that breeds civil unrest and revolution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 19:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The economic return of Iceland has proved that the joke was on us | Even at the cost of bankrupting the State, the "experts" assured us that Ireland would retain the confidence of the markets. Four years later, it is clear that the "experts" have got it wrong. Catastrophically and utterly wrong. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 07:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Knowledge Workers are Bad at Working (and Heres What to Do About It) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 04:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Take Flight, My Boy | If you can stand it, Veronique Pozner's eulogy for her six-year-old son Noah at one of the first two funerals held for the Newtown victims. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 18:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Social Security and the Obama Cave-In | Its unconscionable to cut Social Security at all when then president is proposing to reduce the proposed taxes on the wealthiest by $400 billion-more than three times the savings of the planned cuts in Social Security. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 18:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Right To Die Is The Right To Live | Mother of chronically ill 18-year-old boy, expected to die young, lets the boy take charge. He fires his doctors, stops his treatments. And gets better. Lifts weights. Theres just too much negativity. I want to have some fun" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 01:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mental Health Reform as Important as Gun Reform | When we talk about mentally or emotionally disturbed individuals, our society puts the emphasis on individuals. We just dont have many cultural resources at all to think about mental/emotional disturbance as a societal problem. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-15 17:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Corporate Media's Shameful Exploitation of Bradley Manning | What is protected in the First Amendment is not the right of commercial enterprises to exploit the news for profit, but rather of citizens to become informed. That requires the courage of heroic sources, including Bradley Manning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 17:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Re-examining Significant Research: The Problem of False-Positives | They ran a standard ANCOVA analysis. Lo and behold, they found that after listening to When Im Sixty-Four, as opposed to Kalimba, participants were a good year and a half younger. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-12 19:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hostess' 'Betrayal Without Remedy' Just Got Worse | It's "legal." But they have a great name for it, which makes everything okay. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-11 18:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Debtor Prisoners Dilemma | Those who cannot forget the past are condemned to inflate it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-11 04:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 800-desktop millstone  | You're concerned about investing a significant amount of money in technologies that may not best meet the present and future needs of students and staff. How do you handle this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 07:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corporate Media Gives Up on Factchecking | So long as the fear of being seen as unfair defines the corporate medias approach to factchecking, they will not be those who deliver the facts.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-07 18:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is peace? | I wanted social science that landed smack on the inside of peaceful societies and studied human interactions at the eye-to-eye level, saying something about how peace works in its tight mechanics... Why is peace so hard to think about? Or conversely, why is violence so easy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-06 18:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the rich look down on the poor | It would be nice to think that we could make it a priority to look after the anti-social, the overweight, the smokers, the plebs sordida and the snorter too. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-06 03:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austerity and the right | Outside the loop | Belief in expansionary austerity is far too widely shared in circles that have nothing to do with American conservatism for the epistemic closure of American conservative discourse or media to have much to do with it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-05 21:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Secret of Bernie Sanders' Success | For the life of me, I cant figure out why progressives listen to consultants. Building movements, making progress on progressive issues- you have to talk to people, educate people, organize people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-05 17:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For Pete's Sake, What's Happened to Our Democracy? | One billionaire has the wherewithal to totally redirect America's political discourse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-05 17:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Authentocracy in America | review of Authentic(TM): The Politics of Ambivalence in a Brand Culture | "Theres just something majestic about the ability of humans to turn bullshit into money." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-04 20:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Lakoff: Why Its Hard to Replace the "Fiscal Cliff Metaphor | I agree with Krugmans economic analysis and think that Reichs political strategy is well worth considering.  But from a cognitive linguistic perspective, their alternative metaphors are not going to make it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-03 19:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-01 04:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many great and thoughtful replies -- thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Economics] What would be fair, revealing questions that could be asked of advocates of economic policy by a person who knows very little about the field of economics but will be affected by those policies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-30 04:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-29 23:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So how should ethical treason be treated?  And what about those who applied treasonous ethics to justify their treatment of him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its Not a Fiscal Cliff, Its an Austerity Crisis | Amid these wide-ranging proposals, the conversation in Washington tends to focus exclusively on achieving deficit reduction -- even though the economic threat we face in January is too much deficit reduction. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-29 23:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quantico Psychiatrist: Military's Mistreatment of Pfc. Manning 'Unprecedented' | Bradley Manning was held in solitary confinement despite expert's claim he was no longer a suicide risk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-29 17:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Wisdom of Insecurity | Security is perhaps the most well-known illusion human beings have contrived.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-28 19:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the Bishops Have to Say For Themselves | When there's a situation where a pregnant woman's life is threatened by continued pregnancy and the fetus cannot survive no matter what, it's better to stand by   let both die than to act   save one. That is the official position of the Catholic church. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-28 19:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-27 17:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article:
51.4 percent of conservative Republicans think we're spending too little on either Social Security, health care or both. Only 28.7 percent think we're spending too much, and just 7.3 percent think we're spending too much on both.

That's 7.3 percent of conservative Republicans in support of the position taken by leaders of both political parties.

It's encouraging to see that the leaders are so wildly off base. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warren Buffett: A Minimum Tax for the Wealthy | Only a minimum tax on very high incomes will prevent the stated tax rate from being eviscerated by warriors for the wealthy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 06:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The High Price of Nickel-and-Diming Doctors | Under Medicares bizarre rules, hospital doctors are paid as much as three times more for patient care than those in private practice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-24 19:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neuroscience: Under Attack | A team of British scientists recently analyzed nearly 3,000 neuroscientific articles published in the British press between 2000 and 2010 and found that the media regularly distorts and embellishes the findings of scientific studies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-24 07:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going overboard | The founder of Scientologys stay in Corfu was brief but eventful | "What is it about islands that appeals to little men with big ideas?" [not very pertinent, just interesting] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-23 19:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help Obama Find His Shoes | Obama once promised, If American workers are being denied their right to organize and collectively bargain when Im in the White House, Ill put on a comfortable pair of shoes myself. Ill walk on that picket line with you as President of the United States of America. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-22 18:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-21 05:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, without "Americans":

It looks lazy and weird to we.

vs.

It looks lazy and weird to us.

It makes a difference whether it's used as subject or object. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-20 00:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think *to we* is an improvement on *to us*?  Better not to admit it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ten Numbers the Rich Would Like Fudged | The numbers reveal the deadening effects of inequality in our country, and confirm that tax avoidance, rather than a lack of middle-class initiative, is the cause. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-19 17:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Learning to Love Volatility | 1 Think of the economy as being more like a cat than a washing machine. 2 Favor businesses that benefit from their own mistakes, not those whose mistakes percolate into the system. 3 Small is beautiful, but also efficient. 4 Trial and error beats academic knowledge... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-18 17:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Subprime Students: How Wall Street Profits from College Loan Mess | Given the billions in profit generated by federal and private student loans, along with the billions in administrative costs absorbed by tax payers, is debt the most efficient and equitable way to provide access to higher education? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-18 16:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ralph Nader: 'Grand Bargain' Charade a Scheme to Protect Corporate Welfare | The consumer of Medicare and Medicaid, the recipient of Social Security, and the average taxpayer will take the brunt of the spending cuts, while the wealthy get their income taxes restored to their pre-Bush modest levels. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 18:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PROH-sehs-seez is the plural of PROH-sehs-sihs.  What sounds to me like a misuse grates on my ear. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 18:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the origins of the misuse of the -eez plurals other than pretension?  Once they become widespread people simply copy them, but what gets them started?  

The reason I blame pretension is probably because I first heard these -eez plurals thrown around when I started college.  Plurals of thesis, basis and the like were in frequent use and it seemed many students were consciously trying to get them right. 

And maybe the reason some words are immune, such as recess, is that there's no status gain to be had.  Or have you ever heard ree-sehs-eez? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wall Street Uses "Liberal" Front Group to Lead Its Assault on Social Security | Third Way is not progressive think tank and only represents the interests of the 1%ers | The left is not divided on the need to oppose austerity and the Great Betrayal. Third Way is Wall Street on the Potomac. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-14 18:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trojan Horse in the Debt Debate | Their web site says flat out that the so-called "fiscal cliff" is an opportunity to push for "considerably less" spending on Medicare and Medicaid, and calls for a shift to a "territorial tax system," exempting U.S. corporations' foreign income from U.S. taxes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-14 18:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-12 17:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The five myths, plus "the greatest myth":
The poorest 40 percent own about 10% of the wealth.  Entitlements are the problem. Welfare benefits are a drag on the economy. The American Dream is still alive -- if you just work hard. Prison puts away the bad guys. The rich are being "soaked." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-12 05:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And further:
As you stand in the gap between reality and possibility, the temptation is to jump onto one side or the other. If you jump onto the side of too much hard reality, you can get stuck in corrosive cynicism. If you jump onto the side of too much possibility, you can get caught up in irrelevant idealism. These two extremes sound very different, but they have the same impact on us: both take us out of the gap  and the gap is where all the action is.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-12 05:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also from the aticle:
The brains weakest function is the retention of isolated bits of data. Its strongest function is the retention of pattern, narrative, story, and system.  Dumping data bits into students heads and calling it education Is a system that targets the brains _weakest_ function,
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Only We Would Listen  | The main reason we have dysfunctional education policies in this country is that the teachers voice is almost absent from public discourse about how to transform education. The discourse is dominated by the people who tend to know the least about teaching and learning... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-12 04:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On What We Could Learn About Politics, Faith, And Each Other | If the only way we judge an action is by its effectiveness, we will take on smaller and smaller tasks, because theyre the only kind with which we are sure we can get results. Effectiveness has to be secondary to faithfulness. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-12 04:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-12 04:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also from the article:
When you throw facts at people to refute what they believe, it only hardens their convictions. But if you create a relational container that can hold an ongoing dialogue, its more likely that someone will change  and that someone may be you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Only We Would Listen | On What We Could Learn About Politics, Faith, And Each Other | Citizens are abandoning the public arena because its so toxic, divisive, and abusive - and this creates a vacuum into which nondemocratic powers like big money are eager to rush. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-12 04:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On What We Could Learn About Politics, Faith, And Each Other | Theres heartbreak across the political spectrum, and not just in this country. If Americans dont understand that radical Islamic terrorists are heartbroken about whats happening to their people, were missing the point. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-12 04:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-12 04:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also from the article:
Violence is what happens when we dont know what else to do with our suffering. That applies on every level of life. When individuals dont know what to do with their suffering, they do violence to others or themselves.  When nations dont know what to do with their suffering, they go to war.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Only We Would Listen | On What We Could Learn About Politics, Faith, And Each Other | The more Ive listened to peoples stories, the more Ive found that suffering is an aquifer on which we all draw. Thats one place where we have something in common to talk about. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-12 04:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the Republicans Lost | New Hampshire and the Republican Party in other states should get rid of the overvote rule for primaries and allow voters to vote for any and all candidates on the ballot that they approve of.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-09 21:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Most Untrue Cliches  Those who forget history are doomed to repeat it | Our leaders perseverate over history and past failings and traumas, and act so as not to repeat them, often with disastrous effects, since real conditions have changed on them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-09 21:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Howard Dean: I think we ought to go over the cliff.  It will take 7  trillion dollars out of our deficit.  Any politician who tells the American people there aren't going to be any sacrifices for everybody is a liar and I do not want the sacrifices to be on the backs of the middle class. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-09 20:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-08 18:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emma Goldman: If voting changed anything, itd be illegal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Open Letter to Obama from the World's Poorest Countries | As president you have helped those who cause climate change more than those affected most by it. Helping the world's poorest adapt is now a matter of urgency, and it can be your great legacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-08 17:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Liberal Victory to Disempowerment in Six Easy Steps | The political leader in whose triumph liberals are today ecstatically basking is likely to target their most cherished government policies within a matter of weeks. If history is any indication, this is how this "fight" will proceed: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 20:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Broken US System Needs Watching: International Election Observers Could Face Arrest | Even the conservative magazine National Review acknowledges that foreign monitors are justified.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-04 17:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-30 17:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then the garden path goes away too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Elections Matter | There are significant differences between the two parties and the two candidates; while neither are our allies, one will make our work of building movements even more difficult, will threaten even more of our shredded civil liberties.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 18:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It Might Save Obama This Year, but the Electoral College Must Go! | Candidates are not contesting Wyoming, Alaska, Vermont, Delaware, etc. now because of the winner-take-all College, plus they are not contesting heavily (and diversely) populated Texas, California, New York, Illinois, Massachusetts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-27 19:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why You're Not As Politically Astute As You Think You Are | "No matter how politically astute you think you are, your critical abilities suffer if you don't actively engage with someone you don't know who has a different viewpoint." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-26 18:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-26 18:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me the single.most.obvious.requirement would be open-source code. Nefarious code could alter the paper trail at a level that would be unlikely to trigger a recount.  Paper trails are an obvious requirement though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Objectivity Does Not Mean Neutrality: The Danger of False Equivalency in the Media | A view held by 2 percent of experts does not deserve equal time... If the interests of objectivity and neutrality diverge, a journalists loyalty lies with the truth, not with the political or rhetorical center. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-25 18:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-25 01:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some fraction of a percent comes from [Persian](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_English_words_of_Persian_origin). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hard Times Hardly Hurt the Superrich | In 2010, the top 1 percent captured 93 percent of income gains. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-21 18:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Do You Know, Feminism Really DOES Work |  The mobilization of feminist movements is more important for change than the wealth of nations, left-wing political parties, or the number of women politicians.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-20 23:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-20 02:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am astounded by the wide acceptance here of "free will" as an either/or matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Self-Destruction of the 1 Percent | It is those at the top, particularly the tippy-top, of the economic pyramid who have been most effective at capturing government support -- and at getting others to pay for it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 00:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-12 18:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Cutting the deficit is no big deal. 2. Tackling Climate Change would create jobs and stimulate the economy. 3. Regulations are good for the economy. 4. Occupying foreign countries to prevent terrorism causes terrorism. 5. Government is an essential partner in creating jobs and prosperity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-11 18:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  For a while I thought I had missed an enormous jump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What could account for this anomaly? My brokerage program shows TBT at about $15 yet Yahoo Finance shows TBT has never been below about $60 in its history. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-11 01:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brokerage program is Interactive Brokers Trader Workstation. See my trade history and TBT history [here](http://i.imgur.com/c5h3w.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feast of Fools and the Rule of Money | How American Democracy Became the Property of a Commercial Oligarchy | If democracy means anything at all, it is the holding of ones fellow citizens in thoughtful regard, not because they are rich or famous, but because they are ones fellow citizens. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 17:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Networks Network | Scientists now know that networks of networks dont always behave the way single networks do. In the wake of this insight, a revolution is under way. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 03:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Embracing the Senses: Balancing Novelty and Habituation | The job of the artist is to counter habituation with novelty. Art changes because it is govern by habituating audiences and novelty-creating artists. Both are always reacting to each other. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 21:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Growth or Equality: Two Competing Visions for Americas Future | When wealth and power are concentrated at the top, however, the result is not trickle down. It is a sucking up.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 19:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Correcting Creativity: The Struggle for Eminence | Creative breakthroughs in any domain require strenuous work and a willingness to challenge the establishment. The life of the eminent creator is not soothing; it is a strugglea grossly uneven wrestling match with the muses. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 04:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Terrifying Way to Discipline Children | The use of restraints and seclusion has become far more routine than it should be. Theyre the last resort too often being used as the first resort. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-10 04:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can the black middle class survive? | "Much of the region, particularly African-Americans, were outraged over the opening stories in our coverage, so the hostess, and her friends, wanted a word. The essential message: Inside Times pages, pretend the black middle class is doing just fine." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-09 04:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Thing Nobody Talked About at the Conventions | Between the new torrents of money that are overwhelming the system, and the rise again of voter-suppression legalisms in the various states, the election is coming perilously close to becoming a puppet show. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-08 19:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Economic Policy Beyond Gimmicks | A true recovery should be investment led rather than consumption led.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-08 18:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Revisiting Robbers Cave | In the summer of 1954, 22 boys headed off to summer camp to take part in one of most famous studies in social psychology: The Robbers Cave experiment. Here's what happened, and what it taught us about intergroup relations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-08 04:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-08 03:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reasonable people from both sides cannot come together and hash out a compromise that takes everyones interests into account. The middle ground is an unbridgeable chasm, and ideology represents our attempts to paper over and ignore that chasm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Read iek | To find left-wing thinkers and movements simultaneously laughable and dangerous, disorganized and totalitarian, overly idealistic and driven by a lust for power is to suggest: there is no alternative. It is an attempt to shut down debate on the basic structure of our society. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-08 02:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creative Destruction: From Genesis to Picasso to Apple Computers | "Half of the challenge is having the courage, the temerity, the will to actually stop doing something, which is infinitely harder than starting something new." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 20:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Media Not Concerned About the Very Poor | Poverty as an issue is nearly invisible in U.S. media coverage of the 2012 election, even though what candidates plan to do about an alarmingly growing poverty rate would seem to be a ripe topic for discussion in campaign coverage.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 18:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Defense of Bradley Manning | The rapid growth of secrecy matches the rapid growth in bad ideas and administrative incompetence, as overclassification protects the delicate ego of the foreign policy elite, whose performance in the past decade has been so lethally sub-par. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-06 07:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Often Have To Cut Into The Brain | Somehow I had caused a major stroke, so that she awoke from the operation paralysed down the left side of her body... I knew that any unhappiness on my part was nothing compared to what she and her family were going through. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-06 04:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Are Americans Better Off Today Than They Were Four Years Ago?" The Question That Exposes Incompetent Reporters | The reason we know that the questioners are incompetent reporters is that this is a pointless question. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 20:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Are Americans Better Off Today Than They Were Four Years Ago?" The Question That Exposes Incompetent Reporters | The reason we know that the questioners are incompetent reporters is that this is a pointless question. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 18:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Were Still Fighting for Voters Rights | By making it as difficult as possible for low-income people, the right wing makes it easier to pass industry-friendly legislation. The correlation between income and voter turnout means that the wealthier people are, the more they matter to politicians. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 18:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wall Streets War on the Cities | Elected public officials could not engage in such predatory policies. Only the magic of the marketplace can break public labor unions, downsize public services and put tollbooths on the roads, water and sewer systems while cutting back bus lines and raising fares. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 20:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Designing a Hedonistic and Sustainable Future | What if you can truly have it all? What if you can do something that is good for the environment, while doing something good for yourself and for the economy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 00:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Food hubs' connect school districts with farmers | "The quality and selection we're seeing coming right from the farms is incredible. Children get to eat the product that's picked that same morning." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-02 22:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Lost Art of Thinking Before You Act | The framing of a collective challenge as a moral issue undermines our ability to find rational, thoughtful solutions. Activists who talk about climate change as if it is a moral imperative de-emphasize the fact that it is also a major policy issue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 18:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Lost Art of Thinking Before You Act | The long work hours and obsession with growth that are the hallmarks of 20th-century capitalism have nothing to do with personal happiness. There are easier ways to satiate a taste for the finer things in life than by building a company from the ground up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 18:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank Goodness Labor is its Own Reward! | A wage that condemns people to poverty in spite of their labor condemns them to wage slavery and cripples the idea of democratic community. My friends would begrudge such a wage, because a work ethic, coupled with honest labor, is its own reward. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 17:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never Mind Super PACs: How Big Business Is Buying the Election | After Citizens United, trade associations like the American Petroleum Institutewhose influential members include foreign corporationare free to spend as they wish, unburdened by disclosure requirements. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 17:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Have You Learned As A Police Officer? | 11. Many criminals eventually come to the point in their lives that a criminal lifestyle is more trouble than it's worth to them. Unfortunately, by that time they have incurred a prison sentence that will keep them behind bars until they die. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 04:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Rot Runs Deep 2: Don't Call Out My Scam And I Won't Call Out Yours | Can an economy that has become dependent on lies, misrepresentation, "fudging" of numbers, fraud, embezzlement and a multitude of skimming and scamming operations escape the moral and financial black hole it has created? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 00:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Revolt of the Rich | "If a morally acceptable American conservatism is ever to extricate itself from a pseudo-scientific inverted Marxist economic theory, it must grasp that order, tradition, and stability are not coterminous with obeisance to the demands of the wealthy." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-28 20:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dan Ariely on Behavioural Economics | "You can think about the market economy in this way - almost nobody wants you to do something that is good for you in the long term. The incentive of everybody else is to do something that is good for them in the short term." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-28 06:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can Democrats Compete In 2016? | "There are only three things a re-elected Obama administration should have on its agenda..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 18:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Four Ways the Ohio GOP is Already Stealing the 2012 Election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 17:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nicaraguan girl [2272x1704] [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 00:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time to Get a Grip, America | Voting for business as usual is truly a suicidal choice. Not voting at all is even worse, suicide by apathy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-26 18:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bankers' Profits Soar on Backs of Home Buyers | While millions of Americans are still without jobs, the big banks were bailed out by the taxpayers. Yet they don't want to change any of their methods, fighting tooth and nail against regulations that would curtail their excesses. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-26 18:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Invisible Americans Get the Silent Treatment | Its just astonishing to us how long this campaign has gone on with no discussion of whats happening to poor people. Official Washington continues to see poverty with tunnel vision - out of sight, out of mind. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-25 18:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome To Hell | "The cyclical nature of urban trauma confounds us. We throw up our hands in disgust at the young, violent men of this city. What we fail to grasp, in terms of any coherent policy, is traumas strange dual nature." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 19:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deluded Individualism | Freudian reading of Tea-Party Republicanism. "These people rely on government assistance, but pretend they dont. They even resent the government for their reliance." They construct a fantasy of individualism, and inhabit it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 22:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Are Americans So Confused? | Progressives still believe what they learned in civics class: Give the people the true facts and their minds will lead them to logical conclusions. What the civics teacher left out is the powerful human tendency to look for meaning by thinking in mythic narratives. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 17:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apocalypse Not: Heres Why You Shouldnt Worry About End Times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 19:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 03:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about their potential Supreme Court nominations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
