<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1909</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 22:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call of Wide: Wide at Wide. Did I do it right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 03:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can look good if you don't throw $30 worth of LEDS in a case and hope it looks good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 03:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> . omfg so good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How people view PC Gaming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 03:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 02:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was expecting for them to put that one make up in their eye to make them entirely black. With someone doing a dick copter in the back to make it NSFW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 04:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fuck. That took a dark turn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> may not be directly related to PC but I hope you brothers can help... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 00:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This may seem like advertisement, but I assure you it isn't. It is raising awareness to a charity. If there are other places I could post this where it would be more relevant I would gladly do so, or you could. There is a charity going to get children in Detroit Hospital a "GO kart" which is a kiosk with a tv and everything hooked up so a child who can't leave their room, can still enjoy games. Currently Twitch streamer DanGheesling is doing this charity event to provide these. He has 4 hours left and is half way there. We, the PC gamers, could easily help him, even if we each gave 50 cents. (USD) This is a great charity I think we could support. Now there is one problem, they are xbones, but do you think a kid, who hasn't his bed in a month would give a fuck? If you are donating or even watching, cut the master race shit and support a good cause.

http://www.twitch.tv/dangheesling

http://gamersoutreach.org/media/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 21:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [DONKEH!!!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iNHgafrFeN4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 17:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just pointing out, a black guy gets attacked, its on CNN. A white guy? Local news. Police brutality affects EVERYONE, not just black people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL Exercise makes you unhealthy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, its a shame that ANOTHER black man has been hurt because of police brutality. Oh wait, it was a white cop AND a white civilian. It almost seems like this has to do with police being assholes and it not just being racial tension... huh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Excuse me sir, are you pregnant?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 02:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 03:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hodor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 03:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a teacher but I found my principals twitter. She has zero tweets. But her profile picture is her riding a horse wearing a top hat. She is a 5 foot tall woman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THE DREEEEEEEAM (rip austin too) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 01:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 02:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> never heard of that. Link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 02:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a shark in your pocket or are you happy to see me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 01:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit. You beat me to the karma. D: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 23:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Takin' the downvotes like a champ! Kappa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 23:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do I get mods with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 22:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I is nots sure if these is legit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 00:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> idk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 23:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the soul isn't there. I have no idea how she even died. :/ Also, can I make weapon flamey or lightning? Like the Uchikatana, which I had been using up until the lightning spear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 22:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the weapons I have are taking forever. Any suggestions for weapons I should get? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 22:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would be a good sword to use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did I fuck up my entire run? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 22:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my first time with Dank Souls. I had a standard run I guess. Except my Quelaag fight. I don't know what happened. I fought her over and over again. Kept dying. After 69 times I go and she isn't there. I never got her soul. I cannot make Quelaags Fury Sword. From every lets play I see they ALWAYS use that sword. Is there any alternative to that sword that I could use in Anor Londo or if any of you have a Quelaag sword or souls that doesn't fit your build could I have it? Keep in mind I am a noob. Thanks! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 21:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 666 is the sign of the anti-christ. In the bible people are marked with that to show that they are with the devil or some shit. I would expect the Mark would be the mark in the bible. Which it is. :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 01:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tunnelsnakes.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No. Why the hell would I want to watch "Skylander Boy Girl"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 00:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 21:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's afraid we we find out it's a repost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 04:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy FUCK! This shit is AMAZING! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 23:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm joking. The game will look like BF4. Good on PC. Makes you cry on consoles. :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 23:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star Wars: Battlefront. The new one. That is coming out.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 22:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello Chris! Let me say, I am a HUGE fan and love you as an actor. The question is, how long did it take you to lose weight and get buff for the role of Star-Lord. Also, would you consider making a workout CD. I would buy that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 22:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is probably what the graphics will look like in battlefront. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 22:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT!!! THIS IS NOT TAKING TO SERIOUSLY! THIS RUINS THE ENTIRE KARMA ECONOMY!!!!11one Kappa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HOLY FUCKING WHAT AUSTIN RUN!!!!!11 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 02:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UBER AUSTIN FLAK DREAM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 02:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austin Flak Dream ??? ????? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 02:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 01:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't a cross post. It wasn't the same poster. Two different posters is a repost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 23:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I guess. I would rather see unfunny shit than stolen shit. I mean, would you rather find a dollar on the road or would you want someone to take a dollar from you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 23:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but Dean! The mother won't come back... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 22:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? A repost from a day ago from /r/4chan? I'm disappointed with you /r/funny... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austin Flak Dream 8:34 PM 4/22/2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 03:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 03:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was the strangest/scariest thing to happen during a filming or while in an anonymous chat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BEAMS SUCK FLAK 4 EVER </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 02:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nobeamnobeamnobeamnobeamnobeamnobeamnobeamnobeamnobeamnobeamnobeamnobeamnobeamnobeamnobeamnobeamnobeamnobeamnobeamnobeam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austin Flak 6:53 4/22/2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 01:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austin Flak 5:51 4/22/2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 00:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 00:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, hey Ice! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 03:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That DOES exist. It is called Apple's "Maps" app. :DDDD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 03:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title is 2long4me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help pimping out my sub (Background) (Upvotes/Downvote Icons) (etc.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 02:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need help. If you know any of the things above message me. The sub is /r/flakdream </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 02:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NSFW [Cute raccoon on the side of the road.](https://encrypted-tbn3.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcQy3skMXrXb2LNsrvlxvinmJVsvdQnqpoQBaKXZowWjyRO794WI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 02:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/dankmemes would be every talk show. The entire sub. Everyone who has ever posted on it. All on Oprah. "How did you know?" Oprah asked. "Well, the first step is to realize, jet fuel CAN'T melt steel beams." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 02:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You, scoot back" Kappa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 02:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conveniently, you were sick today. Right? RIGHT!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 01:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to make a joke about balls.I can't, too cute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 01:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure how this works at all... I may join? Can you explain how Steamchat D D works? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Picked up Sims at a thrift store. The nostalgia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 22:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 01:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are there so many moons? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 23:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it doesn't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 23:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not including this one, of course </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The man plan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 01:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 20:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, yeah. Sorry I got confused. :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> B E S T G A M E </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 20:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 19:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Chef! I will cut the crap and just ask you a question. Has someone ever been too good to get on the show? and have you ever had to cut the show because something happened like the building burned down, they were good, they were too shit, etc.? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 16:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hug now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post about Putt-Putt will ya!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 06:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt putt-putt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 06:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, this did better than most of my posts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 05:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't a repost? I literally went in and made this meme with imgur meme maker before I posted it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 05:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait what the fuck? How? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 05:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh..... i now see.... also... WTF 1 UPVOTE 96 COMMENTS HOW!?!?!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
