<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1473</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 19:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that 5-15 year old Mazdas rust like hell in Canada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody else look at the front of the current BMW 7 series and think of this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 19:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/SCRvS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 16:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really think of this view that way. What I mean is the potential to help out overpopulation a bit is the reason why I think things such as driving without a seatbelt on should be legal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one who hears "Doing so and so is a good idea because it will save lives" and think "Sure, it saves lives, but is that necessarily a good thing"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 05:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 02:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did a surprisingly good job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do professional race car drivers drive on normal roads? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 03:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are the tobacco and firearm lobbies actually controlled by the funeral lobby? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 17:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 05:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FWD: 1971-72 Cadillac Eldorado Biarritz

RWD: Mercedes S65 AMG

AWD: R32 Nissan Skyline GTS-4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best comment you have ever seen with a score below threshold? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 02:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 22:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most muscle cars from 1974-84. Such as the Chevy Cosworth Vega, Olds 442, and Volare based Road Runner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 01:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and this Ferrari, http://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2013-10-23/wrecked-ferrari-sells-for-250-000-basquiat-5-million </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 00:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, I feel safer when I don't have to rely on technology to drive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 00:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its the same car, before the fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it immoral that I believe that riding motorcycles without a helmet and driving without a seatbelt on should be legal because making both legal would increase the supply of organs for transplant? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 22:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 21:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I thought, driver aids and other electronics, but otherwise the difference between 2005 and 2015 cars seems quite small when compared to say, 1955 vs 1965 or 1985 vs 1995 cars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In what way are today's new cars most different from the cars of ten years ago? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 21:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is this worth $20,000? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 19:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 19:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Infiniti Q50, Cadillac XTS, Mercedes C/E, Lexus LS/GS/ES/IS are all good choices. Also check out /r/whatcarshouldibuy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 17:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with a wall of text? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did the 90s end in 2005? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 14:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 06:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yup.](http://jalopnik.com/the-six-best-unreliable-cars-you-can-buy-from-carmax-1687770994) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 06:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A 5-7 year old C-Class might not be the most pleasant when its time for repairs, but should be less expensive than an E or S class. If this worries you, I would recommend finding one with lower miles or trying to find one from Carmax if you can, since they warranty all their used cars.

http://www.carmax.com/search?ANa=283 D=90 zip=11050 N=4294963073 Q=ce08978e-3b29-41c9-82e6-f3b2289c56e0 Ep=search:results:results

Edit: Unfortunately they don't seem to have any AWD in stock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 06:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2008-10 Mercedes-Benz C300s and C350s were available in manual with AWD. Here's one, but they seem to be relatively rare in the US,

http://www.carsbuyerinc.net/2008_MercedesBenz_CClass_Butler_NJ_251483355.veh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 03:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toyota Century </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 00:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 69 cents </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 23:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free candy sign </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 22:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> coins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would happen if I sodomized someone with a loaded gun and pulled the trigger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 22:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 00:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These poorly added aftermarket sunroofs were popular in the 70s and 80s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 21:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chevy Suburban, Tahoe, GMC Yukon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and why most German cars in the northeast are now all wheel drive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does whether a car is front wheel drive or rear wheel drive matter to most non-enthusiasts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like even though enthusiasts complain about some cars being FWD, most buyers could care less. For example, a non-enthusiast cross shopping a FWD Audi A8 and a RWD Mercedes S550 is probably more concerned with amenities and badge prestige than they are with which wheels propel the car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 04:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is getting old and annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 15:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should be cheaper to maintain than similar German cars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the risk of being downvoted discourage users from posting unpopular opinions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 14:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 10:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 01-06 Infiniti Q45 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 21:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it was likely not the texter's first time texting and driving. This was just a fender bender, but sometimes texting while driving can be just as dangerous as drunk driving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does it seem like whenever someone admits to bad driving on reddit, they are either given a lot of sympathy, or heavily flamed and downvoted, with nowhere in between? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 20:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These posts are kind of old, but are still good examples of what I mean. Both did something pretty dangerous, and likely not for the first time, but the difference in how in one there is a lot of flaming and in the other one the commenters take on the attitude of "Sorry you messed up, good thing your car looks nice again" seems interesting to me.

[Given sympathy](http://www.reddit.com/r/mercedes_benz/comments/2ygnl6/texting_and_driving_on_my_w211_never_again/)

[Flamed and downvoted](http://www.reddit.com/r/cars/comments/2vo6nb/hi_my_name_is_luvs2speed_and_im_a_speedaholic/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 17:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one who sees a little BMW in the roofline of these? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 17:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=JQMQkMvRG3I you can still drift FWD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 07:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BMW 1M: The future classic that is already appreciating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AMG GT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 13:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nissan Skyline GXi

BMW 316d

4 cylinder Chevy Nova

1975 Dodge Charger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 13:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, if this were 1975. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 03:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buick Regal GS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When do you think will the world have it's first trillionaire? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 22:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most embarrassing thing you ever got in trouble for doing at school? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 18:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 02:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meant to write LR2, the other name for the Freelander. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 00:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was silver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 00:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The XF is pretty nice looking, but took some getting used to since it is such a radical departure from traditional Jaguar styling. I strongly agree on the Freelander, that thing looks like a poorly restyled, overpriced, Ford Escape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does Stephen Hawking sound exactly like Speakonia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 00:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 00:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They sell very few and most people don't see the appeal of a "luxury Kia". They should've developed a separate luxury brand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much does the badge of a car affect the way the driver drives? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 23:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few days ago, I saw a 99-02 E55 AMG driver going 80+ mph on the highway and driving like an asshole in general. I think that the reason why he drove like this is because he thinks that since it's an AMG, it feels like a supercar to this douche, when in reality it's a 15 year old, 350 hp, mid-level luxury sedan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one who thinks that Korean luxury cars look like video game cars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 23:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason, I think that the Hyundai Genesis and Equus sedans, and the Kia K900 look like they would be more at home in a video game like GTA, Saints Row, or Watch Dogs than the would in real life. I'm guessing it must be because of how they are an amalgamation of different familiar designs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 22:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem isn't that it's a bad car, the problem is that by not marketing it properly, making it too expensive, and not making a manual available, they have screwed up it's potential at being a popular car. I have only ever seen one in person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 22:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mercedes-Benz: A, B Class

Land Rover: Freelander/LR2

Lexus: HS

Kia: K900

Ford Motor Company: All the current Lincolns

Chevrolet: SS

Dodge - Avenger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 19:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NADA guides should work, they go back all the way to cars from over half a century ago.

http://www.nadaguides.com/Classic-Cars/1987/Chevrolet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 15:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For readers who don't already know, this is the Australian version of the Subaru Legacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yet another lower drinking age bill out of Minnesota. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 11:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does my gf always leave the toilet seat up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 09:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it usually the other way around? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 08:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Population control </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 08:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long Island, NY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 08:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a girl around here drive this 90s Sentra for about six months with really bad rear end damage. The trunk lid was smashed in and didn't look like it could close or open, bumper was split, taillight lenses cracked, and lots of duct tape. This is in a state with yearly inspections. 


Edit: Also once saw an elderly man driving an 80s Olds Cutlass that was completely covered in rust, as if it had sat in a pond, and dragging its tail, as if there were a few bodies in the trunk, going 10 under the speed limit.


Edit: Your rolling wrecks and the speed they go sound 10x worse, sounds like you live in a third world county. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 06:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/murica </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would be worse, buying a used rental car or buying a used cop car? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 05:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 04:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the way MB styling has been going, I hope it's better than the current facelifted E. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any particular reason why the Mercedes-Benz models such as the S500 are called the S550 in the U.S., but not in the rest of the world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 04:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 02:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tata or Tatra? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waste of a good Benz. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 00:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 00:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last year my aunt called a W126 a "15 year old Mercedes". Also, one time when I was 11 I saw a 560SEC and thought it was a newer car (this was 07-08ish). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 19:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many German cars (W210, E38, etc.) and the LS400 also. I would never mistake any of these, or the NSX or Supra, as well as the Skyline for new cars, but they don't yet appear to stand out in traffic as "old" looking. Part of it might also be because I'm a child of the late 90s-early 00s and the designs still seen normal to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is it that many 90s cars still seem relatively modern today, but 10 years ago, few 80s cars seemed modern? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 17:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 03:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I strongly agree on the Cadillacs, but I think the 3 series BMWs have aged pretty well in some cases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 01:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of this early 80s Mercury Grand Marquis I've seen driving around with a Regan-Bush sticker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which old luxury car do you find it hard to believe was once viewed as a status symbol? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 00:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 15:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the CA government is always concerned with the environment, I'm guessing that due to pressure from enthusiasts with older cars who don't regularly use them, they've decided to compromise by making them pay a fee to avoid smog testing, while also not making it any easier for people who are broke to keep their old clunkers on the road. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California bill to allow fee payment instead of smog test for cars 30 years or older introduced. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 13:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://japanesenostalgiccar.com/2015/04/16/ca-bill-to-allow-fee-payment-instead-of-smog-test-introduced/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 07:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Lamborghini Countach (formerly)

- Maserati Quattroporte

- 190E 2.6

- 1990s S600

- 1976 and 1981 Chrysler New Yorkers

- Chevy Camaro IROC convertible

- Some kind of 60s-70s Mercedes that never leaves the garage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 00:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NO as is too expensive, or NO as in its a bad car? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 22:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These can all be found for 7k with under 100,000 miles where I live.

- 2001-07 Mercedes C-Class

- Pontiac G6

- Lexus LS430

- 2001-08 Subaru Impreza </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should we raise our son as a girl? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 15:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We wanted a girl but are having a boy. I would consider raising him as a girl instead if you think this would have a good outcome. I figure that we will treat him as a girl and not tell him he's really a boy. Put him in dresses, grow his hair long, give him dolls to play with, etc. I  believe that when puberty comes testosterone will make "her" into a "girl" who is, bigger and stronger than most actual females, giving "her" an advantage in sports. I am also hoping that her masculine features will deter boys from wanting to date her when reaching high school age. Will this work and have you ever tried something like this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would happen if a boy was raised as a girl? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 09:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 08:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The V12 S600s are also very complex and expensive to maintain, making an earlier trip to the scrapper more likely, but I don't think that most of the W140s produced are S600s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 06:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first thought was how out of place it seemed there. Perhaps it was originally a military import. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does it seem like there are so many more W126s than W140s still on the road? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 06:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Random vehicles on the Nrburgring. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 03:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't criminals ever hide in the sewer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 23:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have watched a lot of police pursuits on TV and the internet and when I saw a foot chase recently that was recorded by helicopter, where the suspects were out of sight of ground cops for some time, I noticed a manhole. I then wondered why no one ever hid in the sewer to evade in these videos, wouldn't that put them out of sight of the helicopter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would it be considered a hate crime if I told a person with a peanut allergy to "Go eat a peanut and die!"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 21:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 04:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you ever go to a poor area, you will likely see older Lincolns and other ratty luxury cars with broken air suspension. They scrape, ride high, bounce up and down going over potholes, and sometimes have one side far higher up in the air than the other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 04:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were largely purchased by elderly people, often as their very last car. This means that low-mile, well maintained examples, available at low prices are not hard to find. If you live in Florida or another warm state, it is likely that they were only driven half the year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its the supermarket storebrand F F. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is emblem theft making a comeback? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember hearing about this being a big issue for Mercedes-Benz owners in the 1980's, but recently, I have been seeing a few Mercedes-Benzes and one Cadillac driving around with the grille emblems yanked out. I remember seeing a small, sudden amount of them about six months ago, but yesterday, I saw three, two MBs and the Cadillac, all late model. Do the emblems have any resale value or does somebody just think its fun to be a dick? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 14:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 70s-80s full size American cars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 22:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1988 Lincoln Town Car </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the 2009-13 Hyundai Genesis the modern reincarnation of the Ford Granada? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 22:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both are Mercedes-Benz imitations built by mid-range brands and sold for a comparatively lower price, with lower quality.

[Granada, Mercedes comparison ad](http://www.americangranada.com/gallery/ad-2.jpg)

[Genesis side by side with S Class] (http://thedailydrivers.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/09/GenesisMercedes.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sexy classic American car </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 22:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 22:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any one of these or all three, 

- Z06 swapped late 70s early 80s Chevy Caprice.

- 630E W123.

- LS400 with Toyota Century V12 and supercharger.

All would be kept stock looking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It seems so crazy to me that the oldest E30 M3s are now 30 years old, the same age that all the 1970 muscle cars were in 2000. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 16:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think about it. All those muscle cars seemed old and impractical back then, as well as earlier. Today, the E30 M3, and some other 1980s European sports cars still seem practical for daily driving and feel somewhat modern. Also, it seems like I perceived the 60s-70s as longer ago back then than I perceive the 80s as being now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a car that you would like to rent, but wouldn't buy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 01:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why these GM and Ford execs are skeptical about self driving cars. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 01:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the weirdest person/thing you have ever found yourself sexually attracted to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 22:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 21:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised to see the XTS here. It seems relatively popular around here. Not terribly common, but far from rare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 19:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trans Am WS6 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> is the 2009-13 Hyundai Genesis the modern reincarnation of the Ford Granada? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 16:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both are Mercedes-Benz imitations built by mid-range brands and sold for a comparatively lower price, with lower quality.

[Granada, Mercedes comparison ad](http://www.americangranada.com/gallery/ad-2.jpg)

[Genesis side by side with S Class] (http://thedailydrivers.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/09/GenesisMercedes.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 16:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How accurate have previous renderings been to what is actually built? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 05:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see it, to me it looks as much like the current S Class as the W124 looked like a W140. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 04:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the W212 first came out, I thought it was ugly and felt disappointed that the W211 out of production, but then it grew on me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 04:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just thought of this, how about a vintage VW Bus, or a Vanagon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 04:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pontiac Aztek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 04:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a professor who has a fear of rodents. If this were available as a t-shirt, I would wear it to her class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this really the 2016 Mercedes-Benz E-Class? If so, it looks pretty good. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 03:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is MB planning to build a W205 coupe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 22:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 21:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once saw a highly modified 55' Chevy that had been put on a 96' Caprice chassis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the craziest redditor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 21:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few weeks ago, I came across a user who has posted various radical and nonsensical opinions, including [this one] (http://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/2ywoot/dad_smuggles_baby_in_plastic_bag_out_of_hospital/cpdnfvq?context=3), and has been showered in downvotes because of how crazy what he writes is. He is apparently a [sovereign citizen] (http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sovereign_citizen_movement) and sounds like a real tinfoil hatter. I would love to see this guy defend himself in court, though I'm sure somebody else must be even nuttier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 06:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was this the inspiration for Professor Quirrel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 04:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> W124 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 04:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I call Subaru and Toyota's shade of orange "county orange" because it reminds me of prison jumpsuits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 04:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Whenever I see a beige or gold Mercedes or BMW I always cringe. Once I saw a beige Bentley and thought "why?". On the bright side, some golds from the 60s-70s aren't so bad looking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which color always uglifies an otherwise decent looking car? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 04:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 04:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CPO BMW, Mercedes, Audi, Lexus, Infiniti, or Cadillac. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This 1985 Ford LTD Crown Victoria served nearly 30 years of service for the Maricopa County Sheriff's Department </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 04:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 05:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crown Vic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 00:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've been playing too much GTA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 21:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but it's just interesting to see the flaws in their attempted realism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mercury Marauder X-100: The intersection of Muscle and Brougham. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 19:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Isn't it silly that in San Andreas and Vice City you can cut down street lights and road signs with the chainsaw, but not trees or telephone poles. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 19:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Learn English </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 19:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 03:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure it isn't too common, though I have seen these types of cars a few times on eBay. I thought of asking because I recently watched the Jay Leno Toronado video.

Edit: and apparently I'm a prick for asking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 03:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first such car I can think of off the top of my head is Jay Leno's Olds Toronado, http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zuB5DULvw7Y. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddidtors who have converted a car from front wheel drive to rear wheel drive, what is it like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 03:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In particular, how did you do it and what was the result. Most cars are built specifically with their layout in mind, so I would imagine that a RWD converted car that was FWD from the factory may be kind of awkward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A cheap BMW will drive you to homelessness. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 19:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else here who wishes they would add the Virgo to GTA V? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 05:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The BIGGEST SLEEPER EVER - Buick LeSabre Goes NUTS with Nitrous </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 01:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 06:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apple products auto select Cupertino for weather updates, so maybe they just decided to give their otherwise obscure hometown a name in case the site becomes famous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 05:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This does not sway me at all. 1.2 million fatalities a year out of a global population of 7 billion isn't so bad for our species. That means 1.2 million less people around to pollute and use resources. The decrease in deaths will also be bad for those of us who need organ transplants, since the supply will be decreased. Why don't we ban contact sports, motorcycles, and bicycles too. I personally believe that at best self driving cars will be cars with driver aids and at worst, a novelty item like flying cars, at least in our lifetimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would it be possible for a very wealthy corporation or individual to make a profit by "buying" politicians to manipulate stock prices? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 04:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I mean by this is that it is common for billionaires such as the Koch brothers or Sheldon Adelson to influence politics by giving campaign contributions, gifts, etc. to politicians (arguably legalized bribery). Could such a person with tens of billions of dollars buy a large amount of stock in a highly regulated industry, such as alcohol, tobacco, or firearms and then pay politicians in order to make regulations more lax and decrease taxes, therefore making higher sales of these products easier. After doing this would they likely sell the stocks with a value that has gone up significantly and make a profit doing so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any chance that Cadillac may actually make the Elmiraj? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 02:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trevor Phillips in real life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 00:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 00:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/gtavcustoms/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 23:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ram raid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 16:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://gta-myths.wikia.com/wiki/Big_Smoke%27s_Ghost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 03:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he meant 93'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do so few people buy the Chevy SS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 02:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 01:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.lefthandutes.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 01:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you consider converting it to RWD or AWD? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 12:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The malaise era wasn't so bad. Sure, there weren't too many good performance cars coming out of America, but there were still plenty of cars with style. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do I always think of the perfect thing to say after it's too late? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 11:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A reality show where klansmen and neo-Nazi skinheads are forced to live in either Africa or Israel for a year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 05:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ammu Nation on Google Maps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 00:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 23:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tough Crowd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 23:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like one of the cars I saw in one of my dreams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 23:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are about four US legal R34s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some people just have no respect for classic American luxury cars. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 23:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 22:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1978 Chrysler New Yorker Brougham Coupe, because somebody else already said 79' Continental. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some people just have no respect for classic American luxury cars. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 22:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 20:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few days ago I was thinking, what if I started a subreddit called /r/gtainreallife? But then I realized that it would probably become a haven for nutjobs who want to glorify robberies, dangerous driving, mass murder, and other violent crimes which would probably give GTA fans a bad name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Allow redditors to buy karma through microtransactions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 15:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I being shadowbanned? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 14:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 05:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> III era GTA logic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have any suicide bombers ever survived their attacks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 17:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My prediction about GTA Online. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 00:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that the reason why GTA: O is not officially called "GTA V Online" is because when newer games come out like GTA 6, 7, etc. GTA Online will still be the same GTA Online, but with new additions. There will be a major update with each new single player title, which will add and replace some things in Online. This means that there will be new missions, characters, maps, cars, weapons, improved graphics etc., added on as a significant update when each new game is released. In the future, we may be able to drive across state borders or take flights to other regions in GTA: O. Is this a possibility or am I just dreaming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 11:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A classic car that isn't in great condition but has character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
