<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9153</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 11:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely and absolutely disagree!

The Chinese are a communist state and could harness whatever they needed for their opening.  It was spectacular, but as I was watching it, I thought "at what cost?"

The Brits had a terrific opening themselves, and free world.  

However, it was their closing ceremony that I will always remember.

Beat this, anybody free or commie:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jiu0lYQIPqE

Edit: hey all you 5 commie online bastards: ONE SHINING DAY BEIJING WILL BE KNOWN AGAIN AS THE CITY THAT THOMAS JEFFERSON INTENDED IT TO BE:

**PEKING**


[I TRULY LOVE PEKING DUCK](https://www.zazzle.com/rlv/i_love_peking_duck_postcard-ra7a36784ec9d4c71b00b7c15a118f8b3_vgbaq_8byvr_324.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 10:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only during sports and reality shows.

Fun anecdote: when Survivor was a cultural thing, in the season 2 finale, I was watching with my windows open.  Runner-up Colby made a decision that guaranteed him not to win (he took Tina to the final two).  

As soon as he did it, I yelled "YOU FUCKING MORON!" out of frustration and anger at the top of my lungs... and could hear people up and down my block laughing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 10:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I re-checked -- yup somebody posted it in there, but only part 2.  Only 18 upvotes.   

I dunno.

I absolutely love /r/truereddit -- you have great taste in r/'s.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 10:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm kind of happy about this.  Uber's great but I never liked how it puts the costs   benefits of driving for them onto the newbie drivers.  It's not a career driving for Uber.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FIFA's movie about Sepp Blatter "United Passions" is confirmed as the lowest-grossing film in US history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 09:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 09:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this was a fake due to the euro style of printing of the phone number with a period instead of a dash...

but apparently it's true:

http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/wonkblog/wp/2015/06/18/one-photo-perfectly-captures-the-insanity-of-americas-relationship-with-guns/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 08:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I can say is that we were both in ski boots, which is a great equalizer.  

I imagine he wears higher heels or lifts when in day to day public. 

Nothing wrong with this at all -- he needs to project his larger than life persona and I wouldn't fault him.  

I'm just saying I think he's naturally shorter than me -- I, too, was surprised to find this.  

He's still a big MF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 08:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Aleksa Palladino

I have been in love with her since her arc in Boardwalk Empire.  I don't speak metric, but an online converter says she's 5.74147 feet and that Lee Pace of 195cm is 6.39764 feet tall.  That's about right actually.

I'm 5'11" and a 5'7" girl would be roughly at the level of my nose.  Had I grown another four inches, shoulder is about right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 08:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He speaks in a Texas "good ole boy" vernacular.  It's not important.  He rarely says what he really means.  Those guys speak in visual cues.  I love them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 08:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm old enough to remember Jolt cola, the Red Bull/Monster too early energy drink -- this is the soda can Gordon speared at the beginning.

I had one once.  Once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 08:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rumor on Dexter: the reason he became a lumberjack is because as a child in that container, he watched his mother get dismembered by a chainsaw.

I just heard this today and was all Sudden Clarity Clarence.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 07:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet the Turner family isn't going to let GRRM anywhere near that cute doggie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 07:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really?  If I don't hear the confirmation beep, I try to rescan it once or twice, and then the driver usually nods me back into seating. 

I've never been yelled at by a Metrobus driver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 07:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you go:

http://img.pandawhale.com/post-29542-Charlie-Brown-pitching-basebal-GVg5.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 07:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly it for me.  The Orioles seem nice enough but OMG how I hate their owner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 06:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you haven't read this two-part long-form article on the investigation into Silk Road, this is a must-read:

http://www.wired.com/2015/04/silk-road-1/

http://www.wired.com/2015/05/silk-road-2/

I read them in the print edition. Force is a major character, but I don't remember anything about Bridges.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 05:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK Mythbusters, solve this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 05:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know where they'd fit.  Too long for new, I'm sure tech's already seen them, and I think I saw them on truereddit -- I was suprised because I had to wait a month between part 1 and 2 for the next issue to arrive -- I subscribe -- and there it was online.

The formatting of the print articles was really interesting so I waited it out.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 05:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YAY they remembered us in DC! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 05:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If a 1960s show is rerun today, the content may be edited by nine minutes to make room for the extra advertisements.

This really infuriates me.

Anyhow, I DVR basically everything and ffwd through the commericals.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 04:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've met Schwarzenegger while skiing.  I'm 5'11" and he's shorter than me.  Maybe 5'9".

I have never seen shoulders that wide though, even under a ski jacket.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 04:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Staged.  Why would the frisbee thrower throw it to the dog? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 04:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The celtic chief probably trusted a lieutenant to bury them, then the Romans killed anybody who knew where they were buried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 03:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope somebody remembers this article when it comes time to hand out the Pulitzers.  Not only did the journalist write a compelling true crime piece, but also explained the technology seamlessly, not to mention the applicable laws.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 03:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have it -- is that what caused it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 02:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy crap you're right.  All three were about the same age -- Gable was six years older.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 00:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For anybody with interest, this is a must-read:

http://www.wired.com/2015/04/silk-road-1/

http://www.wired.com/2015/05/silk-road-2/

I read them in the print edition.  Force is a major character, but I don't remember anything about Bridges.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 00:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's terrific!  Choreographing that must've been like planning D-Day.  

edited to add:

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Great_Race#Pie_fight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 00:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to see a burning squib.  I've always wondered what a squib is.

https://books.google.com/books?id=FRbrl0pI_VcC pg=PA26 lpg=PA26 dq=tort+squib source=bl ots=22nEyRh3k5 sig=39LgobiCvTosOWIEp2VnktddUfo hl=en sa=X ei=9j-DVbCXErCHsQTT5aP4Bg ved=0CDcQ6AEwBg#v=onepage q=tort%20squib f=false </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 00:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd go see it, too, if I was in the area one day.

I'd wear a Ford Pinto Owners' Association T-shirt though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 23:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still there?  I'm typing to you from a rainy Georgetown.  Do you ever miss DC? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 22:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they should've planted a callback?  I dunno.  It's still a pretty bad finale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 21:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They could even take away his red stapler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 21:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gave up on the first season for that reason.  The red herring of the Muslim school teacher?  I was out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 21:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa.  Thank you for that!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 20:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah he wasn't a draft dodger by any stretch.  He was 34 when Pearl Harbor was bombed.  That being said, he didn't exert himself to serve.  I have read that the WWII vets resented him for all of his war movies.

From wiki:

America's entry into World War II resulted in a deluge of support for the war effort from all sectors of society, and Hollywood was no exception. Wayne was exempted from service due to his age (34 at the time of Pearl Harbor) and family status, classified as 3-A (family deferment). He repeatedly wrote John Ford saying he wanted to enlist, on one occasion inquiring whether he could get into Ford's military unit, but consistently kept postponing it until after "he finished just one or two pictures".[4]:212 Wayne did not attempt to prevent his reclassification as 1-A (draft eligible), but Republic Studios was emphatically resistant to losing him; Herbert J. Yates, President of Republic, threatened Wayne with a lawsuit if he walked away from his contract,[4]:220 and Republic Pictures intervened in the Selective Service process, requesting Wayne's further deferment.[4]:213

Wayne toured U.S. bases and hospitals in the South Pacific for three months in 1943 and 1944.[4]:253 with the USO[27][28][29] By many accounts, Wayne's failure to serve in the military was the most painful experience of his life.[4]:212 His widow later suggested that his patriotism in later decades sprang from guilt, writing: "He would become a 'superpatriot' for the rest of his life trying to atone for staying home."[30]

U.S. National Archives records indicate that Wayne had, in fact, made an application [31] to serve in the OSS, today's equivalent of the CIA, and had been accepted within the U.S. Army's allotted billet to the OSS. William Donovan, OSS Commander, wrote Wayne a letter informing him of his acceptance in to the Field Photographic Unit, but the letter went to his estranged wife Josephine's home. She never told him about it.[32] Donovan also issued an OSS Certificate of Service to Wayne.[33] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 20:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I saw the one with 37 miles (kilometers?) on the odometer and thought the same thing.

It's a Toyota.  Of course it'll eventually start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 20:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lived in London in '89 and can't donate either.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 20:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact: in the movie Invictus, Mandela gives a copy of the poem Invictus to the rugby captain.

In real life, Mandela gave him this speech. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 19:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erin Cummings -- Sparty's wife in Spartacus -- is in the mix, too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 19:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I know.  Armed guards in a very tight space.  I'd had too much vodka the night before.  It would've been a real problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3 carriers, 1 pier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 21:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dave Chappelle wont be making jokes about Rachel Dolezal anytime soon. Heres why. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 10:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick question: has Sepp Blatter attended any of the Women's WC matches? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 08:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Previously unseen photo: "Audrey Hepburn dressed in Givenchy with sunglasses by Oliver Goldsmith (1966)" (detail in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 23:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In White Houses Iraq debate, military brass pushed for doing less </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 12:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poltroon | Definition of poltroon by Merriam-Webster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 09:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25 years ago, 2 Live Crew were arrested for obscenity. Heres the fascinating back story. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 08:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maren Mjelde's insane free kick against Germany </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 08:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kit Harington Judges "Game of Thrones" Character Jon Snow Impressions | Jimmy Kimmel Live </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 07:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jack Warner responds to John Oliver's T T rant: That comedian fool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 04:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Owl you doing, m8? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 09:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The train was so slow I saw 3 legged dogs passing us" FP on his troubled Acela trip to New York, June 9, 2015. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 09:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch John Oliver's Message To Jack Warner That Aired On Trinidad TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 07:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Olympic Theme Los Angeles 1984 - Original - John Williams Conducting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 09:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Debbie Harry at Max's Kansas City, 1975 vs. a Sunn amplifier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 04:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bevo Francis, college basketballs unlikely scoring king, dies at 82 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 21:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Students find key error on SAT's given across U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 09:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Footage of BB's Vince Gilligan directing a new commercial for Jack in the Box </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 08:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A predecessor to the Pledge of Allegiance, written in 1917 and found yesterday during renovation work at an Oklahoma school [1,484px  989px] (and story in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 07:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Haunting chalkboard drawings, frozen in time for 100 years, discovered in Oklahoma school </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 02:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats the point of being humiliated, poked and probed at airports if its not making us safer? (Washington Post) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 11:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cops Use DNA Analysis to Prove Chili's Waiter Spit in Customer's Drink </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 09:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Korea quarantines 1,300 in race against MERS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 19:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FIFA shift bribe blame to dead man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 20:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Europes climate policies have led to more trees being cut down in the U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 09:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patient with fever, recently returned from West Africa, admitted to Johns Hopkins Hospital </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 05:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S.-trained commander of Tajikistans special forces has joined the Islamic State </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 18:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 8 best things from the New York Daily New's Chuck Blazer and FIFA corruption investigation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 02:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi! Michael Garcia thanks you for finding this subreddit. Can somebody set a timer from the moment Sepp wasn't arrested? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 11:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FYI, all hell's breaking loose in FIFA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 09:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What your name tells us about your age, where you live, your political leanings and your job </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 06:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Catastrophic flooding hits Texas and Oklahoma </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 08:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roger Federer steaming over fan who stormed the French Open court for a 'selfie' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 09:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its Memorial Day weekend. One of the mattressiest times of the year. (The Washington Post just unleashed Monica Hesse into the Maryland suburbs.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 09:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man dies after being burned while lighting a cigarette at gas pump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 06:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans gave their lives to defeat the Nazis. The Dutch have never forgotten. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 05:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nationals Park, 5/22/15, and this thing appears to think highly of Bryce Harper if it thinks of anything </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 07:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nationals Park, 5/22/15, and this thing appears to think highly of Bryce Harper if it thinks of anything </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 07:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New trial likely for man convicted of killing intern Chandra Levy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 07:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here is a .gif of that thing dancing around in the early innings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 04:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pershing Park to be redesigned. Has anyone here actually walked through it? (I did once and it's depressing.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 04:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody notice the rainbow Irish shamrock? Since when did reddit insert itself into an issue and since when did we become Google? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 11:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suspect in quadruple killings captured! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 06:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suspect named in killings of four people in Northwest Washington </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 04:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nationals come in at #16 in an ESPN global salary survey across all sports </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 00:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: Metro trains bypassing Bethesda stop because of track fire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 12:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getaround, the app that lets you rent a strangers car, launches in Washington -- or would you let a stranger rent your car? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 17:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Supreme Court: Maryland has been illegally double-taxing residents who pay income tax to other states </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 17:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome to Twin Peaks! (Promo video of the Hooters-style chain that hosted the Waco biker gang shoot-out) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 15:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama announces restrictions on distribution of military-style equipment to police </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 14:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The mystery of the Tsarnaev brothers (Opinion) - CNN.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 09:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Border collies: A 'mouse trap' for geese on the National Mall -- NPS has hired a real character who runs a business called the Geese Police ("Call Us to Get the Flock Out") who uses trained border collies to chase the geese off of the Mall. This video keeps on giving. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 07:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Crazy Drunk Bruce Jenner Look-A-Like At The Bus Stop Sipping On A Beer And Talking To Himself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 10:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HMB while I video a man breaking into a beer cage in Ireland -- warning: umbrella defense. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 10:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "People on the east coast are in the future." Saturday May 16 when it was still Friday May 15 in San Diego. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 08:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A bulletproof cross rises in Karachi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 08:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dupont Circle homeowner: Loud events by Airbnb renters will stop (no more Ja Rule houseparties; he's now limited to 8 occupants) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 07:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bryce Harper, Matt Williams explain their ejections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paragraph 76 of the defamation suit against Rolling Stone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 22:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Verizon is buying AOL for $4.4 billion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 18:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obamas quiet nuclear deal with China raises proliferation concerns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 15:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: Metro suspends train service on Orange, Blue and Silver lines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 14:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudi Arabias King Salman skipping Camp David summit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 14:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Etan Patz trial holdout juror: I wanted to force people to think  including myself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 14:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In South Korea, beauty is skin deep (just make sure to pierce the stubble) -- South Korean Men Join the Skin-Care Craze </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 13:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A blonde who showed up at the cancelled Powder Ridge Fesitval, 1970 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 11:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nepal earthquake victims' families prevented from leaving Qatar FIFA World Cup building sites to attend funerals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 09:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brazilian pet store replaces for-sale pets with shelter pets, not telling customers that they're for free (Portuguese w/ subtitles) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 04:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Full list of aircraft in Friday's WWII Flyby </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 01:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ian Desmond switched his gloves to feel more comfortable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 09:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Django Unchained' actress ordered to apologize to LAPD over racial profiling allegation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 06:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fully restored and flying Mk. I Spitfire up for auction at $3.8 million </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 23:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Star Wars' director pulls out/rumored to be fired </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 21:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Battle of the Oranges - "the largest food fight in Italy" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 21:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A minute of horror, then hours of panic on the path to Mount Everest (long-form Washington Post article on the earthquake   Mt. Everest) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 04:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> R.I.P. MESSENGER: The little spacecraft that could </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 13:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas A M professor tries to flunk his whole class </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 12:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hundreds found dead as details of fresh attack by Boko Haram emerge in Nigeria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 11:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Assads hold on power looks shakier than ever as rebels advance in Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 13:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RomanCessna comments on Who are some "One-Hit Wonders" in fields other than music and compiles a link library of F1 driver Pastor Maldonado's greatest crashes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 12:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Microsoft ad paints a terrifying future where employees are working literally 24 hours a day -- and yes they used "literally" correctly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 09:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HMB after I try drinking it upside down </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 10:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HMC while I try a backflip over a counter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 08:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jim Vance takes first step towards retirement, stepping down from the 11 p.m. newscast in May </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 07:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Law schools try to adapt as job market sours </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 12:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kim Kardashian is one of "The 100 Most Influential People in the World" according to Time Magazine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 09:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another WH fence jumper arrested, but this time from the south </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 11:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Movie footage of the Wright Brothers flying their 1908 Flyer -- is this real or a recreation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 10:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a Malaysian Playboy Controlled the Most Powerful Naval Force on the Planet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 08:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a Malaysian Playboy Controlled the Most Powerful Naval Force on the Planet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 07:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new political order in Scotland threatens to upend the British election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 07:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is going on in this 1954 picture of the Lincoln Memorial? Was traffic around the half-circle only one-way back then? (Source from r/pics in comments.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 08:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edwin Moses - note the international Laureus connection, which was likely why he was there </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 10:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Metro to debut first of its 7000-series cars on Blue Line on April 14 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 02:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little Girl Goes Off On Her Mother For Dyeing Her Hair Blonde! "You Think You Caucasian?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 09:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Critics fear historical amnesia will bring Winter Olympics to Beijing in 2022 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 04:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Collection of Veep Insults (Vol. 1) -- Veep's back on Sunday; this ought to get you warmed up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 04:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is going on with the campaign guy saying "blah-blah" all the time. An inside joke? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 08:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Law school is way too expensive. And only the federal government can fix that. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 00:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rawrr_dinosaurs comments on I met this guy while skiing this weekend, he's cute but his legs are kind of short </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 11:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man's 17 girlfriends show up at the same time when he has a car accident and is hospitalized </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 11:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man missing at sea for 66 days defends survival story: 'God knows I am a truthful man' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 10:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Announcement expected Monday to name Nationals Park host of 2018 All-Star Game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 08:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I will attend opening day. What wisdom can r/nationals give me to give to a pair of five year old twins? Max + Bryce = cute? I need serious calm advice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 11:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New Worlds Oldest Person Is Gertrude Weaver </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 09:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thai Junta Replaces Martial Law With Equally Draconian Security Order </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 09:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Military Suicide: Suicide in the Army Is Not Related to Deployment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 08:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gandalf visits reddit today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 04:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC: Spaghetti Harvest in Ticino (1957) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 08:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody wanna talk about what subreddits have switched with others for April Fool's Day? Ex: r/TIL for r/conspiracy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 07:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dupont Circle in Washington DC. It's difficult driving through it in real life so have fun as a Pac-Man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 06:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Maps turns Dupont Circle into a game of Pac-Man for April Fool's Day. Note the multiple lanes inside the circle. THIS IS AWESOME!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 06:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Active shooter investigated at Inova Fairfax Hospital </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 11:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Virginia State Bar cancels Israel trip for CLE's, citing discriminatory border policies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 11:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mother reportedly locked up son with cerebral palsy and no one noticed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 10:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Addition to Metro safety manual suggests problems at control center during the smoke incident </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 09:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bulldog loves the leaf blower </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 10:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CSI's William Petersen joining the cast for season 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 21:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudi officials say they have launched a military operation in Yemen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 01:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese car company building four-door VW Beetle clone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 05:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> INTOXICATED Driver Causes Major Accident! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 09:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [bug] Never ending reddit is conking out too quickly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 06:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *What's the problem?*   
I reformatted my computer three weeks ago.  Never ending RES used to get me to 1000 or more and is now conking out at 200. 

Just now I got "There doesn't seem to be anything here! (Why not?)" at 25.



*What other browser extensions are installed?*  
On Firefox: AdBlock, BetterPRivacy, FEBE, Ghostery, HTTPS-Everywhere, NoScript, NoSquint, RES, SecureSanitzer, TinEye, and the only new addition to my line-up YouTube High Definition 36.0.

Except for YouTube HD, this was my exact line-up pre-reformatting.  

Is there anything I can do to get back to seeing never ending reddit displaying deep into the 800's?


*Did you read the known issues and search /r/RESissues?*  
Yes but nothing seemed current.



- Night mode: false
- RES Version: 4.5.4
- Browser: Firefox
- Browser Version: 36
- Cookies Enabled: true
- Platform: Windows

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> England prepares a funeral fit for a king </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 03:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Korean Company Commander Saves Recruit When He Drops Grenade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 12:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian meet/cute recorded on dashcam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 11:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glenn Beck: 'I am not a Republican' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 09:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Passenger blasts pepper spray on Metro train </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 03:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/ Karma_Trooper misreads the title "Driving instructors of Reddit, what are your worst student driver experiences?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 07:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cop does not like being called out for parking in a handicap spot to pick up some grub from Mickey D's </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 10:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Instant Karma </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 06:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The origin story of the new r/MFPMPPJWFA, or Music French people might play at a party or just with friends around </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 06:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who says you need a law degree to practice law? (Washington state is launching a program to let paralegals practice family law.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 06:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Complete Parks and Recreation Guide to Los Angeles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 09:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawyers say Canadian-born Ted Cruz is eligible to run for president </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 08:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> u/iowan tries to photograph a hedgehog at night in Tanzania; things go from good to bad to even better </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 05:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kremlin: no truth to stories of Putin's ill health </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 03:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Move over, Reddit: Tumblr is the new front page of the Internet. (Caitlin Dewey, Washington Post) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 11:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit: can anyone clean up the mess behind 'the front page of the internet'? -- an interesting Guardian article on the state we're in these days, both glory and affirmatively evil. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 11:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If You Want Healthy Cows, Feed Them Magnets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 09:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unequal shelves in D.C. school libraries benefit wealthier students </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 11:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Just Because You Did It Doesn't Mean You're Guilty" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 07:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biggest shopping mall in U.S. slated for South Florida </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 09:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I shadowbanned? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 09:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A mostly white voter wave is reshaping politics in D.C. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 11:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bus passenger violently attacks State Trooper sent to arrest her </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 11:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are Archer and Justified the Same Show? A Thorough Investigation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 11:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Knowing your energy personality can save you a lot of money </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 10:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wild Boar Charges Hunter **Warning: graphic** </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 09:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1971 American Tourister "Gorilla" Commercial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 07:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Cute mugshot girl" arrested again, this time for shoplifting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 04:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> D.Dot Transportation Director: DC streetcar may never open </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 04:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Cute mugshot girl" arrested again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 03:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prosecutors criticize D.C. crime labs handling of DNA evidence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 10:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The vigilante copy editors who are correcting Ecuadors graffiti grammar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 10:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First look at the next generation USPS mail truck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 09:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Internal cable from Hillary Clinton's State Department office barred use of personal email </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 09:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sweet Briar College to close because of financial challenges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 08:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton used a private e-mail for government business at State Department </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 07:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
