<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4807</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 23:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've left instructions that when I die, my friends and relatives will all say that Nixon did it. 

He did, in fact, take years off my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 22:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The context was 1972. You kinda had to be there to understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 22:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Please, everybody, when you see an article produced by ProPublica, go to the source and post *that* URL.**

Here are various submissions from [the original source](http://www.reddit.com/r/politics/duplicates/37m9kg/killing_the_colorado_part_one_how_federal_dollars/). This is the first of a five part series -- exactly the sort of intensive investigation that newspapers are no longer willing to pay for, *which is why ProPublica exists.* 

Don't get me wrong: I'm *glad* this story is getting around. But the organization that paid for this reporting deserves the clicks, not the publications that pick it up.

EDIT: Turns out this was [previously submitted here directly from PP.](http://www.reddit.com/r/environment/comments/37h1tc/killing_the_colorado_how_arizona_cotton_is/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 22:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Please, everybody, when you see an article produced by ProPublica, go to the source and post *that* URL.**

Here are various submissions from [the original source](http://www.reddit.com/r/politics/duplicates/37m9kg/killing_the_colorado_part_one_how_federal_dollars/). This is the first of a five part series -- exactly the sort of intensive investigation that newspapers are no longer willing to pay for, *which is why ProPublica exists.* 

Don't get me wrong: I'm *glad* this story is getting around. But the organization that paid for this reporting deserves the clicks, not the publications that pick it up.

   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 22:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you missed something there ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 22:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...waiting for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 22:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oooh, scary! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 22:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I see what you mean.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/We_Will_Rock_You_%28musical%29#Critical_reception) Glad I missed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 21:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It probably will. The volume of submissions here is overwhelming. You might want to post it to /r/cats, which is lower-traffic, higher quality (because it asks for original content) or /r/catpictures. I *know* others there will appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 20:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really is a great pic! You can almost feel his excitement, sniffing the wild air ...

So many of the posts here are lazy, sloppy cellphone snaps of cats asleep on the OP's lap. But this one really stands out, and hopefully may inspire other redditors to try to capture images that more clearly convey their cat's adventures and emotions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 20:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wash your mouth out!

EDIT: OMG, you're speaking about a real possibility. I thought you were making a sick joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 20:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one reason why I love reddit, warts and all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 20:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Animals and kids know: Everything is food until proven otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 20:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's even possible to make Freddie Mercury boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 20:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe this kitten is that old. It looks to be *maybe* six weeks old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 20:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great photo! I'm sure Bruce had a wonderful time -- but shouldn't he wear a collar if he's going out alone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 20:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cute enough for /r/corgibutts ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 20:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Double trouble! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 20:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't happen to a better bunch of shithead lawyers. Play on, SpreadTheLove! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 19:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the first segment of a five part series from ProPublica. [More here.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=36ZOYohGuSk utm_source=et utm_medium=email utm_campaign=dailynewsletter utm_content= utm_name=) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Killing the Colorado, Part One: How federal dollars are financing the water crisis in the West </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 19:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 19:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just said more about yourself than about anything I wrote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 19:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not even reading your own comments correctly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 19:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  this poll omits Elizabeth Warren

Who will. not. run.

Why do people persist in this fantasy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 19:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's one BIG kitty! That's about three times the size of my oldest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 18:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In the case of pets and children: they're stupid.

Not stupid; they just can't read. Also, it's sweet, and apparently tastes good. Do you happen to know if this treatment works for animals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 18:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much does she weigh? (How much of that fluff is fur?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 18:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [And this doesn't help.](http://www.boston.com/news/nation/2015/05/01/news-media-won-cover-bernie-sanders-because-news-media-won-cover-bernie-sanders/Fd4VrpGvVqhACVdPuVjOlM/story.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Pennsylvania newspaper is very sorry it printed a letter calling for Obamas execution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 18:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 18:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ... years of "divisive rhetoric" made the violent phrasing seem normal.

So much for editorial judgment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Pennsylvania newspaper is very sorry it printed a letter calling for Obamas execution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 18:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 18:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might help to leave the radio on, tuned to a good classical music station. That seems to keep our cats happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 17:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The nearest [Rent-a-Wreck](https://www.rentawreck.com/cheap-car-rental-akron-OH.htm) is in Akron, but it's worth a call and might be worth going that far to pick up depending on rates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 17:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. But I posted this because I think the dynamic cited in the headline is a real problem, and not just on the Sanders campaign. I've been in this business along time, and the amount of self-censorship I see today based on what's assumed to be the consensus about what's worth covering is quite alarming. I think it's partially a function of overvaluing what readers want, rather than an editorial vision of what readers need to know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 17:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I hate Kroger. 

If all you've seen are their stores along High Street or in student/poor neighborhoods, that's understandable. But go look at one of their best Marketplace stores and try to say that again. The variation in quality is infuriating, but they do have some very good stores.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 17:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before there was an actual study, there was [this prescient satire, written in 2001.](http://angelamotorman.blogspot.com/2007/04/study-shows-rats-have-better-ethics.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 17:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I wrote [this piece about rats](http://angelamotorman.blogspot.com/2007/04/study-shows-rats-have-better-ethics.html) in 2001, it was a satirical news item for April Fool's Day. Ten years later, [science caught up with satire](http://www.sciencemag.org/content/334/6061/1427). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 03:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  leucism

[Check out this example.](http://mcmikephoto.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/01/LeucisticEagleNooksackMTMScreen6219.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plane Wreckage Found in Grand Canyon: Likely from missing 2011 aircraft </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 02:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 23:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't sure where to ask this in general

You might also ask at /r/Pets and /r/Dogs to get more opinions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 22:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Good Sam" funds -- which are donations from wealthier clients -- are never advertised, and are used at the discretion of  the vet. I've had good luck with just being upfront at the first appointment about the fact that we have almost no money. 

I hope you will be able to get him in sooner than later, because while this could be a big nothing, it could also be an upper respiratory infection. 

Adding, I once found a filthy, scrawny white kitten so close to death that we named him Spike (after Buffy's undead boyfriend). With a little help from an understanding vet, we saved his tiny life -- and he's now a big, robust 9 year old! So please come back and show us photos of your kitten once he's feeling all better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 22:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know how you feel. But he will always be part of you. Maybe [this](http://img1.etsystatic.com/000/0/6011550/il_fullxfull.330687981.jpg) will be of some comfort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> News Media Wont Cover Bernie Sanders Because News Media Wont Cover Bernie Sanders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 21:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 21:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So sorry for your loss. What was this handsome fellow's name? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 21:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here today, gone tomorrow...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 20:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the nicest things about cats is that -- unlike  everybody else you run into day to day -- they *just don't care* about money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 20:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Somebody* doesn't like the outdoors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 08:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no info here, because this isn't imgur -- it's reddit.

And this type of post is against this subreddit's rules (see the sidebar), so it will be removed sooner than later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 08:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> go away, idiot spammer.

reported. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 08:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So did you take little Trivia home with you? She's irresistible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 08:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You're gonna need this.](http://www.alleycat.org/Page.aspx?pid=289)

Trust me: if you don't trap and neuter these kittens and their mom, the next time you turn around you'll have three, four or five litters in your back yard. Best to deal with it now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 08:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask him for a picture of Arlo with his granddaughter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 08:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For whoever reported this comment: it isn't doxxing. It's public info about a public figure.

OTOH, it's also unnecessary, and because of that it looks like an invitation to harass. So let's keep such comments to a minimum, please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over the Edge 3D: Interactive 3D map of all deaths in Grand Canyon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 08:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over the Edge 3D: Interactive 3D map of all deaths in Grand Canyon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 08:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 08:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inspired, and based on the book, by Ghiglieri, M. P. and Myers, T. M. (2012) Over the Edge: Death in Grand Canyon, this map is presented in Chromadepth and is best viewed with Chromadepth 3D glasses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over the Edge 3D: Interactive 3D map of all deaths in Grand Canyon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 08:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 02:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All true. Every defendant has the right to the assumption of innocence, and to a vigorous defense at trial. But usually this level of comment from defense counsel is saved for the trial, rather than trying the case in the press by blaming the victim.

This particular lawyer, whose bread and butter is DUI cases, has a long-standing obsession with the way consent is defined. Is it ideological? Is it a career move? I don't know, but I do think this interview is over the top. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 00:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reyes' attorneys are calling the women opportunists.

"What police failed to mention is that the victims were present during the game, called to Mr. Reyes, waited for him after the game," defense attorney Brad Koffel told the judge Tuesday. "They went out and had drinks afterwards. They voluntarily went up to his hotel room."

**None of which matters.** What year is this, anyway?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 00:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They mean packing material (from appliances), not food containers, but it's a start.

And no, I have no idea what they plan to do with it. But at least it won't be available for my demented feline to keep chewing on, and that's what matters right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You CAN recycle styrofoam -- at least some of it -- this weekend at Chadwick Arboretum Community Recycling Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 00:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 22:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure there's any right way, given [this guy's bias](http://www.reddit.com/r/fatpeoplehate/comments/347opv/xpost_rtia_there_is_no_such_thing_as_a_small_fat/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 22:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This bitter 111-day strike was more closely-watched than most strikes in the US because it was so violent and so disruptive to business. [This article puts the strike in context](https://www.wsws.org/en/articles/2006/01/mine-j25.html), detailing the history of both the industry and the union, in a way that other, less "biased" sources can't match.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The National Coal Strike of 1977-78: A Discussion with Local UMWA Members </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 22:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 21:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 1985, the strike by meatpackers at Hormel's Austin MN plant, represented by United Food And Commercial Workers Local P-9, was the cause celebre of the labor-oriented left in the US, gaining wide support nationally from everyone to the left of Ronald Reagan. Only a handful of trade unionists and labor activists disagreed with the strategy of the local, which pitted it against the national union as well as the bosses. P-9 supporters were outraged by the criticism, which history has vindicated. The dispute has long-lasting implications for all labor organizing, and deserves the closer look it did not get at the time.

The linked piece was written while the strike was ongoing, but it remains the most complete explanation of the issues. It's a very long read, but the key graf is this one:

The outcome of the struggle between industrial unionism
and enterprise unionism will determine the nature of the labor movement in decades to come. Concessions can be won back in later bargaining, as many unions have shown. But a fundamental shift to enterprise unionism will destroy whatever class consciousness still exists in the labor movement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Second Look at the Hormel Strike: one of the most highly-touted labor struggles of the 1980s wasn't what its supporters assumed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 21:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 21:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think you're just hating on radicals for no reason, frankly. 

I can't read past this. You clearly have no idea how absurd that assumption is, but you should have caught a hint by now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 20:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, and that's one reason why I don't want to be the submitter there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 20:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a noble effort, but it's unlikely that backpack was left there by its owner, don't you think? It's more likely that you found a pack that had been ripped off and discarded by the thief after everything of value was removed. If there was mail in it, it presumably showed a street address -- is there any possibility that you could take the further step of going back to the bridge, getting the pack and taking it to that address? Even if it's soaking wet by the time you get there, I bet Abigail G. would rather have it than not! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 20:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You did the right thing. I'm just amazed that they took the hint! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 20:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. If you recognized my username, you'd know it's true. I've had to get mods and admins involved on more than one occasion. Having me as OP on such a post would get it downvoted and turned into a flamewar.

Why would you *not* want to do it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 20:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Did it occur to you that a lot of those people have the same sort of analysis of all this that I have? Because they do. 

I suspect that I have a better handle on who does this work nationwide than you do -- if we're talking about people who primarily build organizations and coalitions rather than people who turn out for demonstrations. In my experience, the latter group have almost no idea who the activists are *in their own cities*, let alone nationally, who have been working on this issue for decades. They often don't even know whether DOJ has had any previous involvement with police departments in their own state -- which is such basic ignorance it blows my mind. 

There are *plenty* of very radical people involved in the national movement for police accountability, but they are not anarchists. They are people who have learned the cost of letting the perfect become the enemy of the good, and they are not about to let that happen again.

DOJ intervention does make a difference. I live in a city that was forced into a settlement, and although there are still problems, policing here is nothing like it was before. It is literally a life and death difference for people here, so hearing you dismiss it as "an attempt to sap the energy of movements with shallow reformism" is incredibly insulting.

I don't think you and I will get any closer to agreement with further arguments here, but please, get to know the people who were on this case before you woke up. It will expand your political horizons and give you lots more leaders to respect.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 19:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a good person to do it, for several reasons including the fact that I have a small posse of haters who follow me around reddit and downvote everything I post. So, please: lead on! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 19:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Extremely important question: how did you "send the dogs home"? Did you just tell them to go? I'd be afraid they'd insist on coming along for the whole trip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 19:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't it be a good idea to cross-post this to /r/OSU and /r/Columbus, if not also /r/Ohio? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 03:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [citation needed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 03:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell that to residents of cities where long-term campaigns for accountability have made real differences. From your grand theoretical anarchist heights, you're trashing the work of thousands of community activists over many decades because you think your analysis of hierarchy is more important than their real life struggles for civilian review, better training and better policy.

You didn't say "give up" in so many words, but that was the clear message your vague rant delivered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 00:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, so we should just give up, then. I see. Well, thanks for dropping that "knowledge" on us. 

Anyone else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 00:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where'd you find that --Santa Barbara beach? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 00:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The operator end of a cat toy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cleveland reaches settlement with Justice Department over police conduct </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 23:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cleveland reaches settlement with Justice Department over police conduct </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 23:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 23:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, cats hunt. I was just making fun of the idea that domestic cats, not habitat loss, is responsible for large-scale bird loss.

You *can* teach her not to hunt, BTW. She's bringing you gifts, and if you make her understand that you don't want her to do that, she may stop. I've had best success with lecturing the cat: they absolutely hate being lectured. It's much more effective than a spray bottle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 22:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you saying American soldiers in general today have an easier time in war, or that soldiers who ignored the warnings and went to Iraq anyway are less deserving than those who fought in a just war?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 22:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  All I know is that I'm not anywhere fighting and other people are.

For *any* of the sacrifices made by American soldiers to mean anything, it's incumbent on *every* American to know and care about where and why that fighting is happening. Some wars are just, some are wars of aggression to control resources or trade. 

I really hope your comment was just overgeneralizing, not jingoism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 19:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is that? The one time I tried to visit friends in Tucson, there were so many cockroaches in their otherwise nice house that we (native New Yorkers) couldn't sleep and fled the next morning, days ahead of schedule. What causes this level of infestation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 18:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait: you mean it wasn't those evil domestic cats? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 11:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Er, somebody didn't bother to read the sidebar... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 11:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/seniorkitties would be happy to see him! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 03:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reply, and a sincere wish for the very best luck to all of you in your new home! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 18:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking as an Ohioan: we're already horrified by having Kasich as governor -- this statement just makes it that much more urgent to stop Kasich before he manages to slither onto the national stage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 18:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something worth calling the EPA over. This is a serious reply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 18:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lists which are always dominated by cities in the Sunbelt.

Maybe because they have, y'know, *sun*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 18:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Details, details. It must have been true: a constituent told her that she heard it from her son, who *was there*.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 11:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you somehow miss her claim that 5,000 Black men were executed in the aftermath of Katrina, their bodies sunk in the swamp, their names entered into a Pentagon computer, their families never notified?

McKinney has been batshit  insane for many years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 06:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aside from everything else about your crusade to be right at any cost, this thread was about schools *in the 1960s*. 

In any case, we're done here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 06:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  When the universe decides you need a cat, who are you to argue?

...and the timing is always so convenient! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 06:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn straight! You let that toilet paper get started, and it'll take over the whole house. The only defense is offense: tear that sucker to *shreds*. It'll be years before any roll of TP is fool enough to come by this way again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 06:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It seems he does this a lot

Exactly why I never bought one for my beloved ~~tank~~ cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 06:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm having a hard time imagining cuddling in bed with a chicken! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 06:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stevie is apparently a practitioner of advanced [Slackitude.](http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=slackitude)

Probably another [Friend of Bob](http://reasonswhyimhappy.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/07/slack.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 05:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've completely misunderstood my meaning. I was saying your situation is the exception to my original comment about never, ever re-homing a pet. You're doing it exactly right, and I'm glad this kitty has a better home now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 05:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this. ISPCA's malfeasance has done a lot of damage to the reputation of all humane and welfare organizations. You've put the emphasis right where it belongs: on individual donors' responsibility to look this stuff up on Guidestar or Charity Navigator, but to keep on donating.

I found [this partial explanation of the differences](http://www.differencebetween.info/difference-between-aspca-and-spca) at the website most people will trust to tell them which is which. 

I have to wonder why this three year old article is suddenly floating around again now...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 05:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you talking about?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 05:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of which is surprising, since OP's submission history seems to be all about picking stupid fights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 05:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Did someone say Diaspora?](http://gizmodo.com/5949784/whatever-happened-to-facebook-killer-diaspora) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 05:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Caera is beautiful. And you are a good person. May you have many happy days together! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 05:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll have to do some explaining before you can get karma for this.

Plus, this is not the right reddit for seeking assistance, so this post may be removed sooner than later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 05:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moving across national borders is a special case, and arranging for a (possibly permanent) foster home for the duration is the best way to deal with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 05:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How nice for you that you had a good experience in a co-ed HS, just like millions of other girls. Now please stop attributing to me the ideas you want to argue against. Apparently, "YMMV" went right over your head.

I never suggested you "suffered'. The schools I spoke about are not the caricature you posit but (as I said) rigorously academic prep schools. 

You have a chip on your shoulder about this that no amount of discussion will fix. You'll have to find someone else to argue with.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gov. John Kasich on Friday erased the right of independent in-home health-care and child-care workers to collectively bargain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 01:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 01:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I'd known to teach kittens while young to expect to get their nails trimmed, their teeth brushed and their ears cleaned on a regular basis for the rest of their lives.

But mostly, I wish everyone knew, before adopting a pet, that it's a lifetime commitment or it's nothing. Cats live to be older than many redditors reading this -- one of ours is turning 20 this summer. Pets are not props for a lagging social life, and they're not decor for a particular lifestyle. You don't "give away" pets when living with them becomes inconvenient. People who do this deserve sharp criticism, at best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 22:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What will you do for them? Do you need info about how to care for baby kittens? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 21:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah? You and what coalition? You show up here as a brand new anonymous account, throw out a call and expect anything to come of it? At best, this post is an insult to all the people who actually do the work necessary to *organize* the kind of mass movement that deserves support.

Mostly, though, it's just pathetic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Cleveland police officer who climbed onto the hood of a car after a chase and fired repeatedly at its unarmed occupants, both of them black, in 2012 was acquitted of manslaughter on Saturday by an Ohio judge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 21:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 19:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some vets will give you a Good Samaritan discount if they know you've just rescued a stray -- it's worth asking. Also, look for rescue organizations in your general area, which may be able to help with this. Where are you located? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 18:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious: Was that a guess, or did you use [ELA?](http://fotoforensics.com/analysis.php?id=5164066968486e7805cb2fcbbe867210144e6803.1657160) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 18:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1500+ karma points in 4 hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 18:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you checked out the **reddit Guide to Columbus**  linked in the sidebar? It has listings of recommended bars and restaurants.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 00:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That eyeliner! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 00:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 23:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have guessed NY's favorite would be "a slice". It's certainly the most sought-after, by natives and tourists alike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 23:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because of the subject, it feels uncharitable, but somebody has to say it: this post isn't extraordinary. Thousands of people have stories from that day, and this is far and away the least interesting one I've ever read. This reddit deserves higher standards for what constitutes a "gem". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Native American mascots have to go, Oregon State Board of Education rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 22:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Native American mascots have to go, Oregon State Board of Education rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 22:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 22:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, cute baby *what*? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 22:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What post is this a reply to? Where in the world is Henry?

EDIT: Never mind. This post is just incompetent spam from a new user whose only other post was also promoting one of her books -- but there, she remembered to include the name of the book and her website address. I'm reporting this as spam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 22:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (1) Is your cat neutered? If not, do that ASAP.  

(2) When you go to open the door, only open it enough to put your foot in the opening, and use that and your voice ("Back! Back! Back!") to make sure the cat can't come through. You'll have to retrain *yourselves* to open the door differently, but once you learn it, he'll never get out again. [Source: eight years living with *five* escape artists.] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 22:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **GO TO THE VET NOW!** Not tomorrow; right this minute. This is a serious emergency -- that stuff is a nerve poison, and an overdoes could easily kill your cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is the original report from which somebody ripped off those pictures and reposted them, without credit, to imgur.](http://www.reddit.com/r/RATS/comments/36pmxq/african_herorats_detect_landmines_and_tuberculosis/crgj80f?context=3) Next time you see something that professionally produced on imgur, please take the time to find and credit the people who did the work. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A New Map From Foursquare Reveals the Highly Specific Food Tastes of All 50 States </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That map will even show you where to buy them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio craves pierogies:A new map uses Foursquare data to reveal the most unique tastes in food or drink, state by state </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 17:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have attended co-ed schools, so I do know the difference. I was just lucky enough to attend an all-girls school for the critical years when we were all hormonally deranged and socially insecure. If you had no problems in a mixed school, you're lucky. The  problems girls in co-ed schools have are of the sort that are hardest to see, because they consist of omissions: not being as assertive or competitive as they would if not competing for  approval from potential dates; not forming the same kind of intellectually-based friendships with other girls, etc.

EDIT: Adding, this is not just my opinion. There is plenty of research that has consistently found the same result over many decades: [single-sex school produce girls who are academically better prepared, more science oriented and more likely to continue their education.](http://newsroom.ucla.edu/releases/graduates-of-all-girls-schools-85038)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 19:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He loves you! My tiny calico used to bring home multiple snakes every spring, to the point where we had to put a sign on the inside of the front door cautioning everyone to beware of cats bearing snakes: if you didn't check before opening the door, she'd run right past you to deposit her "gift" in the middle of the LR floor. Once I took the same snake away from her multiple times, releasing it back into a ravine nearby, only to have her go find the damn thing and bring it back over and over. 

And the thing is, kitties are so *proud* of the gifts they bring that it's hard to get really mad at them for doing what they're born to do.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 19:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes:  that's the imgur rip-off of the full story -- this is the original source. I saw that album on imgur, recognized that it *must* have come from some journalistic source, because it was too detailed and professionally shot to be just "some guy on the internet", and so went looking for the original source. As a journalist, I'm allergic to rip-offs that don't credit the journalists who did the work.

Oh, I'm sorry -- were you chastising *me* for failing to notice that this had "already been submitted"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 12:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Earliest cite is @susannawolff on April 15, 2013 for [CollegeHumor.com](http://www.collegehumor.com/post/6883988/where-should-you-post-that-thing-you-want-to-share) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NJ.com Editorial: Gov. Christie loses his marbles on national TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 07:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NJ.com Editorial: Gov. Christie loses his marbles on national TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 07:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newark Star-Ledger Editorial: "Gov. Christie loses his marbles on national TV" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 07:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 06:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's infinitely easier to grow into a confident, educated woman at an all-girls high school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 06:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's see if we can elect a democratic socialist before jumping to any conclusions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 06:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so sorry for your loss. [May this thought be a comfort to you.](http://img1.etsystatic.com/000/0/6011550/il_fullxfull.330687981.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 06:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting to note that the AP story as published in the NYT headlines Metzker as a journalist, but omits any description of his work while citing a source speculating that this was a crime of passion...

EDIT: Here is more detail, and a much sharper analysis, from the [Committee to Protect Journalists.](https://cpj.org/2015/05/brazilian-blogger-found-decapitated-in-minas-gerai.php). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brazil blogger known for reporting on corruption found decapitated: Evany Jos Metzker, who had investigated child prostitution and drug dealing, found dead five days after being reported missing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 06:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 05:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this post. Laws about euthanizing animals that have bitten humans are changing, but some places still insist on this. I think I'd do exactly what you've done, and I hope it goes well for all of you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 05:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the feature story about this, with lots more photos.](http://www.abc.net.au/radionational/programs/latenightlive/african-herorats-detect-landmines-and-tuberculosis/6481122) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> African HeroRats detect landmines and tuberculosis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 05:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> African HeroRats detect landmines and tuberculosis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 05:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> African HeroRats detect landmines and tuberculosis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 04:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> African HeroRats detect landmines and tuberculosis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 04:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 23:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One nonreligious group doing this is [**Feed The Streets**, a project of the group Pursuing Our Dreams](https://www.facebook.com/PursuingOurDreams). I like this one because it's grounded in a plan to grow community.

More info about them and the local affiliate of the national group #Hashtaglunchbag -- which isn't connected to any church but is apparently motivated by faith -- can be found in news coverage [here](http://www.columbusunderground.com/local-groups-feed-homeless-in-columbus-one-meal-at-a-time-sx1) and [here](http://www.dispatch.com/content/stories/local/2015/02/23/volunteers-make-take-meals-to-homeless-each-month.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 23:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry for your loss. Baxter looked like a lovely friend.

This is a terrible way to learn it, but perhaps your experience can help others get the lesson that cats *always* freak out during a move, and need to be carefully monitored during the run-up and contained during the move itself. Four of my cats flipped out and fled while I was loading the car for the last bit of a move, and I had to stay behind for three days in an empty house before I was able to round them up. I was lucky that time, but I should have known better because it wasn't the first time I'd lost a cat while moving.

May all of us be extra careful with our fur friends hereafter, and may you be comforted by your memories of handsome Baxter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 23:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not fiction. That's true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 23:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and just for symmetry, here's a fan page that collects links to all the works of [Theodore Sturgeon](http://www.physics.emory.edu/faculty/weeks//misc/sturgeon.html), whose name and career [inspired the creation of Kilgore Trout](https://books.google.com/books?id=EvCsY3IEJ14C pg=PA173 lpg=PA173 dq=theodore+sturgeon+kilgore+trout source=bl ots=P10yCAL9a9 sig=0_TxLIKZSYrdXkicb8RhgzqyEKc hl=en sa=X ei=xvlcVfPbHYPksATw1YGQDQ ved=0CFoQ6AEwBw#v=onepage q=theodore%20sturgeon%20kilgore%20trout f=false). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 23:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... nothing in [the last round of answers](http://www.reddit.com/r/Columbus/comments/1s5e19/good_guitar_tech/) worked out for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 22:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Once you get the footage, I'm not really sure what you would do with it...

Anybody who does this should remember that events like concerts and festivals usually prohibit commercial use of photos of those events, and there's a whole industry of researchers looking around online for images violating those bans. Plus, the big ones have major police presence (that includes OHP), which could bring unwanted attention to the drone operator.

EDIT: [Here's some info on current FAA regs for drones.](http://www.faa.gov/news/updates/?newsid=76240).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 22:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you think it's not "what Columbus is all about", why not tell us what you think IS appropriate?

I sorta like it, but am open to change (as always).

EDIT: Having just looked at the two you suggested, I amend my view: our current header is much better than either one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 22:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have *any* idea how completely you're presenting as a stereotypical sophomore? There's a reason for the cliche that a little knowledge is a dangerous thing. 

Anyway, go on about feeling superior. We're done here.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 22:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AFAIK it's just a listing, although I suspect they wouldn't list any org with a seriously bad rep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 20:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay then, as an editor trained as a lexicographer (in which field, what the public thinks *matters absolutely*) I say to you: 

It's a variant. Deal with it.

Anyway, don't you have homework to do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a pet-friendly apartment? Columbus Dog Connection has just updated their excellent list of resources (for cats, too!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 20:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Columbus Dog Connection](http://www.columbusdogconnection.com/dog_cat_info.htm) can help you find vets, trainers, fence companies, dog-friendly apartments, insurance, food pantries, you name it. This is a rare and precious resource that deserves support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 19:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your car is new and high-end, you probably won't be stopped for this on city streets around central Ohio. Driving while poor is another thing altogether -- that's when "no front plate" becomes another pretext for stop and ticket in places like Worthington and Dublin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 19:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a variant, as recognized here by at least two dozen redditors who upvoted it over the last two months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 19:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to a prep school, not a Catholic school, and uniforms had been worn there since the founding. And our uniforms weren't just pieces you buy anywhere, they were made by one specific outfitter, so the price issue was even worse for students whose families were not rich. 

Still, I'm incredibly grateful for having attended a school where uniforms were required and academics were primary. (I'm also glad there were no boys around to confuse us about how smart we all were!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 19:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I'm not a reformist so I don't bother myself too much with the impact of reforms.

The reform struggle is the real world that you live in, and it's filled with people who should have socialist politics (and very often do), so you'd do well to start taking notice. It's not selling out to recognize, appreciate and even work in reform struggles -- but not knowing the whole political terrain in front of you is a serious mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Starting up with uniforms meant having no hand-me-downs

My school and many others had a "little shop" where students could buy used uniforms for exactly that reason. Socks and shoes were the only thing we didn't buy used. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shift dresses, yes; miniskirts, no. It would have to have been *very* late 60s for those skirts to have such high hemlines. In the mid-60s, the rule in many schools was still that the hem had to touch the floor when the wearer was kneeling. (I have no idea where that standard came from, but it was everywhere.)

Anyway, another commenter has cited the original source as saying it was 1972, which looks exactly right to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one area in which we could take a lesson from Mississippi. Sometimes the old ways are just plain better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to give back a bit as well as provide a service for a non-profit or smaller Healthcare facility 

Good on you! Everybody should have such reflexes.

[Columbus Free Clinic](http://www.columbusfreeclinic.com/index.html) -- which is exactly what it says it is --has volunteer openings for medical, pharmacy, laboratory and social services.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats Lurking Behind the Suicides at Pine Ridge? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 19:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats Lurking Behind the Pine Ridge Suicides? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 19:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News pundit Bill O'Reilly reportedly beat his wife in front of his daughter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 16:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News pundit Bill O'Reilly reportedly beat his wife in front of his daughter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 16:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No, Just Because Seymour Hersh Had The Same Story As You, It's Not 'Plagiarism' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 23:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Great Grief: How To Cope with Losing Our World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 19:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FHRITP phenomenon: CBC journalists share 'mortifying' experiences </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 17:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FHRITP phenomenon: CBC journalists share 'mortifying' experiences </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 17:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FHRITP phenomenon: CBC journalists share 'mortifying' experiences </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 17:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rescue kitten reality TV: Live streaming 5 tiny kittens from birth to adoption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 18:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Milwaukee Experiment: What can one prosecutor do about the mass incarceration of African-Americans? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 18:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At Zappos, 210 employees decide to leave rather than work with no bosses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 18:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legislators Introduce Bill Calling For Nationwide Ban On Non-Disparagement Clauses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 07:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The wealthiest ZIP codes in America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 22:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toxically Pure: Joe Bageant drops out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 20:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Self-defense tips against fake news </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 17:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Self-defense tips against fake news </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 17:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What your levels of sensitivity say about you </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 23:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Newsfeed of Fear:You wouldn't know it from the headlines, but things are getting better. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 17:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martha Stewart's Spring Cleaning Checklist: Don't forget to dust your refrigerator coils! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 08:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hal-An-Tow: from Cornwall, an ancient ritual procession song to usher in the summertime </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 07:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mistaken Fox News reporter on Baltimore shooting report: We dont have to worry that much about confirmation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 18:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mistaken Fox News reporter on Baltimore shooting report: We dont have to worry that much about confirmation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 18:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is why we don't hike Grand Canyon in the summer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 17:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> D.A.R.E. gets duped by anti-pot satire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 02:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 1928 newlyweds Glen and Bessie Hyde decided to take a boat trip down the Colorado River. Two months later, after a resupply stop at the South Rim, they vanished without a trace, leaving their boat eerily intact. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 14:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drilling Chaco: What's actually at stake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 21:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drilling Chaco: What's actually at stake -- It's the archaeological landscape beyond New Mexico's Chaco Canyon that is most threatened </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 21:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drilling Chaco: What's actually at stake / It's the archaeological landscape beyond New Mexico's Chaco Canyon that is most threatened </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 21:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
