<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4065</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 23:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah, wish I could help. I don't know what's available around there. I've heard of sovernet and vtel as providers, you could look them up. Not sure if Fairpoint serves there, but their service is hit-or-miss depending on where (ie. you exact house location relative to their equipment) you live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 23:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> depends on where you live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 20:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man...that worries me. If an offensive lineman isn't motivated by the guy lining up across from him bent on ripping apart the guy he's paid to protect then he'll never be motivated. No amount of money or yelling would do it. Change of scenery...well we'll see I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 20:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This helps us how? Another mediocre guy for defenses to humiliate on their short journey to Tannehill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 18:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike Sherman is not the problem.

1) Tannehill hands the ball to the Bills for a TD on the first drive, then fumbles for them in the 4th quarter when we had the lead.
2) Our o-line lets more guys in than a cheap hooker. Yesterday's "improved" o-line performance (measuring sacks) was a mask. Tannehill was able to buy more time by rolling out and we ran better, but they did not play better.

It's really easy to call out coaches as the problem, but you don't know what play was called, when Tannehill audibled out, how they prepared...do you expect Sherman to suit up and play tackle? Or run on the field and stop Tannehill's occasional bad decision? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Courtesy warning about windows 8.1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-20 03:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing the game just fine on windows 8, but it constantly crashes on 8.1. Googling shows others with similar issues. 

Be warned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 18:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the suggestion, I'll take a look at Roku! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Micca MPLAY-HD 1080p - Riddit's Thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 14:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to get something to play digital movies I have on a hard drive on my TV (I've tried Plex through my blu-ray and for some reason it always craps out after about 45 minutes).

Any experience with the below? Other recommendations?

http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B002XVBAKI/ref=s9_wish_gw_d98_g23_ir03?ie=UTF8 colid=3TQMIRNINX5I2 coliid=IOGBZQZWD5HFT pf_rd_m=ATVPDKIKX0DER pf_rd_s=center-2 pf_rd_r=1XWC4QAXE16F4RCAR8MA pf_rd_t=101 pf_rd_p=1630072222 pf_rd_i=507846 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 18:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taking away from EMDs is speculation. After the most recent Penguin update I'm seeing multiple reports of EMDs rebounding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 22:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just had to totally furnish my place (divorce sad face). I found Willie D's to have good deals on some quality stuff.

Ashley Furniture too depending on your price range. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 22:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Latoya? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 19:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awesome! needs to be compiled into a wallpaper...maybe a project for the weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-29 00:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like farts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 05:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should have guessed it was you since the pose was so on. 

Definitely post your film! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 00:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good job dude. I like your concept, and your hunter buddy has a great stance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 02:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where can I stream this with decent quality? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best place to stream Thursday night football? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 02:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 17:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a good movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 18:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Love to hear that! These players deserve that support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patriots vs. Falcons next week. Their first true test. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 02:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like the Phins have played better teams than the Pats (and we've been on the road), and with us both at 3-0 it'll be good to see how the Pats do against the Falcons next week. 

I'm sure the dirty birds will be pissed too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 02:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome to hear! I hope that all those people experiencing a great win will mean more will return for future games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 01:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ditto. I'm stuck in New England. If I was around Miami I'd have season tickets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How great was it to hear noise from a crowd!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 01:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't heard noise like that from the Dolphins stadium since Marino! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 18:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool! Please share your final! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 14:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Them holding hands makes it a bromance movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 23:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UVM alumn here. I drive by that spot often. Apparently not at the right times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 03:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been there. Confront him in public, in front of his friends. Be fearless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 03:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1,2,3,4. You know what I mean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 23:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crappy quality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 19:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the detail! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I fix large screw holes, and holes filled with cement, in wall? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 18:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi reddit.

I want to paint a wall in my new place and there are large screw holes (where material is actually protruding out) and a few holes that look like their were filled with some cement like material -- where the cement is not flush but again protruding out.

Pictures: http://imgur.com/a/kl8Iz

What's the best way to fix these? Probably a noob question, but I'm a noob to this kind of stuff.

Thanks for any help!

oh, and I'm in New England (U.S.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-08 15:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Introduce yourself and ask people about themselves. Get them talking, people love talking about themselves. 

There's an expression that I use to my advantage "being interested is interesting".   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 17:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was called "Puppy Go Home." A card game I would play with my Dad where the rules would change based on the cards I had. I always won, go figure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 15:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good points.

As you were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 13:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not against balance, you just may not understand the rest of the mod. Good players can dead stop a hunter (I can the majority of the time on standard servers), and great ones can cut a smoker's tongue before being wrapped in it (I have a tougher time with that one).

Play on evilmania's servers and you'll see what I mean. Infected teams can select the special infected they want to be (can't duplicate an infected without spending points that are collected by playing) and Survivors can purchase weapons or health. It's not for everyone, but if you've been playing for a while and are fairly skilled it adds another level of strategy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 02:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 00:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Browns home opener? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 00:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shouldn't quit just because your team isn't doing well. 

Sounds like you were on a modded server.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 20:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your girlfriend does for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 13:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa whoa whoa!

Before this gets all ugly in here let's get something very clear. They're called "Caucasians". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 13:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and now it's down :( 

someone upload it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 07:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. Great character development. Hulk had heart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 04:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of like Seinfeld for me. He just IS funny. He could recite a recipe for Mexican wedding cakes and I'd laugh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 04:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turkey I assume.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 14:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moving to the noosk Friday. What have I done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-25 20:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The average person eats 8 spiders a year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-25 15:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try that some day. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-25 15:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw that movie for a different reason. Dat ass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 20:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No fucking way.

No.

Fucking.

Way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 22:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You use up more ammo that way. 

Just get better at aiming :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 04:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a simple man with simple tastes. Nothing beats an Old El Paso taco dinner kit. So, for restaurant tacos I like Moes and Chipotle, but if you are searching for "true" Mexican then look elsewhere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 23:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see the tree of life.

Conspiracy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 18:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed on the Browns game.

The first few games are scary. But...with this team, with so many being new and Philbin having their trust, if they won 3 of the first 4 games they would be a confident bunch, and that would make them dangerous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 12:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what you're saying is there's a chance? Nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mini with the Max? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 02:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the chances of the Mini (the NFC phone) coming with, or being available at an extra charge, in the US for the Max? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where to sell domain names </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 23:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's get a list going of the places to sell domain names.

**sedo.com and afternic.com** are both marketplaces where you can sell domain names at retail. Escrow is available through these.

**namepros.com** is a domain name forum that has a section for sales; however, generally these are not end users purchasing, but other domainers, and so the price you'll get will be at a step discount. Note that the buy/sell process is outside of the forum so use escrow to protect yourself during the transaction.

**tobyclements.com** is a broker who deals with premium domains. He handles the transaction and takes 20%. You send him names that you are interested in selling along with your asking price (he'll reject if you don't include a price) and he uses his network to help sell. Often these are not end users, so you may not get top-dollar, but he does work with companies or individuals who will be end-users who are looking for the right domain.

**ebay.com** is really hit-or-miss for domains. Your listing would have to be viewed by someone interested in that industry/niche specifically. It is possible to sell on ebay, and many domainers have, but there seems to be quite a bit of luck involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you like to see from r/domainnames </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 22:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi redditors!

I have taken over r/domainnames and would like to know what you would like to see from this subreddit.

I'm open to ideas, but a few of mine are below:
* Industry news.
* Premium names for sale (keyword-rich .com, .net, .org). I don't want this to get spammy, so possibly these go to a moderation queue if that's possible (I'll look into).
* Questions on domaining as a hobby or business.
* Success stories, case studies.
* Domain names   SEO

I've been dabbling in domain name buying/selling for many years and so can help others, though I'd like to see more users here to assist each other. I also have a lot of experience in SEO, and so can answer questions that pertain to domains in relation to that discipline.

Domaining can be really fun. Finding that diamond either not registered or about to be released and flipping is a lot like real estate with many of the same principles applying.

train_subject4065 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 22:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah!

Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-05 02:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus! 22lb cat on your back in a bar, are you sure you don't want to make the front page? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-05 01:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cat in a backpack sounds like instant karma. 

Could do a bar that's in a restaurant, like vt pub   brewery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-04 06:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was one a couple of months ago, and yes it's allowed :)  I'm up for another.

This time I say we make a rule that no drifters with backpacks full of rotisserie chicken are allowed! Not that he wasn't a nice guy... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 00:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reposts. Get over it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 22:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The narc is watching this reddit closely. It's down already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 03:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twice on Tuesdays.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 03:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same with Super Bowl wins. This is the ultimate team sport, it takes more than a QB to win it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 04:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lump them together. My understanding is how they respond is a part of the director AI. If not my bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 04:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's terrible. Playing single player, or online with a bot on your team, is horrible. In fact I'd say single player is not worth playing on the hardest setting because of how bad the AI is. I've literally lay dying on the ground with the bots standing around me doing nothing at all, not even picking me up. 

I just consider them extra health packs, they aren't worth anything more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 03:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't be of any help...but this brought back some nostalgia. I played this in high school and college. So much fun! I'd put in dark movie soundtracks and turn off the lights. Those were the days! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 03:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't mind, please report back on your choice and outcome. I may be moving to Winooski and was wondering the same thing.

Fairpoint sucks where I am now, rumor is that there are places where Fairpoint isn't bad, and considering there's a Fairpoint building right in Winooski I had hopes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 20:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.

Sorry for not  posting specs, but really wasn't about that as much as if it could even be upgraded. I've bought desktops in the past that were just impossible to upgrade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the ASUS M51 desktop upgradeable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 18:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need a good starting point for a desktop pc (some gaming) but want to make sure it's one that I can upgrade later (graphics card, processor, for example).

Any one know if the ASUS M51 can be upgraded easily?

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-26 20:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one old enough to remember the generic store brand products like this 30 years ago?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 09:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Subreddits...get your mind out of the gutter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 03:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll show you mine if you show me yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 03:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally faster to use Sprint 3g, which is the laughing stock of mobile data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 03:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://media.tumblr.com/tumblr_lnlzhmlbYX1qafrh6.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 03:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't have kiosks to purchase tickets (that I know of) up here.

Glad to hear it's working for you. When my finances are more settled I may subscribe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 02:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's generous of you. I've done that on their website, but it's unclear if they only look for theaters that take Discover, or if they've somehow confirmed their card is accepted.

My zip is 05401 though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 01:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But whyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
