<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7036</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What music do you listen to that would surprise people you know and how does it not follow your regular listening habbits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 01:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll start. I listen to Rush and prog rock as much as I listen to what is considered "hip" or "trendy" today. That and some awesome more dad esc yaght rock; I am far from a dad. What do you listen to that would make your friends go "hmmm"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Saints Go Machine - Parix [Electro Art Pop/Alternative] (2011) Beautifully different </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 18:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 18:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Harry...](http://24.media.tumblr.com/14832d03a57d8cacef89ec57dbca5d90/tumblr_mjfxfsibE51s83re0o1_500.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tainted Goods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 23:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dynamo -- Common Ground [Jazz/Fusion] (2014) A real journey of a song </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 06:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris McClenney - Booty (On the Floor) [House] (2015) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 22:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 06:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man I love those. My absolute favorite is 'Turtle Bones'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 05:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We racked a blueberry ale to secondary and bottled that little bit of cinnamon cider. Super pumped about that blueberry ale. Were calling it Brewberry Yum-Yum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Mother Hips -- Stoned Up the Road [Rock] (1995) The best rock n roll band you've probably never heard of </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 02:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 00:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 15:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom always said to stop eating such spicy food. Now I can use this as ammo against her. Take that Mom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I cannot handle this right now [7] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 04:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 21:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source
http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-london-32157618 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the power outage looks like due to the underground fire today in London </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 21:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Royal Thunder - Glow [Rock/Grunge] (2015) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 21:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 22:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoever writes these editorial headlines needs to watch an ehow.com video. Says she died at 117 weeks old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 18:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAMN SON! Got me lol. Yea you're right still awesome AF tho right?? 'Pride' by Dynamo is killer. Their vocalist has a beautiful voice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 18:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Laurance was an original member Snarky Puppy, not to mention many of the personnel on his new record are from the current incarnation of the group. This includes Snarky Puppy's leader Michael League on bass and "Sput", one of their amazing drummers. Makes sense to me that Bill Laurance would record his album in similar Snarky Puppy fashion. The 'live' recording setup seems to work well for Ropeadope artists. 

As far as the musical influence, I hear something that strays a bit further left field from Snarky Puppy's concept of sound but I can totally understand what you're saying. In my opinion 'Swift', Laurance's new record, strays further away from the gospel of fusion that Snarky Puppy has given us and has taken an almost Phillip Glass contemporary classical oriented approach. The textures and themes throughout the songs almost are reminiscent of minimalist music of the 20th century. Sprinkle some Snarky Puppy juice on there and you have one hell of a musical cocktail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me and my Brew partner-in-crime are starting to really turn around some quality homebrew and were feeling confident in our creations. Any competitions still accepting applications? We'd like to at least try our hand at one of these things. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 14:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If our beer sucks, oh well. We love it and so do our friends so we thought we would give it a whirl! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 02:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. So pumped for their album. If you like Snarky Puppy and Bill Laurance you'd love Dynamo. Check out (Pride)[ Dynamo - Pride (Find Your Way)[https://youtu.be/wUxXaHdzxQU] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Odds that Jay-Z's friends and some of music's biggest names today will debut their next albums on his new streaming service, Tidal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 23:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 21:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a very quick jump to the extreme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and for regular-sized Snarky Puppy with full Orchestra check [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BoF7ZzMUrgA spfreload=10) out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 17:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is Bill Laurance's group but a lot of the players on his new album are from Snarky Puppy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
