<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8834</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-09 17:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. It's how dumbasses fight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-09 17:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That can really be said for anyone, whether they cheated previously or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-09 14:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If any of you guys have looked at the new covers for the ebooks, a lot of the characters look much, much better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hoping Against Hope, but Here's a Romance Question for ME3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-08 07:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you romance Aria T'Loak?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-08 06:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am at this exact point and looking for confirmation on this. Also, if you romanced Ashley in ME1 and Miranda in ME2, is it still possible to romance Liara?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-03 03:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I need a cigarette after that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-27 08:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't see it and figured reddit would tell me if link was already posted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mass Effect 3 "Fight" Trailer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-27 04:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-25 19:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not telling you do anything, and I definitely do not agree with incorporating any personal beliefs or opinions into education/politics. What I am saying is that I accept the fact that people have different beliefs than I do, and I don't belittle them for it. 

Personally I think it is ridiculous that so many people allow their own personal beliefs to influence their decision making in regards to politics/policymaking. The fact that people like Rick Santorum can potentially become the President of the United States of America shows that we are still a long way away from achieving that kind of separation of not only church and state, but personal/moral beliefs and state.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-25 18:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> uh huh, tell me more about how I'm trying to govern people's private lives using a 2000 year old book with no scientific support as my guidelines. fuck you.

Never said you were. I said that you only think what you believe as correct and allow no room for anyone else's beliefs/opinions. Just because you choose not to believe in an idea that has no scientific backing to prove it does not make it ridiculous. That is what the main problem of this video is. Atheism is no longer just denying the existence of a supernatural creator, it's about throwing it in everyone else's face and telling them to "fuck off" if they don't agree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-25 18:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mark Meer is badass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-25 18:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have to say this is a pretty narcissistic point of view. Just because you don't hold the same beliefs as another it suddenly becomes inferior and not deserving of respect. That puts you on the same level as idiots like Rick Santorum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-25 17:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://eurogyro.net/locations.html

444 East Exchange Street, Akron, OH 44304 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-25 17:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all reality it is just another person mocking the beliefs of others. Nothing new here. When are people going to just respect others beliefs and be done with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-24 20:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next on my list after I finish The Wheel of Time then :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-24 18:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I am interested, but I get the feeling that a large part of this series was spoiled for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-24 16:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but not the one this city needs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-21 14:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need 1920x1200 :(

Thanks though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-21 03:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone get a 1920x1200 version? The only one I see is the one from bioware that has the banners.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-20 15:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What this tells me, is that a Mass Effect movie would be amazing. Here's to hoping that there is enough positive feedback from ME3 to prompt more discussion on this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-20 15:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine would be that I love to cook/bake, and I like to keep my kitchen looking nice. Just picked up a new set of Pfaltzgraff dishes and I plan on picking up the matching set pieces when I get a few more bucks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-15 01:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> at 1:23 I was like, "....WTF?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girl Can Say Any Word Backwards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-15 01:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-15 00:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am probably the one of the only people who disagrees with this. Definitely a very good story for the second game in a trilogy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-13 20:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially the last few seconds of video in this trailer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-11 19:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aside from some of the others I have already seen posted here, I would really like to be able to re-experience Grandia 2 again. One of my favorite games of all times. Also, Enslaved: Odyssey to the West.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-11 19:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good pick. I put down the second game after about 2 hours of playing, but the first still ranks as one of my favorite games.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-02 06:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I laughed pretty hard at this... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-16 16:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As did I. Seriously, I was thinking, "28 comments...nobody could have thought about Dead Island yet." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-21 06:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Wheel of Time (series) is every bit as good in my opinion. On book number 4 right now and can't stop reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-06 06:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please tell me there is a 1900x1200 res around here somewhere...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-03 22:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drinking and driving </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-16 21:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not an insult, just stating a point. Also in your previous post you neglected to mention that his affiliation with the Tea Party had anything to do with your not respecting him. Also, even if he is a member of the Tea Party, that doesn't make him any less of a person. I can understand your sentiment if he was one of the crazies in the crowd holding up signs calling Obama a Muslim, but nothing you have said here seems to indicate that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-16 20:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like you are the one being judgmental, not him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-16 19:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with this 100%. Your first few bullets almost never seem to make contact although you are aiming right at the guy! I have a 30Mb connection with a 15ms ping and I consistently run into these problems in MW3.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-13 04:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this only on PC version, or can you see this on Xbox as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-11 15:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy said he liked Twilight Princess's controls better. His major gripe about the game has just been invalidated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-11 14:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Sometimes it takes a good minute before a care package even comes out and by that time the round might be over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-11 14:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually think this is good, because it will force IW to get a patch out reasonably quick due to the amount of people who will most likely have this problem. Hopefully they will take care of some other things along with this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-10 20:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why you are getting downvoted. Even though the OP made a mistake I think this is what he was getting at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-10 20:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bog! Anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, /r/mw3, What's Your Favorite Class/Killstreak Setup So Far? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-10 14:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Gun:** 
G36C (Red Dot Sight)
.44 Magnum

**Perks:** 
Scavenger Pro
Assassin Pro
Steady Aim Pro 

**Killstreaks:** Support
SAM Turret
Advanced UAV
Escort Airdrop

Sometimes I use Dead Silence instead of Steady Aim and I use Hardline in place of Assassin when running an Assault package.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-10 14:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one that thinkgs the UM is a lot less OW than from MW2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-09 22:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haters gunna hate. This place is like /r/gaminghipsters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-09 21:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Normally I would say so, but after maxing out the UMP it still isn't quite like the MW2 version IMO. No big deal, just takes some getting used to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
