<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4034</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 23:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you please add the Seabrook Star? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ben Mezrich will release the first chapter of his new thriller, Seven Wonders, if enough people add the book to their Goodreads page. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 18:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 19:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was the best part of filming Joe Dirt working with Kid Rock, or inspiring millions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do I have nightmares when I take caffeine pills? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 16:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 18:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How has the success of Gone Girl affected your writing habits? Has anything changed now that you don't have to be concerned with your finances? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 04:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Romanski how proud are you being from NH? Probably my greatest achievement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 01:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ernest Cline's Ready Player One.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 16:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Junot Diaz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does the expiration date of Tylenol and Advil really mean? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 20:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My bagel shop today... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 15:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Probably shouldn't have done this... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 22:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 18:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always attended the interactive sessions, so I can't speak to the music. That being said there seems to be a give and take with the popularity of these festivals. They are becoming larger and more intricate, which takes away from the grass roots feel of the whole thing, but also moves them towards bigger acts and more legitimacy. 

Plus even at interactive the music is still killer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm currently on a flight to Austin for SXSW, in my opinion usually the most interesting part of the whole trip, sitting amongst tech luminaries and comm execs. AMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 18:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $1 Million in "New Digital Age Grants" Awarded by Google Executive Chairman Eric Schmidt to Organizations Fighting Global Challenges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 13:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 17:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clay, I'll be attending your talk with Emily Parker this evening at the New America Foundation. How do you know Mrs. Parker and what are your thoughts on the possible balkanization of the Internet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just wrote this article on fan fiction, and who really owns the worlds we love, for a major media outlet. Let me know your thoughts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 22:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Second Monitor issues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 19:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Lenova laptop, plugged into a Lenova docking station, which is hooked up to a Dell monitor (VGA to VGA). I recently picked up a Lenova monitor. I would like to use the docking station to have dual monitors, but the only other port is a DVI-D and the monitor has a VGA port. 

I ordered an adapter (VGA to DVI-D) and it didn't work. I did some trouble-shooting, and both monitors, chords, and ports work. This leads me to believe that it's the adapter's fault, but before I order a new one I'm curious if there's something I'm missing. My IT team tells me that the video card, comp, and docking station support dual-monitors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 21:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on experience and writing. Do you have any writing samples? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CALLING ALL WRITERS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 20:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the process of rolling out a new tech-oriented website with a focus on futurism. I would like to hold an open discussion about how technology is effecting out culture; think "the future of optometry in a world of Google Glass" or "Snapchat is mocking your privacy; here's why you don't care." I'm open to most topics, but I"m looking specifically for beat writers to cover drones, wearables, and 3d printing. 

Message me if this is of interest to you and I can share more details.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does brain size effect the potency of your hangover? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 23:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you genuinely think there's a future for closed software systems? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 23:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't help but feel that open systems are dominating the market right now, and that any desirable closed system is being cannibalized by open source software anyway. More curious than anything else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I changed the light bulb in my kitchen and found a dozen of these. WTF are they? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 20:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 15:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations. As someone who works in publishing, this is no small feat. However I have to warn you, the hard part is just beginning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
