<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9876</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 07:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way to go buddy! What life you've had there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Text] What Are You Waiting For? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I admit I also read it a couple of times before totally understanding the story. And when you do, you'll really appreciate the novel. Maybe reading still depends on the interest of the reader. I for one cannot get the hang reading the likes of Robert Kiyosaki.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how far can technology go. And can human catch up? What's next after nano-? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 16:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should have found an alternative long ago considering the vast profit that they have amassed from their patrons (meaning the loyal children who begged their parents for this very expensive toy). That is if they were really concerned about the welfare of many and not just for their own personal gains.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let Go of Your Fears and Live </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 14:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 14:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading is good for everyone, so I am happy when there's a new recruit. And to add to your future reads, 'Brothers Karamazov' by Dostoyevsky is a good one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 13:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leave it as it is. History is imprinted on it already. Just create a copy and put color on it instead. Sometimes, we do more harm than good on things that should have been left alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How todays architects and designers are creating offices in the great outdoors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 13:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 13:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should have done that a long time ago instead of spending more of their national funds on nuclear power plants which they know are harmful to their people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LG Listens to Conservationists and Preserves a Landmark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 13:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting creative about freeway removal: If Portland can do it, why can't Detroit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 13:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Delicate Pencil Lead Sculptures Carved by Salavat Fidai </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 12:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 6 New Must-Try Summer Beers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 17:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla is taking its unique dealership design on the road: the company has constructed a mobile pop-up shop out of shipping containers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 18:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
