<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5807</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study identifies key cells in touch sensation and gleans how these cells, located just beneath the skin surface, enable us to feel fine details and textures. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 01:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientist finds the worst places to get stung by a bee by experimenting on himself. In order, it's the nostril, lip, and penis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 16:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 16:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seemed to me like the author did a decent job of summing up the research and then applying a critical, skeptical mindset to the results, which any decent science journalist should do.

Any scientific research is limited in scope in some fashion, but the point of comparing a one-off study like this to prior research is to give perspective. Sure, maybe the prior research had some limitations, but a whole lot of it also seemed to have reached the opposite conclusion as the current study, which is very important to know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study finds that the benefits of infant male circumcision to health exceed the risks by over 100 to 1. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 05:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are The Mafia Psychopaths? A new study finds that members of Cosa Nostra in Italy have lower psychopathic traits than other criminals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 21:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The study that found a vegetarian diet to be associated with poorer health has a "host of inescapable limitations" and goes against prior evidence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 18:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eating harder foods leads to a 13% reduction in caloric intake. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 22:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CrossFit Almost Definitely Won't Kill You </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 16:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well this is intriguing: DARPA is launching a biotechnology office. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 15:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists announce a new theory on why zebras have stripes. Zebras have them to prevent bites from flies, not predation by lions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 17:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Health Check: four myths about vitamin supplements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 20:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video Gaming Doesn't Replace Player Social Lives, It Expands Them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 19:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MIT Engineers design "living materials," which combine bacterial cells with nonliving elements that can conduct electricity or emit light </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 23:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gravitational waves explained with a towel and an apple </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 05:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is the best explainer I've read on the discovery of gravitational waves from moments after the Big Bang. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 16:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MIT researchers have created a "bionic" plant by augmenting it with nanomaterials. The plant can now capture 30% more light energy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 14:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The planet Mercury has been shrinking ever since it formed roughly 4.6 billion years ago. A new report finds that its radius has shrunk by as much as 7 kilometers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 20:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study highlights the prospect that global civilization could collapse in coming decades due to unsustainable resource exploitation and increasingly unequal wealth distribution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 04:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reduced-Gliadin Wheat Bread: An Alternative to the Gluten-Free Diet for Consumers Suffering Gluten-Related Pathologies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 00:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A team of researchers has identified multiple genes linked to musical aptitude, providing further evidence that musical ability is heritable. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-13 14:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Ross Sea, a major, biologically productive Antarctic ecosystem, "clearly will be extensively modified by future climate change" in the coming decades. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-13 06:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Changes in the suns energy output may have led to marked natural climate change in Europe over the last 1000 years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 23:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A research team has discovered a group of molecules in the blood that can predict with 90% accuracy whether older people will develop Alzheimer's over the course of 2 to 3 years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 00:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 16:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The results of this study really aren't surprising. If teens start using nicotine before adulthood, they're more likely to crave nicotine throughout their lives. Prior research has demonstrated that brain development is altered with nicotine use. 

A major limitation of the study to keep in mind: "The studys cross-sectional nature didnt allow the researchers to identify whether most youths initiated with conventional cigarettes or e-cigarettes."

That's a pretty big drawback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Male fruit flies restricted to monogamy show reduced cognitive and learning abilities. "Sexual competition may drive the evolution of intelligence..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 15:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 06:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fooled a lot of people:

"That is so dope but did you filter that or something? Looks almost too good haha"

"Sweet car man, New York?"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 28-square-kilometer living coral reef has been found in the coastal waters of Iraq. Until now, it wasn't thought that Iraq's waters could support a reef. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 19:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 18:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who copy their friend's drinking behaviour will deny that their decision has been influenced, researchers at the University of Liverpool have shown. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 06:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have discovered a 30,000-year-old virus in the Siberian permafrost. It's one of three viruses that are as large as bacteria and it's still infectious. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 21:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Physicists have measured how the surfaces of glassy materials flow like a liquid, even when they should be solid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 16:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 00:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taco Bell... breakfast, lunch, and dinner.

But in all honesty, [this](http://www.gastro.org/patient-center/digestive-conditions/gas-in-the-digestive-tract#Foods%20 %20Gas) guide from the American Gastroenterological Association lists foods like cauliflower, brussels sprouts, dried beans, broccoli, cabbage, bran, dairy, and fructose. Sounds like a lot of vegetarian diets are probably high-flatulogenic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 21:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right to be skeptical. The picture the article paints is somewhat bleak. But there's a tinge of hopefulness at the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New Yorker goes behind the scenes at ITER, the international fusion reactor being built in France. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 18:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In two new papers, researchers correlated three types of gut bacteria with the frequency of "anal gas evacuations" and found that a "low-flatulogenic" diet can reduce farting by up to 54%. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 16:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA's Kepler mission has announced the discovery of 715 new planets, doubling the exoplanet count. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 04:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since most of the gases our body and gut bacteria produce are lighter than air, do you weigh less if you're incredibly bloated? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 18:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adverse psychological side-effects of anti-depressants are more widespread than is commonly thought. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 17:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have discovered what created a 6 million-year-old fossilized whale graveyard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 01:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 22:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Studies like these prompt a lot of boneheaded, insensitive comments, which attract the ~~sharks~~ amazing and awesome mods. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study links believing in hell, and perhaps even thinking about it, with lower levels of happiness and satisfaction in life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 18:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The people who are "disengaged" from science are the most likely to think that it creates more problems than it solves and that we should depend more on faith. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 18:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
