<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3651</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 13:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original study: http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0091743515001668 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most Americans, including gun owners, now support stronger gun control policies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 13:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Social class influences music tastes. Poorer, less-educated people tend to like country, disco, easy listening, golden oldies, heavy metal and rap. Wealthier and better-educated people tend to like classical, blues, jazz, opera, choral, pop, reggae, rock, world and musical theatre. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 13:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 16:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, though, we need an astrophysicist to help us. Any volunteers?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 14:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the original study: http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0925231215004725 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 14:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the original study: http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/pirs.12163/abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> College grads in the 90s moved to cities with fast-growing "smart" industries like tech. But now, US college grads choose cities with the biggest labor markets and the best chances of landing literally any job. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 14:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 13:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the original study: http://rspb.royalsocietypublishing.org/content/282/1809/20150229 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chimpanzees have the cognitive power to cook their own food. Like humans, chimps prefer cooked food over raw food, understand the transformation of raw food into cooked food and often transport food over long distances. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 13:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 13:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the original paper: http://iopscience.iop.org/0004-637X/803/2/80/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astronomers can now "weigh" the Milky Way Galaxy, using approximate measurements streams produced by dissolving globular clusters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 13:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 23:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! That explains my altruism...but does it explain my autonomic nervous system?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 20:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the abstract from the [original study](http://www.nature.com/neuro/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nn.4035.html):
"Independent evidence associates -amyloid pathology with both non-rapid eye movement (NREM) sleep disruption and memory impairment in older adults. However, whether the influence of -amyloid pathology on hippocampus-dependent memory is, in part, driven by impairments of NREM slow wave activity (SWA) and associated overnight memory consolidation is unknown. Here we show that -amyloid burden in medial prefrontal cortex (mPFC) correlates significantly with the severity of impairment in NREM SWA generation. Moreover, reduced NREM SWA generation was further associated with impaired overnight memory consolidation and impoverished hippocampal-neocortical memory transformation. Furthermore, structural equation models revealed that the association between mPFC -amyloid pathology and impaired hippocampus-dependent memory consolidation was not direct, but instead statistically depended on the intermediary factor of diminished NREM SWA. By linking -amyloid pathology with impaired NREM SWA, these data implicate sleep disruption as a mechanistic pathway through which -amyloid pathology may contribute to hippocampus-dependent cognitive decline in the elderly." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 18:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.docdroid.net/1293f/psychological-science-2015-miller-0956797615578476.pdf.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 18:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like when science is behind a paywall. Here's the full study: http://www.docdroid.net/1293f/psychological-science-2015-miller-0956797615578476.pdf.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 16:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's sort of interesting is that the study also links altruism to "autonomic flexibility"...which is some sort of biological thing I don't understand. 

Can anyone explain it to me?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poland will kill off about 5,800 pigs to prevent the spread of African swine fever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 16:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Children from poor families tend to be more altruistic and more willing to make personal sacrifices for others. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of UK patients with gonorrhea were prescribed outdated antibiotics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
