<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3761</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 07:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheez-its and Mountain Dew is a favorite. Oreos are also fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 05:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flexing is not a turn on. I'm sorry. 
What is nice, is a randomly clean counter or something. You can flex your muscles all you want whilst wiping down that beer you just spilled instead of throwing a towel on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 05:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Puberty roulette master. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 05:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dem eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starting the nephew young. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 02:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-06 17:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the *worst*, but I know life's just not as easy for ugly people. I'd hate to have to see my kids deal with a ton of bullying and rejection because of a few bad genetics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-06 15:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait...is NotaMethAddict Kyle or Thorian1990 Kyle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-06 14:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm terrified to have children because of that. I'm not the worst looking person on the planet, and I probably won't end up with someone less than decent looking, but knowing my luck there will be that one gene from that one ancestor that fucks it all up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-06 12:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an edited picture for a show where the countries are personified. In the show, they have glasses. America's are named Texas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-06 12:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HETALIA. Gay nations everywhere. I hope I beat someone to pointing out this CanAme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-06 12:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Futurama and MLP? *highfive!* Working on one now~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-05 23:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh! I must be on the right track-I've worked with the Greybeards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-05 10:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a big quest besides all of the Dragonborn stuff? I just got the game and went straight onto Dragonborn quests. It was escape being executed, Riverwood, Whiterun, YOU'RE A DRAGONBORN. I'm level 10 thinking the Dragonborn quests are the main ones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 23:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't like boys at all for a while (thank you Spy Kids). But then I saw Shark Boy and Lava Girl. Bi forever. So elementary school for me...and my first crush was a girl. But then some boys. I didn't know there was a 'right' and 'wrong' way to do it. Just liking people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 09:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He got reddit gold. I'd consider that a very good thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 02:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats! Your stories are absolutely amazing, I actually want to read them more than once-they never lose the effect! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 23:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 03:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I often feel the same way. One second I'm "OMG MEN" but then I just find it difficult to see myself in a relationship with a guy. I guess I just confuse myself a TON. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 02:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So cons I guess. It would take work to drag her out of the friend zone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 02:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-30 22:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-30 22:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This movie always puts me in a fantastic mood. And in the mood to get things done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-30 22:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both girls...so friend zone is okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 11:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I'm not that bad.](http://i.imgur.com/jSfjA.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 22:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup! I love Pinkie Pie because she is just that awesome and always hunky dory.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-26 19:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-26 19:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We would wrap it around the playground a few times! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swix paste wax? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-26 06:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom picked some up for me and I'm just wondering if anyone has used it and if so, how do I use it? The packaging for Swix is never too descriptive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-26 04:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friends and I have sat all day and used tons of yarn to make these things yards long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-26 04:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want gold for Christmas...
And it did continue to you! But skipped him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-26 04:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom was so proud she found it. I had a mental breakdown over the loss of Twinkies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-26 04:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup! I got my xbox today so I hardly know what I'm doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-25 18:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks~! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have an Xbox account already, but now I can't set up my Xbox properly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-25 18:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It says my email is already in use...but that's because I already have an account. How do I fix this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-25 17:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got the same Xbox package. I almost broke it rolling around in happiness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-25 17:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, was trying to sneak the picture whilst standing in line to hand it in.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know I picked E. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-25 00:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-24 09:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your HTML skills make me fear your photoshop skills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-21 04:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omnipotence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 23:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup! Southeast Wisconsin. Can't wait to get to the hills tomorrow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blizzard conditions all day! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 20:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 04:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being in Wisconsin, half of my teachers planned around the hopeful snow day. Others just planned for a movie or test (genius). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 04:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The middle ring-that's fine. The BOTTOM RING. NEIN. And of course it's the bottom right on *all* of my binders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 04:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Do you at least get lack of snow days? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 04:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant, because it was just announced that my school has a snow day tomorrow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just announced-snow day! What's your plan? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 04:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those of you that get snow days, what is your plan for the day? Snowboarding? That homework you didn't do? All I know is that I have a huge can of Code Red and Minecraft in my taskbar waiting patiently for me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 23:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You fuck. This was awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 23:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Algorithm. MATHCORE FTW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 23:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a freshman, this is a dangerous attempt buuuut, here goes. 
 1. Walk on the right side of the hallway. I don't wish for you to walk over me.
 2. Don't you dare point out we were supposed to turn in homework 10 minutes before class ends. 
 3. Upperclassmen own the school. Get over it.
 4. If you are a freshman, walk against the wall. It saves the rest of the planet from walking into your backpack.
 5. Do not announce it is your birthday if you did not bring a snack. 85% of people at school don't care.
 6. We know you're tired. Anyone who has to wake up at 4:30 in the morning for school is tired. Stop complaining and go to sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 23:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, I have done my fair share of interesting presentations. You could do a paper and presentation on Japanese culture. Or Vocaloids. I was asked by a teacher to put together a powerpoint and the class was absolutely hooked by singing holograms. It really is fun to research. You could write a persuasive paper on a famous (or even controversial) person. I have a friend who wrote a persuasive essay on why Ivan the Terrible wasn't actually that terrible. Freedom and the Internet is also a go-to topic for me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 23:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What type of topic are you aiming for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 23:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! My brain must have shut down~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 22:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could someone explain the Imperialist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 22:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I now enjoy you greatly. The only thing that could have made the Japanese better was if it was possible to put it in someone's voice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Merry Christmas from the Axis~! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 22:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 13:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. I have a couple fandoms where I'm always thinking of more ideas, most of which I end up being too lazy to throw on paper. Others it is a rather painful experience and I hope that I never get a request for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 05:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I know, a group of griefers. They griefed the farm of my friends and I, who, from what I know, have done nothing to provoke any griefing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 02:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't want to join due to fear of being a target, but you have gained an ally! I'm always willing to help others in the server!
Edit: Unless you're in my base/taking my stuff. Then I will either do my best to crush you or run away in fear. Probably the latter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 02:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's me before snowboarding a couple weeks ago.](http://i.imgur.com/V1iNo.jpg) It was also my first or second week on the server.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 02:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't stand the pointless griefing either. I get when two teams/players have a grudge between them or war is declared or something, but my friends and I built a huge farm open for use by anyone (as long as seeds are replanted) and we keep getting griefed. This isn't playing. This is immaturity. DFS and RoT have hit us so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 01:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is awesome. But I didn't get asshole on my envelope. I got my name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 06:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you find out? Did you do extensive research and come to the conclusion? Did you see a therapist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 04:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see. I'll make sure to watch for you guys then :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 03:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does the rest of it stand for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 03:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes...I loved that base. It was a shared base. I have a much nicer one now. I needed to renovate anyways~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 03:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's a Hindu peace sign, but I doubt whoever made it intended it as such.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else a victim of Reuben? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 01:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glad to see such creative griefing... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 01:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 00:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not as much r/nosleep as much as it is r/wtf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 22:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So...this app is only available in the UK... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-13 22:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When reddit shuts down and after half an hour of refreshing, only vaguely admitting defeat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-13 02:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see. That makes sense then. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-13 01:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But who knows how long each power would last? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-13 01:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> College is free in the UK? Lucky! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-13 01:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today the power (well, the lights) shut off in half the school and the network was down so we all got sent home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-12 06:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have these. They work really well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So much obsidian? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-12 06:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've come across settlements (and seen pictures) with HUGE amounts of obsidian. I'm just wondering where it all came from.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-12 06:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This tactic really doesn't work. It usually ends with "If you want to fuck up, go right ahead."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-12 01:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, the 4. I don't have money (or the desire) for a 5 so I'm glad it's safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 08:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unique? After looking at the comments here, I really have to find a different one. Let's see...I got it! That swoopy 2010 Bieber hair cut. No. I don't want to feel like I'm dating someone who is either 12 and/or just took a helmet off after a week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 07:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. Accents are awesome. My friend and I go nuts over them~ 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For some reason, I still can't listen to this song.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 04:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 03:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know; I'm more in the Sunburst/Little Switz area. They should have some snow made though, it's been cold enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 03:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm American and write similar to that. Not necessarily cursive, but not full on printing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 02:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Momo and Rukia. I just couldn't stand Rukia from the beginning, and Momo is pretty damn useless. At least Komamura can use bankai. Or a decent shikai for that matter... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Wisconsin FINALLY checking in! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-09 18:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by dumping chocolate milk on my iPhone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-09 00:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I dumped chocolate milk on my iPhone. It was charging pleasantly on the table. My cup of milk was sitting pleasantly near it. That is fuck up number one. Number two was when I decided to grab my cup for a drink of that lovely beverage. Miss. I hit the cup and the milk went flying on my phone. I have never ran so fast than when I did to get some rice to throw my phone in. I also managed to wipe excess milk off with my shirt. It has survived (for now-last time it got wet, it took days to take effect) and is currently in a bag of rice. Fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-08 20:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see. I've had teachers that go absolutely nuts over scantron. 4 question vocabulary quiz? SCANTRON. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-08 19:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to pay for them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
