<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8959</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 00:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're spinning off PayPal so when it tanks after Apple, Google and Facebook replace it, they can contain the losses and keep eBay afloat. Source: Brain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 00:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rot in hell, Comcast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 19:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 Bush presidents with a third on the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 19:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sara Palin said the same thing about climate change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 19:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People pay money and wait in earnest to see Chris Brown? That's a reap what you sow lesson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 19:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And US. Don't forget those concentration ca- I mean "reservations". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 19:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were at their peak anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daughter who plans on marrying her father talks about their incestuous relationship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 18:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Hampshire rally backs Warren for president </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 01:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 21:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you implying concepts like income equality are not feasible? I'd be interested to know your sources on that, because there have been numerous examples throughout history of economic equilibrium.

Converse to your critique, history shows that when the income gap widens to publicly perceived "insurmountable" levels, as we saw in Greece for example, the top heavy system tends to collapse on itself and leads to economic turmoil for all. As bank systems can be deemed so big that they can plunge the world into grief should they fail, the economic ramifications of having a massive gap between the haves and the have-nots can theoretically result in much more catastrophic market consequences. Some of these I would wager we are beginning to see currently in the US in the form of widening state financial deficits coupled with coagulation of corporate holdings. In short, as the rich get richer and practically eliminate taxes, the poor grow poorer as the infrastructure that supports and more importantly employs the lower classes begins to fail.

Again, I'd love to see your source for the disparaging remarks against income equalization because I don't believe they are rooted in any formal education on the issue at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were given the opportunity to pass one single law in your country with no questions asked, what would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 20:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 21:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching Republicans juggle pushing for less government oversight of banks while pushing for more oversight of DC residents and their rights during a Presidential election cycle is going to be fascinating. "The government shouldn't meddle in our lives. Except pregnant women. But that's it. And marriage, ok just those two. And birth control rules for companies. But seriously those three aside...no, marijuana too. Ok those four things aside, we want government out of people's lives." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> D.C. challenges Congress to halt marijuana legalization in nations capital </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 21:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are electronic voting records in the U.S. retained and audited? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 19:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do asexual people desire sexless assignment surgery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 14:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Portishead - To Kill a Dead Man [Trip-Hop/Alternative] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 03:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 03:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You overeat and say you ran a 7:20 mile...tell me more about your not understanding this question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 03:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have to understand the point of something to acknowledge it exists? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 03:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you seriously implying you don't know people are hypocritical? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 02:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4chan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's something you publicly condemn but privately do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 02:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 23:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that's what it read, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia has a knockoff version of 'It's Always Sunny' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 22:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 19:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soundgarden - Ty Cobb. Great track, has what IO believe to be a banjo breakdown in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 03:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great parenting all around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kidz Bop Kids covering 'In The End' by Linkin Park </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 01:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 00:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been drunk before. I have been "Wow, I can't believe I called my ex" drunk. Been "I can't believe I didn't die from my own vomit" drunk. I have NEVER been "That amputation was a breeze" drunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 00:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going with the discovery of anesthesia. I honestly cannot imagine how much life sucked before that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To date, what do you consider to be the most commonly underrated achievement in human history? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 00:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 00:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to think the hype is only helping Reznor secure all permissions and funding to make this release as absolutely perfect as possible. I know from multiple interviews he seems baffled by the surge in interest, but I know he also is hearing people who are begging for it. Looks like people tweet about it regularly too. It's one of my top three favorite albums and I am going to be patient, because when it comes out I know it's going to blow me the fuck away just like it did the night it came out.

Tl;dr - this is going to be worth the wait </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 00:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia blamed? WTF? Weeks ago the Wall Street Journal and Reuters were gloating that the crash in oil was going to destroy Russia. People can't even rage consistently anymore. It's insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 00:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing you haven't been anywhere near it in decades. Even condos in North West are selling for 400k. The worst ghettos of DC are still getting 200k for the rowhomes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1 dead, dozens hurt after Metro car fills with smoke </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 09:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The possibility exists that someone murdered another person, was never caught or even suspected and right this moment is reading this post while wondering if it's referring to them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 06:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 19:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that it is increasingly less fantastic with every read makes it one of the scariest books ever written in my opinion. Every day, it becomes a little less unlikely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 19:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perpetual War for Perpetual Peace by Gore Vidal, read it just out of college and it caused me to reconsider a lot of positions I had taken for granted. For better or worse, it changed my outlook on a lot of things to this day. I'd love to hear about other books impacting others in similar ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most thought-provoking book you have ever read and how did it affect you personally? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 19:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for a book that affected you long after you finished reading. Something that made you consider or reconsider your position on a subject, your attitude, your lifestyle, your job, your relationship, your habits etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 15:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Antiviral, 13 Sins, Gone Girl, Would You Rather, The Hole,  Cry Wolf are a few that come to mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 23:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already forgot she ever existed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 21:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In line at Wal Mart? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 21:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not as bad as it sounds, just make sure you're really drunk. Trust me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 21:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think mine would involve paying for my Comcast services with a Comcast bank issued credit card that I make monthly payments on with income I make working in a Comcast owned grocery store that I drive to every day in my Comcast sponsored transport pod. On the way to work, I pass the Comcast Public Library, the Comcast Community High School and wave to my friend who is headed to work at the Comcast Water Department. On the radio, I only hear the "latest pop hits" Comcast plays on their menus and between each song I am exposed to 5 minutes of advertising for the lastest "hit reality show" Comcast will be showing that night.

Yes. That sounds like hell to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your personal definition of hell? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 21:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 17:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he is singling out blacks as a group he won't help, it's bad. If he is implying everyone is suffering in the same way and he won't extend customized solutions to specific groups of people, that's actually worse.

How out of touch can a person be to believe everyone in the US are facing the same issues? If he's racist, that's one thing. If he's so clueless he thinks every problem in the US is shared because we're all Americans, that's just insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb In 94: I Would Do Probably Nothing For African-Americans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 08:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 07:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I missed something...did this comment actually address what he said, or was it sort of a generic statement thrown out to change the topic in lieu of an actual response? Just want to make sure I didn't miss some credible explanation for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We Edit Life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 06:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 04:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somewhere, someone who doubts North Korea carried out the Sony hack upvoted this link... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something people wouldn't guess about you just by looking at you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 17:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 17:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm starting to believe he really has a mental handicap of some sort. He honestly thinks he is somehow supposed to be president because he wants it, and it just does not compute to him that it isn't happening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Class-action suit claims Comcast forces residential customers to pay for its public wi-fi hot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 01:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parents of Reddit, in what ways do your parenting methods differ from the methods of your own parents? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 23:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 20:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's the money for church tax exemptions  and bank bailouts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 04:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this headline so much. Thanks for making me laugh OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 21:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd add diamonds to this. It's hard to believe people still pay so much for something worth, realistically, so little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 21:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice restaurants. It's just dressing up something that winds up being flushed in the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something many people happily pay for that you think is an absolute waste of money? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 21:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How dead pop stars might look now if they were still alive, in pictures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 05:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man in "Minimally Conscious' State Suddenly Speaks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 18:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chase Utley Responds to Macs Letter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 03:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 23:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just keep having these same dreams at different times, or are they combined? That seems like a lot... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 23:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading Freud does no one any good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those of you who experience recurring dreams, what is the dream about and how long has it been happening? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 23:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 22:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^^^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 20:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to see those stats. How many people use Netflix, Hulu, Prime, Crackle etc who were enrolled in cable television when they started, and how many dumped cable television within 30, 60 days of using those services. I feel like Comcast attempting to buy Time Warner is an admission  from them that the broadband cable is their last possible attempt at future profitability, because television is dying. And once Google fiber and other comparable services start rolling out en masse, I think Comcast is going to start breaking off pieces of their company and spinning them off to avoid complete bankruptcy. I cannot wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Morningstar Assigns A- Credit Rating to Comcast while Maxim Group lowers Comcast stock rating from 'buy' to 'hold'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 19:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 16:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't agree more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The number of pay-TV subscribers fell in 2013 for the first time ever. Some 25 million U.S. households -- about one-fifth of the total number -- don't subscribe to pay TV. And that number is growing." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 08:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What makes you truly happy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 01:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 17:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As people in Kansas are trained to be ignorant. Isn't it amazing how effective training can be?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 17:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uneducated people can't be unhappy? I'm sure you aren't smiling all the time, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 17:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Water is wet...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 16:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a completely different discussion. They aren't even educating their children to the fact fossils are real. There are some basic steps that need to be taken before they can learn how the legislative system works, don't you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 16:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What part of Kansas are you from? The part of Kansas I hear from want him out. The locals call it 'Brownbackistan'. There's even a running joke he keeps everyone out of work so they can't afford the gas to run him out of the state. So overall, I'll give you a 4.5 for form, but your substance was lacking a bit in truthiness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans are Delusional: Jeb Bush Doesn't Stand a Chance at Becoming President </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 04:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC to vote on net neutrality rules in February </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 02:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the biggest opportunity you missed in your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 23:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there anything you could have done that may have changed the outcome?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To those of you who have been screwed over by someone at one time or another, did you ever get revenge? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 19:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those of you who have been beaten up, stabbed, shot, involved in a major car accident or injured in a significant way, what did it feel like? How are you now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 17:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are Monarch Butterflies Endangered? Population Down Ninety Percent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 00:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 21:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with that comment: Headline still true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The last time the GOP won the White House without a Bush on the ticket was 1972. The last time without a Bush or Nixon: 1928. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 20:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 19:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every radio station. All of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What pisses you off? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 19:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 11:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure it impacts the majority of the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 11:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Celebrity worship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could erase one thing from existence to make the world a better place, what would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 11:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 10:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://strictlycomedancing.info/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/Victoria-Pendleton-Brendon-Cole-Strictly-Come-Dancing-Series-10-2012-4x600.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wealthy Redditors, what tips do you have for poor people? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 10:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 10:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's visible from....cyberspace. Bam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 08:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife is from Eastern Europe and she REFUSES to teach me insults or swear words. One day, she got really irritated in traffic and spouted something that as far as I can tell roughly translated to something about a mother servicing a farm animal. I would love to know if other such insults existed in the world, I have to drive on the beltway and could always use some suggestions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gmail blocked in China, Great Firewall suspected </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 08:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Non English speakers of Reddit, what is the worst insult you can say to someone in your native language and what is the approximate English translation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 07:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 16:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, appreciate it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Negative Outlook', mixed media, 24"x36" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 09:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 20:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spend a lot of time thinking of incest, do you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 18:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much like the endless row of gentlemen outside of my moms bedroom, I walked into that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 18:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This question brought to you by Die Hard - a film series I've never seen and am now being relentlessly taunted by two close friends for never having seen.  My schedule and Die Hards schedule just never lined up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something everyone else seems to have done that you have not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 17:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any particular reason you haven't done that thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 16:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never watched a Die Hard movie and likely never will. Am I going to hell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 02:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So...patients hooked up to vents in hospitals, you're on your own. This is America. *lights out* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blind people probably save a great deal of money on electric bills. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 20:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 18:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 03:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sad people who have known me my entire life can't get even close to this level of awesomeness in the gifts they get for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC Delays Review Of Comcast-TWC Merger Over Undisclosed Documents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 02:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 10:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure, but I'll try to find out or direct him here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 10:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Odd, they scare me. Then again, I live in Baltimore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 10:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a manner of speaking, yes oddly enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend filmed a Google car passing him, then found the image the car took of him as it drove by. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 10:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 16:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.fool.com/investing/general/2014/08/06/is-the-peak-oil-myth-dead.aspx

There are some sources that argue that way of thinking. Personally, I think if people (including me) were manipulated into accepting higher prices once due to a false belief in a shortage crisis, there is every reason to believe they (and you) are being manipulated again.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are media outlets and pundits referring to the recent drop in oil prices as a "slump" instead of referring to it as a return to normal prices? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 15:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The extraordinarily high price per barrel is a fairly new phenomenon. Viewed as statistics over decades, isn't the latest drop representative of normalization? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polls supporting torture are misleading </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 01:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sued by Google, a State Attorney General Retreats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 05:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Director Stanley Kubricks personal assistant was assigned many tasks including cutting fresh grass each day, laying it on the carpet for Kubricks cat to roll in, then vacuuming up the grass afterwards. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 20:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Israel has a socialized medical system </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 07:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 06:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are aware people have been arrested, tried and imprisoned for DDOS attacks, right?

http://www.businessinsider.com/dutch-teenager-arrested-for-pro-wikileaks-ddos-attacks-2010-12

http://www.theguardian.com/technology/2011/jan/27/anonymous-hacking

http://www.theregister.co.uk/2011/04/19/operation_avenge_assange_suspect/

You might think they are "simply pings", but those pings get people arrested when they are used AGAINST corporations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 05:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except they [allegedly] are.
http://www.extremetech.com/extreme/195753-sony-fights-back-against-hackers-stolen-file-sharers-by-firing-a-ddos-back-at-them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] How is Sony able to launch DDOS attacks against target sites and systems involved in their hack without being investigated for cybercrimes themselves? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 03:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
