<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7806</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make your plant tweet when thirsty with Arduino with 1 line of code. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 14:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to post on Twitter from your Arduino (Comparison between using Ethernet Shield, Spark Core and 1Sheeld) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 17:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For people who were asking about voice recognition earlier. Control your home lights using your voice with Arduino and 1Sheeld (Voice Recognition Tutorial) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 22:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 22:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprisingly yea though I like Alasdair very much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arduino IDE 1.6 Released </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 16:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 18:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info. So there is no existing solution for this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 18:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea so my question is, is there and Arduino-like product that has a good enclosure as well without having to design it with a 3D printer?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 17:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks but as I said in the earlier comment, she won't like the Arduino shape itself, I need a well designed enclosure package. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 17:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea but I meant the packaging and enclosure + I don't want to build a  new PCB, I have space for the Arduino but itself needs to have a good package design.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Use Your Cat to Hack Your Neighbor's Wi-Fi | WIRED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 17:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I built an Arduino based project for my girlfriend for Valentine's day. I was wondering is there any solutions out there to deploy Arduino projects? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 16:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean a beautiful designed platform that I can use to build the project and then give it to someone as a gift, something without the hassle of wires and visible boards. Any ideas of the existence of such platforms? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 03:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I send SMS and it stops :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Built a DIY anti-theft system for my car, tracked and Controlled my car remotely using Arduino and Android through GPS sensor and sending SMS! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 13:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to turn your smart into a generic shield for Arduino with 1Sheeld - Mic shield tutorial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 03:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 03:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the answers guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a recommended test lab in Shenzhen to get a RoHS compliant report for a product? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 15:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 12:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super cool! Add [1Sheeld](http://www.1sheeld.com) to the collection, it turns your Android smart phone into a generic Arduino shield, so you can use its sensors and capabilities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
