<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3482</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 06:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realized when I was in third grade and my mom couldn't help with my math homework that not all adults were smarter than me, just older and taller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 18:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THis is a good question for /r/AskScience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 18:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honda Civic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 16:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That people only care about what they can get from you.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 15:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they'll wait for the UN report.  At least, I hope they do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 09:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we should stay out and let them settle their own wars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 09:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pepper Jack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 22:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> George W. Bush and his political cronies are responsible for the deaths of over a million Iraqui people and a large number of soldier suicides.  He comes in first place, so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 07:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's reasonable for them to leave and it's reasonable for the smoker to make their own decisions and not be told what to do.  What is not reasonable to issue threats to a loved one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 06:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should check out /r/RoomPorn and some of the affiliated subreddits.  You might get some good ideas there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 06:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pregnancy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 05:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never run into anyone who thought someone else was a demon, let alone call them one.  How offensive were you to them, exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 18:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That Papua New Guinea's 'Black Jesus', convicted rapist Steven Tari, was hacked to death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 18:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe they've presented any evidence, only their word on it.

CNN article on it here: http://www.cnn.com/2013/06/17/opinion/bergen-nsa-spying

"On Thursday, Sens. Ron Wyden and Mark Udall, Democrats who both serve on the Senate Select Committee on Intelligence and have access to the nation's most sensitive secrets, released a statement contradicting this assertion. "Gen. Alexander's testimony yesterday suggested that the NSA's bulk phone records collection program helped thwart 'dozens' of terrorist attacks, but all of the plots that he mentioned appear to have been identified using other collection methods," the two senators said.

Indeed, a survey of court documents and media accounts of all the jihadist terrorist plots in the United States since 9/11 by the New America Foundation shows that traditional law enforcement methods have overwhelmingly played the most significant role in foiling terrorist attacks." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 17:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine would be 0.  She's a nice lady who works harder than I do.  I like her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 17:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being as active and mobile as I am now.  I will not be in 20 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 17:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't agree.  Fox is decidedly conservative while NBC is decidedly liberal.  Guests who appear on those channels or news sites are quickly shot down or bullied due to their opposing positions.  Each one caters to a particular mind set, as do the others.  They can say they're unbiased all they want but it doesn't make it true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 16:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I just really want an unbiased answer based on facts instead of opinions."  Yeah, don't we all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 16:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fox News and NBC aren't any different from any other major news site, they just happen to be of a particular point of view opposite to each other.  They're all large corporations going for the money, they all know what sells and they go after it.  There are no completely unbiased news sites and those are as valid as any other.  You have to read both sides to get an idea of the truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 16:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only reason I know of to be intentionally fired is to get unemployment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 16:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it's upvoted it gains a point.  When it's downvoted it loses a point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 07:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ACLU says it does.

Here: http://www.nytimes.com/2013/08/27/us/nsa-phone-data-collection-is-illegal-aclu-says.html

Here: https://www.aclu.org/blog/national-security/aclu-court-government-spying-invades-privacy-each-and-every-american </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 07:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  Anyone can type /user/username and see your comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 07:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no way to know this since war casualties are estimates, and the numbers saved couldn't possibly be ascertained or accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 07:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's bad because this isn't a free advertising website.  If you want to promote yourself you need to pay them for the space.  Otherwise, everybody and his brother would be doing it and reddit would eventually become nothing but an online business listing website.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 05:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buy some paint brushes and hand them over to a bunch of kids with the instruction to make it the Ugliest Truck In The County.  Take pics for prosperity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 05:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tissues.  I've never had to use them but I have them ready just in case I do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 18:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never lost my faith in humanity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 18:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find a good lawyer to represent me when I was sued in court for theft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 18:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd go to work like every other day.  I have no say-so in world affairs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 18:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That if I pulled my dad's finger I'd grow big and tall.  I pulled that finger countless times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 18:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you talking about? Black people use the word all the time.  It is not up to me or you to determine if that's offensive to God or if it isn't, or, if that is considered taking the Lord's name in vain since "God" isn't His name.  You should stop and let God do the judging.  You can't put your personal morality on other people.  Do what's right for you and let God take care of the rest.  Will saying the word "fuck" keep me out of heaven, too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 18:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it offensive too, but it's their right to say any word they want to.  Make your preference known to the people doing it and then leave it alone.  They're adults with the right to free speech, just like you are.  Remember, you aren't their judge or jury. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 17:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the beach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 17:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leaving the house soon after breakfast and not coming home until lunchtime.  Leaving after lunch and not coming home until dinner time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 17:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should not occur at this time.  The US needs to wait for the UN inspector's report and not go in at all without the full support of the UN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 17:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You probably have worms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 17:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Powerball lottery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 17:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google how many psychics have been wrong in their predictions.  Then show her this one: 

http://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/2013/05/09/celebrity-psychic-sylvia-browne-under-fire-for-telling-amanda-berrys-mom-was/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 17:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlikely, since we'd all have to fight for the basics to survive.  I'd get what I needed to live, one way or another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 08:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baking soda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 08:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try /r/History. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 06:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first moon landing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 19:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Community College for the first two years then transfer to University.  Helps keep the costs down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 19:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm never going to be younger than I am right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 19:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll pay less per year if I opt out and just pay the penalty.  I'm paying for insurance now that I don't need, so I might as well pay less for nothing.  If I should need it, it'll be there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 18:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good question for /r/TrueAskReddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 15:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People come into your life and people go out.  Just understand that you don't get to keep them, so be happy for whatever time you had together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 09:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been there as long as I can remember. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 09:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's the one determining your death date?  I don't know where to go with this without knowing how it was determined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 09:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drugging people without their consent is against the law.  I'll relax when *I* want to relax, not when someone forces it on me in the face of sudden death.  This is not a good idea, in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 07:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think all their hard work and effort in anything else gets thrown out the door the instant they portray themselves as slutty women.  Got a PhD? No matter, show me that ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 07:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 14 year olds who think they're experts on foreign policy, and  any other subject that comes up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 06:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When one states they want to make an introduction people assume they're new.  Since you aren't, ask whatever you want to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 06:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There isn't a subreddit for introductions, but you could start one.  This is a subreddit for asking questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 04:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pusillanimous

Garrulous

Apoplectic

Plinth

Ameliorate

Mastication

Supercilious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 04:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since when has the will of the people made any difference, or even been considered, in war plans and strategies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 04:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, not me, sorry.  I can't tell you that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 04:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd buy a new chair I've been looking at for two weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 03:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assad is not a stupid man.  This is part of the plan and he's the sacrificial lamb.  Defense secretaries seem to have a penchant for war and declaring things with no proof but a few internet supplied videos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 00:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knowing that it would be my last life before going to Heaven.  At least I'd know I had made progress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 00:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good question for /r/TrueAskReddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 00:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cauliflower and collards sauteed in foie gras sprinkled with stinky cheese and served over tongue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 21:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone should have and display good ethical behaviour, no matter what job they have or don't have.  Right and wrong conduct shouldn't be an option in society, but that's why we have laws. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 17:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You lack critical thinking skills and can't see what's in front of your face either, apparently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 17:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, *really*.  You'll find out one day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 16:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God has seven eyes that go to and from over the Earth.  Zechariah 4:10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 16:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's omniscient, He sees it and doesn't forget any of it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 08:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the US wants a good reason to sell invasion and war to the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 08:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New York City </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 06:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the view and I'm in no hurry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 06:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, twice.  Scariest thing that's ever happened to me.  I thought I was having a heart attack.  Overwhelming sense of dread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 06:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There used to be one called /r/hiddenrooms, but it's dead now, it seems.  I'd try /r/secretpassages for a start, although there isn't activity there either.  Perhaps you could message one of the mods from those subreddits for an updated place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 04:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd explain the situation to the customer and why I can't take any action at this time, take down all pertinent information so that I could get on it first thing Monday morning. Then I'd follow through on my word on Monday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 04:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm against killing any animal for reasons other than consumption.  If you're going to eat it then it's ok to use the skin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 04:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should have asked him to elaborate on that.  That's going to happen no matter a person's age.  I get that crap from 12 year olds.  Everybody's an expert when you disagree with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 04:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one cares about your jeans or your shoes.  Stop posting this crap before you're reported. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 04:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Print out a note and tape it on the building where they're sure to see it.  Tell them they've been observed participating in illegal activities and if they're seen there again the police will be notified.  You aren't going to stop them no matter what you do, so you might was well warn them to move along. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 03:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The majority of Americans don't trust or support them any more than you do.  I wouldn't be surprised if they reach the point of saturation sooner than the government expects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 03:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as they don't work together directly and one isn't the others' superior I don't see a problem with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 03:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you've figured out that American citizens are not the government.  Nowadays, they do things without securing proper approval or the citizens' support first.  The majority do not support any intervention in Syria and want more attention paid to domestic issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 03:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ferlin Huskey, Mel Tillis, Patsy Cline, Loretta Lynn, Conway Twitty,  Tammy Wynette, Hank Williams, Ray Price, Johnny Cash and all those people famous in country music back then.

Here's one of his favorites, [Jim Reeves - He'll Have To Go](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bpi8Bek6jdM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 02:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe it's your business, either, despite your finger-shaking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 01:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's common courtesy to be respectful to others and some people are more vocal about that expectation.  Those people have lived through far more than you have and have more knowledge and wisdom in things you don't know about yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 01:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You want hope that things will change just like the rest of us.  I'm afraid that isn't going to happen no matter how much we want it to or spout off on websites.  Climate change is the least of your worries, or should be.  There are far greater evils at work right now over which we have no control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 23:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How old are you?  Are you living at home with parents? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 23:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they want Assad out one way or another.  If a "threat" to get that ball rolling is required, then a "threat"  is what they will have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 23:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Education, experience and sometimes Google.  Everything's a resource. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 23:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DrudgeReport.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 23:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course they can.  You don't have to be in every situation but you can certainly have an informed opinion on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 23:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Etch-A-Sketch](http://www.itstrulyrandom.com/wp-content/uploads/2008/04/monalisaetchascketch.jpg) would sidetrack him and ruin his future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 22:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Looks like you get it.](http://i.imgur.com/m79FdAu.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 21:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/videos 

/r/youtube 

/r/fullmoviesonyoutube 

/r/documentaries

uncabled subreddits - http://www.reddit.com/me/m/uncabled

/r/movies 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 21:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It's still on the front page!](http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1l31r3/what_is_a_free_pc_game_that_you_think_everyone/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 19:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you utilize the search button over there on the right of your screen you'll see that this question has been asked and answered many, many times.  I'm sure you can get an idea of what people think from their comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 19:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd leave the site.  I don't do facebook and I wouldn't do reddit.  There are scary people in this world and I don't want them at my house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 18:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We aren't murderers here.  Go to a prison and ask one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 18:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've invited the UN to come in for inspections. There's more than meets the eye on this, so be wary of headlines from biased MSM news sources.  I refer you to this thread:

http://www.reddit.com/r/worldnews/comments/1l3zke/syria_un_inspectors_shot_at_by_snipers/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 18:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1l423z/what_is_a_free_pc_program_everyone_should_have/

That front page link was submitted *4 hours ago*.  Search it first since this has been asked and answered a billion times already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 05:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try these:

/r/conceptart

/r/futureporn

/r/ImaginaryCharacters

/r/ImaginaryLandscapes

/r/ImaginaryMonsters

/r/ImaginaryTechnology

/r/SpecArt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 03:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Android allows you to add the apps you want.  Check out Google Play or the Android Store. See if anything there will work for you.   It's much more customizable.  I know it has Microsoft Word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 03:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mousetrap with peanut butter or cheese should do the trick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 03:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get an Android tablet instead of those. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 03:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Avatar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 03:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll stay with you for a while then go away while you're focused on other things.  It comes back from time to time, but by the time you're old and gray you'll have a better understanding of it and it won't worry you so much.  That's a very, very long time from now so, stop worrying and don't do anything you'll regret later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 03:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, just wrap me in linen and throw me in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 03:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen things...strange things.  But they were not ETs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
