<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5136</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 17:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Could a business even have profits of they had to pay for all of this stuff on their own?

Who knows? That means roads are paid for by businesses - but that also means Walmart wouldn't pay billions in taxes. Likely, they would still make plenty of money - but the cost might be passed to the consumer. 

Even if that's not correct (and it's really really hypothetical), regular government benefits that Walmart and every other business gets, **is not called a subsidy, and defining it as such is intellectually dishonest**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 16:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geeze tell me about it. 

I FUCKING KNOW I AM FULL SCREEN DAMMIT GOOGLE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 16:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is politics. Democrats would never propose this because Republicans would actually vote yes to it - that would make Republicans look good. Well, Democrats can't have that.

Republicans won't propose this because... well frankly, because they are stupid as balls. Why the hell don't they propose something like this? 

I hate politicians, even the ones I tend to agree with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 16:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would happen if those employees receiving partial welfare subsidies didn't have a job at Walmart? 

Answer: they would have to **receive even more subsidies from the government, costing the taxpayer more money**. I would argue Walmart is saving the taxpayer money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 16:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um they pay taxes, which supports roads, municipal services and everything else. It's quite a stretch to say Walmart gets 'subsidies'. Then we can say every business gets 'subsidies'. In fact, **you** get subsidies because you use the road!

Sounds absurd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 16:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What subsidies? Are you pulling this out your ass?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 16:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Change laws to make this much more difficult, if not impossible to happen.

2. Lower corporate tax rate to make sure this doesn't happen.

This will increase revenue from WalMart and companies like Apple, Google, etc. At a 35% tax rate, and with laws that allow you to take money overseas easily, is there any surprise? Instead of getting 35%, we end up getting significantly less. So then what's the point of the 35% tax rate if it forces companies overseas? It is self defeating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Socialist Party HQ Now a $6.5 Million Mansion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 15:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 15:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's megabytes or megabits? I always forget how the capitalization works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 14:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well so was Lebron when he was on Miami. This year too - just his two top guys got injured. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 06:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No duh. Its just a funny comparison </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lebron James is the Peyton Manning of the NBA: he's lost 2x more championships than he's won. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 05:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 02:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this case I probably want to sell. I'm sure the people who bought yesterday will be happy with a 30% gain. Ya maybe I'll sell if it goes down more than 5% tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 02:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait so this guys posts on twitter and the stock goes up 40%? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 23:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does having a small group of people with concentrated wealth imply that there is a large group of poor people?

Practically speaking, they usually come together, but one doesn't imply the other. That's what I don't understand.

EDIT: Have not watched video yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 22:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone actually explain why income/wealth inequality is bad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LIQD is up 38%. What de heck? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 22:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see no news at all about the company, yet it went up 38%. I bought this stock at $.34 or so. Maybe it's time to cash out. Not sure what to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you translate this? The translation someone gave me doesn't sound right. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *  *

From the bottom of [this page](http://hebrewbooks.org/shas.aspx?mesechta=25 daf=9 format=pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Am I better off converting conservative and then once I'm in a place where I can afford to live alone, finally going full blown orthodox?

I think that would make it much more difficult for Orthodox Rabbis to take you seriously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 16:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The counterargument is "We need to stimulate the economy, and *spend more* on the lower class". What you said doesn't seem like a counterargument. 

I say spend less, you say 'we can't pay the interest' - so what are you trying to say? Don't spend less?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 15:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point. Although the austerity measures on Greece is not really a function of 'trickle down' thinking - it's more of a function of "were going bankrupt, and we can't spend this money". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 15:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whether the IMF is right or wrong, how is this any different than any economist making such a statement? Or a college, or some other group? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 15:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money does trickle down. Just not that much. Like a user said above, much less money is injected into the economy when given to wealthy - but **some** is - just not that much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 14:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well not exactly. It's more about how much (or really, how little) wealth trickles down. Even when the wealthy keeps their money in a bank account, it helps the lower class in someway (banks can lend more for example). 

Not saying it justifies certain policies. But saying it doesn't exist at all is simply not true. It trickles down, just not as much as some would have us think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 04:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well at least the karma I got for this point kinda made up for it...

I was actually surprised that was my most downvoted comment. I thought it would have been one of my conservative leaning comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 04:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I did too good of a job - because that was the point. But I used an example that is so farfetched, that no one in their right mind should think I'm being serious. I was trying to use anti-vaxxer logic to the extreme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 20:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea. Here is what I was responding to:

http://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/2x9ww2/law_requiring_california_parents_to_vaccinate/coy93br </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone link that comment from a guy who was a boy, but his psycho mom told him he was a girl. Dressed him like a girl - and he thought he was a girl until he was like 8 years old. He thought his penis would just fall off eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Legend of Zelda and Doom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My most downvoted comment? For making a joke that was making fun of anti-vaxxers. Except people couldn't tell that I was joking, and thought I was serious. 

 I believe that shooting people in the kidneys is good for their health. Who are you to tell me otherwise? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I downvoted that comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, I am a recruiter from Google. We were interested in interviewing you for a managerial position. We regret to inform you that we are forced to rescind our offer. We do not believe you will fit within our culture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giving head? What does 'making her own decisions' even mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 16:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repost from /u/maniactigwelder

 I have had 2 fathers in my lifetime. My biological father and my Step-Father. My biological dad was diagnosed with skin cancer in 2003 and died in 2005 from said disease, which then absolutely crushed my mom. She then got remarried in 2009 to my step dad. In 2011 he was in a work related accident that ended with him drowning in a storm drain due to a careless driver.
I was 17 at the time, and when we received the news, my mom went borderline catatonic. All she did was exist as a shell of herself, and manage to go to her job. So I had to step up and (literally) be the man of the house for her and my sister who was living at home at the time. I cooked, cleaned, and did all the housework, in tandem with finishing highschool, and working nearly full-time. Did that for nearly 2 years before she came back out of her funk, but that whole experience really prepared my for the harsh reality that is life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 16:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was absolutely horrendous. I'm glad. Don't fuck with my bookmarks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 15:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the same problem as you. I couldn't really learn anything on my own unless it was being taught to me. However eventually, when you spend enough time learning, you will be able to learn on your own. It might just take a while.

But if you really can never figure out how to learn on your own, you are probably screwed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 23:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a moment... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 22:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reallly? Can we please make an announcement when this happens?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 22:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm okay that's going to far. There is a moment ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 19:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buy everything I could possibly want, obviously. Then in the 9th year, buy a bagillion Visa gift cards. Then declare bankruptcy when the money is due. But no one will know about my visa gift cards. Keep living the high life. Done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 19:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who drive the speed limit in the left lane. 

**GET OUT OF THE LEFT LANE OR I WILL MURDER YOUR CHILDREN** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love STI/WRXs. One of my favorite cars I drove was an older WRX. Have fun dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wanna roll up in my Mercedes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I own makkos, as well as others. I wanted a digital copy because I left mine at home. but thanks for the unsolicited advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 03:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am on tes amud aleph now. Learning with a chabura. Going very very slow. Its a chabura of balei tshuva. Most of us weren't able to spend enough time in yeshiva. And we are all Russian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 03:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strawman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  a fitting theme for someone who became a billionaire by buying and selling companies.

Except he is not a billionaire. A glaring mistake in the first paragraph. Kind of sounds like a biased, butt-hurt Quinn supporter pretending to be a journalist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or an Obama </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Plenty of slaves for my robot colony"

And of course,

"There is a moment..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amargo went full white-girl: he couldn't even. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little late to the game, but here it goes...

**I once was sent to the principals office in 1st grade because I was "Innapropriately using the hand dryer" in the bathroom.**

And no, it's not what you are thinking. The teacher pulled me aside after I got out of the bathroom and started yelling at me. I think maybe I was slapping the front of the dryer. Honestly I was confused the whole time. While she was yelling at me she said, "YOU HEAR THAT?" - pointing back at that bathroom - "That's what you were doing!!". 

I honestly had no idea what she was talking about. And if that was the case, why didn't she go and pull the student who just came out of the bathroom.

My Mom got a phone call about it. She had no idea what to even think. We laugh about it to this day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha I like that the cold hearted litvak linked this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/namer98 has posted quite a few anti-orthodox articles here. Let's stop taking his post seriously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly what I was looking for. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So basically he wants Orthodox Judaism to become Conservative Judaism? So after 3000 years of tradition, Orthodox Jews will change their stances simply because a bunch of immoral liberals tell them to? I certainly hope not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for Talmud in original text </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find a lot of translations into English, but I am having trouble finding digital versions of the actual text of the Talmud. Specifically, I am looking for Tractate Makkos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought not having legends was part of the joke - turns out it is just bad graph making.

LABEL YOUR DAMN CHARTS.

And thanks for the explanation. Would have never realized we were talking about 'hash'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 23:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 22:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this useful? Who has a resolution monitor that high? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 19:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a moment... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 19:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is more because Cooper didn't go just to save humanity. He was also going because he hated farming - "You were good at something, and you never had a chance to use it". I think she felt he was abandoning her to pursue his dreams. 

This goes well in parallel with Dr. Brand's idea to go to Dr. Edmund's planet. She says she wanted to go there because it was more likely to support life - but really she wanted to see Dr. Edmund. Same thing with Cooper. He said he was going to help save humanity - but really just wanted to do what he loved. And Muprh felt that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 19:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a moment... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 18:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus fucking Google it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 18:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's the definition of premature optimization. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 17:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To remind you, because you seem to have forgotten, my comment was in response to this:

 You know, like the ones its always trying to manufacture for countries it attempts to apply special double standards upon?

Israel is the example. Did I compare the actions of Israel or any country to 200-300 prostitution cases? You made a classical strawman argument, and somehow at least 2 idiots agreed with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 15:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He lost me at 'this' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 15:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most obvious example would be israel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 15:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cough Israel cough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 05:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Former TGI Fridays employee here. 

You dont want to order the pecan crusted chicken salad if you want to be healthy. Used to see skinny white girls order this salad all day long. Thing is, it's around *1400 calories*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 05:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you motherfucker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a moment... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea that's quite a stretch. The 'minute' might have relatively changed  compared to Earth's minutes - but that's really irrelevant even if that was true (which it is probably not, because they don't mention any time loss in regards to Dr. Mann's planet) - as there is no reason for TARS to change the rpm to match 'real time'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 00:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a moment... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 21:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a moment... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 21:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a moment... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work on a team that used to have part of the team work in Mumbai. Definitely lose some quality when using overseas workers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 16:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping that she was going to fall on the way down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 15:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea it was an interesting color outside this morning. I thought it was just cloudy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 12:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just kept saying 'Stop! Stop!' While watching that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 23:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow thank you... /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 19:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain to me what 4chan is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting thought, but I don't think anyone ever means radians when saying 'rpm' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 21:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Voting fraud isn't real. Duh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 18:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol wut? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The Endurance's spin is 67, 68 rpm" - actually if you watch the scene and time the rotation, the spin is actually closer to 20 rpm. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 13:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch the [awesome docking scene](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GhlU3ikw8sA) again. Time the rotation yourself, and you'll see it's waaay less than 67 rpm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 05:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol that's the only line I laughed at </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 17:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, /r/politics is probably most guilty of this than any other subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 14:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> o o. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 14:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You actually didn't answer the question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 14:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was pronounced "youler", not "oiler". Am I wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 23:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another movie with a fantastic soundtrack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 21:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No - the cost of having 'the survival skills of boy scouts'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 19:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey look another way for us to dig ourselves into debt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 19:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering Harvard is sitting on the biggest endowment in the country ($36 billion), this seems like a colossal waste of money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Billionaire gives Harvard $400 million gift -- a new record </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 19:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 18:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calling this 'cyberpunk' is an insult to Hans Zimmer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 16:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was entertaining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 02:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was corrected, it was actually mission to mars.

But there is also a self sacrifice in red planet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 02:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shoot you're right, Red Planet is that one with Val Kilmer and the matrix girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 00:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I feel like Gravity coming out a year earlier was bad for Interstellar, honestly. It looked like 'another space film' so people were maybe less interested. I've met a lot of people who saw Gravity but not Interstellar. Just unfortunate really.

Before I saw this movie - that's also what I thought. I barely read any reviews. I just heard that it was a good movie. I was shocked by how *good* Interstellar actually was. That'd be very sad if someone saw Gravity and not Interstellar. Gravity is a joke compared to Interstellar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 23:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really missed out huh. I wonder if they'll ever air it again in IMAX. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 22:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the biggest thing is not just the lack of winners, but the lack of depth to Nadal's forehand. You see anytime Nadal hit the ball slightly short, Djokavic would move and play the net (very well I might add). I think if Nadal fixes that up, and gets his confidence back, he can easily win next year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 22:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never go full retard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 19:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol no are you kidding? I saw him post this for the 18th time yesterday. I was wondering if that's a number he pulled out of his hat, but he is actually counting. The point is:

**MAKE A FUCKING STICKY ALREADY** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Orbital velocities are a significant fraction of c near the event horizon. Coupled with time dilation even more intense than on Miller's world, Endurance's flyby lasted minutes for the crew.

It is my understanding that supermassive black holes are *light years* wide. Some are thousands of light years wide. So it would have taken them *years*, even at near speed of light. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh interesting. Never thought of that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some thoughts about Interstellar (spoilers of course) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just some observations/questions  I have about the movie (and no, I won't ask how it's possible that the future humans can... )

1. **The music might be the best part of the movie**. I mean really, it's phenominal. I've been listening to it at work. I highly suggest listening to [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iBfk37Fa3H0) from beginning to end. It will make you appreciate the movie even more.

2. **Doyle killed himself**. He could have easily ran into the ranger after Case went to get Dr. Brand. It's really his own damn fault for dying. He waited too long, and then took an extra glance at the wave before dying.

3. **What happened to the spaghetti effect?** So I've read that larger black holes might not have this effect - *but if it is a supermassive black hole, then they wouldn't have been able to 'slingshot' around it - that would have taken years*. Maybe I'm missing something. Either the spaghetti effect should have happened, or they should not have been able to slingshot around the black hole

4. **Murph's reaction to seeing her father**. I get that she was a peace, and old, and didn't need closure anymore. However, I would think she would ask the questions, "Hey Dad, how did you send a message across space and time? And how did you figure out the gravity problem? And where have you been? Why aren't you with Dr. Brand?"

5. **Dr. Brand's poem - Rage against the dying of the light**. I found it interesting that both Dr. Brand (sr.) and Dr. Mann seemed to really liked this poem. The poem seemed to be about fighting against 'the dying of the light' - or the extermination of the humans. Ironically, they are the two characters in the movie that actually *gave up* on plan A - saving the humans. Instead, they *give up*, and opt for just continuing the race - but not saving the people. It seems that *they both did not 'rage against the dying of the light', despite their love for that poem*.

6. **The very cliche "man sacrifices himself to save woman in space"** - I can think of two other times I've seen this in movies. In Red Planet, one character opens his helmet, so his wife doesn't die trying to save him (Tim Robbins). In Gravity, George Clooney cuts the cord in order to save the woman (Sandra Bullock). And here, Cooper detaches to save Dr. Brand. Cliche? Sexist a bit? Doesn't bother me much, just thought about it.

7. **If this movie was released earlier, it probably would have been named 'Gravity'**. Well I'm not sure, but it's a possibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the /u/the_hiding answer:

 It's essentially, for whatever reason, definite to happen

That is literally the definition of the Predestination Paradox - which is not really a paradox at all. But that's what it's called. We need to make a sticky on this subreddit explaining this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But in the end it's all irrelevant. Once he's done in the Tesseract, "they" can put Cooper back into our spacetime wherever and whenever they choose.
 COOPER: They have access to infinite time and space...
 In the end "they" decided to put him back within range of Cooper Station at around the same time that Brand was arriving at Edmunds' world.

This. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 17:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will people stop saying it's the bootstrap paradox? It's not. It is a [predestination paradox] (http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Predestination_paradox) - which is not actually a paradox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
