<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4298</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 08:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit, someone stole my profile pic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 08:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> gotta get there before the hair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 08:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's really laid-back and charismatic. But primarily, he's just damn funny and has been since he was Knighted as Not So Grump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 08:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Yes he is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 08:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People don't have to be bound by something they said in the past. He could change his mind at any time. But yes, it would be great to see him on Grumpcade.

Maybe he and Dan will debut on Grumpcade with the same episode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 07:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ne'er a truer word spoken! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 16:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have Soundbooth? If you do, use the preset "Reduce Peaks" apply it, then use the preset "Everything The Same Level" and apply that.

The Grumps use something along those lines with their own preset in their audio program.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 15:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming this summer: "Anne Frank" starring Miley Cyrus! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 21:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats the one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 21:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, I believe there's a song on youtube about that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 18:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/askreddit is the most curious little boy I've ever met! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 18:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's r/funny being obnoxious again... god, someone needs to change his name... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 16:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my worst nightmare.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 17:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Four Score and Seven Beers Ago, I realized I am lonely... I need someone to accompany me to the theater tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 17:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Executive) You can't use that scene idea for a SpecSaver ad! Put that idea in the rejected pile! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 17:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you already had me shaking it at "ice cold" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 17:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool harp! Do you know how to play "Iron Man?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 17:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Arin the most. He's the funniest and he's clearly a caring and generous guy, considering he built this business using his popularity to give his friends employment, and to help them get their own popularity (I highly doubt Jontron or NSP would be doing well without their involvement with Egoraptor)

I think his comedy is better suited for what he's doing now, a twice a day, ten-minute show where he just improvises, making jokes about video-games, instead of his animations: an occasional 30-second to 1-minute short where he improvises, making jokes about video-games. I don't see all the hype about missing his animations. He's making the exact same jokes on Grumps he'd be making with his animations, he just doesn't have to take months to *animate* the jokes. And let's be honest, he's not exactly a good artist. Decent enough to make animations, but not good.

*Having that said*, I can't stand his opinions on most issues, and I think he has very bad analytical skills regarding video-games and movies. I also can't stand his whining (but I hate whining from anyone, even Dan and Jon.... but Arin does it the most)

And I think he handled the Jon fiasco the right way. If there was a bad-guy in the breakup, I'd think Jon was probably it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 17:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that perception is delusional. It was an official business when Jon was there.

It's impossible to be successful on Youtube unless you run it like a business. It is a job, after all, and Game Grumps was a business from day one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 17:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> with a Kitchen Knife </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 06:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit, have I been weeding out friends on facebook the wrong way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 04:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never knew there was a thing called Maker TV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 23:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Disneyland moved to New York </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 20:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are Arin and DisneyLand still friends? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 18:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was pretty damn clever! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 18:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But dude, there weren't even any jelly beans in that level </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 07:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you all for throwing this WONDERFUL baby shower!  The baby's dead, ANYWAY, who wants cake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 07:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, don't go that way. There's a big mine fiel-- (**BOOM**) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 07:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This summer! Adam Sandler and Andy Samberg star in... "The Host And The Parasite!"

Rated PG-13 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 07:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have money right? Yeah, you can afford liposuction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 07:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they made chemotherapy sound so fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 07:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this scene prompt gets posted in some iteration almost on a weekly basis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 07:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome back to the second season of Firefly! Which takes place in space, but the space part DOESN'T matter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 07:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many times have I told you... you put the cereal in **BEFORE** THE MILK!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 07:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you would feel that same emotional attachment to another form of entertainment that brings you joy, if you stopped watching Game Grumps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 07:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why everyone thinks he's so bad at games. I mean, he did grab *ALL 30 JELLY BEANS* every single time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 06:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually don't care, but there's only so many jokes Danny can make at the expense of Arin's failure before it gets boring. A whole episode of fuck-ups is fine, but not if it's the exact same fuck-up over and over again. Go to a different level and fuck-up there.

Plus, it's just super fucking annoying to hear Arin complain about a video-game. Ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that works. Looked up a quick video </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 03:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah. Makes sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 02:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> really? I have to try this real quick (*fuck* looking it up)


edit: It doesn't work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 06:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, whatever happens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 22:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm... are you stupid or a troll? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 22:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Katy Perry's boobs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 22:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> askreddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 22:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peeing on the homeless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 22:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The more you argue with an idiot on the internet, the stupider and more stubborn you make them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 22:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 22:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> E-mail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 20:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what she said </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 20:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Avocado Cadabra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 20:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lara Croft. Besides the obvious sexual reasons, she also has a job that would bring home a good amount of money, and she'd be able to protect the house pretty damn well. I'd basically let her wear the pants of the relationship, which I'd be okay with because of those sweet, pointy ta-tas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 20:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly being scared </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 20:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno... GOD, I hate questions like this! It just ruins my day! Jesus! Grrr! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 19:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, Candice, I can see where you got that sweet ass..... your dad in those jeans is drivin' me wild! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 19:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You expect me to believe that? ...... are you THAT afraid of an ass-whoopin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 19:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ew! You sick perv! That's your great great great(x1000) grandmother! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 18:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, I think that was on Family Guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 18:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, shucks! I've now been halfway turned into the last animal I touched! This is quite a predicament! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 18:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Story, Mario's hair color, A box that is without a beat, Ross's face, Food, Good Games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 18:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, I think each and every sin should end with "unless you want to" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 18:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should put a parenthetical next to Ross like this:

Ross (Sometimes?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 18:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They mostly play older Nintendo games that are basically an abandoned market. The primary reason is, Nintendo hasn't found the Grump videos or cared enough to flag them.

Plus, Maker Studios has a better understanding of the ins-and-outs of the legal issues presented here. I think they'd be confident enough to defend the Grumps in court if Nintendo tried to claim the revenue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 18:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Send something to their twitters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 07:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am Ganondorf! King of all Evil in the Land of Hyrule! I demand to know what's in the soup of the day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 07:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What'd he do? Rape a bitch? Alright, feed him to the sharks. NEXT!

What'd she do?  Cheated on her taxes?  Alright, feed her to the sharks. NEXT!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 07:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You better have my money by Thursday, you got it? If it aint in my hands by then, I'm gonna hook you up with a nice job with medical benefits that pays 35 dollars an hour so you can pay off your debt!

....trust me... you don't want it to go that far.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 07:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I brought you a little something that'll warm your house.... it's a *fire!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 07:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robin! Quick! To the Batmobile! Mr. Slippy Fist is getting away! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 07:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed it. I kinda have that same behavior when my best friends talk about hanging out with other people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 07:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was probably planned for it to be once Danny had a series longer than Sonic 06.

They probably only picked FireRed back up so that they wouldn't have to wait as long to reach that point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 07:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice to see a fan that understands that the channel is more than just a show where people talk around video-games. It's a legitimate business that produces a product in an industry where you walk a fine line between being profitable and being bankrupt, entirely depending on how your audience perceives you.

You also have a fantastic grasp on the New Media industry.

Most people (especially on this sub) don't understand the decisions that Arin made about mentioning Jon and they think that: Jon disagreeing with Arin's decisions = Arin lied.

I think they handled the situation perfectly, and I think they let the right amount of time pass to cement the new era of Game Grumps in, so that they could discuss the old era without the potential to damage the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy Birthday..... Mr. President...... (seductive dancing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn it! Nothing but white kids again... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 18:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who wants Jack Daniels?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 18:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked Jon's part, lol. Like he was in exile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 18:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need Nostalgia Critic and Egoraptor playing a Simpsons game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 18:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, Bloodborne's been pretty boring so far... but I wouldn't say it matters if it's Modern or not. They should just play what they feel like playing. 

I kinda prefer them fucking up a lot though. It reminds me that I'm not watching this show for the games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 18:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> everybody do.... **The Barry Bump!**  (beatboxing begins) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 18:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they turned off the music settings, sure.

It's an amazing game, too, I'd love to see them play it as it'd spark a lot of heavy metal music discussions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 18:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of the things Arin has said about motivation, hard work, and etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 18:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 16:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saved this country 2 billion dollars in debt by switching to Geico! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 16:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the rockets red glaaare!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 15:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, there's a demo somewhere.

it wasn't good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 22:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an actual project, not just a Let's Play. It takes time to produce, and they don't have a big post-production team. There's a lot of editing that needs to be done, which will be more complicated because they'll have to make sure it's coherent and actually tells a story (even if it is a Reality-Show-esque story) There seems to be a lot of live-action elements to it, and that's a lot harder to edit than game footage. There's a lot more to editing a real project than just putting clips in the correct order. Once the raw edit is done, it is immediately followed by Sound Mixing, Music, Color Correction, etc.  Each of which are difficult and time-consuming on their own.

They also have to balance this project with the other projects they're working on (some of which they probably haven't told the fans about yet) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 06:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, Cyclops.... *Staring Contest?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 06:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SERIOUSLY, JESUS!? Heroin!? In MY house!?  I knew being a hippie for 30 years would lead to this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 06:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Well, Mr. Johnson, you're hired! I think you're the best person for this position!" 

(Must....resist....) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 06:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pure evil! 

I'll take seven </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 06:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're my new hero </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 06:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that it's not even clever makes it instantly clever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 06:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> funny shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 06:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Scrolls to the bottom)

"We know you didn't read that.... Agree anyway?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
