<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9585</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 07:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's not forget Gawker, Jezebel, MSNBC, and Salon, quite possibly the most biased news sites on the internet. http://i.imgur.com/S0j2kCD.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 07:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep getting told by the left that all these terrorist Muslims are being oppressed and come from poor uneducated backgrounds, that this is reason why they commit acts of terror. Also I keep getting told that the Quran is the most progressive religious text out there despite numerous violent, sexists, and homophobic verses. So much for that theory, I guess reality doesn't quite have the liberal bias that idiotic SJWs keep shouting about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 06:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not surprised at all, a lot of feminists and SJWs tend to be very scummy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 06:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The very same people that are eager to overlook Planned Parenthood's dark history are often the same people that are eager to point out the history of the battle flag of Virginia which they keep confusing for the confederate flag. It is as if things change but the left is very selective about applying the same standards to everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 00:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The author takes a look at a recent court trial's ruling and how it will affect the current rape hysteria trend and kangaroo courts that are popping up at various schools due to the pressures of Title IX. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Court Ruling Highlights Flaws In College Sexual Assault Proceedings: Male student at UC San Diego who was accused of sexual assault and suspended after a campus investigation filed a countersuit  and won. Heres a look at if and how this could affect college rape trials across the country. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 00:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
