<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1576</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent comment, the keyword is FEELING.  Boredom is just that an emotion just like happiness, anger, frustration, resentment, joy, desire, and cravings.  We get stronger each time we see the emotion and doggedly persist in our daily commitment to ourselves not to drink TODAY, only. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/standardcapacityman to r/stopdrinking.  I don't know what sort of device you're working off of so I don't know if you can see the sidebar, but there is a link to the 2014 survey which you might find enlightening.  Most of us report in the polling data that we were able to stop drinking with little or no discomfort.  Obviously to some extent or another we are all different and our use was different, but I'm suggesting that most of us get through the rapids pretty easily. At this [link is a post called the Baby Steps that lays](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) what I did to stop drinking and to get sober.  There might be some "next steps" for you too.  good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I came back after a 7 year relapse (I had been sober in a previous life for 15 continuous years) the same old things worked to stop drinking that had worked before.  Simple sober actions: [the Baby Steps were not beneath me.](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/)  I still do them today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reason I don't drink TODAY is because I stayed sober long enough to begin to see and value my alcohol-free life.  Life  on life's terms.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the confederate flag ain't 'bout no racism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Court blocks Texas abortion law ruling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confederate flag: KKK chapter to hold rally on South Carolina Statehouse grounds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/kittyhugtime to /r/stopdrinking -- at this [link you will find a post called the Baby Steps](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) which describes exactly what I did to stop drinking and to get sober.  Most of us come into recovery with some real painful memories and consequences.  At your young age you are poised to turn it around early and live a happy and full life.  Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's what works for me when I'm feeling "off" or that maybe I'm not as strong as was--I cling to the notion that I've felt this way in the past and it was usually a prelude to a breakthrough or some real insight that if I had not doggedly persisted I would never have arrived at.  I also cling to the hope and belief that my sharing even when I'm down--helps others when they are down and hanging on by what feels like fingernails.  That's what you did with this post /u/kittyislazy, you helped me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shawn Ford apologizes to family for sledgehammer slayings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Supreme Court's big death-penalty fight just exploded into the open </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Supreme Court ruling clears the way for Ohio congressional redistricting reform </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations /u/notyourtowndrunk on your week sober.  Each day it gets easier and you will have, bit by bit, more clarity.  Stay strong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glossip v Gross: Sotomayor's scorching death penalty accusation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samuel Alito: Death Is Painful, So Why Not Lethal Injection? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holding the Powerful Accountable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Supreme Court passed on a chance to expand the constitutional protections enjoyed by members of Congress. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Court wont hear jailed congressmans appeal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-Carlisle Barracks resident gets 30 years in federal prison in 'monstrous' child-sex case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 19:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 17:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The opinion of the court is at this link.](http://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/14pdf/13-1314_kjfl.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Net neutrality rules off to a smooth start; FCC sets sights on broadband privacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 15:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 15:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He will lose his position as CJ when one of either two things happen: 1. he dies; 2. he retires. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 15:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forget the bed.  Cat sleeps where the cat wants.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Roberts to America: I'm in Charge Here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 14:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 14:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing like upholding your oath of office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Legal Profession Blog: On the Chief Justice's dissent in Obergefell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 14:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prominent Mississippi attorney fatally shot during a deposition at his law office </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 14:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alabama Chief Justice Roy Moore says Christians will be 'persecuted' after same-sex marriage ruling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 14:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rep. Justin Amash says government should be left out of marriage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 14:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cruz, Rove Spar Over Bush Endorsement in AG's Race </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 14:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 13:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All you need to do is let /u/finally_woken know you will take over on Sunday.  We'll be counting on you then to get the check-in up from Sunday, July 4th through Saturday July 10th. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 13:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any candidate more of an arrogant, smarmy, fuck than this guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cruz: Opposition To Same-Sex Marriage Will Be 'Front And Center' In 2016 Campaign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 13:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 13:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha!  I sponsor a guy with 11 years from the time I had 4 years.  There are not hard and fast rules on this, it makes sense to ask someone who you respect and who you can see yourself listening to--who is steeped in the principles in recovery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walmart shoplifter punches employee in face over $6 item </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 13:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 13:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least until this afternoon.  I'm now so used to a flooded basement that I prepare for it in advance, hah!  Acceptance, baby! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 13:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you.  Time for you to do the morning check-in post.  Why not take next week? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 13:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, stranger on the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 12:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you read through the [Baby Steps post](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) to see if anything there makes sense as a place to start stopping.  It worked for me and plenty of others both on /r/stopdrinking and IRL.  Good luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Once Got Fleeced in Mexico, and Hes Still Very Angry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 12:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bush Is Definitely a Better Campaigner Than He Admits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 12:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Christie expert Matt Katz previews presidential announcement: The old Christie may be back. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 12:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Nikki Haley went from tea party star to a leader of the New South </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 12:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not drinking TODAY no matter what happens good or bad; another beautiful day in Cleveland.  I plan to make the most of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote this [post on this topic.  It's on the /r/alcoholism and in the SD sidebar.](https://www.reddit.com/r/alcoholism/comments/2v573a/the_where_why_and_what_should_i_expect_at_my/)  Please update us and let us know how your first meeting goes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you, /u/dirtymartini74.  Also look at the daily check-in as a routine.  I find it very helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What it's like to bike nude at Portland's World Naked Bike Ride </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Serial public masturbator arrested by Beaverton police </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you're going to give SOBER a shot.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/Timetostop1989 to r/stopdrinking.  On the sidebar the results of the annual survey of our population is available.  It's a massive amount of information about almost every aspect of our demographic.  Amazingly, by far and away most of us stopped drinking cold turkey, and most of us reported little or no discomfort.  

Now for how to go about it, why don't you look over the [Baby Steps post at this link?](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/)  It has some good ideas for the "next things" you might want to consider as part of the move to sobriety.  Good luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Booker pushes for more federal protections for same-sex couples </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/nocheesenoprob -- I'm one of the ancient mariners of SD, although Slip's got a few days on me. I'm a cyclist, bike commuter, and I live and work in Cleveland.  I'm also the guy who posts the [Baby Steps link for newcomers.](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/)  I hope to see you around.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 23:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to get rid of these notions of "I should feel...this or that."  We are all different, different DNA, different experiences within a spectrum.  What I do know that works is not drinking TODAY and dogged persistence.  Someone once told me: don't leave the room before the miracle occurs; and, miracles do occur in recovery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 23:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Each day that you stay stopped is one day closer to real sobriety.  You know this because we are telling you so and we have credibility.  We have credibility on these topics because we've been there.  

Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 23:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's what worked for me; don't drink TODAY no matter what and: 

1. Recognize that the first two weeks will probably suck;

2. No coffee, caffeine of any sort after midday;

3. Shut off all electronics an hour before bedtime; 

4. Except for soothing music. 

Remember, many of us went through this and our body and brains are healing.  Sleep will come.  And usually when it does we reach a point where our bodies and brains want to do nothing BUT sleep.  That's ok too.  Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 23:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, welcome back to life!  I'm moved by your courageous sharing of this post.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 23:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/ThePennyDropped -- good vent!  So at this [link is a post called the Baby Steps](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) which is designed to suggest some good "next actions" to stopping drinking and getting sober.  These are the things that worked for me.  Good luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 23:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will not drink TODAY in solidarity with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 23:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you, /u/SDstrawburry -- I'm pulling for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 23:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/flow59 to r/stopdrinking.  Perhaps in your past visits to the sub you came across the [Baby Steps post.](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/)  That post lays out what I did to stop drinking and to get sober.  The post attempts to suggest some good starter actions.  Good luck to you, I hope you get traction this time.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Audacity of Obama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 20:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 16:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posting and commenting serves others--and serves ourselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scalia's View Prevails in Gun-Crimes Case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 15:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 14:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my experience the way to never let the bad shit happen again is to start each day anew with the resolution not to drink TODAY, only and keep to that commitment.  It's amazing how quickly we can rebound and find the energy and momentum to turn our lives around especially if we actively work some sort of recovery program.  Remember it takes action not words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 14:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are doing a great job, super proud of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Alabama Chief Justice Roy Moore setting up a battle over gay marriage? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 14:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio marijuana plan's greedy backers are 'Irresponsible Ohio' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 14:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 14:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to believe that this ass-clown has a law license and a Harvard Law degree.  Apparently his oath to uphold the laws and constitution are secondary to his political pandering and ambition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 13:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/SuperMegaCoolPerson to r/stopdrinking--I do the [things I describe at the Baby Steps post.](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/)  I do these things everyday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 13:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so true.  My sponsor had 10 months of sobriety when I asked him to sponsor me.  I knew him previously from my profession.  He was a like a big brother to me and he has been for 30 years the same solid rock.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 13:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with this 100%. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank you, u/messedupmakeup for your Service Work last week! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 13:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recovery and sobriety works best, in my experience, when you do "service work"--and on /r/stopdrinking there are many opportunities to do service for the community as the morning Check-in volunteers demonstrate.  There are lots of other options, like commenting on newcomer posts, "attaboys and attagirls" for milemarker posts, and participation on the Chat, movie night, and so forth.  Find your niche, or invent it as others have done in the past and you may find that you are ahead of the game.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 13:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously, I'm late to this post, but I wanted to congratulate you on accomplishing the challenge and for this terrific post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antonin Scalia May Be Losing the Culture Wars, But Hes Winning the Zinger Wars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 13:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scalia Is More Isolated, Ferocious Than Ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 13:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At rural South Carolina shop, Confederate flags fly off shelves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 13:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Refuge for Racists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 13:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 11:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not drinking TODAY no matter what happens good or bad; sober in soggy Cleveland! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 03:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is the link to my post on the meaning of Drinking Dreams after an email exchange with dream researchers.](http://www.reddit.com/r/stopdrinking/comments/2dit1m/what_do_drinking_dreams_mean/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> West Shoreway lane closes and speed limit drops starting Monday | cleveland.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 03:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slate's Supreme Court Breakfast Table including Judge Richard Posner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 02:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 02:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it took me sustained time sober to figure out the whole new life-thing.   Thirty days, ninety days, even 180 days were not enough to show me what it could really be.  Even now my horizons and happiness are expanding.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americas Unexpected Civil Rights Champion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 01:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 01:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/redgalatea to /r/stopdrinking.  I'm sorry that you have struggled with relapse.  Relapse is a HUGE part of my story.  I also deal with, or dealt with manic-depression.  I got sober by doing the things I describe at the [Baby Steps.](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/)  As far as programs and faith--I hear you.  I'm super happy with my agnostic AA meeting home group which has enabled me to fully dive into recovery.

Good luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 22:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you read through the [Baby Steps post?](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/)  A lot of us on /r/stopdrinking  have used the ideas there to find a start to stopping. Good luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 22:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What?  Of course /r/law is the place for such distinctions.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 22:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By insistence in a dissent that it's my way or the highway; by inflammatory language, and through ad hominem attack on fellow justices.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 22:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you.  You could always catch an out of town AA meeting.  I always found that an interesting adventure and something that advanced my sobriety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 22:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me be clear then.  Scalia's snark heavy dissent does absolutely NOTHING for the respect of the law or our institutions, the constitution, the court, or comity.  Scalia, who invites readers of his dissent to "go ask the nearest  hippie"--appears to be tainted by his Opus Dei religious dogma and is apparently blind to his increasingly bizarre distortions.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 22:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you.  

But this brings to mind [the post called: The least popular advice](http://www.reddit.com/r/stopdrinking/comments/2szkp8/the_least_popular_advice_dry_people_dry_places/)--which is dry people and dry places in early sobriety.  At 23 days sober there is no good reason to be in a club where the temptation to drink is ever present as you acknowledge.  Please be careful, my friend.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 22:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an obnoxious post.  Prairie Home Companion is a significant media institution created by a formidable New Yorker writer that may elude your limited cultural understanding but which preserved, honored and satirized mid-twentieth century radio broadcasts; illustrated the history of the rural to urban transformation of America; and provided a weekly forum for all sorts of brilliant live music especially the obscure but worthy long before YouTube existed.  Your inability to grasp this fact does not render PHC or Keillor's artistic contributions invalid.  

P.S. Keillor is a Mid-westerner not a New Englander.  Keillor has more authenticity in his little finger than most of artists whose performance altars the Reddit hivemind worship at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why John Roberts Upheld Obamacare But Dissented On Gay Marriage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 21:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 21:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His reasoning is INFECTED with rightwing Christian dogma.  That's what I meant.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brothers accused in Cleveland 'dine and dash' spree charged (great photograph) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 20:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rock bottom is a metaphor not a place.  Everybody's rock bottom is different.  The only real question is when was I going to stop digging.  I didn't have to dig my way into professional disciplinary problems, federal prison, loss of reputation, material ruin--but I did.  

I did find a way out and a way back via [the things I describe at the Baby Steps post.](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) I hope you'll join us in the sober life boat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good honest post.  That's where I was in relapse.  But I got back by not assuming that since I had previously been sober for 15 years I could skip the basic starter steps.  It's like a lot of things I used to be able to do--play guitar, speak Spanish...I had to go to the very beginning.  [Baby Steps.](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scalia seems to be stumbling over it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 14:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait to see this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 14:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sustained time sober solved all my sleep disorders.  In the interim I would limit the caffeine to the early part of your day; not drink too much water 90 minutes before bedtime; and, I'd go with relaxing music in the half hour before sleep.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 14:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  When I first stopped drinking, I scoured this sub, looking for posts from people with lots of time, trying to figure out what their lives looked like. What had changed? What was better? This is going to be worth it, right?

You answered the question for yourself.  The answer was always there--inside yourself.  No one could answer for you for that very reason.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Angering Conservatives and Liberals, Chief Justice John Roberts Defends Steady Restraint </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 13:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 13:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NO.  No, binge eating is not as bad as binge drinking.  I never drove a car into the rear of another car in an automated carwash on potato chips.  I never went to prison on a pint of ice cream.

Of course, compulsive eating is a SERIOUS disorder that should not be ignored, but we shouldn't minimize our obligation to deal with first things first.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 13:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will not drink TODAY in solidarity with you.  You did a masterful job of describing the same thinking and feeling I had around my relapse after 15 continuous years of sobriety.  Two weeks of control and genius drinking which descended quickly into abysmal addict drinking that lasted for 7 years. It was a miracle that I got back at all.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analysis: A Distinction Between Law and Sacrament </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 13:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas Court's Ban of Death Penalty Lawyer Will Stand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 13:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nuclear 2.0? Jeb Bush is Open to Ending the Senate Filibuster to Repeal Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 13:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Eulogy, Obama Transforms into 'Reverend President' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 13:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Boies Reacts to SCOTUS Decision </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 13:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supremes Hit a High Note </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 13:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 11:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not drinking TODAY no matter what happens good or bad; in the immortal words of Antonin Scalia; go ask a hippie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 23:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except for the obnoxious title--the article really does capture this singular perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Media interest in the GOP field versus Public Interest in the GOP field </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 23:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Despite This Weeks Victories, Obama Has Struggled At The Supreme Court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 23:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 23:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know.  It's a hipster-ism.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We Can't Even With The Irony Of Clarence Thomas's Marriage Equality Dissent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 23:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 20:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly right.  The other part of this is--conservatives throw around "unconstitutional, tyranny, activist Judges"-argument forgetting that the SCOTUS and many of these judges are THEIR appointees: Kennedy, Roberts, and so forth.  In other words, their constitutional scholars would beg to disagree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 20:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife drinks.  But I have a completely developed support system of friends and activities that are SOBER.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 18:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you need any further reminder why the GOP can not be trusted with lifetime appointments to the federal courts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texans on Campaign Trail, in D.C. React to Gay Marriage Ruling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 18:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 18:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well-done /u/pickpickpick for making this connection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 18:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see how this feels this way for you IF the only thing you are doing is being alcohol abstinent. In my experience this is called being restless, irritable and discontent, aka, the RIDs.  The answer for me was getting ACTIVE in recovery--by activity in recovery I found new ways to reinforce my sobriety with new friends, new activities, and new daily rituals.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 18:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hang in there /u/xXThrowaway71Xx -- this is life on life's terms.  If I told you about the challenges of my first year of my current sobriety you might be shocked.  But I got invaluable face-to-face support every day at AA meetings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Words that are detached from reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photos Show Celebration Outside Supreme Court After Gay Marriage Made Legal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $700k state grant kicks off Stage 3 of Towpath Trail, designed to celebrate Cleveland industry (photos) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huckabee blasts SCOTUS "I will not acquiesce to an imperial court" vows to "resist and reject judicial tyranny" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antonin Scalia Dissent In Marriage Equality Case Is Even More Unhinged Than You'd Think </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an excellent point.  If he were a sitting local judge he would draw ethics complaints for this sort of nonsense.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Obamacare, John Roberts helps overthrow the Constitution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Court: Gay marriage ruling prompts Obama to tweet '#LoveWins' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antonin Scalia Dissent: I Give Up, Do Whatever You Want </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No union is more profound than marriage, for it embodies
the highest ideals of love, fidelity, devotion, sacrifice,
and family. In forming a marital union, two people become
something greater than once they were. As some of
the petitioners in these cases demonstrate, marriage
embodies a love that may endure even past death. It
would misunderstand these men and women to say they
disrespect the idea of marriage. Their plea is that they do
respect it, respect it so deeply that they seek to find its
fulfillment for themselves. Their hope is not to be condemned
to live in loneliness, excluded from one of civilizations
oldest institutions. They ask for equal dignity in the
eyes of the law. The Constitution grants them that right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/14pdf/14-556_3204.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Opinion.](http://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/14pdf/14-556_3204.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Laurence H. Tribe: Supreme Courts Obamacare decision is a victory for all of us - Opinion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adjunct law and undergrad prof makes less money than a pet sitter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 13:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember falling off a pink cloud, but I'm pretty sure it wasn't at 25 days into sobriety.  What I'm saying is this: early sobriety is a roller coaster of emotions with highs (probably not pink clouds) and lows.  Don't drink today, and I would bet that sometime, 90 days or so from now--a real pink cloud might really give you a ride of your life.  That's my experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 13:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to have courage when things don't go my way or aren't the way I believe they should be.  So in being courageous I win the inevitable wrestling match with MY ego.  I drop my narcissistic obsession with how I am perceived or how I perceive myself and I do what's right.  Sometimes what's right is merely to accept reality.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 13:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite a thought-experiment, that.  Lessee, Bill-O would convene morality panels.  Hannity would be in high-dundgeon.  It would be endless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 13:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was a newcomer to sobriety my sponsor (who gave me most of the ideas that became the [Baby Steps)](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) post laughed when I told him that there was no way I could do 90 AA meetings in 90 days.  He asked, How many days a week did you drink?  How many days a week were you in bars and liquor stores?  How many days a week were you hungover?  

AA meetings provided me with sober friends, sober activities, and a path to my authentic self.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sexual 'slave master' gets 30 years in federal prison for coercing teen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 13:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nina Totenberg on SCOTUS behind the scenes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 13:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Is The Supreme Court Doing Behind The Scenes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 13:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Roberts Courts Reality Check </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 13:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abbott's Office Promised Help to Major Donor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 13:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul Said to Take on the IRS, Again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 13:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 12:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not drinking TODAY no matter what happens good or bad; happy Friday in SD world! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 11:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just great. I am so happy for you.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watchdog lawyer says 6 supremes must be impeached </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 10:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 02:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, /u/hasvegetables I've been right where you are: filled with guilt and remorse and uncertain how to proceed.  Fortunately, my AA sponsor gave me some simple steps forward which along with lots of other info that I've picked up over time I've included in something I call the [Baby Steps which you can find at this link.](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/)  I learned to do the simple sober things on a daily basis and I can quite assure you that I don't carry a load of guilt or shame or remorse around with me anymore.  Good luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walter Dellinger: Solicitor General Donald Verrilli had a great term. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 02:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservatives Unleash Fury at One-Time Hero John Roberts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 00:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP congressman to SCOTUS: If you love Obamacare so much, you should use it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 00:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Delaware bans 'loser-pays' rules in corporate class actions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 22:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 22:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certainly at least 6 experts on constitutional law disagree with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Court went beyond its boundaries in Obamacare ruling, says Case Western law professor whose analysis led to challenge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 22:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 22:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing news, opinion, dissent, and political discussion in /r/politics and r/law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 21:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really capture the essence of life behind bars.  I came back from my 5 months at FCI, Morgantown in 2010 and I told my wife that I was so angry at myself for feeling absolute hatred for some people I knew and resided with in those months.  Sadly, there have been at least one occasion since with a guy in AA where I felt those same feelings, so I strongly relate to this post.  Now imagine that your confidentiality is breached--things you said in a meeting were shared "on the yard."  Wow.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 21:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a bullseye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 20:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/sbarks to r/stopdrinking.  Personally, I found it ultimately not relevant that I answer *a priori* the question: Am I an alcohlic?  What I needed instead was some sustained time sober and the clarity that brings.  So at this [link is a set of ideas called the Baby Steps](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) which is based on my own experiences stopping drinking and getting sober.  I hope something there will be helpful to you.  Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 20:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's AWESOME! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 20:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/ElSaborAsiatico to r/stopdrinking.  So at this [link is the post called the Baby Steps](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) which I created based on my own experiences as sort of "what's next?"-guide.  Good luck, I'm glad you have broken down the denial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 20:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> George W. Bush </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attorney shoplifted Kroger wine, lied </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 20:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 19:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This Rod Stewart video for Tonight's the Night.](https://youtu.be/IZr6AE-u2UM)  Cheesy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Petition to recall Pierce County Prosecutor Mark Lindquist filed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 19:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deputy had alcohol level about twice legal limit after crash, police report says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 19:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Victory for Obamacare: 2016 Candidates React </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 19:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huckabee: King v. Burwell 'Out-of-Control Act of Judicial Tyranny' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This deserves to  be tattoo'ed on my forehead backwards so I can see it every morning when I brush my teeth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dear, /u/catbustime -- I am so proud of you.  You are doing awesome.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you, /u/MisterFreelance -- I was able to do the longhaul by doing it one day at a time.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/MAURICE_DEL_TACO69 to r/stopdrinking.  I stopped drinking and I got sober by [doing the things I describe at the Baby Steps post which you can find at this link.](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/)  Good luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [On the meaning of Drinking Dreams.](http://www.reddit.com/r/stopdrinking/comments/2dit1m/what_do_drinking_dreams_mean/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations, db! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In a democracy, the power to make the law rests with
those chosen by the people. Our role is more confinedto
say what the law is. Marbury v. Madison, 1 Cranch 137,
177 (1803). That is easier in some cases than in others.
But in every case we must respect the role of the Legislature,
and take care not to undo what it has done. A fair
reading of legislation demands a fair understanding of the
legislative plan.

 Congress passed the Affordable Care Act to improve
health insurance markets, not to destroy them. If at all
possible, we must interpret the Act in a way that is consistent
with the former, and avoids the latter. Section 36B
can fairly be read consistent with what we see as Congresss
plan, and that is the reading we adopt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sarah Palin is the REO Speedwagon of Politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maybe Tom Bradys A-plus performance was not entirely credible after all </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 17:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Court: Texas Reinforced Segregated Housing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 17:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 17:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was the juxtaposition I was hoping for when I linked it this morning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here Are The Best (Worst) Lines From Antonin Scalia's Raging SCOTUScare Dissent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 17:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Driving stoned and nearly killing daughter, 4, not enough to strip dad of visits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 16:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 16:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The CJ's opinion is well written particularly as it relates to the whole history and how so much of O-care is based on Romney-care.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 16:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Opinon](http://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/14pdf/14-114_qol1.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Court Rejects Challenge to Obama Health Care Law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 16:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad Punctuation Puts Brakes on Parking Ordinance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 15:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poking the Republican Pyramid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 15:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $3 million spent by Louisiana campaigns on cars, meals, other perks in 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 15:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
