<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject800</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 03:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had problems with this too. It took some time for me to remember that oficially Theon killed Sansa brothers. That's what everybody was told. Only he and maybe some of his guards know that those burned kids were actually some peasant's sons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 02:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not implying it's easy. I know well how hard it is. I've been what people call an introvert all my life, and I still am. I have had problems with anxiety, depression and OCD. I've always been socially inept. But something I have learn is that you have to make an effort to change, you have to push your limits again and again, you have to expose yourself to whatever you fear.

I had social phobia. People still scares me. But this started to change the moment I decided I wanted to change, that I had to face my fears, I had to expose myself to people so it would have less and less power over me.

All I say is this "fucking normies" or "normies suck" or "being normal is wrong" attitude scares me, because is spreading and many people seems to really mean it, beyond memes and irony and REEEEs. I fear that the hikkikomori problem could spread to the western world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 01:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. My english is still not perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 21:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It amazes me that nobody ever mentioned to me that goats make human shouts and frogs scream. I didn't know until a couple years ago thanks to the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 21:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 19:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a certain way, as a non digital native, it scares me that people joke about being just a normal and socially adjusted person. I want to believe they are just joking, but sometimes, because of the things I read, I'm not so sure.

There is nothing great about being socially anxious or having social phobia. There is nothing great in wasting all your time alone at home playing videogames or surfing the web. If you don't feel comfortable at parties or crowds, ok, I understand it, I can relate to that. Don't force yourself to do something that makes you feel bad. But, for god sake, try to be social, get some friends, talk to people, go to some events in your town, get some laid. Either way, you are gonna have a very sad existence.

I want to believe I'm just taking too seriously a bunch of jokes in an imageboard, but sometimes I don't know. People seem so serious about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 16:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of the main concepts in Stephen King's "The Dark Tower". The world of the protagonist is inside a leaf of grass that is located in an empty plot (I don't know if this is the right word) in New York. The leaf is rotting, and so is that world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 15:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are crazy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 15:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There would always be hackers that would find the way to hack the voting system and try to change things accordingly to their will. Some of them would be freelance, some of them will be paid by certain parties or lobbies. Some of them would be more sutile and some of them will just unchain numeric chaos.

I've seen polls hacked many times, like in the Eurovision Show or that time Moot was voted most influential man in 2009 Time's poll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 15:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are super cute. I'd love to see you in a schoolgirl uniform. Just an idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 22:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyway, it's a good compilation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 22:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please, don't upvote this. It has 666 votes right now. It's perfect this way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 14:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, maybe I should edit the title and add "In a NEAR future". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 14:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I checked, and nah, it's just a [scorpion fly](http://geekologie.com/2012/09/11/scorpion-fly-1.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the future, when all human knowledge will be easily accesible on the Internet, we will only talk to other humans to get things that we can't get from computers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 14:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 14:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a proof: I remember perfectly my past lives. I was a peasant in every one of them. That was boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 14:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are probably gonna give me weird looks, but I've played worse things in parties, usually just to annoy people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Playstation recently celebrated its 20th anniversary. I'm 15 years older than it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 14:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 14:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are hacking your penis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 13:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually it has more to do with my dad's kind of sense of humor. He likes those gags in the movies when somebody kicks a dog or something like that. He loved "A fish called Wanda". They kill a lot of little dogs in that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 09:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad laughed his ass off when we went to the cinema to watch this movie, back in the days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 09:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They could communicate if they have an interpreter. They could have interesting things to talk about, like their problems being disabled or accesing to information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 09:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where in America? Like, in Colombia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 09:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I will help you. I'm on my way. I'm in Spain, though. Where are you? I'm gonna have to take a plane, maybe. That will take some hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 08:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They might end flirting because they like each other and they experienced a funny situation together, and he knows she finds him cute. That has nothing to do with a prank, unless it is proven in the movie, which I didn't watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 08:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 23:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That youtube channel is bananas! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 15:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think next time I'm the DJ in a party I'm going to play this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 15:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You obviously haven't seen enough rule 34 material. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 14:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Learn a poetry from heart, like [The Pirate Song](http://www.grijalvo.com/Citas/b_Espronceda_Cancion_pirata.html) or [El Romance del Prisionero](http://www.poesi.as/indx0001.htm) (this one is shorter). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 14:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great. She is one of my favorite voices in the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 14:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The interpreter and the deaf guy started laughing because they found the situation ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 22:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prank? He's just a deaf guy trying to use a sex hot line through an interpretation service. I admit it's something unusual, but when you are an interpreter you have to face awkward situations all the time, and you compromise to do your job, respecting your user rights and desires.

Thanks for the subtitles. Unfortunately my deaf friends are spanish and they wont understand english. I don't know what I was thinking in the first place, hehe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 19:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will use this video in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 18:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The world never ceases to amaze me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 18:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to lick it. I bet it sticks to your tongue and tastes sour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 18:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recommend this album, by the way. I recently discovered Coil and they are certainly interesting and innovative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 18:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call me crazy, but I think this video is about feet fetish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 18:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All this guy's videos are titled the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 15:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems we don't have to be worried about this girl. Apparently her and this guy are good friends. He was kicked out his parents house and she helped him.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ScU90xw9LUg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 15:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, he's a musician. He can't be a bad guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 15:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank mr skeltal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 14:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a former sign language interpreter I must say this girl is making many severe professional mistakes. Things you can be sanctioned for, like lying or removing information. The deaf user could even report her and she would be in trouble. She should translate absolutely everything and don't lie at all. But I guess realism will ruin the fun of the scene.

I wish this was fully subtitled, not only the signs. I could share it with my deaf friends and they would find it hilarious, I'm sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 21:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's that girl? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 17:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will them mine how life was like in the 80's and 90's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 17:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet the DG guys will love this video.

Also, I laughed at this moment: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l9NqFVC0Lwc t=3m23s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 14:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sharing. I love to read about other people experiences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 17:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tool used it too in the hidden track "faaip de oidad"

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=83R54yAB5Cw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 00:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What power do you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 18:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was the sound of an egg being fried, layered 309 times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 23:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are the most perfect tits I'v ever seen. Saved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 23:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how in Reddit you usually can make a question and people really give you an answer, instead of getting the "learn to use google" answer that you get in most of the other sites, like 4chan and many, many forums.

You are cool people, redditors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 22:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not flawless. He forgot to post the dubs-man meme picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 22:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was trying to be sarcastic, but it seems that I failed.

It was a way of saying that u/Bluecool was being a jerk, not taking the effort of sharing the video.

I searched "Death grips sxsw", "mc ride attacks camera" and "stefan burnett attacks camera" and found nothing. It's not so easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 22:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the favorite facts I can think of right now is that they decided to leak No Love Deep Web inspired by Magic The Gathering tactics. Zach's brother is a Magic player and told him about control decks, which basically take control over the opponent's cards and turn them against him. So they got into a simbolic stage of power, the Chateau Marmont hotel, frequented by celebrities, and leaked the album from inside. It's all post-modern magic to me. Epic wanted to control them, so they took control.

You can find better explanations of this story here:

http://pitchfork.com/features/interviews/9004-death-gripz/
http://blogs.artinfo.com/spotlight/2012/11/20/death-grips-are-not-pranksters-just-fans-of-magic-the-gathering/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 22:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The trout mask </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 22:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, just search "mc Ride attacking camera" and it will get you straight to the exact minute and second of the video where that happens.

Jeez, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 21:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is quite hypnotizing too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 21:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, if people is upvoting this there must be a reason, but I must also listen the opinion of those who frequent this board and were here before than me. Of course, if they don't see it as a proper material, they can just downvote the thing, but I'm interested in everybody's opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 19:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for all the explanations, guys. I posted this just because I thought it was a funny comment, just the kind of stuff I usually see posted on this sub. But I see some people have higher standards than that. I'll have that in mind next time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 18:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP here. I'd like to know what I did wrong. I thought this fitted well with this subreddit purpose. But since some of you seem upset, I'd like you to explain to me what's wrong with this post.

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 17:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems a lot of people is coming to the same thought, then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 17:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something similar happens to me with porn. After some hours watching porn, I go to bed and when I close my eyes I see bodies, tits, nude girls everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 17:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not very original. I've seen this one before in Twitter and 4chan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 17:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surf the internet, read books, watch films and chat with friends. Sometimes dance helps too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 17:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure OP will deliver </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 13:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was boring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Somebody posts a gif of an incredibly sharp knife on r/whoadude). It's creator shows up in the thread and receives the strangest questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 13:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 22:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just see a hot thing burning other things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
