<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6921</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I called and spoke with toyota. A Toyota official recall never expires, limited repair campaigns do. The frame rust issues were a recall, and thus should never expire. As I understand it. I had my frame undercoated just this past year, well past April 2012. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 14:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you for sure, love that low end. I'd love to see that little turbodiesel they've got in Australia make its way into the U.S. But yeah the frame can be a problem. Took mine to the local stealership this year and they did a full inspection. Ended up getting a new undercoat on toyota's dime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 04:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girl's a 4x4, but I'm glad to see there's some other 1st gen enthusiasts around, too good a truck not to have some fans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 03:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I can't speak to that, but they certainly are a lot bigger. I always liked my truck cuz it seemed a little smaller than the big three, but now I've got tacos looking down in my windows...manhood takes a shot... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 23:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2000 Tundra SR5, little spacer lift the old man put on when he bought it a 7k miles, I just rolled over 190k this week. Daily driver, but works well as a hunting and farm truck too, hauls the shit outta hedge posts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big Toyotas need love too </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 23:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 07:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah reach out to the national baja SAE folks and maybe some of the advisors/instructors in mechanical and civil engineering if your school offers those specialties. Or even contact some other schools and ask how they got theirs started. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
