<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1490</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 04:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gargoyle bike is tight
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 18:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been caught breaking the law (minor stuff like weed in public) three times now and every single time the cops let me off with a friendly warning. Always polite, never intimidating. I love Alberta cops.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 04:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/marijuanaenthusiasts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How far back can the concept of the Simulation Hypothesis be traced? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 23:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently read how as far back as Ancient Greece, philosophers have had theories about how reality as we know it could be an illusion, sort of like in The Matrix. How far back does this concept go and what caused humans to initially become skeptical of the world around us without any proof?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 11:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cable management needs work
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 09:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> goddamn that's exactly what I thought it was gonna be lol
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 08:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yooo I want one
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 06:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed, for me cyberpunk is more of an aesthetic than it is about the actual advances in technology! Until we get into cyborg territory that is. That shit is quintessentially cyberpunk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 22:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A short by Dylan J Nathan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EXTROPY - Speedhack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 22:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hypnotic new music video for Cosmin TRG's Uzura </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 21:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 19:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All great :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 08:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking love my boosts! Enjoy mate
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 07:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Havel's Helmet
Silver Knight Armour
Shadow Gauntlets
Shadow Leggings

Black Knight Sword
Black Iron Great Shield  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Dark Souls] Silver Sentry (apologies for tv pic) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 07:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 07:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> na dude particle board is super weak it was like an IKEA desk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 07:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah that sounds little too exploit-y, I just want some extra time to heal goddamn
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 07:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> was it no bonfire?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 07:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> never the actual controller, but I had a particle board desk at one time until I "accidentally" put a few holes in it with the butt end of an xbox controller.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 07:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah I fail at parrying and I'm stuck on him right now in NG+++

What's this pillar trick? :P
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 07:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a heavy tank build I think Four Kings is probably the easiest boss in the game for me. If you get right up on them their hits only takes out like 1/15th of my health every time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 07:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm stuck on Gwyn right now on NG+++ and for some reason I just can't fucking get parrying down so it comes down to luck and rolling away in time to spam estus after staggering him..
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 06:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finally picked up Dark Souls a few months ago and fell in love with it after hearing my coworkers rave about it forever. I'm now on NG+++ and about 150~ hours in. Haven't even gotten to trying multiplayer yet (on Xbox and don't feel like paying for live)

By contrast I picked up Dark Souls 2 SoFS after finishing my first playthrough of 1, played about 10 hours into it and quit. None of the things I loved about Dark Souls made it over to the new iteration. Working at a game store, I have met people who really love DS2 just as much if not more than the original, but I find the overwhelming majority of people say Dark Souls was definitely a more impactful game.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 06:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Age of Empires and the school library! I was a nerdy little child. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 06:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> name it Zweihander
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 05:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol k liam neeson settle down
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 03:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what a time to be alive
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 01:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GT was terrible anyway.
Yaay new cannon DBZ!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 01:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what does it mean?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 21:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully she never ever hears about the club Berghain
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 04:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was gonna be a Matt Damon/ Capra Demon mashup. Awesome work though!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 22:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sibyl is located in 101
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 02:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally getting to Bigtits room and acquiring the Lordvessel is by far one of best feelings in the game.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 02:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's waay harder to kill Smough first! Every time after my first play-through  i've attempted to kill him first because I want Ornsteins set (NG+++ now) but every time I end up giving up and killing Ornstein first because I just want the damn lord vessel already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Essential Hip-hop news/release sites? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 02:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright so I'm mostly a house and techno guy but come on who the fuck doesn't like hip hop?

Anyways i've been wanting to round out my rap collection as of late and my question to this sub is what are some of the must-knows of the digital rap world? What are the best places to keep up on both news and releases? 

I love to digitally crate dig and find new music; I know iTunes is usually the go-to place to actually buy the music but sometimes I prefer the more curated sites, ones usually run by the real heads in the scene. Any advice would be much appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 15:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omg I love this sub
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 04:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What he said ^
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 03:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tough choice, both nice boards. I also kind of want a wasd with a little less loud switches haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 12:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ me on an alt
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 11:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol ya
forgot to crop it out
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 10:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I don't think so, Gold serpent ring would help though.
Sometimes I play a game where I take a hit every time I die... almost passed out trying to beat S O
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plain and simple </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 04:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 03:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol I still use BKS+5 as my daily driver 3 playthroughs in. I'm a str build tho so it scales well, out-damages all of the boss soul weapons save for Artorias great sword I think, which i'll never have enough int to use anyway :(

Ps love the username haha, Dank souls is the shit
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 21:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Neither campus authorities nor police believed her. Combined with the fact that she is broadcasting her rape to the media, granting interviews to anyone who will ask (heres a video interview with Time), and using it to get an easy A grade on her thesis, its safe to conclude that we are looking at a false rape accusation by a mentally unstable woman. There is absolutely no doubt in my mind that this girl was not truly raped, and instead was sour about being pumped and dumped after giving up her anus to a guy she had the tingles for." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 21:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LPT: If you're going to comment on a story at least read it first.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 21:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope that mattress causes her to lose her balance on a very tall staircase...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 21:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol yeah I killed them in my first play through but now I always just nope past em to the shortcut
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 13:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hell even the regular hollows are dangerous with their berserk move. And don't get me started on the skeleton hounds in NG++... fucking 1 shots even with tank build and fully upgraded giant armour  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 13:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 21:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I agree he's probably one of the easiest high level boss fights, next to pinwheel..
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 08:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GoDaBmi06S4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 08:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gameplay wise, Four Kings because you just have to go all in and it's a rush falling into the abyss for the first time not knowing wtf is going on. But Nito is definitely my fave. So badass plus finally getting to warp out of the Tomb of the Giants after finishing him is a great feeling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 07:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> media =/= real life
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 07:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL there are elitist South Park fans. Insecure people can be pretentious about anything I guess..
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 07:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you take yourself a bit too seriously m8
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 07:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Half the episodes are based on current events and pop culture. The quality is and forever has been hit or miss. Some episodes are brilliant others are just filler. I'm just saying as long as they keep poking fun at current events the show can never become irrelevant. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 06:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel pretty much the opposite way.. like it can never really get stale unless society stops doing dumb shit that can be made fun of. Which will be never.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 06:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if I told you it doesn't matter in the slightest. Like literally not at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 06:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice, for a second I thought I was in /r/synthesizers
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 12:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally needed this at 4 am....not. haha

but seriously that's some fucked up food for thought. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 21:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I could tell the robot was actually designed to intentionally purchase illicit items from the deep web as part of an art project/experiment. All the items, including ecstasy, a fake passport and a ballcap with a hidden pov camera were confiscated at the end of the project, in accordance with the plan.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 10:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out some fashion designs by companies like Aitor Throup, Musee Noir, Rick Owens. They're expensive as fuck but should serve as good inspiration. 

These are a couple of my faves (some are jackets but they're still hooded)
Aitor Throup
http://imgur.com/IjhNouU
http://imgur.com/zPgeWos
http://imgur.com/tFdAgrr
Musee Noir
http://imgur.com/N0Vhceq
http://imgur.com/G6jobC4
Rick Owens
http://imgur.com/MvbOBj5

Edit* Forgot Acronym... they're pretty dope too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 04:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah so that it can be used as a dual display with no overlap. Some of the newer monitors have it
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 03:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never noticed it before but :9 looks like a weird smiley with it's tongue out. Also nice monitor! Is it one of those ones you can partition?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
