<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2450</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Money laundering investigation stymied by China, Italy says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jurors on Friday convicted a female Los Angeles police officer of felony assault for repeatedly kicking a handcuffed woman who later died </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A top California oil and gas regulator has resigned amid questions about oilfield contamination of the state's water supplies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A top California oil and gas regulator has resigned amid questions about oilfield contamination of the state's water supplies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Consumer borrowing in the U.S. rose more than forecast in April, boosted by the biggest increase in revolving credit in a year. The $20.5 billion advance in total borrowing followed a $21.3 billion gain in the prior month that was larger than previously estimated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 21:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deutsche Bank is looking into possible money laundering transactions by some of its clients in Russia which could exceed $6 billion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 21:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former BP executive David Rainey found not guilty of making false statement in oil spill probe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 21:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Nevada ranch defied U.S. drought closure orders in grazing cattle on federally managed land, environmentalists said on Wednesday, comparing it to action by another Nevada rancher that led to an armed standoff last year with federal agents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 09:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Nevada ranch defied U.S. drought closure orders in grazing cattle on federally managed land, environmentalists said, comparing it to action by another Nevada rancher that led to an armed standoff last year with federal agents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 09:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The head of the state Republican Party said Thursday that GOP U.S. Rep. Frank Guinta "has clearly been untruthful" about where he got $355,000 to spend on his 2010 campaign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 05:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two weeks before an oil pipeline rupture spilled over 100,000 gallons of crude on the Santa Barbara coast, a test was run that would reveal serious wear in that stretch of corroded pipe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 04:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two weeks before an oil pipeline rupture spilled over 100,000 gallons of crude on the Santa Barbara coast, a test was run that would reveal serious wear in that stretch of corroded pipe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 04:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> City With Second-Highest Veteran Population Effectively Ends Veteran Homelessness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 01:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The trial of five white Cleveland police supervisors charged with failing to control a car chase that ended in a 137-shot barrage of police gunfire that killed two unarmed black people could be moved from a county court in the city to a municipal court in an almost-all-black suburb </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 01:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a victory for Native American tribes, an appeals court ruled Thursday that states cannot use negotiations for a Native American casino to challenge the federal government's decisions to recognize a tribe and set aside land for it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 01:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clarence "Bevo" Francis, who had 113 points for Rio Grande College in a 1954 game and was one of college basketball's great scorers, has died. He was 82 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 23:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clarence "Bevo" Francis, who had 113 points for Rio Grande College in a 1954 game and was one of college basketball's great scorers, has died. He was 82 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 23:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ibiza conservationists claim victory as Scottish firm abandons oil search: Locals feared that Cairn Energy project would damage environment and the tourist-dependent economy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 23:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No Pause in Global Warming: A new study suggests that global warming continues to steadily increase </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 23:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pseudoscience and conspiracy theory are not victimless crimes against science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 22:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pseudoscience and conspiracy theory are not victimless crimes against science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 22:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coroner: Georgia jail death ruled homicide by blunt force </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 22:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fourteen arrests at California protest in support of childcare reforms: Activists taken into custody for blocking road and released after peaceful demonstration supporting improvements for daycare workers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 20:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gerrymandering the House, 1972-2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 20:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missouri Gov. Nixon vetoes right-to-work legislation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 20:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missouri Gov. Nixon vetoes right-to-work legislation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 20:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Europe's human rights court will decide on Friday if a man in a vegetative state can be taken off life support in a case that ignited a fierce euthanasia debate in France </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 20:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dozens were injured in eastern Turkey on Thursday as police fired tear gas and water cannon to disperse nationalists protesting against an election rally by the pro-Kurdish People's Democratic Party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 20:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lindsey Graham Compares Hillary Clinton To North Korea's Kim Jong Un </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 20:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Solar cell sets world record with a stabilized efficiency of 13.6% </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 19:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Republicans have voted to keep restrictions on Americans seeking to travel to Cuba. That's a setback to Obama administration efforts to ease the five-decade Cold War standoff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 19:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Republicans have voted to keep restrictions on Americans seeking to travel to Cuba. That's a setback to Obama administration efforts to ease the five-decade Cold War standoff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 19:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senator would limit lobbyist money that fueled liberal allies: Michael Bennet's bill could hit Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee hard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 18:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fossils found in a quarry in Gloucestershire have been identified by a student and her supervisors at the University of Bristol as a new small species of reptile with self-sharpening blade-like teeth that lived 205 million years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 18:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New species of horned dinosaur with 'bizarre' features revealed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 18:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Humanities and Science Share the Virtues of Empiricism and Skepticism: Reason, empiricism and skepticism are not virtues of science alone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 17:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The pot effect on Denver's housing market </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 17:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The pot effect on Denver's housing market </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 17:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> News site Gawker Media employees say they have voted to join the Writers Guild of America, making it the first digital media outlet to organize </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 17:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> News site Gawker Media employees say they have voted to join the Writers Guild of America, making it the first digital media outlet to organize </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 17:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> News site Gawker Media employees say they have voted to join the Writers Guild of America, making it the first digital media outlet to organize </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 17:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As U.S. EPA finalizes its unprecedented rule aimed at reducing the national power sectors carbon footprint, the agency is also focusing its aim on another greenhouse gas emitter: airlines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 17:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peak Sand, Climate Change, And The Coastal Property Bubble </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 16:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blast at Ghana petrol station kills 90 seeking shelter from storm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 16:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hyper-Precise Atomic Clocks Face Off to Redefine Time: A new generation of timekeepers can only be tested against each other </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 16:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The world's major food commodity prices fell again in May to the lowest level in nearly six years amid a favorable outlook for this year's harvests, the Food and Agriculture Organization said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 16:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. worker productivity declined more sharply in the first three months of the year than previously thought while labor costs rose more quickly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 16:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two British lawmakers have gone to court to argue that intelligence agencies' powers to intercept phone and Internet communications violates the right to privacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 15:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seven new species of tiny frog have been discovered on seven different mountains in south-eastern Brazil. The cool "cloud forests" of this region have a unique climate, separated by warmer valleys that isolate the peaks like islands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 15:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seven new species of tiny frog have been discovered on seven different mountains in south-eastern Brazil. The cool "cloud forests" of this region have a unique climate, separated by warmer valleys that isolate the peaks like islands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 15:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thursday, Vice President Joe Biden will bury his son, Beau, who died after a battle with brain cancer. That didnt stop Senator Ted Cruz, who is running for president, from using Biden as a punch line for a bad joke on Wednesday night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 04:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thursday, Vice President Joe Biden will bury his son, Beau, who died after a battle with brain cancer. That didnt stop Senator Ted Cruz, who is running for president, from using Biden as a punch line for a bad joke on Wednesday night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 04:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 100-Year-Old Turtle, the Last of Her Kind, Could Soon Be a Mom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 03:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A German shipping company on probation for dumping oily water off California in 2013 was sentenced Wednesday to pay $750,000 for a repeat offense in Alaska </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 03:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A commercial fisherman sued the owner of the oil pipeline that spilled thousands of gallons of crude on the Santa Barbara coast, alleging the environmental disaster would cause decades of harm to the shore and hurt many businesses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 01:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A commercial fisherman sued the owner of the oil pipeline that spilled thousands of gallons of crude on the Santa Barbara coast, alleging the environmental disaster would cause decades of harm to the shore and hurt many businesses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 01:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The federal government would be unable to block state laws permitting the use of medical marijuana under legislation approved Wednesday by the GOP-controlled House. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 01:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Honduras' president says he has learned that his election campaign received financing from businesspeople linked to a Social Security embezzlement and graft scandal that has sparked large protests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 01:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A bird flu vaccine doesn't work well enough to approve it for emergency use against the current outbreak that's shaken the Midwest poultry industry, the U.S. Department of Agriculture said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 00:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The head of al Qaeda's Syria wing Nusra Front said he saw no solution soon to a conflict with the rival Islamic State group in Syria that has killed hundreds of fighters, according to an interview with Al Jazeera aired on Wednesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 00:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Afghanistan is increasingly relying on a "cheap but dangerous" national militia of some 30,000 fighters, some of whom have committed serious abuses in the communities they are supposed to protect, an international research group said Thursday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 00:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 2-mile section of the Arkansas River near Little Rock remained closed Wednesday following the rupture of a pipeline that released enough natural gas to fuel about 65 homes for a year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 21:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than 50 labs in 17 US states and three foreign countries have been mailed samples of live anthrax </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 21:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A pair of anti-Hillary Clinton political committees are effectively telling the Federal Election Commission to take a long walk off a tall mountain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 21:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A pair of anti-Hillary Clinton political committees are effectively telling the Federal Election Commission to take a long walk off a tall mountain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 21:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 333-million year old broken bone is causing fossil scientists to reconsider the evolution of land-dwelling vertebrate animals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 21:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 333-million year old broken bone is causing fossil scientists to reconsider the evolution of land-dwelling vertebrate animals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 21:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists produce strongest evidence yet of schizophrenia's causes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 21:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BPA Still Widely Used in Canned Goods: Survey of canned-good brands finds hormone-mimicking compound still widely used </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 20:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Masked attackers ransacked the offices of one of the last rights groups active in Russia's Chechnya region on Wednesday as crowds of pro-government demonstrators looked on </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 20:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than 200 primary schools shut down Wednesday as South Korea struggled to contain an outbreak of the MERS virus that has infected 30, killed two and triggered widespread fear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 09:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two activists climbed atop an excavator on Monday, one locking himself to the equipment, in a protest over the building of an animal-testing facility at the University of Washington, halting construction at the site </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 06:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI behind mysterious surveillance aircraft over US cities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 05:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The chairman of the board of the New York Racing Association is taking a leave of absence following allegations that his company provided a "no-show" job to the son of former state Senate leader Dean Skelos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 04:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. state and local governments will have to report billions of dollars in health-care liabilities on their balance sheets under an accounting change aimed at improving disclosure of retiree benefits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 04:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leader in Afghan north dismisses Kabul government as a 'show' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 04:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Hampshire governor blocks baby pictures on beer bottles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 03:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gourmet chimps show how we came to cook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 03:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gourmet chimps show how we came to cook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 03:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Authorities struggled on Tuesday to restore power to a major Colombian port city more than 48 hours after a rebel attack on a transmission line plunged Buenaventura's 400,000 into the dark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 03:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The commonplace practice of billing rape victims in Louisiana for medical exams should come to an end after state lawmakers Tuesday signed off on proposed law changes that the federal government has required for a decade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 02:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A California appeals court on Tuesday upheld former Gov. Arnold Schwarzenegger's decision to dramatically reduce the manslaughter sentence of a political ally's son, saying his conduct may be considered wrong but it didn't violate any laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 02:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 20:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What political views do you think stops me from supporting this action by the President? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 17:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under that logic undocumented workers do not have the any rights so they should be deported immediately but they have the right to challenge deportations. The prisoners at Guantanamo Bay should have no access to the court system but they do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 23:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By the way Happy Cake Day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 23:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burundi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 02:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dolphins are beaching themselves in record numbers in the Gulf of Mexico. They are still cleaning up the oil in Prince William Sound. Those are just two instances of the the things that "never happen."

EDIT: Grammar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 01:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The headline says "make increasing use of...drones." No one is saying drones aren't being used now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 23:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even with non-NHL players the South Koreans will be hard pressed to be competitive let alone win a game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 19:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So a country can avoid paying a debt by declaring its legal opponent "the enemy." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 18:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Rosenberg case has been debated for more than sixty years. The Rosenberg's claimed there innocence till their execution. Any new evidence to settle this case is important </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 17:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all love Jeni's but this is bad news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 04:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you are stealing the fish from the dolphins. You have many choices in meals, dolphins are limited to the fish in the sea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I spend hours doing that over at /r/worldnews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I looked back 24 hours not two days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 01:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The citation for the study can be found at [sciencedirect.](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0012821X15001879) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 03:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Excuse me, is this a piece of your brain" - Fawlty Towers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 23:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What can Europe learn? How to deny human rights? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 02:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Identifying personal microbiomes using metagenomic codes](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2015/05/08/1423854112.abstract) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 11:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are the first three sentences of the story. The headline was more inflammatory with less information, "A Game of Chicken: USDA repeatedly blinked when facing salmonella outbreaks involving Foster Farms" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 03:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the women was attractive would it make her horrendous crime any more palatable? The idea you would comment about the physical appearance of the woman and not the crime is odd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 01:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there some problem with governments demanding that big banks follow the law? These laws were written by the banks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 00:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a story from [Daily Sabah and the AP.](http://www.dailysabah.com/politics/2015/05/06/germany-bans-terrorist-dhkpc-affiliated-newspaper) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 22:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Life is always stranger than fiction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 19:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is not they don't care about their constituents needs but rather winning elections is about money. A legislator can overcome bad press with lots of money but without money there is no media. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 16:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are aggregate contributions not individual donations made directly to a candidate for federal office.

EDIT: If there were no limits on speech you could make unlimited contributions to individual candidates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 15:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is not what the Supreme Court said in [Buckley v. Valeo](http://caselaw.lp.findlaw.com/scripts/getcase.pl?court=US vol=424 invol=1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 21:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a bail of $50 -100,000 would have ensured his appearance. The crime is vandalism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 21:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So attacking a police car is a more serious crime than murder? These two offenses are not even in the same ballpark. If Bullock was on the street would he likely commit the same act? His bail had little to do with the crime he committed. His bail is punitive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 16:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is it that the US government has little trouble trying foreign banks for criminal behavior? Yet that same court system cannot convict a single US banker for the their financial dealings that caused the Great Recession. Just asking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 00:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does someone fully recover from severe depression? A person may have made adjustments in their life to deal with it but it is extremely hard to "fully recover." At the very least he should have been on a medical watch list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 03:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess the Sun thinks those who rioted after the 1993 Rodney King beating were clairvoyant because they were playing out scenes from a 2013 movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 01:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 66 civilians killed in air strikes seems unrealistically low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 03:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many spills does it take to get criminal charges filed? Fines of $5 million have never had any effect on changing the corporate culture of pollution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 00:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This attack is part of the plan to establish a country which would be a "greater Albania" which would include large portions of the former Yugoslavia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 00:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is good news and bad news. The news will be taken by whaling nations as a green light to expand the slaughter of whales. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 02:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nestle may not be the total problem but their unlicensed water business certainly is not helping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 03:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not even a slap on the wrist. These Freddie Mac executives cost the government billions and they will pay less than one years salary for their criminal action. When will there be true justice for the bank criminals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 23:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the old saying goes, follow the money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 22:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Kasich is considered moderate the GOP is now way to the right of Mayberry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 20:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't give the airlines industry any thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 20:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's right. There has never been a nuclear plant disaster./s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 16:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't think working in the food industry clouds your judgment. 

The article starts out talking about Lupin but then goes on to talk about the way food companies self regulate on the safety of additives.
Is this true? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 15:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try the [Gallup site.](http://www.gallup.com/poll/182348/uninsured-rate-dips-first-quarter.aspx) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 04:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would not have happen under Gaddafi. Gaddafi ruled with an  iron fist which stifled the opposition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 03:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now the plan is to pray that it all goes away. Fat chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 21:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first step in building a database is collecting all the data and then getting the specifics on each incident. The only way to find out how many of the deaths are justified or not is know how many deaths there are in total. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 05:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't matter what you call it, if a quid pro quo is involved it is a crime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 01:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The psychedelic state induced by ayahuasca modulates the activity and connectivity of the default mode network.
PLoS ONE
PLoS One 2015 18;10(2):e0118143. Epub 2015 Feb 18.
Fernanda Palhano-Fontes, Katia C Andrade, Luis F Tofoli, Antonio C Santos, Jose Alexandre S Crippa, Jaime E C Hallak, Sidarta Ribeiro, Draulio B de Araujo

The experiences induced by psychedelics share a wide variety of subjective features, related to the complex changes in perception and cognition induced by this class of drugs. A remarkable increase in introspection is at the core of these altered states of consciousness. Self-oriented mental activity has been consistently linked to the Default Mode Network (DMN), a set of brain regions more active during rest than during the execution of a goal-directed task. Here we used fMRI technique to inspect the DMN during the psychedelic state induced by Ayahuasca in ten experienced subjects. Ayahuasca is a potion traditionally used by Amazonian Amerindians composed by a mixture of compounds that increase monoaminergic transmission. In particular, we examined whether Ayahuasca changes the activity and connectivity of the DMN and the connection between the DMN and the task-positive network (TPN). Ayahuasca caused a significant decrease in activity through most parts of the DMN, including its most consistent hubs: the Posterior Cingulate Cortex (PCC)/Precuneus and the medial Prefrontal Cortex (mPFC). Functional connectivity within the PCC/Precuneus decreased after Ayahuasca intake. No significant change was observed in the DMN-TPN orthogonality. Altogether, our results support the notion that the altered state of consciousness induced by Ayahuasca, like those induced by psilocybin (another serotonergic psychedelic), meditation and sleep, is linked to the modulation of the activity and the connectivity of the DMN.
Affiliation
Brain Institute, Federal University of Rio Grande do Norte (UFRN), Natal-RN, Brazil.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 01:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [My article](http://www.reddit.com/r/science/comments/31xcqz/a_psychedelic_drink_used_for_centuries_in_healing/) is authored by Arran Frood and Nature magazine. Nature is a peer reviewed publication. Please restore my post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 22:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what we can expect from President Scott Walker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 17:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The party was held at Christmas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 16:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many SAE chapters have to be accused of racism before it becomes apparent that the entire fraternity has a culture of institutional racism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 22:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is very clear that the Arab Spring has turned into the Arab Winter in Cairo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 01:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a subscription to Haaretz and I can see this story. You can try going into the story [from this site.](https://www.google.com/search?q=cultic ie=utf-8 oe=utf-8#q=cultic tbm=nws)

Sorry for any inconvenience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 21:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saudi Arabia has a gold star and they are not a democracy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 17:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was impressed to see the number of political activists involved in May Day that contributed to this article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 03:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those of us in Ohio, Kasich is not a secret weapon but a dud missile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 16:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the most entertaining explanation of finagle's origin and meaning you'll ever read from the funniest lexicographer in the business.](http://www.word-detective.com/2008/02/finagle/) 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 09:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This story is on the front page of /r/worldnews at 4:30 AM.

Edit: And /r/science </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 03:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The definition of contradiction is libertarian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 03:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How dare you compare these two loonies with beloved kitties? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 22:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if a $900,00 fine can even be described as a slap on the wrist. The fine structure for environmental crimes seems to be out of whack with reality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 03:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The discovery of this hideout shows one of the ways the Nazis were able to hide in South America after WWII. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 03:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think if thy found the part of the gene that correlates with certain traits, scientists could probably replace that area with gene parts you wanted.

However this seems to be the path for someone to try to build the "super-race." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 21:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least in his mind and Bibi's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 16:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under federal law this is the definition of a slap on the wrist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 03:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please see this [US data for poultry population by state.](http://www.uspoultry.org/economic_data/)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 02:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The court basically split the difference between the US government's and BP's estimates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 00:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First they came for the Socialists, and I did not speak out
Because I was not a Socialist.

Then they came for the Trade Unionists, and I did not speak out
Because I was not a Trade Unionist.

Then they came for the Jews, and I did not speak out
Because I was not a Jew.

Then they came for meand there was no one left to speak for me.

Martin Niemller </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 20:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The question is: Is Al-Sisi Mubarak light or just Mubarak? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 00:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regulators decided on that amount because that was all the money UBS had in its petty cash fund. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 20:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for the snide comment. However, the sanity of Harper Lee should not be determined by a court system that doesn't believe rulings by the Supreme Court have any meaning for local court's in Alabama. 

Under that logic the state's ruling in this case will trump any other ruling that may come from a reasoned court. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 20:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if I'd allow Alabama to decide anything more complicated than: Should we go to dinner at Cracker Barrel or Checkers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 02:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look inside the mind of a US liberal icon in the mid-60s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 02:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the GOP's attendance at this weekends anniversary of Bloody Sunday shows why they have little or no support in the African- American community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 02:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those Democrats are now Republicans because the Dems embraced the civil rights movement and the GOP did not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 03:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is certainly going to mess up North Carolina streams and rivers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 19:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet you think your arm is worth a lot more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 03:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But when pipelines fail the amount of oil lost is much larger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just what we need need big campaign contributors deciding how the internet should be regulated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 02:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corrupt politicians are an attack upon democracy. They help subvert the system and make it possible for politicians like Kitzhaber and McDonnell to be elected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 02:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Bob McDonnell was under indictment did you say "another scumbag Republican" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 01:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and ~~fairly~~ incompetent 

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 22:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Scott Walker the reincarnation of Rick Perry in 2012? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 18:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was an environment story because:

1) The environmental group would pay for support

2) The amount the environmental group lost because she did not show up.

3) This is part of the movement to get Chevron to pay for the economic damage in Peru.

However, I respect your decision.

DJ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 17:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a substantial amount of antisemitism among European right-wing and neo-Nazi movements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 03:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another chickenhawk wants to send young people into war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 21:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Kurds are in the way again,

And so, to our dismay again,

If we begin a fray again,

As it appears we may again,

It seems we must betray again

Calvin Trillin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 17:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You missed one.](http://www.reddit.com/r/Columbus/comments/2x806b/abdirahman_mohamud_allegedly_charged_with/coxu6fz) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 01:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not about fraud but rather eliminating people from the rolls no matter what economic status they hold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 01:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not reform but economic homicide for millions of poor people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 00:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No need, Oklahoma has its fair share of mega-churches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 16:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But as the the unofficial slogan of Alabama proclaims "at least we are not Mississippi." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 06:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this what is meant by a living constitution? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 02:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clintonville is not where the wealthy live. The most exclusive enclaves are Upper Arlington, Bexley, Powell, New Albany and parts of Dublin like Muirfield Village, to name a few. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 04:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean what if? The Israelis will reverse engineer the plane, add new proprietary software and sell it back to the US for billions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 18:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 05:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The link is working for me. Please try again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 05:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In an earlier judgement the court determined that 3.9 million barrels spilled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 01:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Alaska years after the Exxon Valdez disaster Exxon is paying for the ongoing cleanup from new oil being deposited on the state's shores. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 01:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is not about praying. The act of fasting is a sign of the commitment being made by those individuals to the issue of climate change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 01:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The idea that Catholics are using one of their holiest periods to take on climate justice is an amazing event. It will not end global warming but it will bring one of the largest religions into the fray on the side of the angels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 00:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because the oil is on the bottom of the Gulf now doesn't mean it will remain there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 21:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evan a broken clock is right twice a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 22:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certainly didn't work in Sochi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 22:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This story look at the unintended consequences of China's blood donation laws. In a system where healthcare is a right, blood does not seem to be included in that right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
