<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1185</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 16:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard a great idea on /r/Firefly that it was a GoT style TV series about 14 different people recieving the message from the end of Serenity and how the rest of the galaxy reacts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 16:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game is so hard on mobile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 12:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nova: Annihilation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 00:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't find most of the New X-Men (Surge, Prodigy, Elixr etc). Are they are there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 23:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but the power he displayed in the movie was still greater than he power SW displayed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 19:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we include Namora, can we include Hercules? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 19:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comic Scarlet Witch? Sure. But she's not really displayed that much power in the movies yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [R/F] Raccoon Deck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 01:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like it needs trimming, but I'm welcome to addition suggestions.

Deck:

Monsters: 24

Spells: 15

Trap: 12

Total Deck: 51

Extra Deck: 15

Monsters:

* Ojama Yellow **x3**
* Rescue Rabbit
* Junk Synchron **x3**
* Dandelion
* Mogmole
* Wind-Up Kitten **x3**
* Pon-Poko the Raccoon Rascal **x3**
* Valerifawn, Mystical Beast of the Forest **x3**
* Kalantosa, Mystical Beast of the Forest **x3**
* Baby Raccoon Tantan **x3**

Spells:
* Creature Swap
* Ayers Rock Sunrise **x2**
* Dark Hole
* Obedience Schooled **x2**
* Mystical Space Typhoon **x2**
* Spiritual Forest **x2**
* United We Stand **x3**
* Closed Forest **x2**

Traps:
* Super Rush Recklessly **x2**
* Beast Soul Swap **x2**
* Mirror Force **x2**
* Magic Cylinder
* Scrap Iron Scarecrow **x2**
* Token Stampede
* Dark Bribe **x2**

Extra Deck:
* Frozen Fitzgerald **x2**
* Junk Synchron **x3**
* Ally of Justice Catastor **x2**
* Daigusto Phoenix **x2**
* Number 64: Ronin Raccoon Sandayu **x3**
* Gachi Gachi Gantetsu
* Armor Kappa
* Number 96: Dark Mist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 01:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't X-Men '92 digital only? If so, what's the point of the variant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 00:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First Class is so much fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 23:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely agree, but for every writer that does a good job of being edgy (see: Garth Ennis or classic Frank Miller), you get five who aren't (see: modern Mark Millar or Grant Morrison's Happy). It annoys me that good writers try to hard and make every other word a cuss or have a prostitute get killed every other issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 22:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's more about having the whole team involved for a sense of visual completion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 19:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So like Milestone, but for women? That sounds awesome. Do you think it'd be likely they'd write Superhero comics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 18:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So did his Daredevil. I'd argue his Avengers was also pretty good when not wrapped up in events. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 18:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not entirely sure, but I think I would have saved Stane as the villain for another film. He would have acted as Tony's mentor, but it was hinted that he was doing some dodgy dealings meanwhile. As they were building a universe, having recurring characters like Stane would have been important. I probably would have gone for Hammer or the Mandarin as other villains and would have had a greater focus on Tony's drinking.

Sorry if that's a bad answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 17:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Hulk in Tokyo would be pretty cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 17:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More importantly, any post slightly critical of these movies is downvoted. This shows quite a closed minded attitude.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 17:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Revolving door of death
* Too many pointless events
* Too many variants
* Superhero comics are the only mainstream image of comics
* Reluctancy to start afresh
* No sense of scale as major events happen in every cape book all the time and they kind of undermine events
* Lack of women in the industry
* Oversexualised characters
* Inconsistent timelines
* Crappy creative teams on the best characters
* Most great Superhero stories are only great in the context of that character
* There's too many creator-owned books that are 2edgy4me. Why can't you tell a story with sex and violence, without playing edgy comics bingo?
* Status quos never last
* Being a new reader is horrifying
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 16:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I need to talk to Caesar!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 16:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, that's not very interesting or entertaining, is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 08:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently Idris Elba can never be Bond because of the leaks.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 08:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you care to go over aboriginal history? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 07:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel The Raid 2 was the movie Evans wanted to make initially, but couldn't due to budget restraints. 2 opens up the world, creating a horrendous Gangster's Paradise whilst still topping the action of the first one. That kitchen fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 07:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iron Man - how does Jeff Bridges' Stane go from a morally complex businessman to a cartoon villain in the last twenty minutes? Up until that point, Bridges was one of my favourite parts of that film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 06:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thor 2's visuals were splendid and made the movie for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 06:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full gay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 06:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to complain that the opening of Guardians of the Galaxy felt forced and undeserved, but now it just upsets me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 06:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 03:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. I don't mind Melissa McCarthy (although our senses of humour differ greatly), but I think Paul Feig is a good director by any means. He's an average television director who made traction because he did some mediocre work on some great shows.

I was never a fan of Paul Feig, but [this video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3FOzD4Sfgag) really enlightened me to why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My father passed away recently, so I found this scene from Fast Five oddly emotional. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 02:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still waiting to watch The Assassination of Jesse James and The Wicker Man. Still waiting... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fast and Furious 5-7 are pretty good movies, the first four... Not so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 23:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Outlaw Josey Wales </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 21:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 20:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Cullen Bunn's Deadpool miniseries. They're so much fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 20:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flashpoint was pretty good, I thought. I only read the main event though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 19:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it'll be fine as long as he's not just throwing out one-liners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 19:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It stopped being a procedural last year though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 19:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 3 was just a mess. It was four episodes' worth of plot, stretched out over thirteen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 19:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather see a Gotham Central TV series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five Reasons Movies Bomb </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 19:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 17:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tokyo Drift ain't got nothing on Fast Five. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 10:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They wouldn't kill Matt's one Asian friend, would they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 10:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to imagine Rupert Grint as Penance now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 10:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of your choices, The Runaways, Young Avengers, White Tiger and Nova. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 04:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James Wan was 27 when he made Saw.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 03:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eminem, but once he's famous. His troubles metamorphosed into a unique beast once he hit platinum. Drugs, rap, assult and fatherhood are pretty interesting subjects for a movie. Alas, I guess having two biopics is a bit unfair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 23:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never met someone else who doesn't like LotR. I knew there were at least dozens of us! Dozens of us! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 23:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was called Lord of the Rings - they're family movies. Don't try and turn kid's movies into an insult. There are so many great ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 22:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually think it's a reference to that famous Superman line, "faster than a speeding bullet." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 18:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, favourably and lots of people will rewatch them time and time again? Does that mean this sub's equivalent to T2 in 30 years is The Winter Soldier? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 14:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not Adamantium nails? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 13:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this Macbeth as an action movie? I'd think that'd be pretty cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 04:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bendis really knows what the kids are into. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 03:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as I love it, I kind of doubt it. It's so dependant on poking fun of contemporary films and filmmakers it'll date pretty poorly IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 16:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Django has a bunch of unofficial sequels starring other actors. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 15:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snikt, bub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 15:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can take Cornwall as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Henry Jackman coming back to score Civil War? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 06:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's one of my favourite film composers and having him come back would greatly excite me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 04:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very funny and all, but they've kind of misunderstood Ultron's motives, then again Whedon didn't really make it very clear in the film himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 04:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And an episode of The Office. I belive it was the episode before Joss Whedon's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 00:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody said there weren't. Maybe you should review the title again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 23:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't remotely blame them, but wouldn't you love to see more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 23:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant this year. In the grand scheme of things, this isn't that many movies. These movies have been over twenty years, the average amount of non-cape comic book movies a year is still under two on average. That really isn't great, especially compared to the number of book adaptions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 22:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there? Obviously I can think of the classics like A History of Violence and V for Vendetta, but I can only think of one comic movie released so far this year that wasn't a cape movie (Kingsman). Care to give me some more examples? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 21:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's about being able to see him making a difference. It has more weight and substance when you can immediately see the consequences. A caveman can understand the danger when Supes catches Louis in Siperman: The Movie, but the convulted saving the world victories have less weight and are harder to celebrate, especially if you're already not that into a movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 18:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough, although I really meant in the final act. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 18:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hawkeye could get divorced. That could be an interesting direction for the character. Having to move out with only a dog and Kate to keep him company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 17:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite a few years away, but I'm very much looking forward to Gareth Evans capping off his Raid trilogy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 16:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He still didn't break Gordon though, so overall it's a loss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 15:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. He didn't break Gordon, although he did trick Batman into killing him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 15:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superman's character was defined by what others told him, so by the end of the film I had no idea what kind of person he was. I have no problem with Supes destroying clearly vacated buildings, but I do mind him never going out of his way to save individuals. A scene involving him saving people would have helped me see him more of a hero. This one is purely personal preference, but the colour scheme didn't work for me and I can't imagine it in a Superman movie. Even though it quoted All-Star Superman, it didn't really get what made Superman special (hint: his complete altruism). The action didn't really work for me, I felt like there was too much happening on the screen, even when simple things like flight were happening. My biggest complaint is the mixture of conflicting symbols - was Supes Jesus, Moses, the embodiment of the American dream, a foreigner in our land? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her character was older. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the only Zak Snyder movie I've enjoyed, but I still don't think it's that good. Would you mind if I explained why I didn't like it *that* much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Lord of the Rings is well made garbage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I say that's only really true for this century. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't an unpopular opinion, especially on /r/movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 01:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Secret Invasion: Black Panther is really excellent. Jason Aaron writes badasses really well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 01:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Josh Brolin as Nick Fury is brilliant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 01:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How has no-one mentioned Drax specifically? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 11:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Casablanca </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 23:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The annoying thing is, Birdman isn't even pretentious. It mocks pretentious movies as much as it does blockbusters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 23:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the answers to "What's a movie similar to Pulp Fiction/The Wolf of Wall Street/Fast and Furious 7?" Are all the same?

Yup. Sounds like /r/Movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 22:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the point of Wolverine's Adamantiun skeleton? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 21:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been watching this post for the past 5 hours and all I can say is /r/ movies sure is a fickle bunch. Right now it's at +8, but an hour ago it was at -4 and an hour before that it kept circling around -1 to 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 19:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do they present them without bias? Like, did they the bad shit they did as well? I really want to know if they included the beating of Dee Barnes in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 19:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is great. Surprised by the downvotes though, it's as if people just saw Marvel and downvoted and didn't read your excellent analysis of Ultron'a motives and aims. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 19:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were it the late 80s we would have turned on Spielberg, but instead hindsight has caused Jurrasic Park to be the top of this thread.

*I love Spielberg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Daredevil great television? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 18:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If not, do you think it has the potential to be somewhere down the line? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help me decide: is Daredevil great television? If not, will it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 18:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 16:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where in the thread say it defines cinema? I was under the impression we were just listing scenes we really, really enjoyed. Frankly, that is an excellent choice and is one of the best scenes in modern action movies (which makes up a good chunk of modern cinema). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 16:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has the anti-Marvel circlejerk gotten so bad, we're downvoting a guy for expressing the fact he liked a scene in the Avengers? Really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 15:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't even call it House of M as it's named for Magneto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 15:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching him is the most akward, uncomfortable and weirdest thing. I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 15:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Dark Knight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 06:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toy Story 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 06:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eric is just a dick. There's nothing heroic about him, he's just a dick.

I'd actually be quite interested to see an Aronofsky-esque take on Hank Pym; watching his obsession with science destroy the relationships around him would be awfully thrilling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 05:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you on about? The serial-adultering, wife-beating, murder-bot creating, mad scientist isn't a good person?

No? How about a compelling character then? I read an interesting post from a while back saying that what makes Hank interesting is how much he means well, yet still constantly does bad things and this is because he is inherently a bad person, but he doesn't want to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 03:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Movie is Kung Fury BTW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 01:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have fun. Despite a few bum movies here and there, you're set on a real adventure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 23:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favourite podcast for comic book movies is The Weekly Planet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 23:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I'm a bit confused; what led you to conclude it wasn't a comedy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 21:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is All-New Captian America any good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 21:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loving Astonishing X-Men's Cyclops outfit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 18:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hard to explain; just read Alias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 15:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was filmed here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 15:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we're counting 2001, can I count Star Wars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 07:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad they're trying to get more girls interested in science and maths, but I wish they had said "inspire other people" instead of "inspire other girls" as I don't think there are nearly enough female role models that boys look up to and I think there should be more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 02:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always accepted it as a very subtle commentary on politics and comic books that Bendis decided the most powerful people in the 616 are all moderately wealthy, white men. Pointing that out diminishes it's impact.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 18:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stuff like this makes Mark Waid one of my favourite writers   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 17:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a lot of things to complain about. Price, crossovers, restricting creators to a house art style, the New 52 keeping parts of the old continuity without being clear what. I just can't be bothered to phrase it politely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 16:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Several times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 16:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See also: Marvel Studios and Christopher Nolan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 16:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's only a  5 year difference for Arrow, in Dexter it was about 18. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 16:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another TV example, but putting 30-something Michael C Hall in a bowl cut wig does not make him look 16. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
