<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2450</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The International Criminal Court (ICC) has called on South Africa to arrest Omar al-Bashir, with the Sudanese president reportedly in the country for an African Union (AU) summit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 02:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christian Denomination Plans To Avoid Civil Rights Laws By Pretending Receptionists Are 'Ministers' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 02:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oregon Becomes Fourth State To Pass Law Guaranteeing Paid Sick Days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 02:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pro-democracy campaigners will take to the streets of Hong Kong Sunday ahead of a vote on the political reform package that has divided the city and sparked mass protests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 00:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Des Moines, Bernie Sanders' Supporters Nearly Steal the Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 23:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. authorities are examining payments made by Nike Inc under a 1996 soccer sponsorship deal with Brazil for possible evidence of wrongdoing by the company or others </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 03:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Obama administration is expected to announce an agreement with Cuba in early July to reopen embassies and restore diplomatic relations severed more than five decades ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 03:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany drops inquiry into claims NSA tapped Angela Merkel's phone: Prosecutors say they can find no actionable evidence to support claims German chancellors mobile phone was tapped by US National Security Agency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 02:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A federal appeals court cleared the way for a hotly contested Utah law banning price fixing for contact lenses Friday, a ruling that could have wide-ranging effects on the $4 billion industry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 02:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House race has already sparked $1 million in negative ads: Most of the mudslinging has targeted Democrat Hillary Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 02:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House race has already sparked $1 million in negative ads: Most of the mudslinging has targeted Democrat Hillary Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 02:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polar bears are now eating dolphins lured north by warming water. Scientists for the first time observed the bears feasting on white-beaked dolphins in Svalbard in the Norwegian Arctic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 02:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren shot back at criticism from JPMorgan Chase   Co. Chief Executive Officer Jamie Dimon, saying bankers dont dislike her because she knows too little but because she knows too much </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 02:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren shot back at criticism from JPMorgan Chase   Co. Chief Executive Officer Jamie Dimon, saying bankers dont dislike her because she knows too little but because she knows too much </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 02:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oklahoma highway worker killed by airborne 'Stop' sign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 02:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The US has largely blocked terror groups from moving money through banks, but tens of billions of dollars in illicit funds still transit the financial system each year, the Treasury said Friday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 01:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The anti-eviction activist turned politician Ada Colau is assured of being sworn in as mayor of the Spanish city of Barcelona on Saturday thanks to the support of independents and Socialists, the parties said on Friday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 01:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Jersey Gov. Chris Christie's office says his recent foreign trips to the United Kingdom, Mexico and Canada cost state taxpayers $123,893.04 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 01:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An independent panel of experts that examined new information about the mysterious 1961 plane crash that killed Secretary-General Dag Hammarskjold on a peace mission to newly independent Congo has delivered its report to current U.N. chief Ban Ki-moon, the U.N. said Friday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 01:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Native American tribes start yearly harvest of eel-like fish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 01:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of stone tools from the early Upper Paleolithic, unearthed from a cave in Jordan, reveal clues about how humans may have started organizing into more complex social groups by planning tasks and specializing in different technical skills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 20:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of stone tools from the early Upper Paleolithic, unearthed from a cave in Jordan, reveal clues about how humans may have started organizing into more complex social groups by planning tasks and specializing in different technical skills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 20:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As many as 14 million current and former civilian U.S. government employees had their personal information exposed to hackers, according to two people who were briefed on the investigation, a far higher figure than the 4 million the Obama administration initially disclosed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 20:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers at UCLA and the U.S. Department of Energy's Argonne National Laboratory announced today a new method for creating magnetic skyrmion bubbles at room temperature. The bubbles, a physics phenomenon thought to be an option for more energy-efficient and compact electronics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 20:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers at UCLA and the U.S. Department of Energy's Argonne National Laboratory announced today a new method for creating magnetic skyrmion bubbles at room temperature. The bubbles, a physics phenomenon thought to be an option for more energy-efficient and compact electronics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 20:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers at UCLA and the U.S. Department of Energy's Argonne National Laboratory announced today a new method for creating magnetic skyrmion bubbles at room temperature. The bubbles, a physics phenomenon thought to be an option for more energy-efficient and compact electronics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 20:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Left in the Brain: Potentially Toxic Residue from MRI Drugs -- Researchers raise alarms about unknown health risks of GEs Omniscan and Bayers Magnevist, drugs injected to get better MRI pictures that contain the heavy metal gadolinium </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 05:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Harvard-Smithsonian researcher known as a climate sceptic is under multiple ethics investigations arising from his hidden financial relationships with fossil fuel companies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 04:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Harvard-Smithsonian researcher known as a climate sceptic is under multiple ethics investigations arising from his hidden financial relationships with fossil fuel companies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 04:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whirlpool windmill produces power without blades </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 04:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The House of Representatives rejected an amendment to a defense bill on Thursday that would have forced lawmakers to vote on a formal authorization for the use of military force against Islamic State </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 04:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bundestag counting cost of cyberattack: Germany's parliament has rejected rumors its IT system will need to be completely replaced following a recent cyberattack. Reports say large amounts of data are still being stolen from the network </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 03:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bundestag counting cost of cyberattack: Germany's parliament has rejected rumors its IT system will need to be completely replaced following a recent cyberattack. Reports say large amounts of data are still being stolen from the network </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 03:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dozens of penguins wash up dead on coast of Uruguay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 02:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dozens of penguins wash up dead on coast of Uruguay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 02:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Families of the thousands of Bosnian Muslims massacred at Srebrenica reacted with outrage Thursday over the arrest of former Bosnian Muslim commander Naser Oric on a war crimes warrant from Serbia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 02:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Is Creativity Differentially Related to Schizophrenia and Autism? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 01:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rules that treat the Internet like a public utility and prevent companies from blocking or slowing down some online traffic will go into effect Friday after a federal appeals court refused to delay them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 01:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rules that treat the Internet like a public utility and prevent companies from blocking or slowing down some online traffic will go into effect Friday after a federal appeals court refused to delay them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 01:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Variations in the amount of oxygen in Earth's atmosphere significantly altered global climate throughout the planet's history. Efforts to reconstruct past climates must include this previously overlooked factor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Variations in the amount of oxygen in Earth's atmosphere significantly altered global climate throughout the planet's history. Efforts to reconstruct past climates must include this previously overlooked factor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> African Academics Challenge Homophobic Laws: A scientific report demolishes the assertions used to back the criminalization of homosexuality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> African Academics Challenge Homophobic Laws: A scientific report demolishes the assertions used to back the criminalization of homosexuality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas faced the prospect of deep cuts to schools, prisons and other programs Thursday after the Republican-controlled House soundly rejected a proposal supported by Gov. Sam Brownback that would hike sales and cigarette taxes to close a budget deficit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas faced the prospect of deep cuts to schools, prisons and other programs Thursday after the Republican-controlled House soundly rejected a proposal supported by Gov. Sam Brownback that would hike sales and cigarette taxes to close a budget deficit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alaska's Rare Alexander Archipelago Wolves Nearly Wiped Out in One Year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guatemalan President Otto Perez will be investigated for alleged corruption, the Supreme Court ruled Wednesday, and has also asked Congress to consider lifting his immunity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 04:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Korea's central bank lowered its key interest rate to a historic low on Thursday, responding to a slump in exports and the prospect that the outbreak of the deadly MERS virus could slow the economy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 04:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 700-Year-Old Casino Found in Utah </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 04:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roman Archaeological Find Discovered in Ethiopia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 02:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An abundance of objects such as dice, sticks, and darts found in a cave near the Great Salt Lake in Utah have led researchers studying the site to suggest the culture that occupied the cave, the Promontory, regularly enjoyed a variety of betting games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 02:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Al-Qaida 'cut off and ripped apart by Isis': Insiders say group has been drained of Middle East recruits and that US wrongfooted by shift in balance of power between warring jihadi groups </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 01:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The number of vehicles on U.S. roads with potentially defective Takata air bags appears to be less than half the 34 million initially estimated by federal regulators </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 01:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An exchange of gunfire between groups of people in a Phoenix park left three men dead, but dozens of other people escaped injury as approximately 20 shots were fired </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 01:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 01:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course BYOB is not allowed in the park. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At near absolute zero, molecules may start to exhibit exotic states of matter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 22:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One Nation, Under Sedation: Medicare Paid for Nearly 40 Million Tranquilizer Prescriptions in 2013 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 22:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One Nation, Under Sedation: Medicare Paid for Nearly 40 Million Tranquilizer Prescriptions in 2013 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 22:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gay rights opponent transfers millions to LGBT-friendly bank in failed boycott: In an effort to avoid businesses that promote sin, Franklin Graham switched to BB T  perhaps unaware its a sponsor of the Miami Beach gay pride parade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 22:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gay rights opponent transfers millions to LGBT-friendly bank in failed boycott: In an effort to avoid businesses that promote sin, Franklin Graham switched to BB T  perhaps unaware its a sponsor of the Miami Beach gay pride parade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 22:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bosnian Serb MPs reject Srebrenica genocide resolution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 22:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EPA Takes First Step to Regulate Aircraft Greenhouse Gas Emissions: The U.S. agency said greenhouse gases from aircraft endanger human health </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 22:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plants Will Not Flourish as the World Warms: A new study contradicts the notion that higher temperatures will enhance plant growth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 22:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plants Will Not Flourish as the World Warms: A new study contradicts the notion that higher temperatures will enhance plant growth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 22:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The head of Lebanon's Hezbollah movement announced Wednesday that the powerful Shiite militia had begun to fight the Islamic State jihadist group along the rugged Syrian-Lebanese border. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 22:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israel has barred a Palestinian photographer allegedly shot in the eye by an Israeli soldier from entering east Jerusalem for specialist treatment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 21:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The number of Ebola cases has risen in Guinea and Sierra Leone for the second consecutive week, the World Health Organization said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 21:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio authorities say three men have been indicted on aggravated murder charges for a 2006 contract killing in which the hit man went to the wrong house and killed a man with the same name as the intended target </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 21:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Canadian Broadcasting Corporation abruptly dismissed a high-profile, popular news anchor over allegations that he used his journalistic contacts to broker art deals and collect lucrative fees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 21:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Republicans are hoping to repeal a law requiring country-of-origin labels on packages of meat to avoid costly trade retaliation from Canada and Mexico </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 21:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 2015 ComFest Program Guide is now available online, with complete entertainment and workshop schedules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 21:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 2015 ComFest Program Guide is now available online, with complete entertainment and workshop schedules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 21:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The size of the U.S. corporate-bond market has grown by $3.7 trillion during the past decade, almost all of that growth is concentrated in mutual funds, foreign investors and insurance companies That combination could lead to more selling than the market can absorb when the Fed raises interest rates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 09:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This County In Oregon Completely Banned GMO Crops </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 04:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amnesty International said on Wednesday the Azerbaijan government had barred it from visiting the capital Baku, where the group planned to protest human rights violations ahead of the European Games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 04:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Obama administration is considering setting up a new military base in Iraq's Anbar province and is closing in on a decision to send several hundred more trainers and advisers to help Iraqi forces in the fight against Islamic State militants there </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 03:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers in Peru have discovered a trio of statuettes they believe were created by the ancient Caral civilization some 3,800 years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 03:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wild Chimps Seen Drinking Alcoholic Beverage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 02:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists report that after two decades of attempts to save the species, northern spotted owl numbers in the Northwest are still on the decline  and at a faster rate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 02:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists report that after two decades of attempts to save the species, northern spotted owl numbers in the Northwest are still on the decline  and at a faster rate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 02:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A federal judge ordered a Texas company to pay $663 million in damages for failing to tell the government about design changes to highway guardrails that critics say made the systems more dangerous </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 02:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US technology companies are getting hit harder than anticipated by revelations about surveillance programs led by the National Security Agency, a study showed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 00:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Fifth Circuit Just Stuck A Knife In Roe v. Wade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 00:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Fifth Circuit Just Stuck A Knife In Roe v. Wade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 00:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 00:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you open an account to only comment on this story, you should know this is the only responsible response you will get. If you want a serious discussion comment in your own account and not in a throw away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Food flavor safety system a black box: But industry says self-policing poses no threat to consumers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 23:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas officer in pool party incident was sued over alleged racial profiling in 2007: Albert Brown filed a civil rights lawsuit against five McKinney officers including Eric Casebolt after being imprisoned on drug charges following a traffic stop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 23:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House votes to make ban on Internet access taxes permanent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 23:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The House has voted to make permanent a moratorium that prevents states from taxing access to the Internet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 23:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Spanish judge shelved a criminal investigation into the killing of a Spanish cameraman by a US tank shell in Iraq in 2003 after Spain placed limits on judicial powers in international cases </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seattle protesters seek to block access to Shell Arctic drilling rig </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seattle protesters seek to block access to Shell Arctic drilling rig </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Republicans proposed a spending bill Tuesday that cuts the budget at the Environmental Protection Agency by 9 percent and tries to prevent the Obama administration from enacting several regulations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Republicans proposed a spending bill Tuesday that cuts the budget at the Environmental Protection Agency by 9 percent and tries to prevent the Obama administration from enacting several regulations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas woman's death after cosmetic injections ruled homicide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The February death of a Dallas woman who had cosmetic injections at a salon to increase the size of her buttocks has been ruled a homicide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How atmospheric rivers form </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 19:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former GOP Senator Trashes Partys Presidential Field: Scares Me To Death, Not Ready For Primetime </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 19:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. job openings surged to a record high in April and small business confidence perked up in May, suggesting the economy was regaining speed after stumbling at the start of the year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 19:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Archaeologists discover fresh, 358-year-old body in France </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 19:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 19:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is always great to have new documentary evidence of historic events. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amelia Earhart took off from Burbank, California in 1937 on her ill-fated round-the-globe flight. A photographer documented the journey's start, but the world was unaware -- until Tuesday -- that a home movie was also made that day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 19:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How atmospheric rivers form </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 19:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cancer Spending Higher in U.S. than Europe--and So Is Cancer Mortality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 19:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists said they have discovered what appear to be red blood cells and collagen fibres in dinosaur bones, a find that may boost prospects of prising organic remains from a much wider range of fossils </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 18:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists said they have discovered what appear to be red blood cells and collagen fibres in dinosaur bones, a find that may boost prospects of prising organic remains from a much wider range of fossils </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 18:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polish prosecutors are investigating the publication of classified files from a probe into the illegal taping of government ministers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 18:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A federal appeals court on Tuesday threw out a pair of high-profile lawsuits challenging the Obama administration's sweeping plan to address climate change, saying it's too early to challenge a proposed rule that isn't yet final </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 18:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A federal appeals court on Tuesday threw out a pair of high-profile lawsuits challenging the Obama administration's sweeping plan to address climate change, saying it's too early to challenge a proposed rule that isn't yet final </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 18:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A condemned Ohio killer is fighting a second attempt by the state to put him to death. The Ohio Supreme Court is weighing arguments by death row inmate Romell Broom that allowing the state prisons agency to try again to execute him amounts to cruel and unusual punishment and double jeopardy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 07:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A condemned Ohio killer is fighting a second attempt by the state to put him to death. The Ohio Supreme Court is weighing arguments by death row inmate Romell Broom that allowing the state prisons agency to try again to execute him amounts to cruel and unusual punishment and double jeopardy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 07:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top U.S. tech companies are warning the Obama administration against imposing new policies that the companies say would weaken increasingly sophisticated encryption systems designed to protect consumers' privacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 06:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top U.S. tech companies are warning the Obama administration against imposing new policies that the companies say would weaken increasingly sophisticated encryption systems designed to protect consumers' privacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 06:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As talks aimed at slowing global warming drag on, researchers are pushing new ideas that some are calling last-ditch attempts to avert the worst effects of climate change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 06:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Southeast Alaskas isolated wolf population has declined by 60 percent in just one year, dropping from an estimated 221 individuals in 2013 to 89 wolves in 2014, according to the U.S. Forest Service </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 03:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Southeast Alaskas isolated wolf population has declined by 60 percent in just one year, dropping from an estimated 221 individuals in 2013 to 89 wolves in 2014, according to the U.S. Forest Service </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 03:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The last of the "Angola Three" inmates, whose decades in solitary confinement in connection with the death of a prison guard drew international condemnation and became the subject of two documentaries, was ordered released Monday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 03:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas would likely be forced to lay off prison guards, cut aid to public schools and reduce payments to health care providers and nursing homes if legislators don't increase taxes, Republican Gov. Sam Brownback's budget director told GOP lawmakers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 03:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: Some for-profit hospitals charging 10x Medicare rates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 02:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: Some for-profit hospitals charging 10x Medicare rates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 02:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nuclear weapons labs hit with sizable fines for new security violations: A classified material was missing for years before anyone noticed, and a lab official's public slides included bomb design data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 02:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worlds Most Congested Subway Prepares to Host Olympics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 02:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.N. hands Libya's warring factions unity government proposal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 01:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Supreme Court on Monday struck down a law that would let American citizens born in Jerusalem have Israel listed in passports as their country of birth, saying it encroached on the president's exclusive power to recognize foreign governments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 01:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alaska fire crews battling 2 large tundra wildfires </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 01:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alaska fire crews battling 2 large tundra wildfires </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 01:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The British trade organization in charge of benchmark interest rates was warned as far back as 2005 that some banks were deliberately distorting their Libor rates for profit, according to evidence given on Monday at the trial of a former trader accused of rate rigging </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 01:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The British trade organization in charge of benchmark interest rates was warned as far back as 2005 that some banks were deliberately distorting their Libor rates for profit, according to evidence given on Monday at the trial of a former trader accused of rate rigging </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 01:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New AMA policy favors ending nonmedical vaccine exemptions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 01:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greek Finance Minister Yanis Varoufakis warned Monday that EU leaders had a duty to avoid a historic "failure" and urged a swift accord in Greece's debt talks with its creditors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 00:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greek Finance Minister Yanis Varoufakis warned Monday that EU leaders had a duty to avoid a historic "failure" and urged a swift accord in Greece's debt talks with its creditors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 00:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UBS boss says negative interest rates a major challenge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 00:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A federal appeals court says Allegiant Air had the right to make changes in work rules for its pilots. The court ruled that the pilots who negotiated the rules were not an official collective bargaining agent. Because of that, the judges say, the company was within its rights to change the rules. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 00:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As of Saturday, 149 birds and 72 mammals were reported dead after a pipeline along the Santa Barbara coast burst May 19 and polluted miles of beaches and reserves with crude oil, including a natural reserve owned by the University of California </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 20:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An 8-year-old boy falls into one of Mexicos most contaminated rivers. Eighteen days later, hes dead. Fusion investigates how factories--many of them U.S. owned--get away with illegally dumping toxic chemicals into one of the countrys main waterways, with potentially deadly consequences </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 20:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A French court has ordered US tyre company Goodyear to stop dismantling its former factory in the northern town of Amiens, which a group of ex-employees wants to take over, a union lawyer said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 20:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A French court has ordered US tyre company Goodyear to stop dismantling its former factory in the northern town of Amiens, which a group of ex-employees wants to take over, a union lawyer said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 20:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia has refused to sign off on the U.N. nuclear watchdog's annual report because the document lists a nuclear reactor near Crimea's Sevastopol as being in Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 19:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservative advocate Edward Blum is suing Harvard in what he says is a bid to end discrimination against Asian students. His quest, say opponents, could kill preferences for disadvantaged blacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 19:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservative advocate Edward Blum is suing Harvard in what he says is a bid to end discrimination against Asian students. His quest, say opponents, could kill preferences for disadvantaged blacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 19:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers cross a critical threshold in optical communications </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 19:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers cross a critical threshold in optical communications </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 19:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A grand jury affirmed the state of South Carolina's murder charge on Monday against a white former North Charleston police officer who fatally shot an unarmed black man trying to run from a traffic stop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 19:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zimbabwean troops may not use force to oust thousands of street vendors, the high court ruled on Monday, effectively neutralizing the government's threat to clear the streets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 19:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New Jersey Supreme Court is set to issue its ruling on whether Republican Gov. Chris Christie and the Legislature must increase the state's contributions to pension funds for public workers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 19:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oil drilling in Montana has all but tapped out, according to state records showing that the state has been without a major drilling rig since April </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 19:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Haitian conservationist Jean Wiener is leading a homegrown campaign to protect the country's northern coastal areas, including barrier reefs and threatened mangrove forests that serve as crucial spawning grounds and nurseries for fish and crustaceans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 09:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study says that Israelis and Palestinians would gain billions of dollars from peace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 09:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists are launching an investigation into antibiotic-resistant bacteria, known as "superbugs", by gathering data from surfers' rectums </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 05:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unknown to most, around 45 km from Agra, India, and at a height of 150 feet, there were until some years ago 40 sites of grand cave paintings and shelters that belonged to the Mesolithic (Stone Age) period. Today, only a few of them remain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 05:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> India's government has filed for damages from food group Nestle after a food scare involving reports of excess lead in Maggi noodles forced a nationwide recall, government officials said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 05:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany's anti-Islam PEGIDA movement took nearly 10 percent of the vote in mayoral elections in its eastern stronghold of Dresden Sunday, a better-than-expected result for a group whose weekly demonstrations have steadily dwindled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 05:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a boost for hopes to curb climate change, China's greenhouse gas emissions will probably peak in 2025, five years earlier than its stated target, a study said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 04:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Texas company whose ruptured pipeline created the largest coastal oil spill in California in 25 years had assured the government that a break in the line while possible was "extremely unlikely" and state-of-the-art monitoring could quickly detect possible leaks and alert operators, documents show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 00:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Texas company whose ruptured pipeline created the largest coastal oil spill in California in 25 years had assured the government that a break in the line while possible was "extremely unlikely" and state-of-the-art monitoring could quickly detect possible leaks and alert operators, documents show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 00:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Santorum: I'm More Qualified Than Pope Francis To Talk About Climate Change Because I'm A Politician </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 00:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A suburban Dallas police officer has been placed on administrative leave after a video showed him pushing a 14-year-old girl in a swimsuit to the ground outside a pool and pointing his gun at other teens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 00:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservationists are urging the Indonesian government to listen to business and start taking deforestation seriously after a major paper giant joined the growing ranks of companies pledging to stop clearing forests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 23:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A far-right Israeli minister on Sunday called for the international community to endorse his country's 1981 annexation of Syria's Golan Heights, where he called for increased Jewish settlement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 22:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Belgian prosecutors have launched an investigation into allegations of widespread surveillance by Germany, which is alleged to have helped the US spy on Berlin's allies in Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 22:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Egyptian President Abdel Fattah el-Sissi issued a rare apology Sunday over a police officer beating a lawyer with a shoe last week, an attack that sparked a general one-day strike by the country's lawyers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 22:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police in Hungary say they have detained six activists suspected of vandalizing a billboard promoting the government's anti-immigration campaign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 22:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands March In The Midwest's Largest-Ever Anti-Tar Sands Rally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 05:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands March In The Midwest's Largest-Ever Anti-Tar Sands Rally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 05:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Threatened by disease and deforestation, the world's last isolated tribes in the Amazon are on a collision course with modern society like never before, experts say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 05:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hungary has become the first European country to sign a cooperation agreement for China's new "Silk Road" initiative to develop trade and transport infrastructure across Asia and beyond </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 05:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hungary has become the first European country to sign a cooperation agreement for China's new "Silk Road" initiative to develop trade and transport infrastructure across Asia and beyond </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 05:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The European Union's chief executive declined to speak to Greek Prime Minister Alexis Tsipras on Saturday after the leftist leader rejected as "absurd" international creditors' terms for a cash-for-reform deal to keep his country from default </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 05:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The European Union's chief executive declined to speak to Greek Prime Minister Alexis Tsipras on Saturday after the leftist leader rejected as "absurd" international creditors' terms for a cash-for-reform deal to keep his country from default </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 05:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No Fish, No Fowl: European Fish and Birds in Decline, Despite Some Conservation Successes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 16:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than 700 species of wild plants - almost half of the native flora of the British Isles - are found on road verges. More than 97% of meadows had been destroyed in England since the 1930s, with road verges becoming the last stretches of natural habitat for wildlife such as bees and other insects. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 16:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Scalia Blows Creationist Dog-Whistle During Graduation Speech At Catholic High School </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 16:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Lawsuit Machine Behind Student Debt Collection: This is robosigning 2.0 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 15:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of protesters marched through Honduras's capital demanding the resignation of President Juan Orlando Hernandez over a corruption scandal that has seen growing calls for him to quit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 15:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of demonstrators marched in the German resort town of Garmisch-Partenkirchen on Saturday to protest against a meeting of leaders from the Group of Seven (G7) industrial nations that starts on Sunday at a nearby luxury hotel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 15:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of demonstrators marched in the German resort town of Garmisch-Partenkirchen on Saturday to protest against a meeting of leaders from the Group of Seven (G7) industrial nations that starts on Sunday at a nearby luxury hotel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 15:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hundreds of Taliban insurgents launched a major assault at dawn Saturday on a remote district in Afghanistan's northeastern Badakhshan province, as reinforcements were flown in to help beleaguered police officers there </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 15:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holders of $5.4 billion in defaulted Argentine debt won a ruling that they werent treated equally with owners of restructured government bonds, another legal setback for the nation in its long-running showdown with creditors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 04:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The home testing method Lumber Liquidators Holdings Inc. is using to reassure customers that their floors are safe is being questioned by the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 04:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamists claiming to be members of the Islamic State group called for jihad in the Balkans in a video widely reported Friday by local media, on the eve of a visit by Pope Francis to Sarajevo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 04:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Italian fugitive who played a key role in running one of Europe's most polluted steel plants was extradited from Britain on Friday and arrested in Rome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 04:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Italian fugitive who played a key role in running one of Europe's most polluted steel plants was extradited from Britain on Friday and arrested in Rome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 04:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Federal Communications Commission, concerned about the high cost of broadband, wants to put cell phones that can access the Internet in the hands of Americas poor in hopes of reducing the digital divide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 03:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Federal Communications Commission, concerned about the high cost of broadband, wants to put cell phones that can access the Internet in the hands of Americas poor in hopes of reducing the digital divide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 03:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> State broadcaster CCTV says death toll in Yangtze River capsizing rises to 345 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 03:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The eldest son of Zimbabwe's first lady Grace Mugabe has been convicted of manslaughter and fined $800 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 03:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Threatened by disease and deforestation, the world's last isolated tribes in the Amazon are on a collision course with modern society like never before, experts say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 02:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
