<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1317</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 06:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like there is a ton of opposition to this idea and I don't know why. Vader in the black suit ruling the empire with Palpatine in his evil prime between Revenge of the Sith and A New Hope would be pretty sweet. Lots of meat there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else notice the 'watched by Piper Chapman' list that popped up on Netflix? Clever girl... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 08:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 09:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something I've never been able to find online and I don't think it's on the DVD's either is a sketch from HBO's late 90's 'The Chris Rock Show' called "Explosions". It was a parody of disaster movies like Armageddon or The Core where random explosions are happening all over the World and Chris Rock plays the president. At one point he yells at his cabinet saying something like "We gotta do something about these explosions!" And it was just hilariously perfect. But it seems to be nowhere on YouTube, however his similar fecal themed disaster movie trailer "Shitstorm" (which may have inspired "Sharknado" for all we know) is relatively easy to find. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 09:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were watching Drunk History over memorial day weren't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 02:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2" front. 3" or 4" rear. It's kinda low stock. http://imgur.com/kBxvkld </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 10:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dig it. Gonna drop my GMT 400 Tahoe Limited soon. Needs shocks and bushings anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Cat Just Gave Me A High Five </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 09:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 08:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know there are plenty of Mexicans/Latinos in American metal bands like Deftones, P.O.D., Suicidal Tendencies (Robert Trujillo now in Metallica), RATM hmm who else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Cinco De Metal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 03:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 08:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won't call it shit, but Be Here Now did kinda sound to me like it was 'regurgitated' from the first 2 albums to use Noel's favorite word. Sounded great, but was more sizzle, and less steak. You know what some might say... ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
