<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1032</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 07:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm.... This logic does make sense. I shall be scared no more! I will wipe with confidence on my next outing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 05:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm scared the more TP I use, the higher chance of me clogging the toilet and having it overflow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 05:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in class watching Pearl Harbor, the movie. This happened when I was in 11th grade. I am one of those people that laugh all the time and have a hard time pulling back my laugh.
So as we're watching, the scene where the Japanese are attacking Hawaii there's a part where they drop a bomb near a guy who's hiding behind some sandbags. The bomb doesn't explode and the guy yells, "It's a dud!". And a second later the bomb explodes! My friend just turns to me, and says in a stupid tone, " So it wasn't a dud?". I couldn't hold it and I start cracking up. The whole class is serious while watching the movie, and I'm over here laughing while people are dieing left and right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 03:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That toilet paper looks like it's two-ply at least! Better than Disneyland and their thin stuff I'm currently using!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 11:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a freakin nice pass! The way Perry recieved the puck without slowing down was perfect! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 06:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Condoms! Condoms the size of hefty bags!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 12:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I didn't forget, those just happened to be my favorite ones :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
