<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6584</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Record Breaking Crowd Of 10,000-13,000 Turning Out In Madison For Bernie Sanders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 03:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walker continues to dig his own grave with his stupidity and delusions.  He will be completely vulnerable to public shaming and criticism if/when opponents go after him.  He will sink like a rock in a debate with just about anyone, even fellow idiot Rick Perry.  I'd like to see him go at it with Santorum just for the fun of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sickening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As if we needed more evidence about how delusional he is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 19:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A tragedy for everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 19:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He thinks he is, but actually he's on a mission from the Koch brothers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 18:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's religion interfering with the government that is the problem.  Women's reproductive rights and the war on women's bodies are a perfect example.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 17:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At Burger King. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 16:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slavery rhetoric? Does Rand Paul think people will believe his ridiculous argument? He reveals what an evil, greedy pig he is and that as a doctor he's motivated by money alone.  The white male ruling class at its ugliest. Medical bills are the leading cause of bankruptcy.  Americans themselves are slaves to the Medical-Insurance-Pharmaceutical Industrial Complex which addicts them to drugs and pigeon holes them into narrow diagnostic categories/treatment determined by insurance companies and medical bureaucracies.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jussi Bjorling and his wife Anna Lisa - O soave fanciulla - you can see his love for her in his eyes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 23:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scott Walker and Joseph McCarthy - Wisconsin's most shameful politicians.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 23:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her memoirs are brilliant.  I've read them several times.  It's terrible that the Soviets destroyed most of her work and erased any references to her - she was basically eliminated.  I was so happy to discover this recital.  There is another one from a few years later, in the Tchaikovsky Museum in Klin, where she's even more beautiful and impressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
