<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4778</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 18:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tanks alot... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 18:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for responding! When i used version 4 of both crack and update it worked... Haven't had any crashes, works really well! Your tutorial helped a lot, Thanks again :) Now that i know that it runs on my pc i'm going to buy it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 11:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All 3 the cracked files are in the right map and i did everything you said but i still keep getting the "please run GTA5.exe" error... don't know what i did wrong... Maybe a dumb question but does it matter what versions i use? Does crack v2 give an error with update 3? And do i need all the other updates before i can use update 3? (hope you know what i mean) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 09:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a second i thought these were huge fitness dumbbells, but then i thought.. nahh its Reddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 11:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Desolation of Smaug review is pure gold

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZIy_uLF6xI8 list=PL4NL9i-Fu15iZLbSfrxZCpZfKchWr9Vna index=5

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 10:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its the details that did the trick for me, you could just feel the impact of the punches in my theater. This movie has the best sound design i ever heard/felt in a movietheater! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 10:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, the whole movie i thought he would die, especially because of all the emotional wife and kids stuff. I'm so glad i was wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 10:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its one of his most quoted lines from the movie by now... don't know the exact context anymore. Oh well, now i have an excuse to go see it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 18:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America wants to be in the centre of the earth so bad it rips Russia in half... Looks so weird to me (European) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 13:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For number 2 i was thinking Planet Hulk, him flying away like that, still transformed... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 12:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fair enough  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 10:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats why these movies are great, you don't just want to see them F up badguys... (gotta watch the language) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 09:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I laughed so hard when Hawkeye was about to shoot Quicksilver whilst saying "I could do it... no one would know..." i did'nt like Hawkeye in the first movie, but they made him one of the most likeable characters in this movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 09:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what they do right, but you could feel the impact of those punches in the theater... Amazingly done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 09:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely loved this movie! It was such an entertaining experience, but those Russian accents from Scarlet Witch and Quicksilver were terrible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 00:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even the shittiest theater in the shittiest part of the shitty Netherlands has Age of Ultron, and i have seen the first screening of it... Take that America, Ne-Ther-Lands, Ne-Ther-Lands (i guess the chant works better when you shout U.S.A) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 23:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> David Luiz... 25 million for each nutmeg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 14:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't know why but this comment made me laugh out loud... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 20:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pack of Velociraptors, jurassic world style... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
