<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1687</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 20:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just moved to Provo from Massachusetts, and am also not LDS. I live in BYU housing, and will go to LDS services with my roommates (for socializing). I've had no real problems. Everyone is nice, understands I'm not a member (if they know me, that is), and generally don't try to proselytize me as I have my own faith.

That said, I do like it here, as an outsider. There are plenty of events going on at BYU or UVU, and there's a good stream of local musicians doing shows downtown. 

If you drink, there aren't that many bars around, so you'll have to get used to that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 20:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's good to see some bipartisan work on this. The issues that the PA office had are pretty shocking, like the changing of dates for visitations. I'm inclined to believe the issues are more a regional thing than a system-wide thing, but only further investigation will tell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senators seek VA probe to see if mishandled claims systemic - Belleville News-Democrat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 20:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 18:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lawyers and lobbyists can make that much, depending on the firm or group you work for.

And of course, medical professionals have that earning potential as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 18:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right time, right place is always key.

I recently lost a job with AmeriCoprs in Wyoming where I helped a non-profit doing communications and outreach for their homeless veterans program. After I lost the job, I moved to Utah, and applied for a few other AmeriCrops positions (as I was actually placed on administrative leave, which allowed me two weeks to find a new AmeriCorps position before I was officially let go from the program). I found a veteran mentoring program with AmeriCorps contracted through the Red Cross, so I applied. This was three months ago, and only last week did I get a call back, and then only today (as an of an hour ago) did I finish up an interview for the position.

The fact that the position exists in the current city I just moved to is pure luck. And the fact that the position aligns up with a job I just recently had, is also pure luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 00:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the exact same as his. He was my inspiration for it :)

And thanks for the input.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 22:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the baby boomers blame Millennials for believing the report, or blame them because it was published? 

That does make sense though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 21:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you explain how baby boomers made millennials racist and skeptical of vaccines?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 20:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Paul's have been okay at grabbing the attention of the youth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 20:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) Those are my favorites as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 20:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went out with a photographer. Got 27 pictures that are somewhat usable. A few of them aren't very flattering...but let me know which ones work:

[Link](http://imgur.com/p1l5gFr,VolDP1F,MARYbql,OXay3Hj,AwXzu57,o1gtk3L,PkiRDUN,Of7e3Br,EY4JghD,soaTv5T,wJ1drOl,2cqKQrK,Nqyn1LV,CqMLBXv,Etdo762,nskxSTF,TFETp2g,WOqAvJJ,01NLeam,W3uGwl0,OAIKiHK,6G0F8WQ,m8qNWm7,zm0lUhE,0EKb2X4,8NcyYVt,Ekwnq0P) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 07:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> US intelligence and Mexican authorities will collaborate on raids, on occasion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 06:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First dates are destined to be awkward. Maybe the second and third as well. After that the ball is your court. 

Also, no, I dont have this problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 05:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My suggestion is to make smoke signals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 03:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you have an unknown twin out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 03:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alcoholic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 03:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fahk you, Havahd's bettah

Signed,

An angry Masshole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 03:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **I spend a lot of time thinking about**

Secret societies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 00:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Switching jobs. If my interview goes well...

Currently in a call center. Not very fun. Please help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 00:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually follow them home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 23:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Provo, Utah. It's. So. Cheap. 

Also, Google Fiber  lt;3

Also, Mormons! They are a pretty people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 21:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interview with the Red Cross coming up on Wednesday. It's the exact job I've always wanted (working with military families). It's part time, so it'll be struggle to find complimentary work alongside it, but boy am I exicted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 21:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no such thing as too few. Start small, grow large. Build a presence in your neighborhood, and grow from there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 19:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could have met someone, moved, had something come up, etc. Life can get crazy. This is why you get the number early though, generally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 08:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love most of your pictures. They radiate confidence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 02:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I switched from analogs to an e-cig and it's absolutely great. Highly recommend the change.  You won't smell, you'll maybe save money (depending on what mods you buy and so on), there's no fire hazard, and you don't litter!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 21:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe this applies to Japan as well, where the Emperor is just there for ceremonial reasons. He holds no real power, thanks to the US.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 19:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. I like this photo. Very colorful, bright. Has a certain time to it that's kind of nice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 03:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not like they have much power (in the UK). They're just there for show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 04:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but if they didn't attack Hillary for being with Bill then that'd clear the way for Bush to move forward a little better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 02:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I find it interesting how all a lot of GOP voters seem to be already against Bush, despite Bush's track record as governor. The dynasty concern seems to be really bothing a lot of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In early horse race, Marco Rubio threatens Scott Walker- Politico </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 02:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 21:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most facisinating thing about this is some states like North Carolina are offering compensation for such victims, and the big question is "How much is the ability to reproduce worth?" How on earth do you put a number on that? How much is enough to apologize for such a mistake?

NPR strory on the compensation program

http://www.npr.org/blogs/health/2014/10/31/360355784/payments-start-for-n-c-eugenics-victims-but-many-wont-qualify </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 19:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I may be getting a job with the Red Cross. Super exciting! It's only part time, but it should be worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 04:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably few to none. The only ones that would most likely be present would be American defectors, of which there are already barely any already (I think there's only this guy: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/James_Joseph_Dresnok#Other_defectors_to_North_Korea) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 18:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I needed something which allowed for more independent thought, so I went from Mormon to Quaker.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 18:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Friend, I appreciate the mention of the AFSC! They really are awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 01:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe there have been much, much, worse. Scalia wasn't around when we threw the Japanese in camps.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 07:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for posting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 05:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rituals generally relate to God, brotherhood, and unity. Can't go into detail due to the fact we swear an oath not to dispel the secrets of the craft. 

Charity for various causes. One of the main one is the Shriners, who are a part of Freemasonry. They do hospices for youth. 
My own lodge ran a summer camp for girls. 

Also, /r/freemasonry exists :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 03:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freemason here. 

We are a fraternity of men who do charity work, preform rituals, and try to better ourselves as men. Not much else to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 17:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like they have chances to me:

https://www.google.com/maps/d/viewer?mid=zYw5SbHYVKBM.kLaJN-znQs40

Any thoughts on the map?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 09:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm nearing the end, and it's been okay so far. There are some great scenes, and a few sluggish parts. The thing about the book is that it's a micro-view of a larger event by zooming in on a single town and a few characters while the whole country fights off a disease. Similar concept to *The Leftovers* if you're familiar with that.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 08:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference is what the defiance does, and what it stands for. It's one thing to trash the HQ of the IRS, FBI, the local police station or whatever, and it's another thing go looting Macy's and your local liquor store. 

If these rioters were choosing meaningful targets, and not their local community, then we'd be having a different dialogue. Look at the LA riots and what that accomplished; it's the same thing here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bela Fleck   Abigail Washburn - Railroad [Bluegrass] (2014) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 06:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 03:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **The Executioner's Song, by Norman Mailer**

Having just moved to Utah, I'm excited to dive into this, especially concidering Utah's recent legal rulings on allowing death by firing squad for capital punishment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 22:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seconded. I had a polisci teacher who started off the class by mentioniung his political biases (he was a Marxist), and kept that known throughout class by mentioning it on occassion. All teachers should do this when it comes to politics/econ, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 02:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that I'm not preached to, am considered an equal, and need to not follow any doctrine but the ones I personally subscribe to.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 16:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I was trying to explain the argument since the other user said they didn't understand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 16:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is also a factor in your confusion (different understanding of word usage), but I think I made their argument clear. I was just trying to explain what they were saying, since you said you don't understand (not that I blame you, it can be a hard concept to grasp). 

If anything isn't understandable, let me know. I don't really have a horse in this race, but I do think the other user's argument deserves to be made clearly to those who don't get it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 08:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think their point is that the distinction between the two words can look off. In nearly all else in the world, you wouldn't call someone moving into another land a settler, as you'd rather refer to them as an immigrant. Even in other places of illegal or perhaps "wrongful" movement of persons the word settler still isn't really used. For example, Mexicans crossing over the American border illegally aren't called settlers, but rather illegal immigrants, or aliens. Using the term settler in that case would feel a bit odd (or might not, depending on where you learned English). 

I think it really depends on how you view the connotation of the word, hence your confusion as to what they mean, and their different definition.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 06:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have iOS, try BookBuddy. Holds a limited number of books for free, and once you get past a certain number (one hundred, I think), you have to get the paid version.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 05:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Massachusetts: We have funny accents sometimes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 04:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the offer legit? I'd be willing to take it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 19:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One hour train ride to work with headphones, a drink of coffee, and a scenic route of Utah's beauty. This is my habit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 18:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seconded. One of the most well written books I have ever read.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 05:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of my blind friend I recently met. We were crossing the parking lot to get to my car and had to walk over some rocks to get there. I walked across no issue, and my friend, upon feeling the rocks with his cane, giggled in excitement. He had a blast climbing over them (I didn't care enough to help, feeling confident in his abilities) saying most people wouldn't let him do such a thing due to fear of him hurting himself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 20:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Shop of the Lin Family* by Mao Dun. Taught me everything I needed to know about revolutions, capitalism, and China, all in less than sixty pages.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 18:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's a minister?

(#)NoReligiousAuthority 

(#)Quakers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 08:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Browsing the book store is where I get my fix. If something catches my I, I'll gloss over it and buy it. I might look up reviews quickly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 08:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a similar sign over by the CenturyLink building. I'd take the job...if there was a contact listing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 04:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Into the Wild. Really did a number on me as a teenager.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 02:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll get back to you in a month, ha! How long did it take you to finish? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the Executioner's Song by Norman Mailer worth it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 01:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently picked up the book for cheap, but boy is it long. Is it worth the journey? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 20:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **The Last Town On Earth, by Thomas Mullen** 

Very interesting take on the 1918 epidemic we seem to forget ever happened. Heavy socialist/pacifist themes abound.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 07:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gardening groups and language classes could be fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 04:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take your favorite political book and condense it's ideas down to your speech (while also adding your own take).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 03:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does that happen? I was thinking of In Cold Blood! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 03:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 02:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went to LDS services with my roommates. It was a little uncomfortable, but still somewhat enjoyable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 02:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two guys kill a whole family, rocking a quiet, small town.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 00:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it similar in style to Tina Fey's *Bossypants* (assuming you've read that as well)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 00:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Of Mice and Men* or *Cannery Row*, both by Steinbeck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 00:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Fall - Camus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 09:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had no idea about this! Thank you for the suggestion! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 06:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, must be a state by state thing. There are records of blank ballots for my home state Massachusetts.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Want] Any Library of America collections of any author </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 06:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello all,

I'm after any Library of America collection editions of any authors. Preferably, I'm after Philip K Dick or Ralph Waldo Emerson, but I'm open to any authors. I absolutely love how LOA organizes several stories/writings/books into one, and highly enjoy how they look on my bookshelf.

Willing to buy outright or trade from my limited collection.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 01:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best Coast is absolutely necessary for a good summer. Their music is perfect for sunny days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 01:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I joined for the same reasons. Have since switched denominations, but I sympathize heavily with that view. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 00:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might not make it to the press, but the amount of votes any candidate gets is public record (in the US) including blank ballots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 20:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, and I've run for office before. Your vote sends a message when you vote outside of major parties.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 20:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seconded. I'm between SLC and Provo and haven't had an issue.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 19:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of customers use it for very basic things like email, and only email. You'd be surprised. We want to make sure that you're getting a higher speed for good reasons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 19:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My best bet is they were trying to gauge whether you use things that require a lot of data usage (Netflix, downloading games, etc.). That is pretty funny though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 19:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm paid bi-weekly, and donate a small amount to my meeting, when feasible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 17:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In short, the owner of /r/LDS wasn't happy and didn't like the direction the sub was heading in, so he closed the sub down. Thus, here we are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 17:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but I was just explaining why some people like him. He's a different type of thinker for a lot of people, which is his main appeal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 17:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His books are pretty different than from what else you might read today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 10:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watched *Nightcrawler* last night for the second time,this time with a more analytical mindset. It's a really strong critique of hyper capitalism and dog-eat-dog competition. There are so many specific points made if you watch for analogies. Any one else have any thoughts about the film?

Also, anyone know where I can buy an anarcho-pacifist flag? I've been looking, but only found one on Amazon, and it was really pricey. I could make my own but I'm not very good with my hands!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 08:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a prospective non-LDS BYU applicant, thanks for the write up. Extremely helpful in determining whether I apply or not :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 08:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have to understand that many former members have been hurt by the church, as when they leave their families and friends may leave them, and outcast them from their normal social circles. It's hard to win back hearts which have been so damaged by loved ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 08:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found this place via either /r/mormon or /r/exmormon maybe two years ago, can't remember which </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 21:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love being called "Young Man" by them. Just warms my heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 21:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My company does the same thing. We choose the "closed" option when we step away for a second (as oppsed to "open", which lets us recieve calls). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 02:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could it not be argued that selecting the Bible is not endorsing any particular established religion, since Christianity is so general? As in, they're favoring a broad category, rather than something like Catholicism or Methodism. 

That's the only argument I can see being made in state court, if this law goes there.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 20:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the write up. I agree conservatives are a little out of touch. They have many solid good points, but how they go about sharing them often goes insensitive. 

Here's a video on combing social justice (in regards to poverty) with conservatism: http://youtube.com/watch?v=OPOnzzB3OZs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 18:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do people think of "Shooting An Elephant"? It's probably one of my favorite essays I've ever read, as it describes the problems of colonialsm very well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 18:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just an FYI, tithing is not related to getting any sort of position inside the LDS church, since all members pay an equal amount (10% of income). Unless you're referring to something I'm not aware of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 06:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if I don't know squat, and have never coded before, but am willing to commit, would I be a good student? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 23:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always miss the Lindsy Stirling sales :(

Thanks, though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 07:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure how it would be drafted, or if it would be even feasible, but I'd like to see the allowance of citizens to avoid paying taxes towards war, if they object to said action.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 07:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As already said, the DMZ is heavily guarded. Very few who escape NK do so through the DMZ, due to risk of mines and being shot. The Chinese border, though still guarded, is relatively more easier to escape through, this why it is the border many choose to flee over (and Chinese guards can be bribed).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 04:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Though I've only just started my job, I know that if it was not for my amazing coworkers, I'd be having all the same problems as everyone else has written. Plus, the view of the mountains from my desk helps make me feel relaxed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 23:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessarily. Many more democratic countries have multi-party states, rather than only two parties: http://i.imgur.com/gCutY.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 09:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the pictures and AMA; I learned a lot from your experience. 

You mention the medical students asked you about Beyonce. How up to date did they seem on outside culture, like music, TV, and movies? I'm surprised they even knew about her - as far as I understand, imports of outside media are forbidden. 

Secondly, you mention you talked with the pastor of the church you visited, while noting the oddity of the churches attendees (all older women). Did the pastor seem knowledgeable on scripture? Did he seem real, as opposed to being an actor?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 08:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You never know. I'll have a heated conversation with someone, only to realize they were right a few days later. We often don't admit we're wrong in the heat of the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 03:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "In an attempt to even the playing field, privacy activists have turned the tables on the surveillance industry keeping tabs on everyone else." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet the privacy activists who spy on the surveillance industry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 03:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 03:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's /r/geopolitics for news updates on American foreign policy (though not all links are related to the US).

They have a list of good sources over on their sidebar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 03:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sort of is. Some meetings will bring something to either provoke thought or discussion. You don't have to speak or think about the topic if you so choose, it's generally up to you. However, this all varies meeting by meeting and how they handle things.

After the prompt was shared, no one else spoke for the next two hours of meeting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
