<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5096</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 11:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> from an economic standpoint, in a world without countries the currency would be the same. so we would be better able to help the sick the sick and poor right? 

thank you obliging my stupid mind. i would love to have a discussion about this but i'm pretty drunk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 10:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you think that dogs have dreams when they sleep? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 10:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nothing that communistic. i was just thinking of either

1. countries without borders: which might make the rich richer and the poor poorer but would help the desperate. 

2. a unified world: which has the potential for disaster or peace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 10:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do dogs dream? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 10:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't know but if the love of my life looks through my stuff she will see people like me and will contact me and we will meet and then she will be grossed out but not before i smell her and take some of her hair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 10:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i just delete my posts that get bad karma. except the ones i think are funny even if no one else does </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> would the world be better off without borders or countries? what would be the most humane way to do this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 10:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> without borders everyone could be happy but there's a chance that everyone could be sad. with borders some people are happy and some are sad and the happy people want to separate themselves from the sad people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 10:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how does this affect me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 07:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i liked the story. don't worry about about knives it'll be ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 07:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awesome! my mom works for the IRS and we're going to the movies tomorrow now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (request) i want an anime with with lots awesome action and not much filler please. maybe something like the second season of full metal panic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 09:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 07:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's been awhile but i think i just didn't like their design. it reminded me of that old game Space Invaders  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 05:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mainly i didn't like the new enemy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 03:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i keep thinking about gurran lagann because i dropped it after it jumped ahead in time. i wonder how it ends, but i don't really want to watch it anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 01:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i can't believe i'm the only one wondering why they don't just clean the bathrooms and kitchens? are all of them just waiting for someone else to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 04:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't like it when that woman talks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 02:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i can't get food stamps because my parents claim me as a dependant, but don't feed me enough. where's my government assistance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 01:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darker than Black maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-21 01:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> more like BUTTom lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-14 23:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no its not. try it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-14 22:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> evan williams   sriracha sauce. thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> try putting a little sriracha sauce or any chili sauce in your beer and let me know what you think. i'm liking it a lot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-14 22:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its good in whiskey too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 11:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you just told two girls (who i assume are friends because you have liked both for 3 years) that you like them both? fuck man. please keep updating this journal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 01:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there should be Underground Olympics. 

stealing - it can be an art and if you get caught, it can also be exercise. put the athletes in any store with any security measures and judge them on how cleanly they get away and what they steal. 

assassination - give the athletes a target and paintball guns

graffiti - judge on the art and the lengths it took to tag that shit

cop chases - think ghost rider  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 20:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> last night i was swinging a chair around because i heard that that badass ancient warriors worked out by swinging a heavy mace around. the chair broke but luckily nothing else did </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 20:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> go rob a church. unless you believe in god. then don't do that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 19:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when you truly don't give a fuck you would say "i would fuck buffy the vampire so hard she pees" instead of "i don't give a fuck" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 16:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP Mexico City council </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-04 18:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I always carry hot sauce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 18:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aren't you a little young and skinny for a bike like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 05:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think the scooby doo shapes taste better than plain old noodle shapes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 23:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe i'm a lightweight but it would take me over a week to drink all that icewater </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 21:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i just wanted tissues
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 00:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm looking at KLR650's as my first bike... what's this doohickey mod?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-25 05:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm in the same boat as you OP. i actually fit your description too. i've been looking at KLR 650s and DR650s so far. they seem to be pretty cheap and durable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 21:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what's farkle mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 04:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what's a valve? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 10:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats a good one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 05:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you for this, helps a lot. money is my main concern so i think i'm getting a KLR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 05:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i would like a DRZ more but it's a lot more expensive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 05:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm missing something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> i can't decide between a klr650 and a drz400sm for my first bike. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 03:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> which is better for a 6 foot 3 tall person? 

which is easier for a beginner to ride? 

which is more durable/long lasting? needs less maintenance?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 03:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why flatten the tires? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> About how much would it cost to make a dirt bike street legal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 05:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 04:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how did the photographer get in the stall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 12:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wheelie  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 11:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Which one were you talking about though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 19:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what's the difference between a dual sport and supermoto? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 15:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i loaned $500 to a "friend" and now she's ignoring my calls and texts except for when i call from a different phone, then she hangs up. i have no way to get the money back because she moved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 07:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but now what are they going to rape? oh yeahh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 04:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 18:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i took speech therapy for about 3-4 years (elementary and middle school) and that only made my problem and anxiety worse because it was always on my mind. and that was when my parents paid for it, i can't afford it now anyways </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 18:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but then i would have to piss ten times before i get a buzz going </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 16:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i won't remember. but thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 16:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm friends with most of the cashiers and they don't check my ID. i'll bring it up next time i go in but i don't want to cost anyone their job even if he was a dick. fucking effort went into this grammar. hope you appreciate all my spellchecks haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having a speech impediment sucks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 15:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never been able to pronounce the letter R. Speech therapy didn't help so i'm stuck with it and with my stutter, and i've always been pretty embarrassed about it so i don't talk much. I just got off work, i work overnights (9pm to 6am) and went to go buy a couple steel reserves at one of my usual stores. Some new guy was working and after the pleasantries and he took my ID, he said he wouldn't sell me the beer because i'm slurring my words. i told him that i have a speech impediment and i can't pronounce the letter R, and that i just got off work so i can't be drunk yet. then he changed his mind and started ringing me up again, but i couldn't help myself and muttered something like "this is fucking nuts." he asked what i said so i said it again, and then he changed his mind again and wouldn't ring me up. 

i had to go across town to get my beer and am drinking pretty heavily now. i only wanted a couple beers but now i'm getting shitfaced because i don't want to face that i'm always going to sound like a fucking cartoon character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 04:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just curious, what would be a good price for it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-04 13:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want that bike for my first bike too but craigslist isn't helping me out. Where did you get it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 06:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks, that clears things up. i'm thinking a supermoto would be a better first bike then. but which would be better suited for a really tall person? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what's the difference between a supermoto and a dual sport? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 06:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 04:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> didnt mean to sound like a dick my bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 04:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if it's the one off of the highway by Outback steakhouse then make your employees wear some fucking hair nets. shits disgusting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 04:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm confused. you talk about having money problems but you have a shrink. doesn't make sense man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 02:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i work overnight shifts and so i usually buy most my alcohol around 6 or 7am. i always get weird looks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 00:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what are the main things to look at when buying my first (used) bike? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-22 00:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what does the MSF course consist of? i'm looking to take it sometime next month and don't want to go in with no information beforehand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 18:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm glad those people weren't redditors or they would have kidnapped the fox cub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 17:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> new rider here, is there an exact speed that i should from counter-steering to steering normally? i mean if i'm certain to crash, should i steer normally or counter-steer at.. 11, 12, 13mph? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 15:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i got to watch the finale for the time twice because i was blackout drunk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> can someone please explain countersteering to someone who has never ridden? i don't doubt it, but just have questions in the comments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 16:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> at what speed to you go from steering normally to counter steering? i mean if i was lane splitting at 10mph and can't make any mistake, should i steer normally to get into a lane or counter steer? 20mph? 

i assume counter steering at higher speeds comes naturally once i take my test, so i guess that's my only question. but i'm still curious of the balance between counter steering and leaning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 16:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i want a tortoise so he can play peek a boo with my cat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 16:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> egg cartons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
