<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7329</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 18:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am just starting to watch the episode.  I find it weird that girl is addicted to gabapentin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 18:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have hardware and other gnarly looking mri's. Pm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 00:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are they giving out free opiate based drugs at this super bowl??  if so, yes, yes I am very fucking interested in this bowl that is super. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 03:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> stop taking them immediately and send the rest to me for further evaluation
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 03:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must purchase one of these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 02:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah you're right about the driving around part haha just did that today with a pound of weed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 20:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> never used SR or any of them. Probably never will. Seems way too sketchy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 19:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok thanks for the info. and i have been in the same boat as you more or less with anxiety/depression issues my whole life most likely so I know that any pill is no cure all to anything. i am still waiting for them to approve fucking opiates for depression!! not gonna happen but still can wish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 18:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha i'll accept that as a viable answer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 18:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh ok.  I was prescribed it in hope of getting something more like xanax.  I have been on Paxil for 12 years now and have a history of depression anxiety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 18:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep exactly what happened for a bit. not too long tho and it was when i was dozing off sleeping so i thought maybe it was happening naturally since that is when people tend to jerk around.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone here use the new SilkRoad?? Link inside. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 18:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 17:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so it's like Jesus is putting his arm in place of dude's?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 17:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy shit!! 50 is supposed to knock most people on their ass.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 17:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok that kinda started to happen to me when i was falling asleep now that you mentoin it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 01:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have taken 100mg on top of several norcos. Nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 01:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have taken 100mg on top of several norcos. Nothing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 22:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy birthday.  nod it out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seroquel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 22:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've seen a few posts here and there about seroquel and taking it with opiates but never really got much from those threads.  I guess basically the seroquel intensifies the nodding effects.  Curious because today i was prescribed seroquel and took 100mg and so far not much!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 18:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has been discussed many times but i'll chirp in again haha.  I don't know, have a job i guess??  When I have no cash flow i do recycling and coinstair.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 18:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i'm curious about those grainy looking pills too haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 21:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep it sucks. next time around on subs (I have access to real opiates at the moment) i am going to probably quarter what i was started on.  I don't know why bupe doctors heavily overprescribe the stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 19:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually my story is just an example of how this shit can backfire in your face.  i thought that since my doc was referring me to a pain specialist i'd be taken care of right??  well the exact opposite happened. Yes they will or at least should pee test you but if you are on narcotics already you should pee positive for them and that is completely fine.  They want to make sure you are actually taking the medicine that they prescribe to you.  but yeah hopefully what happened to me doesnt to you-just a cautionary tale of when everything should be set in stone it gets all fucked up.  Murphy's law at it's finest.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 18:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have to say I was on about the exact same dosage as you and put on 8mg twice a day.  It worked yes but in the end jacked up my tolerance immensly so that when i went back to use i had to take way more to feel the same effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 18:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you feel up to reading my post from a few months ago here is my 1st (and worst) experience with a pain management program.  This is how it should not go!!  http://www.reddit.com/r/opiates/comments/1pzawa/doctor_question/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 19:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 22:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok. i've never done any drugs other than weed so the freebase part i don't follow but its all good.  so the other day my homie got a small amount of tar for $50. i looked at it. seemed a bit bigger than say a nickel. i thought it was just so small but now that you told me only a match head size you can smoke to get 3 hits off of it makes more sense now.
thanks for the info!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 19:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok also i want to ask you some questions. I have only ever done pharms: norco, oxy, etc.  I just usually pop them but I have foiled some roxi blues. How does the tar compare to smoking a roxi? do you do it off foil?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 19:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol how many norcos and kpins you working with?!?!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 01:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am in almost the same exact thing as you. norcos then started buying roxy to supplement.  i have to agree with everyone saying tolerance.  thats really all it is.  oxy is a bit stronger than hydro in comparison but not enough for me to notice.  tolerance sucks!! i hate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 00:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol the ninja opiate. didn't know that about fent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 18:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tramadol is so weak I am surprised you get anything from it. but that's actually good for you if you can still catch a buzz from it.  Why don't you tell your doctor you at least need something to replace the tramadol with.  If you get lucky he might give you something better but i'd stay away from saying names of meds like "I want Norco" or etc.  its not fair that he cut you off completely he should at least taper you.  I have been in very similar situations too.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 02:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $1 per milligram sounds about right!?!?  I am not positive though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 21:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nevermind sorry for asking a dumb question you already answered!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 20:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how many 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 22:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah ok haha
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 18:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mmmk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 21:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> let's party
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 21:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am just using trams for being able to sleep thru the night right now.  that and gabapentin help a lot.  I don't have a huge habit/tolerance.  I'd say about 120 mg hydro daily. but lately like the last month i can't sleep up until 8am without jerking all around and crawling outta my skin.  That sucks and I am now realizing shit is getting serious.  So anyways I got tramadol and gaba scripted to me and take them around 2am and they really do help me just sleep.  I am trying to keep my tolerance in check so yeah in that respect if you have em for maintenince and don't want to go crazy with your tolerance they do help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 20:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUCK YEAH!! and don't they suck when you wake up???!?!!! but this one was different. it wasnt completely lucid like i knew it was kinda a dream to begin with so when i woke up i was like wtf but not totally bummed haha.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 20:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL ok. i just never seen any asians dabbling in opiates like  I have never seen an IV user strung out on the streets. to me that's a picture of a white guy/girl.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 18:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol it was basically like how they sell "legal weed" synthetic stuff now. but this was claiming it was a certain % pure heroin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dream </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 18:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a pretty cool dream last night.  Basically I was looking through a magazine and they were advertising selling heroin.  Thing is somehow it was legal to sell because it was only 7.xx real heroin so they were able to find a loophole I guess haha. I think i remember it was sold and shipped from some little tiny country as well. Woke up like damn!! not real.  Anyways thought I would share that with everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 20:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK I have been using this lately for withdrawls in between my doses.  I am taking pills-oxy or hydro.  In the early morning I had been getting the classic symptoms-jerky body, restless legs, basically couldn't sleep and I did NOT want to waste my precious limited suppy of real opiates so I was able to procure a script from my doc. Took 2-3 around 2am and voila no more symptoms whatsoever. I can now get a great mornings sleep.  Other than that, the times I did take Trams they made me a bit nauseous but I was riding in a car and hadn't had much to eat.  As far as recreational value, if you have little to no opiate tolerance I bet they would be kinda cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 23:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol probably. opiates, at least to me seem like a white mans burden haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-29 00:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So are you looking for pills? if you now graduated to H would pills still do anything for you? I guess it depends on your habit and ROA?? I haven't gone the H route yet so I am not sure.  Anyways I live near a big college town and pills are pretty hit and miss but then again I am 10 years above your average freshman college goer so I don't really run with that crowd.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 21:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading the last paragraph oh this really sums it up for a lot of people on this sub i bet.  It at least hit home with me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 19:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the op 80s i have now i put in coke overnight so my tolerance is 1 a day of the op 80s and the buzz lasts me a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> blues vs op 80s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 04:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so i just had op 80s for the first time the other week. i like them.  paid $20 a piece for them.  i have a chance to get blue i think 30mg roxis for the same price.  is this a fair price and what is the difference between the 2 as far as the high is. i am bit confused as to why they are both the same price when one is an 80mg pill and the other is only 30.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 22:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oh8zcbC_Dcw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 19:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it was actually an oral surgeon!! haha you'd think he would know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 20:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol i got darvocet for my wisdom teeth and they were impacted meaning they had to cut out my gums to get to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 20:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dying of cancer and last leg of life shit basically.  doctors are getting to be assholes about scripting anything anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 20:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok i just drank the whole concotion yesterday and it seemed to work fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 19:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok last night i threw a whole 80 in a a shot glass of coke. this morning it's looking all gelly and i can still see the actual pill or carcasss of the pill. its all blown up like 3 times bigger than original.  just sip the mixture or what? haha i hope i didn't mess up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 22:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i did haha it worked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 20:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ok i just checked on it. its all gelled up but seems to be broken down. i am just scooping some out and eating it haha is that ok?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 20:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok i just checked on it. its all gelled up but seems to be broken down. i am just scooping some out and eating it haha is that ok? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 20:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol it's all good. thanks. lots of good info in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 22:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> will do. thanks everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 22:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly what im doing.  How long do you wait?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> bought these yesterday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 21:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know i'm probably beating a dead horse her but i've never had them before. my tolerance is up to 10 norcos in 24 hours. usually a bit less though.  i currently broke one in 1/2 and have it sitting in a shot glass of coke and they are floating around haha.  any other ideas? they are the op 80s incase it's hard to tell in the pic.  http://i43.tinypic.com/2s6mu50.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 02:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn that s a ton of pills but i recently go cut off as well. My script pales in comparison to yours but i can still understand the betrayment and downright fear you  feel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 21:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chico 530 help a n*gga out
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 02:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you been at the local dog park picking up the turds?!?! hahaha jk have fun!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 01:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-30 21:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anyone around chico? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-30 21:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are you yelling at me?? I don't understand I was just asking a question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-29 22:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what are in you in the hospital for?  you got a do it your self pump in your bed?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-29 20:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never heard of this ever in the states. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 20:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i was in a similiar situation before.  I thought it over then i decided not to do it since i'd be totally up shits creek with nothing if I got caught and i hear that pharmacies call the doctor back sometimes a lot nowadays. depends on on the pharmacy maybe.  you can do it but just weigh the pros/cons i guess of the situation haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 20:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha it didnt really do anything!! Gonna go with 100 mg today and see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 03:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ite. Just popped one 50mg tram a few minutes ago.  would try more but it's my 1st time so i'm being safe hah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 02:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok cool. Im not on subs right now but i might try a couple trams tonight when i get home.  Got the script yesterday and haven't touched it yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 23:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i usually do that with norco the empty stomach routine and never have had a problem with that. i also have a pill crusher and use that.  i started on subs recently as well but have a decent amount of norcos left so i was wondering what will work best haha.  Yeah the buzz from subs, not really a buzz but i'd call it like a dirtier version of a norco buzz.  It's not bad it gets me thru the day but i'd take norcos any day over subs.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 21:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also do you think that if i took these with norco it would help or hinder the norco buzz?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 21:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright thanks.  i have little round white pills that say an 527 i believe on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 04:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol dude!! exactly............ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 01:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aight. i will look into it though. since i am going to use anything before I have to go back onto subs which I assume will be the rest of my life.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 21:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i'd like to know too after being in my current situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 21:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok this is probably a no but is it possible to take this with suboxone?  I am doubting it..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 21:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and also I am under Kaiser insurance.  if you haven't heard of Kaiser its like a network of hospitals and doctors all intertwined (is that a word?) haha but anyways i cannot simply just switch doctors under kaiser to get back on my meds cause any doctor under kaiser will see that fucking recommendation from the head of pain managment saying something like no more norco. so i'm fucked unless I change insurance and start all the way fucking over again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 20:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She reffered me to pain mgmt. Head guy there is anti meds and put a recommendation to my doc that my norco should be pulled.  funny thing is i thought i was moving up the ladder when being reffered.  I am now on suboxone which i did with my own money and no insurance since they fucked me over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 04:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> isnt that essentially a speedball?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 04:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok. i am on paxil as well. heard of any interactions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
