<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject770</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 07:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damnit, I was so afraid this was going to come after I saw the vid. First off, you didn't ruin shit, by the amount of flaming done by the opposite team, they deserve no less. Plus, it's bronze and you're climbing really fast, these people have basically a 0% chance to ever play with you again so for them, it's one game where they're either on the right or the wrong side.

And to be fair, I'm in gold and would love a game where I get stomped by someone of your level just to see where all my mistakes lie.. Seriously, keep it up, do whatever you feel like doing and fuck us, Reddit will always find a way to disagree! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 18:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it because he streams on azubu.tv now that his channel isn't being shown anymore on lolstreams? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 16:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll give that a try, thanks! However, I'm afraid that even when it dries out, it will still leave behind that sticky mess wich will destroy everything anyway, any tips for that? Btw, seems like it's only on the side with my battery, ventilator and USB ports, HDD, Ram and video card seem safe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need a new gaming laptop after M14x broke. (1600) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 15:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

I manged to spill half a glass of red vodka on my laptop the other night and it's basically dead now. It was an Alienware M14x with pretty decent allround stats, bought for 1600-ish. Now, I'm going to send it back to Dell and ask if they can fix it and if now, if they can just replace the broken parts or give me a discount if I buy the same one since there's probably parts in that that work just fine.

In case this doesn't work for whatever reason, I would like some suggestions for a new one, with about the same specs or better but perhaps for a cheaper price because I know Alienwares are expensive.

Stats I had now:
Windows 7 Home Edition
500GB 7,200 RPM SATA + 32GB mSATA Caching SSD 
8GB (2 X 4GB) Dual Channel DDR3 at 1600MHz
and a 6GB Nvidia card (forgot exactly wich one it was)

All suggestions are welcome! Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-05 16:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I main adc and can trade while farming pretty well now, however, due to always having a support by my side, my map awareness is not what it should be. I notice this especially when I play the occasional top or mid lane. More practice I guess! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 23:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is he a dick? He just put out a fire using a cat!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 19:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems so surreal when you try to imagine it happening to yourself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 16:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed 100%, someone should answer to this because it is in no way fair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 13:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget our beer! And some chocolate for dessert :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 12:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are these top comments getting deleted when they're telling the truth? Already seen multiple of these.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 08:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for giving such a detailed answer. I'm going to buy and download it now, will let you know in some time what I think of the game and wether it was worth it! I'm very interested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SIB: Test Drive Unlimited 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 00:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm looking for a (if possible) Steam  racing game. It has to have an open world and preferably a large collection of excisting supercars in wich you can cruise around. I don't really like racing other people or AI itself, just would love to just drive the cars. Bonus points is if's not needed to grind points/cash for hours before you get your first decent car.

I looked for a game like this and found TDU2. Is this the right game for me? Or other suggestions? Thanks alot!

Ps: I know it's weird to want a racing game without having to do alot of racing itself but I remember I just loved to drive in GTA with the faster cars. This is what I'm looking for now, only more realistic and perhaps less killing stuff :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-28 01:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *sigh* gifbin.. You have no idea how long it took to load on mobile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-27 23:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right in the feels indeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-27 12:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a second there I read r/spacedicks:beautiful pictures from space and tought you were trying to trick OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 20:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can delete your own post.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 19:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the internet and he is a stranger, why would he lie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 15:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Well played](http://i.imgur.com/IK4LCfg.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 02:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saving this for when I'm not on mobile, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 20:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I don't know who made the call to go back in or why bad that was a really big mistake that lost them the game in my eyes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-22 17:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe we killed it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-22 15:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Impressive 'OP fag' gif collection </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-22 00:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very nice, good job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 23:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn mobile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 18:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually laughed with this one, gj OP

EDIT:heh'ed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 17:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oracles/pinks banned aswell. Or is this too cruel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 15:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or it's a Nano Virus in wich case they start developing a cure the moment it's released. However, then the cure % would probably be higher then 1% at 2M infected </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 21:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can Ezreal's Q still crit at lvl1 with 1 crit chance mark or has this been patched? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-15 23:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was already wondering wich one would be the chosen thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-14 22:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Hmm, I can only see Olaf on the map. Oh..' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 23:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be scared aswell, creepy as fuck. Thanks OP [8] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 17:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Katarina: You learn that OP champs exist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 17:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wanted to say this, have an upvote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 00:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to watch that gif at 1 FPS the first time before seeing it normal, took me atleast 5 minutes. Fuck i.minus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 17:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen everything on /r/Gore, /r/MorbidReality, /r/Shatter etc, nothing makes me even twitch but for some reason that made my stomach turn a little, looks so gross </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Audi RS4 Ultimate Paintball Duel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 16:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 16:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Krepo talking to Alex after reporting](http://img197.imageshack.us/img197/593/alexich.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-23 18:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How come EG doesn't play on Day2 according to this scheduele? Or is that a mistake? 'Cause Db is on there twice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-23 17:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know what was worse, the actual video or his spelling. Doughter.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 22:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly what I tought of the first time I heard it!'Put a beat under this and it could be Macklemore telling a story! It's even his style and everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 21:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAE BROODWAR TERRAN MUSIC? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 20:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm well aware of this. Still, I wanted to do this, regarding of what the outcome might be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 20:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Redditor for 3 minutes. Err, got any proof it's you?:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apologies to my team. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 19:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 17:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly my tought aswell, especially ar parties, MDMA has given me way better nights then coke probably ever will </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-21 21:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not from the US and I don't understand 80% of the references to the commercials, anyone else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
