<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7720</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 07:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awesome when i clicked the tweet there was no pic still awesome though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> adam copeland possibly going to tna? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 06:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i dont know how to post a screen shot of his twitter but he said he was doing something with sting in june anyone have any info on this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> awesome ecw documentary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-31 03:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 05:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think the colors might be off lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 04:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> lets build a competitive junk mid-range standard  deck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 04:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i was figuring with a vote by the comunity as to what goes in  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Art With Salt - The Joker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 04:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 05:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> punk dissaperes into the earn comes back a month later claiming he has found a higher power, becomes a student of the undertaker, undertaker passes punk the dark powers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> response to the brad maddox math problem posted ealier in the whats the deal with brad maddox </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-15 16:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> just a thought... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-13 09:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what if... and bear with me here, what if wwe is doing the things it does with john cena to anger the iwc?   what if all the superman stuff is to make cena a meta heel, one that is specifically pushed to make a certain fan base angry,  he is over with casual wrestlers yes but that was probably the plan all along, get over with the casual and do what ever you can to anger the smarks... eh just a thought </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Undertaker vows to wrestle at all WWE events within walking distance of his house </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 21:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 00:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i really want to do commissions because it seems more fun than just drawing them and keeping them around lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
