<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5469</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 17:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a new defense called *The Firing Squad* defense. 

If you have 13 people shooting at someone - make sure the other 12 get off on lesser charges (or no charges) and throw the book at the 13th (to calm the mob). 

Then when the 13th person goes to trial the prosecutor can shrug and say 'We don't know beyond reasonable doubt if *this* guys bullet is the one that killed the victim".

So make sure if you ever go to commit murder to bring at least 12 friends along. Apparently in America it's a "Get out of Jail Free' card now, seeing as it is enshrined in precedence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 17:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stated:

 If you think that running from the police should automatically mean a public execution, on the spot, maybe you are in the wrong country.

The Bill of Rights, state laws and the oaths that police officers take do not hinge on personal opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 17:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New York City alone has belched up half a billion dollars since 2009, to settle [police brutality civil suits out of court.](http://www.thenation.com/blog/204425/police-story-unravels-how-did-nypd-break-nba-players-leg?_ga=1.150872820.338813853.1432479337)


I bet if that money were coming out of FOP retirement funds, things would change in a hot minute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 16:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the job is too mentally stressful for them to abide by the Oath that they took upon getting the job, then it's time to quit and get some mental health care.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 16:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Look at the comments. Submit or die.

And you are just going to accept 'submit or die' as the way things are in the US now? Why don't all of these 'commenters' just go have a good old fashioned Constitution burning party? Then they can lay down in the street and show everyone their big, fat yellow bellies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 16:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what they were thinking before they were turned into target practice. I have never been black. 

They didn't have any drugs or weapons in the car and they weren't wanted, so logic tells me that they were in fear for their lives.

If you think that running from the police should automatically mean a public execution, on the spot, maybe you are in the wrong country.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 16:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I'm too old to bother about being yelled at on reddit. I just want young people to wake up to a few things, or they are going to have a really bad time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 16:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never heard of 'roid rage'? Seriously. 

Of growing concern to physicians and psychologists is the mounting evidence that anabolic /androgenic steroids cause severe and sometimes permanent mental disorders. The addictive nature of steroids often leads users to administer progressively higher doses and more exotic combinations of the drugs to maintain and increase the initial muscle building effects.

***Abundant clinical and anecdotal evidence suggests that steroids often lead to unusually aggressive and irrational behavior.***

And using steroids isn't a problem for a guy who straps on a gun every day and goes out to deal with the public?

Just using a little common sense here.

http://www.afpafitness.com/research-articles/anabolic-steroids-and-the-depression-connection </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 16:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wondering where all this water is coming from? 

Short vid from a 2012 Rutgers study: https://youtu.be/gAiA-_iQjdU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oklahoma Flooding, Evacuation, Weather news - updated on this page regularly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 16:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 16:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Jet Stream has shifted - finally. Have you seen this? 

https://youtu.be/gAiA-_iQjdU

It is the very best explanation of 'weather weirding' that we have seen lately.

I first found her study when i noticed the Jet Stream doing very anomalous things in 2013. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oklahoma, Stay Home. Massive flooding, closed highways, 70 flood rescues in an hour and multiple tornado warnings ongoing- touchdowns all day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 02:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 21:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that is why this web group is collating officer involved civilian deaths by collecting media stories. Right now that is the only way to get a real number.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 21:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the car backfired, the plainclothes reported that it was a gunshot. That brought in the Rambos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 20:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The really sickening thing about this case is this. I have relatives in medicine- one is a coroner. He has autopsied 2 'hero' police officers killed in the line of duty. Both of them had cocaine in their systems. One exhibited long term steroid use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 19:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot a 0.

By the narrowest measure possible  in which we give police every benefit of the cause of death doubt in incidents where they Tasered or restrained suspects  85 percent of the sampled incidents were the sort of police killings the government might be expected to keep track of. If we include other arrest-related deaths (and theyre included in Bureau of Justice figures), then 93 percent of incidents qualified as police killings.

Applying these percentages to the total count at Killed By Police would imply that officers acting in the line of duty have killed in the neighborhood of 1,250 to 1,350 people since May 1, 2013. Thats about 1,000 deaths per year.

http://fivethirtyeight.com/datalab/another-much-higher-count-of-police-homicides/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 19:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 113?


Applying these percentages to the total count at Killed By Police would imply that officers acting in the line of duty have killed in the neighborhood of 1,250 to 1,350 people since May 1, 2013. Thats about 1,000 deaths per year.

http://fivethirtyeight.com/datalab/another-much-higher-count-of-police-homicides/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 19:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is *exactly* like saying "it's ok". It sets court precedent that automatically justifies future shootings, chokings, beatings, etc by the police.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 19:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing that everyone seems to overlook here. Every single one of these cases in which a cop is found not guilty of killing a civilian stacks the deck on precedence in a court of law. 

If this keeps up, police will be able to show justification in any court of law for killing anyone for any reason- due to precedence of prior case law. 

And it won't matter what color you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 19:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have one issue with the mannequin element. There were 5 shots to the womans head that was not on the mannequin for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 19:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> officer reported that was not the case and at 10:47 p.m. radioed: Passenger just put his hands out asking us to stop. He does not have a gun. He has black gloves on, the officer said, according to the transcript.

Theres a red pop can in his hand.

http://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/cleveland-police-officer-found-not-guilty-in-fatal-shooting-of-two-people/2015/05/23/280844f0-f028-11e4-a55f-38924fca94f9_story.html?tid=sm_tw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 19:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a plainclothes cop in an unmarked vehicle attempting to pull them over for not using a turn signal. That's what started them running. 

If some stranger in street clothes tried to get you to pull over, would you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 19:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Officer at 10:47 p.m. radioed: Passenger just put his hands out asking us to stop. He does not have a gun. He has black gloves on, the officer said, 

Theres a red pop can in his hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 09:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never been afraid. Only kind of irritated at times for having my sleep broken up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 09:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posted this yesterday to /r/StormComing. 

http://www.reddit.com/r/StormComing/comments/36ue17/salmonella_outbreak_linked_to_tuna_hits_san_diego/

Wish you had dropped by.

I post outbreaks or harmful events regularly for people to watch out for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 19:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok that's odd. I always feel like there is someone there by the side of the bed when I wake up. Sometimes it's been so powerful that I wake up in the middle of reaching for them. Then I look at the clock- 3am. Been happening off and on since I was little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 19:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any idea how many conservative politicians are  or claim Dominionism? Truly scary stuff. This is the kind of nightmare stuff that, at it's extreme, ends up with slavery, chattel laws, the criminalizing of atheism, scientist executions and witch burning being resurrected in a country.

http://www.publiceye.org/christian_right/dominionism.htm  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antarctic going from in balance to massive ice loss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean Al-Ciada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they have enough pics of your wifes/husbands/girlfriends/daughters/sons dicks, boobs, asses and vages to pay for at least 10000 black operations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I was looking for here. This is what happens to me. #wierdness.

11:11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well be careful fucking around with the time-space continuum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This guy](http://i.imgur.com/8UbS7Kk.jpg) knows what's up.

I just wonder what sort of Dino he descended from, [from this study.](http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2015/05/150512075417.htm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 17:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially fascinating in Joplin, Missouri and Sendai, Miyagi Prefecture, Japan: pre and post 2011. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 16:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom is getting older and I need to go see her and spend some time with her. I need to get my van fixed because I can't leave my animals behind. Every time I think I can get this done something else comes up that absolutely cannot be avoided. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you ever wake up at 3:00am, regularly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 12:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 12:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need to take care of the puppy- absolutely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Wants to Patent its Creepiest Idea Ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 07:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby Survives Colombia Landslide That Kills 12 Members of His Family </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 07:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Summer! Early Heat Wave to Bake Eastern U.S. Next Week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 07:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deaths from Heat Stroke in Isabela Philipines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 07:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flooding in 5 States, Southern Plains: Mandatory Evacuations Ordered, Power to Be Shut Off In Some Neighborhoods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 07:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Storm causes massive damage at Big Mineral Marina </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 07:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 07:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that you, Jake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anomalous event- Deadly (tropical) box jellyfish found in New Jersey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 07:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salmonella Outbreak Linked to Tuna Hits San Diego </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 07:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oil spill off Santa Barbara (we don't want windmills) now up to 105,000 gallons from earlier 'estimate' of 21,000. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 06:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 01:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pine nuts are the little seeds between the 'shells' on the pine cone. Take a fully dried but fresh pine cone (like just off the tree for a week or two) and hit it hard on something- they fly out. Pine nuts sell for about 12-15 bucks a lb around here.

Washoe   Paiute Indians [make pastes and flour out of it](http://travelnevada.com/sites/default/files/styles/rotator_detail/public/field/image/PineNuts_Paiute.jpg?itok=py4U05Og) and you can eat them raw like regular nuts. Delicious and very good for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 01:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a related note, my kitten can't hunt.

Obviously he CAN CATCH TREE BABIES. Of course he can hunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 00:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You see about the end of the Harry Potter segment the other band just leave like fuck this y'all can have it. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 00:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best damn band in the land. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 00:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should read The Breathing Method. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 00:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw it referenced last week. Something something Theon Grayjoy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 00:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh only once every.. hour or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 00:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Swallow your damn pill next time you insufferable brat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 00:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why old people look like hell. All the hugs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 19:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously the point of the matter isn't the deed, but the *justice* or *injustice* of the deed combined with viewers personal immersion with the character.

You are trying to shift the point of the matter to fit some pre-defined political stance.

People *did* go out of their minds at the Red Wedding - because of perceived injustice toward innocent people. 

People *didn't* go out of their minds with the golden crown scene, because the brother was a violent, stupid dick who sold his little sister to barbarians.

People *did* go out of their minds when Ned was beheaded, because it was unjust. 

People *didn't* go out of their minds when Ramsey (justly, give or take) tortured Theon, because Theon killed or had killed hundreds of innocent people who were nearly family, including 2 little boys.

Sansa? It wouldn't matter if she were raped or had her hand cut off or was flayed or poked in the eye with a pin. 

It wasn't the *details* of the act that mattered. It was the *unjust* violence against this wholly innocent girl who has been with viewers since the beginning- and who has already been through total hell. 

Capiche? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 14:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course we didn't. Point being that nature has managed to generate an exquisitely balanced series of symbiotic relationships within biological and geographical systems that functioned pretty damn well before humans came along. And will continue to do so long after we are gone- if we don't succeed in utterly wiping it out.

To imagine that nature 'needs' us to keep things straightened out is the height of arrogance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 14:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Santa Barbara did a study on coyotes killed because they had become urbanized  - autopsies to check their dietary habits. Out of 200 coyotes they found that 80% of their diet was rodents. Rats, wild rabbits, mice and shrews. The rest was mainly garbage. No cats. No dogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 13:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Coyotes only expanded to most of the United States relatively recently, and as a result of us killing off wolves. 

You just made my point. You kill off an apex predator- another will come along and fill its place. "Nature balancing itself out." And the prey animals, rodents to deer, will overpopulate until that occurs. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 13:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok I'll make this clearer.

Bob kills 100 people, including 2 little kids. He gets the death penalty. 

Everyone shrugs.

An innocent, 15 year old girl does nothing wrong. She gets the death penalty.

Everyone raises hell.

Obviously the point of the matter isn't the *death penalty*, but the *injustice*.

You are trying to shift the point of the matter to fit some pre-imagined political stance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 13:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not as useless as Florida.

edit: Source: I owned a home in Florida. I am allowed to express my opinion on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 13:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suggested he build a Gigafactory right in the middle of Texas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 13:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suggested he build a Gigafactory right in the middle of Texas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 06:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amendment my ass. I thought they were going for repeal?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 06:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, you really aren't that stupid are you? 

http://www.reddit.com/r/aSongOfMemesAndRage/comments/36km4d/s5e6_ramsay_is_just_confused/crg1i07 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 06:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sansa is a naive child who has been pretty much harmless her whole life. She lost her entire family in horrible ways and has been used as a pawn for 3 years.

The man Ramsey mutilated and tortured killed most of the people of Winterfell, men, women and children that he grew up with, including his teacher and weapons master - then had two innocent children killed and bodies burned to hang on the wall - in front of people who loved them (they didn't know they were farmers boys)

So of course peoples sympathies are with Sansa. Peoples sympathies are always with the innocent. Has nothing to do with sex. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 06:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have had 2 free roaming, spayed sister cats for 9 years living out west. Coyotes and bears coming into the yard regularly. Smart cats, no problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 06:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White knighting a whole state. A shitty state. Congrats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 06:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't need to ask whose dick they're sucking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 05:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Chinas ranks of engineers making drones, software, satellites, planes, ships, weapons and missiles. With 10 times the manufacturing power that we have.

China Is Building 42,000 Military Drones

http://nationalinterest.org/blog/the-buzz/china-building-42000-military-drones-should-america-worry-12856 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 05:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was March '09. The numbers continued to rise until nearly 2011. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 05:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Nature doesn't always balance itself out- what the hell happened before these oh-so-wise humans showed up?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 05:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an important point. People got to know each other. You couldn't server hop, no blended servers. To ninja or act like an asshole back in the old days would get you shunned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 05:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lived in a hay growing area in NV. One year the good ole boys had a 3 day coyote hunt. For 3 years afterwards they lost tons of hay to Jackrabbits.

Coyotes are native to every state in the US. Best to leave shit the hell alone. It will balance itself out. That's what nature does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 21:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw what someone else posted to the wow forum and it was right on. http://us.battle.net/wow/en/forum/topic/17346427864

 I would flawlessly recreate the Vanilla servers. The only elements of new content I would add is reforging and transmogging. Besides these, this game would follow the original game, right through WotLK. No LFR or LFD. No player/server phasing. Recreating the sense of community is a goal here.
 
 Other content that was hinted at, but not followed through with, would be added; like the Emerald Dream. This would extend the time frame of events and add new content within the old framework. 
 
 It would be available to all players for a one time fee of $10, same for returning players. And I can guarantee there will be returning players, millions of them. So many would come just to see the Emerald Dream fulfilled.
 
 Upon log-in players would have the normal choices of servers and characters- but with an added choice upon making a new character- in Vanilla. This would be the fork in the road that players who paid the $10 fee could choose.
 
 This would not eliminate the new game, it would still be available for ez mode players. 

This would make me so goddam happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 21:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this yesterday and posted it to reddit.  I would immediately drop $10 make a new toon on this and never look back.

http://us.battle.net/wow/en/forum/topic/17346427864 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 21:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blackrock chain running- actually sparked my fear of heights. I would hold my breath all the way.

I just realized how badly lfr/lfg impacts immersion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 21:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These weren't created when we started. It was full on guild run to the dungeon. Damn those were fun times- killing shit along the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 21:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed [this chart of subscriber stats](http://www.statista.com/statistics/276601/number-of-world-of-warcraft-subscribers-by-quarter/) just yesterday and noticed that the downward turn started in '10. Right about the time lfr/lfg started.
I wondered about a connection, seeing as lfr lfg had such a huge impact on player experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 21:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved ST. Hate what they did to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 21:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Traveling to get to the dungeon was the first half of the adventure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 21:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they were pretty much color coded shortly after release. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 21:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there such a thing as power leveling any more? You can sleepwalk through it and it happens so fast you barely see half of the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 20:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this even legal?

Not in Europe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 19:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Followed by "What Musak would be playing in the Elevator to Hell?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 19:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny story about LBJ.

A very good friend of my mothers was the (young, pretty) widow of a gentlemen who had been in French politics. She and her dead husbands brother were invited to a dinner party at a major hotel after a diplomatic meeting in France and LBJ and his retinue was there. Things got drunkenly boisterous and flirtatious as the evening went on and she eventually retired to her suite.

An hour later she answered a knock at her door and there stood LBJ, in a silk bathrobe with a bottle of champagne, a bouquet of flowers and a huge cigar- with two secret service men flanking him.

He said "Madame, your President has come to pay you a call."

And she let him in.

When he left in the wee hours the secret service men were still standing there outside of the room.

She said he "was not pretty, but he was very persuasive". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Early 40's through late 70's. They raised 4 children. They bought one home and then they had a large home built in the mid '50s on 10 acres. They took two week (or longer) vacations every year. They could have been the poster children for "The American Dream"

It had a strong union. I remember my grandfather going out the door to a strike with a lead-filled baseball bat. And he was white collar system designer.

My grandfather had briefly played for the Pittsburgh Steelers (back injury) and my grandmother was a Rosie the Riveter who got her degree between having babies.

They retired before NAFTA - after which the plant moved manufacturing overseas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "**The question is whether it would make them fear for their safety, or the safety of those around them..**

Making threats of physical violence against another redditor and/or redditors family and friends is pretty fucked up. 

In some situations, speech can even constitute a crime, such as in the case of criminal threats. [A criminal threat,](http://www.criminaldefenselawyer.com/crime-penalties/federal/criminal-threats.htm) sometimes known as the terrorist threat, malicious harassment, or by other terms, occurs when someone threatens to kill or physically harm someone else.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Sure people need electricians, etc. But who is going to design the systems in the first place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only reason we won WW2 was because of our massive and innovative manufacturing base. We needed a large number of educated people to design, innovate and create for those manufacturers. 

Now we cannot even make umbrellas. 

WW3 is not going to be won by ranks of baristas and we cannot maintain superpower status with herds of burger flippers.

The US produced large quantities of military equipment into late 1945, including nuclear weapons, and became one of the strongest, most technically advanced military forces in the world. In addition to out-producing the Axis, the Allies produced technological innovations including radar (instrumental in winning the Battle of Britain), sonar (improving their ability to sink U-boats), the atomic bomb (eliminated the need to invade Japan) and the proximity fuze. Five times as effective as contact or timed fuzes, the latter was devastating in naval use against Japanese aircraft and so effective against German ground troops that General George S. Patton said it "won the Battle of the Bulge for us."

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Military_production_during_World_War_II </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 16:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandparents worked for a major appliance manufacturer here in the states. They both had degrees and would not have had their positions without them. 

It's not that we have too many people with college degrees, we no longer have an innovative, massive manufacturing base to support them. This is what needs to change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 08:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know someone who works for them- this melt is exactly what they have been waiting and planning for so they can move in to drill.

Thing is, it's happening 4-6 years earlier than they had expected. Some of the people, upper mid-level, have a lot of concern. The guys at the top do not give a shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about the best Pranks Blizzard ever played?
 
Corrupted Blood Plague (actually a glitch- but funnier than hell, regardless). https://youtu.be/RxDvxKeLWlA 
We would actually go fight Hakkar just to port hunters back to main cities to spread this. 

DK Plague:
https://youtu.be/7DUzJklzJ0Y?t=13s

And the Zombie Plague (actually part of the scourge invasion):
https://youtu.be/zdT3Tert6DQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under a 14 yr old boys bed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the main ones was kiting dragons and mini bosses to main cities. 

Blizzard ended up tethering them. But the fun and excitement of doing it- or other people doing it and the spontaneous mini raids that would form to kill it were part of the excitement of 'whats going to happen today?' when you logged on. 

The last one I was able to kite was Shan Bu to the Emperors Step. Someone forgot to tether him or they thought it couldn't be done. He stayed there through the weekend until re-set. 

Album: http://imgur.com/a/4vqEV

The other prank, also removed, was snowballs. 

[This was hysterically funny.](http://i.imgur.com/eA2QeC0.jpg)

When they first made snowballs in the game the victim would flip over onto it's back. Everyone loved them. 

Also, as I discovered when my friends and I went to have a snowball fight on the SW/IF Tram, snowballs travelled at exactly the same speed as the tram. So the result was that once they got off the tram they would be hit by every snowball thrown at them during the ride. 

BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM - the target would be doing flips in the air, totally stun-locked.

So we would lurk around the station, wait till some poor, unsuspecting player got on, get on the last tram car and start pelting snowballs at them. I'm laughing right now thinking about it. They would fly through the air- same speed as the tram - and all catch up once the victim got off the tram.

Also we discovered that if you threw a snowball at a target at the *moment* they mounted a taxi bird, the snowballs would hit them as soon as they landed - anywhere. Took exquisite timing. Best was when you and a friend were going to taxi somewhere- let them mount while you pelt them. The cursing in pm when they landed .. freaking hilarious. 

And blizzard stopped it.. such a bummer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 18:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit you don't know what you are talking about.

'talking about'? I am looking at a graph that is basically in a constant state of plummet, besides a few bumps, since end of WotLK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 18:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, LFR and LFD were rolled out between 2009 (lfd) and 2011 (lfr) - about the time that blizz had 11-12 million subscribers. 

By Q2, 2012 they had dropped to 9 million subscribers. So that's pretty damn interesting. The only times it has come up above that number is briefly during expac releases before going down again.

Hell, maybe it did kill the game.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 18:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So basically it is losing a million subscribers a month. Unless they do something drastically imaginative, the game is dead by fall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 17:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the biggest rise of subscribers ever?

Do you have a link for this? I don't know of any 'rise'.  If it were different, you would not have stated this:

normal servers are already struggling.

I know of a lot of players who came back, hopeful, then left again.

Here's the numbers: https://youtu.be/8dOsT8x6iy8
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 17:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From your post of 6 days ago:

Yeah, but Lich King dropped a weapon for every spec and class. Therefore, all players had access to slightly higher item level weapons and no specific classes were left out. Same with Spine/Madness in Dragon Soul - between the two bosses, all classes had access to a weapon/trinket of the same ilevel to their peers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 17:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Normal servers are struggling to maintain a player base after losing millions of players due to WoD. This could refresh that player base. 

If you didn't like Vanilla, that's fine. You don't need to play it. A lot of people did and still do love it. I know a lot of old school players- all but two of us are on WotLK servers. As one of them put it "If Blizzard won't do it, someone will (and has)."

ps How did you get from Vanilla to WoD unless you played it through? If so- it obviously wasn't 'bad'. If you never played it- how would you know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 17:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank god people blinded by nostalgia can't decide what Blizzard does or doesnt do.

If you enjoy WoD, how would this impact your game? 

I think the post is brilliant. It takes nothing away from the current game, while giving a lot of people what they want. You have a personal problem with that?

I have watched players unsub for months now and know more old player friends who are now on WotLK rogue servers than in the official game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I were King (of World of Warcraft) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 16:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 05:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how you put that; 'chupacabra'. 

It was while studying the Jarrell that I first discovered Gravity Waves in relation to amping up storms. I have a fascination with resonant waves and effects so it is very interesting.

I had heard of Jarrell, but had not really studied it until during the 2011 outbreak one of the tornados took a 'backward' track and I went into research mode. I cannot recall which tornado that was now. 

Thank you for your info. I did not know the other tornados you mentioned were also linked to gravity waves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 05:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except for the Republican crabs, who all sit around and chant 'DOWN WITH SOCIALISM!' as they slowly strangulate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 04:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unbelievable that we have gotten to the point of nearly killing off our prime pollinator. Sometimes I feel like I have stepped into a different dimension. A bad one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 04:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Ohio my mother was married to a top end blacksmith. He did ortho horse shoeing with a veterinarian. He had an aussie named Sassy and Sassy would sit on a stool in front of the horses, literally calming them to the point that they looked hypnotized. 

 This was good because he would have to work on them for longer than standard shoeing would take. 

Very smart dogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 04:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ..potential to be really, really bad had there been any sort of population center in the way.

Like Philadelphia, MS.

I am very sorry to hear about your illness. I hope you get through it quickly and come out the other side better than ever. When you are feeling up to finishing your posts, I'll be here if you want to chat. Meanwhile, lovely to meet you and welcome to StormComing :) Message me any time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 03:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this information. I will look into this event, it seems extraordinary. 

I have had a serious love/hate relationship with tornados since 1974. I was 14 and lived just outside of Xenia. 

I had just asked on /r/stormchaser if you were *the* stormstalker of the blog. I am so glad you are. I am a big fan of your blog. It's extremely well written. If you ever have any questions about Xenia,  I'm available. I remember it very well and possibly remember a few things that haven't been written about. Like the 're-planted tree' in a neighbors field.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 03:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you StormStalker from https://stormstalker.wordpress.com? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly more like the Mussolini style of Fascism. Where certain corporations ruled the government- and quietly kept competitors subdued. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pleases me and my druid, greatly :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it called when corporations have to get permission from the government to sell something? Let's see.. it's not capitalist.. must be a word for it.

Whatever it is- that's what we are now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone call Spielberg immediately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is [watching this](http://i2.kym-cdn.com/photos/images/original/000/676/205/57b.gif). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And reddit's the perfect location for this story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Besides, Japan hates those fascist bastards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 01:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> schooling
skooliNG/
noun
education or training received, especially at school.
"his parents paid for his schooling"
synonyms: education, teaching, tuition, instruction, tutoring, tutelage; 

In the late 18th century, Thomas Paine was amongst the earliest proponents of universal, free public education, which was considered to be a radical idea at the time.

Apparently, for some who want us to go back to those days of uneducated masses and slavery, it's still a radical idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 01:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course you know that a tornado can double back when its bottom is hit by outflow winds from a thunderstorm's core. In this case I believe it had to do with the massive gravity wave to the south east -that generated a strong pocket of localized shear as well. 

If I seem wrong on any of this, please correct me. I am always learning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 01:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's another option- trees or bushes ripped out of the ground, leaving holes. Pretty brilliant actually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 01:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Report to whom? The priest was a priest for a corrupt police dept.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 20:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I suppose we don't need all of this silly edumacation, seeing as it has done nothing for U.S. advancement in the world. Yep. Education, business development, scientific research leading to technology breakthroughs, maintaining a lead on other countries, etc. is all just something we should be cutting costs on.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 20:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you ever go up into Jarrell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 18:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen the video of the Philadelphia MS ground scouring? 

https://youtu.be/AcIqU6w-_04 

This was thought to be created by sub vortices within the main. 

I will revisit a map and images to see the orientation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 18:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They deserve the "college experience" right?

Actually our country deserves to have the brightest kids with the best education moving out into business creation and the workforce. Our former high levels of affordable education is what grew this country in the first place. As it fails- so does the country.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 18:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, apparently it was at 2mph when it hit Double Creek. I was thinking that possibly those divots were from surface removal - apparently they also had to remove top layers for recovery purposes in some areas. The clearly circular patterns, though, seem odd for this.

Also, the [gravity wave effect study](http://homepages.vvm.com/%7Ecurtis/Jarrell/Jarrell.htm) is fascinating in regards to 'backward motion' and the low shear, high CAPE of that day. I had just posted a story on /r/StormComing on this http://www.reddit.com/r/StormComing/comments/36azjw/the_incredible_jarrell_tx_tornado_probably_one_of/

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 18:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a possibility. I am going to scan more aerial tornado damage images to see if I can find anything similar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 18:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  no one (read: employers) in America will recognize your school.

And why would anyone want to go back to work in America?

Germany: The law requires a minimum of 20 paid days of vacation annually, but some companies give much more than that, sometimes as much as 30 paid days.

Paid sick leave is six weeks, during which you will continue to receive your full salary. After that time, health insurance pays 70% of your last salary until you either return to work or have to retire because of your health.

Mothers are allowed six weeks leave at full pay prior to the childs birth and eight weeks at full pay afterward. The mother or father is then allowed up to three years of unpaid leave to stay at home with the child.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 17:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We adopted 2 young sister cats - both preggers. They gave birth within 6 hours of each other. We had set up a long clothes closet for them to do this and have privacy- one cat at each end. Within a day one of the cats had moved to the other end with the sister and sisters kittens. 11 total. Thereafter it was just one big nursing cat/kitten pile. I don't even think they knew whose was whose after a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 06:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I was thinking the same- about the spacing and regularity. They just look very odd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 06:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know 4 'top tier' Americans currently studying abroad, and one more getting ready to go to Germany.. Americans studying abroad has become, once more, the thing. Mostly because of the high cost of native universities.

And once there - a lot of them decide they want to stay. One of my friends ended up with the Berlin Orchestra and married. Another is currently at Oxford, teaching.

Do you happen to have statistics of what you claimed? Europeans coming to American Universities in droves? And students from third world countries do not count. They are escaping a bad situation as much as anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick question about divots/circles on the ground- Jarrell, TX tornado </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 04:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have noticed in several ground 'after' pictures of the Jarrell TX May 27 - 1997 there are these odd round circles on the ground. I am familiar with cycloidal arcing, drag marks, etc. but don't recall seeing these before in tornado damage images until Jarrell. 

https://extremeplanet.files.wordpress.com/2012/06/jt-dc-1.png

Is it possible, since Jarrell was a multi-vortex, that these are touchdown 'suction' marks from small vortices within the larger body? They seem very tightly clustered. I just can't figure out what else they could be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 03:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok if american tax payers are so fucking tight fisted- the smart kids will go to other countries and they will benefit. 

http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/worldviews/wp/2014/10/29/7-countries-where-americans-can-study-at-universities-in-english-for-free-or-almost-free/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 03:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better than watching them go to other countries that will educate them for free. 

http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/worldviews/wp/2014/10/29/7-countries-where-americans-can-study-at-universities-in-english-for-free-or-almost-free/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 03:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The class capable of chipping in is a ten ton elephant at this point - and since it is the 'job creating' class it will benefit the most.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 03:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what? Fuck Chase Bank   Wells Fargo, fuck the brain drain they have created, fuck high college tuition rates. 

"...the German government fully funds the education of its citizens -- and even of foreigners."

"..Finland charges no tuition fees, and it offers a large number of university programs in English.

"French University programs charge only a small tuition fee of about 200 dollars for most programs (covers everything but off campus living situations).

"Norwegian universities do not charge tuition fees for international students. 

So fuck the banks and any kind of possible excuse you can come up with for them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 02:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> College finance loans were originally designed to be non-crippling- at 1-2% interest when I was in college.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 02:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank god maybe we can start catching up with the rest of the civilized world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The incredible Jarrell Tx. Tornado. Probably one of the most powerful tornados in the U.S.. May 27, 1997. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 00:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Jarrell Tornado has also been called the Dead Man Walking tornado from [this image.](http://lssn.us/image/JARREL~1.png)

By the time it passed through Jarrell, Tx. it had cleanly removed yards of asphalt from the road. Fragments of human victims were mixed with bits of formerly living livestock. Human chains of recovery personnel slowly moved across the landscape, combing through mud and debris for every trace of remains that could be retrieved for identification and burial.

The Jarrell tornado had another unique identifier, [it actually reversed course at one time- moving 'backward'.](http://homepages.vvm.com/~curtis/Jarrell/Jarrell.htm) 

In my years of experience in studying storms the Jarrell tornado is one of the most powerful, if not the most powerful, of tornados spawned in the United States.

Video clips: https://youtu.be/EQxhpcMc33I

StormStalker coverage site- an amazingly comprehensive site with images you won't find anywhere else in one place, including search and damage images as well as radar, atmospheric and synoptic information on this incredible tornado. 

https://stormstalker.wordpress.com/2012/11/23/jarrell/#more-249 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forty-foot wide sinkhole opens in Granbury, Texas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 23:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 22:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a very crafty bird right there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 22:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get too relieved. We had laying hens and I had a few that I raised from the egg. When I would come out and sit on the porch they would come running up and compete for lap room, just like small dogs. One would lay her head up on my chest for a cuddle. No food involved. Just feathery cuddles and low cooing noises. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 19:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did that with my Warcraft account 10 yrs ago. 

So this year they sent an ugly Orc statue to some poor asshole at a pizza place in downtown Detroit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 05:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been in Marketing for years. Most of those articles are written by men and at least half of them are gay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 04:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The camera is shaking like it is in an Earthquake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Following chase teams today live: Mod-High Tornado risk in OK - KS - TX - NB (links in text) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 19:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Live chase:

https://tvnweather.com/live

NOAA Meso Analysis Page:

http://www.spc.noaa.gov/exper/mesoanalysis/new/viewsector.php?sector=14#

Wunderground interactive map/radar/severe warnings:

http://www.wunderground.com/wundermap/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 17:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they were just waiting till Affirmative Action laws were overturned. Save on reprinting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 05:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew Lisa Levys family (She was one of Ted Bundy's victims at the Florida sorority house). Her father was of no certain religion, but very spiritual in nature. He wrote letters asking for life instead of the death penalty for Bundy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 05:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... and bought a dozen donuts and a gallon of milk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 05:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She blew him.. but he didn't give her the Coup de Nom? Even if she knew the phone was ringing...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 05:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course .. there would have been a *Juicy Couture* sign under it if it were for the prepubescent set. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 04:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And just how many porn sites do you cruise in a day? 

..and 'letting'? Is your wife/girlfriend like..12? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 04:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually laughed out loud
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Diego rainfall shatters May record </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 02:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who killed the young nun, Cathy Cesnik in 1969? Did she know too much? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 23:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This time, though, Maskell didn't bring Wehner home. He navigated his car past the Catholic hospital and industrial buildings that surrounded Keoughs campus and drove toward the outskirts of the city. Eventually, he stopped at a garbage dump, far from any homes or businesses. Maskell stepped out of the car, and the blonde, freckled teenager followed him across a vast expanse of dirt toward a dark green dumpster.
 
 It was then that she saw the body crumpled on the ground.
 
Story at:

http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2015/05/14/cesnik-nun-murder-maskell_n_7267532.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 18:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Socialism as in collective buying in order to streamline, save money and improve efficiency. Unlike the American Consumer model where everyone is expected to buy their own 'thing'.

Wealthy people and corporations practice this type of socialism on a daily basis. If you ever spent time in a wealthy neighborhood you will soon see that none of them own a lawnmower. They all use mower services. And most corporations have a fleet of cars that are used by mid-level management on up. 

It's only the lower classes who are discouraged from this by accusations of 'socialism'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 18:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another part that they missed- the part after they are 'raptured'.

The Apostles ask Jesus where they will all go and he answers:

 Where, Lord?" they asked Him. He said to them, "Where the corpse is, there also the vultures will be gathered." 

Luke 17:37 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 18:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should have left Saddam and his wood chipper the hell alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This kid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 16:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 15:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thing is, Saddam was a Secularist and a lot of the folks that were in his 'torture prisons' were hard core islamists who wanted Iraq to toe the line with the rest of the Islamic fundamentalist nations. Some of the IS that were captured had spent time there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 15:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in 25-50 years, they'll just say "Who could have known? The science wasn't in."

People are already [on to that one:](http://i.imgur.com/xNc31Or.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 15:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you think about it- if the GOP got every single wish fulfilled - the US would resemble Bangladesh in a few years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 15:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The U.S. Military is one of the most 'socialist' organizations on earth. No one seems to notice that part though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 15:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somehow they missed the last chapters:

The nations were angry, and your wrath has come. **The time has come** for judging the dead, and for rewarding your servants the prophets and your people who revere your name, both great and small-- and **for destroying those who destroy the earth."**

Rev. 11:18 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 15:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She looks incredible. T'would take a brave man to climb that tree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 15:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. Glad I only got sheep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 14:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My gynecologist, when I passed one and took it in to him. If I hadn't used a pad that night because of a particularly heavy, late period I would never have known. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 06:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feminists? Probably over 80% of the really nasty posters were men jumping on a bandwagon. I'm a feminist. That makes no sense at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 05:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You came in 'making claims'. So according to the rules, you first. I'll drop back in after I go have some wine and kill some orcs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 05:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they are dealing with this along with the Meningitis outbreak. . man, what a mess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 04:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It got cold as hell in the mountains today and started spitting snow.. brrr! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 04:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I have had a habit of growing my annuals from seed for a long time. Much more fun that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 04:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! I was right in the framing of that statement. You had me second guessing myself for a minute there. 

[Prey Animals](http://digital-desert.com/wildlife/prey.html)

The term prey refers to an animal that is sought, captured, and eaten by a predator. A predator is an animal that hunts and kills other animals for food in an act called predation. Smaller predators, such as mice and lizards can be, and often are, prey for larger predators. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 04:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High school debate?

...it says with big, innocent eyes. 

Give it up dude. Basic statistics already wrap all the things you tried to state into a big bullshit burrito and flush it into a cesspool of hyperbole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 04:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High School level debate team? Declarative statements based on fallacy and framed as questions are very overused, boring and blatant. Find a new trick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 03:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I detest the ultra conservative republican party- and I detest Fabian Socialists. Hilary is a Fabian. Just praying for a Bernie win. Or we are pretty much fucked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 03:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 60's through the 70's - greatest years in America.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 03:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To the point that I am ready to move to Italy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 03:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prey animals i.e.: predators prey on them. But maybe I got the .. nm. fml </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 21:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take it from a one time endurance rider: it's done all of the time, regularly, over rough terrain. Horses are prey animals who have developed great night vision.

http://www.aerc.org/ENApr10Ed.asp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 21:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. We just [keep on riding till we get to the cemetery.](https://youtu.be/FIXlNsNi32g?t=51s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 21:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I really do wish for a God to deal with assholes after death.. cause they sure don't seem to be dealt with here on earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 21:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I was wondering what was so NSFW about a tornado. Brazil just had one last week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 21:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are.. in Norway, Switzerland, Germany, Netherlands, UK etc.

Just not in the [U.S.](http://consumer.healthday.com/senior-citizen-information-31/senior-citizen-news-778/u-s-seniors-health-poorest-global-survey-shows-693917.html?lexp=true utm_expid=38353063-4.pIV1hUrQR8K_MJ1_OqjLag.1 utm_referrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.google.com%2F) 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 21:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got hooked on trains when I had to go to Chicago from San Fran. I had the time and something about it just seemed appealing. I figured if I didn't like it I would get off in a major city and hop a plane. 

I got a cute little sleeper (came with three great meals a day) and I loved every second of it. It was like a mini vacation and was almost the same price as flying. That decided me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 21:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a friend who lived near a private area used as a shooting/training range for the Michigan Militia.

If they started shooting before 6 am he used to aim his speakers out the upstairs window and blast the Barney Song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 21:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in a resort area and have to go to san fran regularly. I used to drive it- utter nightmare. Now I take a nice bus to the train, have breakfast on the train, catch up on emails, Skype, prep for meetings. Get off refreshed and ready to go. It's wonderful; and cheaper than supporting a car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 21:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mussolini, who is credited with creating fascism, often said that fascist governments should be "corporatist" regimes, essentially ones that were run entirely by companies and the elites of society.

Fred Koch, father of the Koch Bros helped Mussolini develop this style of Fascism. Then came back to the US to spread it here via the John Birch Society and, apparently, his sons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 20:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My idea of [glorious miles](http://www.iamtonyang.com/1208/concord_coach_bus_interior.jpg). Let someone else drive while [I kick](http://johnnyjet.wpengine.netdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/02/BobRavitzFloridaCarTrain20085.jpg) back, drink coffee ([or have a drink](http://images57.fotki.com/v1418/photos/2/211932/13400374/AMTRAKSPACIFICPARLOURCAR2-vi.jpg)), do emails, listen to music and watch movies. 

Got rid of my last car a few years ago and have saved around 6k a year ever since. Haven't regretted one moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Map Of How Far The Earthquake In Nepal Moved The Earth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 20:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 19:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not good.

 According to Ibach, the farm has been quarantined and the birds on the property will be killed. NDA will work with Nebraska Department of Environmental Quality to ensure proper disposal of dead birds. The likely method is burial at the site of the infection.
 
 In addition, facilities within about 6 miles will be quarantined and those within about 12 miles monitored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Nebraska Cases of Bird Flu Confirmed in Flock of 1.7 million chickens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 19:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scores of workers killed in Philippine factory fire- dozens still missing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 19:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Niger Meningitis Outbreak Worsens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 19:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MORE THAN 40 PERCENT OF BEE HIVES DIED IN PAST YEAR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 19:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sydney in Chaos with Power outage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 19:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 19:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The National Weather Service says a 9-inch rainfall over a three-hour period may happen only once every 500 years; meteorologist Melissa Huffman said Clear Lake received 11 inches over three hours Tuesday evening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
