<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4034</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 04:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll probably be picking that up soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To ease baseball fans through the long All-Star Break, I present an excerpt from Bernard Malamud's "The Natural" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 21:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 21:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is an epic western about the Texas frontier. It's a very dark cowboy and Indian story that spans about 100 years, similar to Marquez.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm reading The Son by Philipp Meyer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 21:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work in the book biz, so I saw dozens of reviews for this book when it came out. If I can help it I won't read a review before I read the book, so I basically ignored The Son until a few weeks ago, when I met Philipp Meyer and had a beer with him. I started reading the book the next day and, though I'm only a dozen chapters in, I know this will be one of my all time favorites. The writing is as close to perfect as I've seen in recent memory. Have you all read the book and what do you think? I'm afraid I'm just a fan of the man instead of the writing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What will be the greatest turnaround story in American history? This author says Detroit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 15:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 01:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a publicist, this is an awesome list that will add hours to my workload next week. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 01:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a book called Christian Nation that is all about if McCain won the election and died weeks later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 04:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a book publicist in NYC. My firm is a freelance consulting outfit so I have worked with virtually all publishers and about a dozen bestsellers every year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kim Stolz is doing an AMA right now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 21:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kim Stolz discusses some topics from her new book, Unfriending My Ex. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 19:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 07:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ready player one by Ernest cline  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 14:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're running the NYC marathon under the banner of the joe Torre safe at home fund. All the money we make goes to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 21:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The money we raise is headed here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gM-meqdHUw4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 21:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the book was inspiring. The whole time I was reading it I was thinking that I should really get out there and do something big. The specifics didn't matter so much to me as that feeling I got while reading it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friends and I are bearding it for charity. Daily selfies to track growth have commenced on Instagram. Feel free to follow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 19:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 14:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the fun in that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My 2 friends and I are growing beards to raise $$ for charity, and will be taking daily selfies for the next 5 months. Here's the first week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 22:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 01:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had a middle school gym teacher fired and jailed for being intimate with a student. I believe this occurred on several occasions, and they were discovered by the gym teacher's wife, also a gym teacher at the school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 16:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 15:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You won't even know what chafing looks like until you see us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A crow challenged a hawk to battle for eating his friend today, and it all happened through my back window. I live in Queens. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 18:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 03:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're missing an 'e' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 03:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read your autobiography in middle school. Did you write it or was there a ghost? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
