<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3936</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NSFW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help thinking of movie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 14:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for the vagueness and ambiguity but its 530am and I don't know why my brain just started to think about this but about ten or fifteen years ago I remember seeing this movie where this guy who is an increasingly shitty husband comes home to find a really fucked up video of his wife confessing to a bunch of fucked up shit like cheating on him and the video gets worse and worse until the end it actually shows her cheating on him on the video with his neighbor and then he finds out that its not a recorded video but a live feed from the neighbors place and he tries to kill her and or the neighbor or something. It may not have been in theaters maybe just made for/by HBO or Cinemax or something. Sorry/thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bonerfist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 00:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carrion, My Wayward Son </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 22:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 18:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Www.pornhub.com .... One lifetime of HIV prevention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 18:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ANUSTART </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 18:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also why is he laying on his back with no pants on in what appears to be a dirty bathroom in an old insane asylum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 18:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like 80% of rap songs from the 90s are full of those sounds too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If there was one phrase that your dog could say or one question it could ask, in English, and understand its meaning, what would you want it to be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 18:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would either choose "oops" or "what's that?". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 18:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its cool because English is such a garbage language that when you read it out loud all the a's make different noises. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Soon kids will grow up without knowing what an actual scrapbook or photo album is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 18:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because of Facebooks-n-such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 06:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There needs to be infinity more of these types of videos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 15:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the husband of some bitch can be president, then some bitch who's husband was president can also be president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 07:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Panda Venom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 22:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 22:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Panda Venom new band name I called it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were to take all the blood out of your body, and divide it up into 8-ounce bottles, and set it on a digital scale, you'd die. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 22:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sciatica, Pube Grenade, Penis Federal, Poison Douche </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Magnus Effect </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look it up, its actually a physics phenomenon in the sport of table tennis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno man I saw one on the Science Channel that can essentially print 3d buildings from locally acquired mineral resources, which NASA is considering using for building a moon base, and moon bases probably won't have to be breastfed, have diapers changed, wake up crying every night, and throw up constantly for the first year of their lives... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that every straight guy age 12-35 walks around with a banana in their pocket. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, in the kitchen, women complain about doing the dishes, and in the bedroom they complain about having to make the bed and fold clothes, and in the TV room they complain about the TV being too loud or food being left on coffee tables; ergo, they need something to complain about in a bathroom that is otherwise dominated by their mess, so they use the toilet lid as their vehicle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baby pandas are in fact much more dangerous than adult pandas because their venom is just as potent, but as adolescents they haven't learned how to control the amount that they inject into their prey when they bite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He should upgrade his name to Dwayne "The Tectonic Plate" Johnson. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 19:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 16:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 14 year old me was pretty certain you were supposed to pee inside a girl's bagina when you had sex, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 16:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like Lynch is a pretty racist surname too. It's like having the last name Gaschamber. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 16:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm tempted to create numerous extra accounts just so I can give this more upvotes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
