<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1094</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atheists Inspire Thoughts of Death in Many Americans: Atheists consistently rank among the lowest of the low in the court of American public opinion. Now, research suggests one reason why: Thinking about atheists reminds people of death. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 15:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poroshenko: Kiev 'must be ready for attack' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 15:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Birds 'weigh' peanuts and choose heavier ones: A new study suggests that some birds may be able to "weigh" peanuts and maybe even "listen to" peanuts while handling them in their beaks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 15:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sports Reporter On FIFA Corruption Allegations: 'Only Tip Of The Iceberg' "Even the head of FIFA's evaluation commission admits that Qatar and Russia submitted the weakest bids for 2018 and 2022 ... So there must have been other elements of persuasion." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 14:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How climate change is making Californias epic drought worse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 14:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Faced with an increasingly segregated education system, Dutch immigrant children have taken to the streets of their ethnically mixed Amsterdam neighbourhood seeking "white" pupils to attend their schools and help their integration. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 14:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The new GOP strategy on Iraq is to blame Obama "After struggling for days with questions about the genesis of the Iraq War, the GOP presidential candidates appear to be coalescing behind a new strategy: Shift the focus to whats happening in Iraq right now, and blame it all on Obama." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 14:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have revealed the musical, flirtatious side of a common spider. They played the male spiders' call to females, revealing that they used leaves to transmit sound. The researchers think this could provide clues about the earliest evolution of sound-based communication. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 14:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraqi forces retook territory from the Islamic State group east of Ramadi Saturday, in their first counterattack since the fall of the Anbar provincial capital a week ago. The offensive targeted the sprawling Euphrates Valley town of Husyabah, an essential stepping stone for any assault on Ramadi. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 12:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you know where same-sex marriage is actually legal? (Spoiler: it's hardly anywhere) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 20:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russians seized in Ukraine: We were following Moscow's orders "Why are they turning their backs on me?" he was quoted as saying by the Russian weekly Novaya Gazeta. "There was an order. I gave my oath to the motherland ... There was an order and, as a military man, I carried it out." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 20:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State: Is the US-led campaign flawed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 20:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-Maidan Activist Booed By Moscow Students </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 19:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pass the USA Freedom Act "Americans are rightfully fed up with dysfunction in Congress. Constantly passing new extensions to get through old deadlines is no way to govern ... We cannot extend this government-by-cliff model of legislating to our national security laws." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 19:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Norwegian capital has inaugurated the world's first 'bumble bee highway', a corridor through the city pollen stations every 250 meters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 19:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edward Snowden: my work is not finished "In regards to people's privacy, he argues that it is about more than just changing laws and systems, but actually people's values " </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 19:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who post Facebook status updates about their romantic partner are more likely to have low self-esteem, while those who brag about diets, exercise, and accomplishments are typically narcissists, according to new research. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neuroscientists Are Making an Artificial Brain for Everyone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AT T et al challenging net neutrality order on 1st Amendment grounds: ISPs resurrect Verizon claim that they should control speech on their networks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists on Thursday unveiled the most comprehensive analysis ever undertaken of the world's ocean plankton, the tiny organisms that serve as food for marine creatures such as the blue whale, but also provide half the oxygen we breathe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 17:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nvidia Teaches Cars to See: The system can, for example, detect the difference between a taxi cab and a police car and will know that the driver has to pull over for the police car if its flashing lights at the driver. It can also learn to recognize images its never seen before. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 16:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finland has sent letters to nearly a million reservists to collect their contact details and remind them of their duties in case of combat, a defence ministry spokesman said. The letter tells reservists which regiment or unit to join in the event of war, he told the BBC. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 15:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexican children who 'torture and kill six-year-old in game of kidnap' charged with murder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 15:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hanergy Plunge: The Man Who Lost $14 Billion in One Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 15:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a new study, researchers report successfully swapping out some 450 of the genes in baker's yeast with similar ones from a human. Each swapped gene got its own strain of yeast, so hundreds were created. With about half of those swaps, the yeast survived as a human-yeast hybrid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 15:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google patents 'creepy' internet toys to run the home: The firm has published a patent that describes devices would turn their heads towards users and listen to what they were saying, before sending commands to remote computer servers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 15:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the eyes betray your thoughts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 14:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Hello dictator,' Juncker says to Hungary's Orban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 14:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eiffel Tower Closed as Employees Protest Against Pickpockets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 14:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sorry, Republicans: Obamacare is getting more and more entrenched "This is the problem of King v. Burwell, which is why every smart Republican is now probably praying the Supreme Court comes to their rescue and shoots the lawsuit down" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 14:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State: How it is run </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 13:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than a quarter of a middle-aged person's skin may have already made the first steps towards cancer, a study suggests. Analysis of samples from 55- to 73-year-olds found more than 100 DNA mutations linked to cancer in every 1 sq cm (0.1 sq in) of skin. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 13:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The House just passed a bill about space mining. The future is here. "Any asteroid resources obtained in outer space are the property of the entity that obtained such resources, which shall be entitled to all property rights thereto, consistent with applicable provisions of Federal law." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 13:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Shi'ite cleric urges plan to purge Iraq of IS after fall of Ramadi "We must have a precise and wise plan drawn up by professional and patriotic figures... to resolve the military and security issues and begin to purge Iraqi lands of all terrorists." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 13:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The worlds top selling beer is a watery lager sold only in China for $1 a liter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 12:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google a step closer to developing machines with human-like intelligence: Algorithms developed by Google designed to encode thoughts, could lead to computers with common sense within a decade, says leading AI scientist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 19:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astronomers using NASA's Hubble Space Telescope have uncovered surprising new clues about a hefty, rapidly aging star whose behavior has never been seen before in our Milky Way galaxy. In fact, the star is so weird that astronomers have nicknamed it "Nasty 1," </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 19:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: Climate change makes the world more violent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 19:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have developed heat-triggered self-destructing electronic devices, that dissolve the circuits completely. They also developed a radio-controlled trigger that could remotely activate self-destruction on demand. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 19:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An architecture experiment using data collected from 2 million people has resulted in the creation of Sweden's most "statistically desirable" home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 19:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two new laws that ban communist symbols while honouring nationalist groups that collaborated with the Nazis have come into effect in Ukraine, raising concerns that Kiev could be stifling free speech and further fragmenting the war-torn country in the rush to break ties with its Soviet past. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 18:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have unveiled a comprehensive genetic map of advanced prostate cancer, hailing it as the disease's "Rosetta Stone". The study, published in the journal Cell, shows that nearly nine in 10 men had gene mutations that could be targeted with drugs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 18:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fossil parasite discovery reveals missing evolutionary step </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 18:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most people lie in online forms, because they don't trust companies, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 18:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Look ... It's My Name on This': President Obama Defends the Iran Nuclear Deal. In an interview, the U.S. president ties his legacy to a pact with Tehran, argues ISIS is not winning, warns Saudi Arabia not to pursue a nuclear-weapons program, and anguishes about Israel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 18:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans care about their digital privacy, but not enough to protect it "few Americans -- less than one in 10 -- said they have a lot of control over that actual process. And they have very little confidence that data collected about them by third parties will be kept private" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 18:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indonesians living in New South Wales have been advised to take extra care after a letter was sent to the local diplomatic office threatening retaliation over the execution of two Australians a month ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 17:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study shows that while video game players exhibit more efficient visual attention abilities, they are also much more likely to use navigation strategies that rely on the brain's reward system (the caudate nucleus) and not the brain's spatial memory system (the hippocampus). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 16:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man arrested 492 times in Tennessee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 16:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey's state intelligence agency helped deliver arms to parts of Syria under Islamist rebel control during late 2013 and early 2014, according to a prosecutor and court testimony from gendarmerie officers seen by Reuters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 15:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New patent lawsuits are down for the first time in five years. Heres why thats a huge deal. "We haven't seen anything like this since 2009  which is about when many companies started getting hit with their first demand letters." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 15:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The principal of a middle school in Ankara wiped the blackboard of a classroom with a students head as punishment for not having cleaned the board earlier, according to a video secretly recorded by another pupil in the class. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 15:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bees Hatch Before Your Eyes: Witness the growth of larvae into bees in this time-lapse video from photographer Anand Varma. Varma said the six-month project, for which he built a beehive in his workshop, gave him a new respect for the meticulous job of beekeeping. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 15:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Romania acts to save forests from logging spree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 15:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Blast-proof" wallpaper that could protect soldiers from explosions is being developed by the US army. Rolls of lightweight sticky wallpaper, lined with tough Kevlar fibres, could be carried by troops to reinforce the walls of temporary buildings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 15:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watching 3D movies 'helps improve brain power': British study suggests surgeons, boxers and tennis players might benefit from watching films in stereoscope before taking on challenging tasks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 14:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sick man whose Obamacare story went viral could be thwarted by Supreme Court "a Court ruling against the ACA  followed by GOP unwillingness to do anything in response  could make that gap in the safety net created by Obamacare a whole lot bigger. And it could claim a whole lot more people." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 14:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First images of collisions at 13 TeV: Last night, protons collided in the Large Hadron Collider (LHC) at the record-breaking energy of 13 TeV for the first time. These test collisions were to set up systems that protect the machine and detectors from particles that stray from the edges of the beam. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 11:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The gap between the rich and the poor keeps widening. In its 34 member states, the richest 10% of the population earn 9.6 times the income of the poorest 10%. There is no standard measure of inequality, but most indicators suggest it slowed or fell during the financial crisis   is now growing again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 11:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Octopus Can See With Its Skin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 10:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Global food markets could be disrupted by the El Nino event predicted for later this year. A strong El Nino is likely to increase prices of staple foods such as rice, coffee, sugar and cocoa, say scientists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 10:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sophisticated Tool Kit Predates Humans: The earliest known stone toolkit could write a whole new chapter in the book of human evolution, especially since the tools were not even made by our genus. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 19:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Childhood Vaccine Reduces Risk of a Cancer: The vaccine for Haemophilus influenza type B lowers the risk for acute lymphoblastic leukemia, the most common childhood cancer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This video by a Columbia University neuroscientist might be the best case against the drug war ever made </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German police Wednesday recovered two life-sized bronze sculptures of horses worth millions that once stood outside Adolf Hitler's chancellery but vanished in the year the Berlin Wall fell. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Defects Can "Hulk-Up" Materials: In a study at Berkeley Lab, exposure to alpha-particle radiation has been shown to transform certain thermoelectric materials into far more powerful versions of themselves. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Troll uses Twitter adverts to urge transgender people to kill themselves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The German government plans to pay a total of 10 million euros in compensation to an estimated 4,000 surviving World War Two Soviet prisoners for their suffering at the hands of Nazi Germany, coalition sources said on Wednesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have found a way to couple the properties of different two-dimensional materials to provide an exceptional degree of control over light waves. They say this has the potential to lead to new kinds of light detection, thermal-management systems, and high-resolution imaging devices. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More people dying in fewer armed conflicts, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet the future of meat: A $10 lab-grown hamburger that tastes as good as the real thing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowden Sees Some Victories, From a Distance: Edward J. Snowden, exiled in Russia, is globe-hopping via video appearances and enjoying victories in Congress and the courts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British police investigating allegations of historical child sex abuse said more than 1,400 people had been named as suspects including 261 described as "people of public prominence" including dozens of politicians and TV stars. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tiny island off Australia exploits legal loophole to grow and export tonnes of cannabis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 16:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mothers are more likely to coo at their babies, while fathers address them more like small adults - but both approaches help children learn, a study suggests. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 16:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missing MH370: Search Expands, 'Not Possible' to Know Where to Look Next </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 16:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A group of German scientists say they've used X-rays to figure out the underlying process behind the "fat blooming" on chocolate in an effort to help reduce the whiteness. They published their findings in the latest issue of the journal Applied Materials and Interfaces. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 16:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The death toll in a sudden die-off of critically endangered saiga antelope is nearing 20,000, according to authorities in northern Kazakhstan who are still unsure of the cause. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 15:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Predatory patent trolls could soon find it harder to operate in the United States. Legislation to curb frivolous patent lawsuits has regained momentum after lawmakers in the US Senate added a provision to stop university patent holders from being penalized along with the trolls. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 15:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exercise may affect how and when we move, even when we arent exercising, according to a fascinating new study in mice. The findings suggest that, by influencing our built-in body clocks, exercise may help our bodies to recognize the optimal times we should be moving, and when we should be still. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 15:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Euro under pressure after Greece warns it could fail to meet IMF repayment: Single currency loses ground against dollar as leading Greek politicians say the country may default if a deal with creditors is not reached </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 15:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amputees control bionic legs with their thoughts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 15:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German Islamists are returning from war abroad, some reformed but others more dangerous than ever. Social workers, imams and extremists are fighting for their souls -- and for Germany's safety. Government officials have few answers to the problem. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 14:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch a computer being assembled in less than one minute: a startup has created a computer thats simple enough for a child to build and sells for just $150. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 14:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No encryption back doors, says EU digital commissioner: We dont want to destroy peoples trust by creating some back doors, he said, adding that if there were back doors then sooner or later somebody would misuse them." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 14:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A bus powered by cow manure has set a land speed record for a regular bus by driving at 77mph. Reading Buses' "Bus Hound" was recorded doing a lap speed of 76.785mph (123.57km/h) at Bedford's Millbrook Proving Ground. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 14:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The GOP still doesnt get it on Iraq "Republicans have not confronted the failure of a worldview that sees military adventurism as the solution to our problems abroad. Indeed, as far as the partys leading voices are concerned, the lesson of Iraq is that America can still police the world." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 14:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aquariums in Japan have voted to stop buying live dolphins from the town of Taiji, where the annual slaughter of hundreds of cetaceans has drawn widespread condemnation, after being threatened with expulsion from the worlds leading zoo organisation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 13:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Men who drink the equivalent caffeine level of two to three cups of coffee a day are less likely to have erectile dysfunction (ED), according to researchers from The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 13:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Electronic Tongue Identifies The Correct Beer  Every Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 12:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Italy's Renzi says Europe blind to migrants' plight: Europe cannot just say 'out of sight, out of mind'," he said, as he vowed to recover hundreds of bodies from a boat that sank last month. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 12:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manchester United boss Louis van Gaal produced what was described as the "greatest speech of all time" to steal the show at the club's player of the year awards evening. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 12:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Desperate Chinese are turning to mass suicide to get their government's attention "... a group of about 30 men gathered and, in front of hundreds of shoppers, swallowed a quantity of pesticide. They fell to the ground en masse and, according to several eyewitnesses, foamed at the mouth." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 11:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraqi forces thwarted an attack by Islamic State militants east of the city of Ramadi overnight, police and pro-government Sunni fighters in the area said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 09:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iron levels in brain predict when people will get Alzheimer's </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 19:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nepal calls for return of stolen statues after quakes: In a strange twist of fate, some holy statues survived the two quakes and their aftershocks because they were stolen and smuggled abroad several decades ago. Nepalese people are now calling for their immediate return. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 19:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Scientists Debunked the Biggest Anti-Gay-Marriage Study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 19:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 18:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://www.cell.com/immunity/abstract/S1074-7613%2815%2900173-9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A dramatic video has captured the behaviour of cytotoxic T cells  the bodys serial killers  as they hunt down and eliminate cancer cells before moving on to their next target. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 18:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A township and county in Tibet have moved 60 centimetres southward as a result of the devastating Nepal earthquake last month, a Chinese geologist said on Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 17:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Awe promotes altruistic behavior, UCI-led study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 16:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Browser Extension Decides How Trustworthy You Are </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 16:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These Scientists Want to Unleash an Army of Caterpillars to Destroy Cocaine Crops </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 16:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This ice shelf is nearly the size of Scotland  and it could be at imminent risk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 16:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secret US X-37B plane takes to the skies to experiment in space </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 14:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The real story behind Jebs Iraq follies: The Bush Doctrine lives on in GOP "...all express an unrestrained enthusiasm for military adventurism. Thats one thing Iraq hasnt changed: Republicans still believe that the application of military force is a great way to solve problems around the world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 14:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Priceless historical artefacts have been lost recently, to violence in Iraq and earthquakes in Nepal. But "cyber-archaeologists" are working with volunteers to put you just a few clicks away from seeing these treasures - in colourful, three-dimensional detail. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 14:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Secret Weapon Vs. ISIS: Garbagemen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 14:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ebola has spread further in Guinea and Sierra Leone, with 36 cases in the past week, four times as many cases as the week before, the WHO said on Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 14:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ice hunters lasso an iceberg to turn it into vodka </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 14:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rick Santorums claim that hes responsible for the crushing sanctions on Iran "His bill was a relatively minor moment ... so minor that its core sanctions element has never been implemented ... such embellishment of the facts is worthy of Four Pinocchios." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 14:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian President Vladimir Putin has ordered designing a Russian space station, Deputy Prime Minister Dmitry Rogozin said on Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 13:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chilean authorities are investigating what killed some 1,300 seabirds that mysteriously turned up dead on a beach. The birds, which belong to the Procellariidae family, may have drowned after getting trapped in fishing nets or died from a disease such as bird flu, which is not endemic to Chile. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 13:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missing molecule prevents puberty: The researchers found a genetic fault that prevented this molecule, called SEMA3E, from being working correctly in two brothers with Kallman Syndrome, an inherited condition that prevents people from undergoing puberty or being able to smell. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 12:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The British public will for the first time be able to help decide which historic figure - in this case a creative one - appears on the next version of the country's 20 pound note, the Bank of England said on Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 12:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ISIS Fighters Seized Advantage in Iraq Attack by Striking During Sandstorm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 10:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neurobiologists have successfully re-created a critical juvenile period in the brains of adult mice. In other words, the researchers have reactivated brain plasticity  the rapid and robust changes in neural pathways and synapses as a result of learning and experience. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 18:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans face six-fold hike in exposure to extreme heat by 2070: If you live in Texas or Florida, rising temperatures will combine with population growth to create a sixfold rise in numbers of people exposed to extreme and potentially fatal heat events from 2041 onwards. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 18:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Computer engineers have developed an ultracompact beamsplitter  the smallest on record  for dividing light waves into two separate channels of information. The device brings researchers closer to producing silicon photonic chips that compute and shuttle data with light instead of electrons. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 18:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Indian Ocean may be the dark horse in the quest to explain the puzzling pause in global warming, researchers report on 18 May in Nature Geoscience. The study finds that the Indian Ocean may hold more than 70% of all heat absorbed by the upper ocean in the past decade. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 18:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Home-brewing could soon take on a more dangerous twist: Scientists have engineered brewer's yeast to synthesize opioids such as codeine and morphine from a common sugar, an international team reported on Monday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 17:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do men exist? A new study used 50 generations of beetles to examine just how important sexual selection is to the survival of a species: Males are required for a process known as "sexual selection" which helps species to ward off disease and avoid extinction. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 17:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine says Russia tried to kill captured Russian soldiers: Ukraine Foreign Minister Pavlo Klimkin said on Monday that Russia had tried to kill the two Russian servicemen Kiev says it has captured in east Ukraine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 17:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> European Parliament President Martin Schulz has apologized for mistakenly adding Catalonia to official documents as if it were its own country after complaints from a Spanish unity politician. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 17:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Practice may not make perfect, but visualization might. New research shows that people who imagined a visual target before having to pick it out of a group of distracting items were faster at finding the target than those who did an actual practice run beforehand. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 16:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the most well-known symbols of the Vikings - a palm-sized dragon's head - has been discovered during excavations in the Viking trading town of Birka in the Stockholm archipelago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 16:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 102-year-old who was denied a Ph.D. by the Nazi regime in the 1930s is to finally receive the honor following the successful defense of her thesis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 15:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A democratic socialist campaign? Its about time. "Combining his avowed socialism with his gruff grandpa manner, Sanders brings to todays politics an authenticity otherwise in short supply. At best, his role, like that of Debs and Thomas, may prove to be prophetic." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 14:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Israel Defense Forces rules that tanks are no place for women, saying it's 'beyond their physiological limits' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 14:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even when Congress does things, people still hate it "Most Americans think Congress is doing a bad job. Its overall approval rating is up slightly, to 19 percent. At no point since January 2010 has more than a quarter of the public approved of the job Congress is doing." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 14:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Googles Plan to Eliminate Human Driving in 5 Years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 13:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boy digs up 1,400-year old wine press in Jerusalem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 13:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Algerians bare their legs to support girl snubbed for short skirt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 13:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ground level in the Owakudani hot-spring area of Mount Hakone in Japan has risen by up to 12 cm since mid-April, days before volcanic activity intensified in the popular tourist spot, according to a geographical survey institute. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 12:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside the Soyuz simulator at Star City where astronauts are training for off-nominal situations they could face during their spaceflight. In practice, this includes anything their Soyuz instructor decides to throw at them - including scenarios such as fire or depressurisation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 12:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ecigs dont stop people smoking and adverse effects are prevalent, major review concludes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 12:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Salt-Rich Diet May Delay Puberty Study Claims: A new study published by researchers from the University of Wyoming found that rats that consumed a sodium-rich diet had a significant delay in reaching puberty compared to fellow rodents that imbibed normal levels of salt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 11:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU foreign and defence ministers are expected to approve a mission to destroy the boats used by people-smugglers operating in Libya. Italy has proposed that the mission should be led from Rome by Adm Enrico Credendino, who ran the EU's naval mission against piracy off the Horn of Africa in 2012. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 11:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Indian nurse dies after spending 42 years in a vegetative state following a brutal rape, a case which sparked a debate on euthanasia laws. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 11:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are more women choosing to become nuns? "Recently, the Catholic Church said the number of women becoming nuns here had reached a 25-year high, with the number of women taking holy orders rising to 45 last year. Many are aged 30 or under." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 10:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shiite militias converge on Iraq's Ramadi after IS takeover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 10:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The increasingly ugly gerrymandering of America  in 7 maps "With America's population increasing and the number of House seats holding steady, we're not going to see a return to cleanly divided districts any time soon." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 19:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU to open shelters in Niger in bid to keep illegal migrants out of Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 19:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 19:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://www.cell.com/cell-stem-cell/abstract/S1934-5909%2815%2900161-7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Epilepsy has been found to reduce the generation of new neurons: researchers have discovered that hippocampal neural stem cells stop generating new neurons and are turned into reactive astrocytes, a cell type that promotes inflammation and alters communication between neurons. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 19:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Computer That Changed Everything (Altair 8800) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 18:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Space Station Astronauts Talk Loneliness, Missing the Weather and Their Crazy Work Schedule </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 16:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The manager of a Turkish third league team, orum Belediyespor, rented a lifting crane to watch his teams playoff game, after he was banned from entering the stadium. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 15:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ecuador's president urges Brad Pitt to scrap Amazon oil spill movie: Socialist leader Rafael Correa concerned film will be based on a book he alleges covered up actions of oil giant Chevron </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 14:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hyena society is founded on friendship: They can tell clan members apart, discriminating among their maternal and paternal kin. Theyre also choosy about their pals and form tight bonds only with specific membersthe friends of their friends. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 14:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A gift basket for Clinton from the GOP "At this point in the campaign, do you see the Republican presidential hopeful whos going to beat Hillary Clinton? I didnt think so. Not if what were watching now is the best the GOP can do." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 14:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shutting down huge pirate sites has no 'positive effect': it in fact led to some healthy competition in the online piracy world. It provides evidence of the oft reported "Hydra" effect, where pirates simply move to multiple, smaller resources to get content, rather than sticking with one service. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 13:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Luxembourgs prime minister on Friday becomes the first serving leader in the European Union to marry someone of the same sex, and only the second worldwide  and all in a tiny, mostly Catholic country often considered rather conservative. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 12:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smoking induces early signs of cancer in cheek swabs: The study provides evidence that smoking induces a general cancer program that is also present in cancers which arent usually associated with it  including breast and gynaecological cancers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 17:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austin greets first majority-female city council session with special training on dealing with women "Women: They ask a lot of questions, they dont listen to financial arguments and thanks to Hillary Clinton, legislatures around the country are probably going to be seeing a lot more of them." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kim Dotcom Q A: "Extremism is if you are a Hollywood studio, and you release your content in one country firstin the USand then roll it out over a couple of months in other countries around the world, and expect the Internet community in all these different countries to wait for the release." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study by geneticists has for the first time identified the genetic clues behind what makes you a lark or an owl. Based on analysis of a fruit fly, the scientists have discovered nearly 80 genes associated with morningness and eveningness. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/ajpa.22728/abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sibling marriages among Pharaohs stunted their height: According to the study, the average height of the pharaohs was at 166 centimeters (54 ft.), while the queens and princesses had an average height of 156.7 centimeters (51 ft.). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poland and three Baltic states said they were seeking permanent NATO deployments on their soil to counter increased Russian military activity. The Baltic states - Lithuania, Latvia and Estonia - said they were preparing a joint approach to NATO command asking for permanent stationing of a brigade. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UCLA report shows 75 percent of Los Angeles County water systems vulnerable to drought, other challenges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 14:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Small towns in Finland have been trying to boost their dwindling populations by giving bonuses to people who move there. Some councils offer patches of land for a euro ($1; 70p), and others hand out cash to new parents. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 14:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese company sends 12,000 on Thai holiday: The visit comes less than a week after France received more than 6,000 Chinese holidaymakers from a single Chinese firm that booked 4,760 rooms in 79 four-and five-star hotels. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 14:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iris-scanning smartphone puts paid to passwords in blink of an eye: The new smartphone made by Fujitsu uses an infrared LED and a special camera to snap a picture of the iris of a persons eye. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 14:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is funding Amtrak such a struggle? Because Republican districts dont use it. "Of those 184 districts, 116 are currently represented by Republicans. On average, ridership in Republican districts was about 41,000 in 2014 -- compared to 261,000 in Democratic districts." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 13:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One in three European birds is endangered, according to a leaked version of the most comprehensive study of Europes wildlife and natural habitats ever produced. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 11:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ISIL jihadists threaten Syria's ancient Palmyra: monitor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 11:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Large Hadron Collider experiments first to observe new subatomic process </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 10:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear Google: open letter from 80 academics on 'right to be forgotten' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 10:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Female Indonesian military applicants receive 'two-finger' virginity tests "Female military applicants in Indonesia are subjected to virginity tests - including the discredited 'two finger test' to determine if the hymen is intact - in order to recruit the "best people" to the armed forces." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 10:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prostate cancer drug 'extends lives': A chemotherapy drug can extend the lives of patients with advanced prostate cancer by nearly two years, a major "game-changing" study shows. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 09:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xenophobia, racism, and right-wing radicalism: Hungary's Jobbik party is only three percentage points behind the ruling Fidesz in recent polls. And the killing of Roma is greeted with indifference. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 19:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> May 13, 1992, Record-Setting Spacewalk on Shuttle Endeavour's First Mission </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 19:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mysterious beautiful blue crayfish is new species from Indonesia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 18:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of Europes earliest known humans had a close Neanderthal ancestor: perhaps as close as a great-great-grandparent. The finding questions the idea that humans and Neanderthals interbred only in the Middle East, more than 50,000 years ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 18:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian bear attack: Woman 'in critical condition' "Some reports say that the bear thought she was dead and tried to bury her so that it could return to its prey later." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 18:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breast-Feeding May Cut Breast Cancer Recurrence Risk: A new report suggests that breast-feeding, which has been associated with a reduced breast cancer risk, may have another benefit. In mothers who later develop breast cancer, breast-feeding may reduce the risk of cancer recurrence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 18:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 17:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://online.liebertpub.com/doi/abs/10.1089/chi.2014.0104 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 95 percent of parents think their overweight children look just right: Most parents can no longer tell what a healthy weight looks like, and their doctors aren't helping them understand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 17:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tokyo beer mats depict faces of battered women to reduce domestic violence rates: Bars in Japan launch Violent Coasters, which use thermochemical ink activated by cold drinks being placed on them to reveal faces of domestic violence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 16:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Second-in-command of Islamic State, Abu Alaa al-Afri, killed in air strike by US-led coalition, Iraq government says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://www.nature.com/npp/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/npp2015114a.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brains of Smokers Who Quit Successfully Might Be Wired for Success: The study, published in Neuropsychopharmacology, showed greater connectivity among certain brain regions in people who successfully quit smoking compared to those who tried and failed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> France's Sarkozy accused of pandering to racist sentiments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 14:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://www.ebiomedicine.com/article/S2352-3964%2815%2900105-X/abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have identified new molecules that kill cancer cells while protecting healthy cells and that could be used to treat a variety of different cancers. The research shines a light on what happens to cells at the moment they become cancerous. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 14:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brain-eating amoebas kill by turning your body against you: The immune system launches a counter-attack by flooding the brain with immune cells, causing inflammation and swelling. It seldom works: of the 132 people known to have been infected in the US since 1962, only three survived. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 14:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than half of Russians see America as a threat, and many fear US military invasion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 14:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The emerging populist agenda "All agree that our extreme inequality is not the inevitable result of globalization or technology. It is the result of policy and power. The rules have been rigged. No one reform offers an answer; broad reforms are needed. " </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 14:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Six Strikes" Anti-Piracy Scheme Is a Sham, Filmmakers Say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 12:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A district of 5 million people in Chinas restive far west has demanded that residents hand in their passports to the police for indefinite safekeeping, the latest government crackdown in an area where Beijing has declared a peoples war on violent separatists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 12:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey's foreign minister: Foreign fighters from 90 different countries have tried to pass through Turkey on their way to join ISIL in Syria. Turkey is the only member of NATO to have borders with Daesh. This is not a sustainable situation. It poses a significant threat to us,. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 10:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jabhat al-Nusra launches war against IS in Qalamoun: Known for his support to the Islamic State, Jabhat al-Nusras emir in Qalamoun, Abdul Malek al-Talli, recently decided to fight IS militants, whom he described as Kharijites. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 10:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Romania turns hacking crisis into advantage, helping Ukraine "Both historic twists have ironically turned Romanian cyber sleuths into some of Europes best. So much so that NATO tapped Bucharest to defend Ukraine from Russian digital espionage by sending experts to monitor Kiev gov't institutes..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 09:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists Regenerate Bone Tissue Using Only Proteins Secreted by Stem Cells: The new study, published in Scientific Reports, is is the first to extract the necessary bone-producing growth factors from stem cells and to show that these proteins are sufficient to create new bone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 19:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why so many Dutch people work part time "Some attribute their high quality of life and general good nature to a rather laid-back approach to work: more than half of the Dutch working population works part time, a far greater share than in any other rich-world country." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 18:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our immune systems vary with the seasons, according to a study led by the University of Cambridge that could help explain why certain conditions such as heart disease and rheumatoid arthritis are aggravated in winter whilst people tend to be healthier in the summer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 18:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mass shootings at the hands of unhinged loners perpetuate a commonly held belief that mental illness triggers violent crimes. But a new study from UC Berkeley shows that hallucinations and delusions associated with psychiatric disorders seldom foreshadow acts of aggression. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 18:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the ruling against the NSAs phone records program could have huge implications "because many laws rely on very similar relevance language, the decision should bring new scrutiny to other programs...'Most surveillance statutes are copy and paste,' said J. Mayer, a lawyer and computer scientist" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
