<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9242</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More housing stock would temper it a good bit. We haven't been building enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God-mode lifestyle choice is getting a good degree or high income job in a low cost of living state. 

Engineers or nurses in those kind of environments can make some serious headway in their financial lives  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1.6-2k miami </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is fucked is that the elderly/"low income" people get these sweet apartments subsidized, and middle class or like 80 percent of the country get fucked. 

The luxury condos often are allowed to be built at a higher density if they have a portion that is below market rent. Now this goes beyond the federal affordable housing programs, and makes rhe upper middle class responsible for housing the urban poor,which is controveral in the firdt place. It is like taxing your home. 

What it also does is upbids and increases the price that the middle class has to pay, as there are even larger blocks of people who are taking up housing stock at a subsidized rate. 


Really I think zoning needs to be relaxed in many places to promote infill, smaller units, multifamily, and independently managed apartments. 


It is most profitable to only do luxury units because they make more money and have more stable clients, so when the government puts a bunch of red tape on a market that has little interest in it, it is pretty damn hard. 


I wish we had more unconventional housing in odds and ends,  on top of buildings, multistory, housing connected to workplaces and the like. 

Europe has a lot more housing like that, but instead we have our workplace/entertainment/housing rigidly seperated thanks to zoning in most places. My large street where I lived a while back had no food/gas on the whole street because all of it was zoned residential, and it seemed like such a clusterfuck not to have those amenities. 

Even the rental market is heating up a good bit, but there are so few units vacant and new ones are at a higher price point, so many people don't save money doing it. 

I will likely just get roomates well into my future as a young professional and invest the saved money. 

I will not pay 1450 a month in rent plus utilities and comcast to boot. I am more than happy to share a washing machine and actually keep my money. 

If housing prices weren't artificially subsidized by the mortgage interest deduction, the deductability of taxes on a house, and artificially low interest policies/zero interest rate policies, the value of homes would fall back into equilibrium. Somethinng like a lower multiple of average yearly income than where it is now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of communities that are older fear too many kids will raise property taxes, which fund schools. Having only seniors move into their city/neighborhood can in theory save a little bit on taxes in the short term, but really hinders the region. This kind of thing forces young and middle aged people to commute from further out if they are going to work a job. 

It really is discriminatory and needs to be cracked down on. It is highly ageist. 

It happens all the time in new hampshire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What shpreme court cases are you upset about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breh he think it real cuz he aint got good credit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Shitty cameras probably have poor low hight performance and low resolution.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is self perpetuating a bit. Once communities get an "anchor in" by having an expat community, it is easier than being one of very few people there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe low end gear doesn't work as well on those metrics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And there are pretty easy workarounds. Like non mandatory after school religious clubs and whatnot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surging Bernie Sanders Expects Huge Crowd As He Rides Grassroots Tidal Wave Into Madison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a public school giving money essentially to a person who is running for president </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surging Bernie Sanders Expects Huge Crowd As He Rides Grassroots Tidal Wave Into Madison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9,500 expected at Madison rally for Democratic presidential candidate Bernie Sanders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9,500 expected at Madison rally for Democratic presidential candidate Bernie Sanders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am from florida but I lend you my rsvp. We can do this. The event is going to be awesome!


I am going to watch a stream of it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \I CAN FEEL THE BERN

JSM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disgusting and wasteful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A college balks at Hillary Clintons fee, books Chelsea for $65,000 instead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A college balks at Hillary Clintons fee, books Chelsea for $65,000 instead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would income discrimination be a good thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has been my experience in Kenya as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I think they are ota in many/most places as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Puerto Rico's Crushing Debt is Unapayable-and the Fallout will hit Florida </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 18:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And earthlink is cheaper?  I am asking about alternatives:  the apartment in pembroke pines I'm moving to is only wired for comcast cable. Idk how dsl works though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 18:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes sense. I just want to see her on top of the charts again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 18:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DRC is way more progressive than people realize </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 18:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Metropolitan limits have only been around since the 1950s and it would be troubesome to switch methods halfway through. I wanted data since the 1700s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 18:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/93/Carte_Utah_population.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 18:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is brighthouse dsl?  Soy de Miami  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is easier to act like it is a consipacy when you don't consider all of the problems like energy density in airplanes and the like

The world can't pay 30 cents per kilowatt like german solar costs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 10:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Artpop wasn't a critical success and didn't have many good singles, and cheek to cheek was a jazz project, rather than pop music.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 10:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the world isn't either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 10:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheek to cheek is niche jazz music though, not meant for popular consumption.  

I mean like dancepop. 


Music people actually listen to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 10:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at the estonia population chart from like the 1990s to now and it is uber telling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 10:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're the greatest superpower ever to exist, have the highest gdp of any country, and bankroll your continent. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 10:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Costs an arm and a leg to get there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 10:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, VIVIDLY. 

Almost nobody lives in Utah outside of the wasatch fron/ogden valley. 


It is VERY clear and easy to see. Please educate yourself with a population density map of utah.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 10:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer Sluts for Sanders </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 10:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please take your reaction imagrs back to 9gag with the other kids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 10:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They posted the story before you. Delete this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 09:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know that amy winehouse song?  .... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 09:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While large amounts will knock you out of ketosis, even small cheats like tart cherries are something I allow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When will Lady Gaga return to making music? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 09:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss listening to her music in the last few years. Where has she been? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby boomers: We need to talk about money </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 09:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 09:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \for an actual argument that isn't mindlessly luddite, and would actually be erudite enough for this subreddit


Ftfy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 09:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Le wrong generation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 09:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't new. 

http://www.amazon.com/Bowling-Alone-Collapse-American-Community/dp/0743203046

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bowling_Alone



http://bowlingalone.com/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 09:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That seems like a major oversight to be that short of a common size. I guess it keeps weight down and mpg up.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 09:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.truth-out.org/opinion/item/31626-interrupting-pride-for-black-lives </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More coverage of Bernie Sanders is merited </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 09:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 09:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Socialism is the policy, and it works. Just look at Sweden, or rich countries like Norway that are heavily socialist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 09:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can't be quiet or stifled. We need to start a political revolution in this country ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 09:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/SandersforPresident :where there is only one flavor of koolaid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 09:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah things like that aren't that bad when you contextualize them. Bernie was doing a good thing and he is a feminist, unlike conservatives who want to ban abortion and make it illegal to be a woman and illegal to be gay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 08:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should follow his lead then! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 08:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \adults are probably more informed and way more against it


.....uuuh. ..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The world is defenceless against the next financial crisis, warns BIS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 08:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 08:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In fact, they were born here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 08:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enhance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 08:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please attack his logic not his personage. 

You know nothing about him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black Lives Matter Protesters Disrupt Chicago Gay Pride Parade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 08:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black Lives Matter Protesters Disrupt Chicago Gay Pride Parade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 08:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 06:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only one kind though. Got to save money to feed the kids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 06:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Romania grew like poland for a bit it wouldnct be unrealistic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 05:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can gay men come? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US now has more Spanish speakers than Spain  only Mexico has more </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 03:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 03:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uVjRe8QXFHY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 03:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the situation kinda sucks for you, but there are some awesome resources for free at your local library.  They have "pimsleur" series CDs at the library, and you can copy the CDs to your laptop or MP3 and pick up some surival spanish very easily.



The peace corps/dli/FSI courses for free here are in the public domain and are more than enough to learn spanish with:


https://www.livelingua.com/#project

I just moved to Miami and speak no spanish.

I'm doing it, you can too.  Man up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US now has more Spanish speakers than Spain  only Mexico has more </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 03:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 03:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *frist-kund h//ow d=@re oo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: You just have to slam it to make it lock into place.

I am an idiot.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gen II: How the hell do I lock the back seats back into place? I let them down once upon a time and now I have no idea how to secure them again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White power! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to the post office and they had 3 actual workers who were 50 and working slowly, and a woman who was in her early 20s who was doing all of the work,  not allowed to sit while she was working, and had to sort the crowd of people into lines and then help them with their postage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch Jeb Bush defend a campaign ad that exploited the murder of a 10-year-old girl. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch Jeb Bush defend a campaign ad that exploited the murder of a 10-year-old girl. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is from florida. 


Maybe he is a hermit crab? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is the two systems existing side by side without progressing either way. 

If union benefits phased out it would be more fair, but now it just acts like creating a second tier class of workers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can also tutor younger students in computer science. You could easily charge 15/20 an hour for coding lessons for high schoolers or other college students. A few hours a week freelance can easily make some grocery money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10 billion is a lot but not relative to german tax revenue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These kind of social democracies can really backfire. It is like jobs where the old people are unionized and have killer benefits and then there are young people who are only allowed to work part time at minimum wage with zero benefits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turning off data when not on wifi is the way to go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Angolan_general_election,_1992


Total clusterfuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give me your house.  I donct have one. I'm in a time of need.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have only had bad experiences with traditional taxis and only good experiences with uber.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yellow cab is the new terrorist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supreme court rules that literally everything is interstate commerce in the 1920s. This would take a case at the supreme court decision to overturn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FSI Free Swahili Course with Audio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean chinese equities are massively overvalued, and the PE ratio of us stocks aint that hot either. College debt is another massively real bubble.


Trying to time a bubble is hard, but it isn't like there aren't sectors that are overblown or not worth their valuation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting a roomate he basically knows he will make 500-1000 a month. Getting a mortgage for another property would add debt and the liability of taking care of the house, and what happens if real estate values decline and the house becomes underwater?

I just mean getting a roomie is by and far the most simplistic solution with little downside relatively speaking. 

And the stock market is a lot more liquid than paying off your house esrly, with the added benefit of being able to cash out if he wanted to stay in that home during retirement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Just a bit of levity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blackrock did this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is so obnoxious is that they want the right to sue gun manufacturers for people killed when their product is misused. Imagine if you could put ford out of business because someone drunk drove. It is such stupid and ignorant view of the legal system.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that is a lot more legwork and speculative real estate wheeling and dealing than just getting a roomate where he is currently </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And obviously betting you can work till seventy is a risky proposition, but if OP's dad waits at least until his full retirement age his SS benefit won't get nerfed. Really he should wait as long as possible to take SS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Usually with people so close to retirement I have them get into FOREX shorts to start them off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dad already has a house. A much easier solution is either moving out somewhere cheaper and renting the house, or getting a roomie for his current situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop the double payment, pay the minimum, and put that money that your dad had been putting extra into the mortgage into an IRA or other savings vehicle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many rooms does his house have?  This may sound silly, but getting a roomate for a few years would give him a lot more cash flow and cut his expenses on things like utilities in half.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do I need to ask my barber to get this style? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Andrew WK? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont see color.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it doesnt. They pay the same rate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except there were no fascists. The anti-republicans who stopped a communist revolution are heroes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh well we'll just wait another 100 years. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 12:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/FloridaMan/search?q=dick+oranges restrict_sr=on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 12:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already submitted a million times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 12:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Total Ghandi move lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 12:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prosecco, but yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 12:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The people with minimimal education or drive who migrate through civil service/dmv type jobs are quite apathetic from what I have seen. The lifers at colleges/universities can be pretty bad, much like those in city govt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 12:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have more constructive to contribute or are you just going to use ad homenim insults against others? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lazy is as lazy does. Why don't they get jobs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vote ACT or NZF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and we can do it here too!  Bernie Sanders 2016! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a speaker of old cement, our language is spoken in south sudam as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Lesbianism Intensifies] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn he even won new orleans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the hole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Western Sahara is Morocco </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But everyone pays the same percent so it is equal. 

Or do you just not believe in math? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone stole the key... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shave it this minute it looks bad and you will look a lot better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moscato.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks fine. Dont change it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Americam Crew Fiber. Toustle it when it is moist. Apply from the roots out. 

Use like a 3 on the sides and grow the top out to make the look complete </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do people not support consent with cosmetic non-medically needed procedures?  To me it is inexplicable that with all of the antirape activism that people still support male genital mutliation. 

How can babies consent to something that isn't medically necessary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 10:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the OP that oblivious or are they trolling? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 10:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is used in the USA too. 

Basically they are bernie sanders voters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 10:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hipsters don't want anyone to join their cool treehouse clubs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 10:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liberals and progressives can be really hateful when it comes to this kind of stuff. Liberal.michiganders and wisconsinites habe all of these weird phobias about the great lakes being drained by foreigners. It is dumb as fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 10:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ffs most new world wines can rank onnpar with french wines of similar class and has been that way for decades. France has been making wines only on par with california for decades </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 10:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't mind the slight of hand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 10:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh bestof and srs inevitably do it as well. I am amazed shitlibertarianssay has mods that are that caustic to socialists/communists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 10:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Champaign socialists? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 10:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sls? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 10:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either way I'm getting the popcorna. This is more entertaining than the hissyfits after an Angolan election </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 10:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NEVER FORGET 1994 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 10:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The french are huge japonophiles though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 10:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you marry a giraffe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 10:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This song has helped me through some tough times. Listen to the lyrics. 

www.youtube.com/watch?v=B1n2KgKpb3Y </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 10:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait isn't details " "not a gay magazine" " "? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 10:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \crossfit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 10:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my frienda from changsha china always tells me about the new orleans chicken they sell

The whole nola stuff gets appropriated weird ways over there. It is funny though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israelis demolish 1,000 Palestinian Homes in Negev Per Year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 09:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (VIDEO) Virginia Man Is Harassed While Eating In Hotel Parking Lot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 09:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What One Nairobi Doctors Healthcare Dream Has to Do With the Cheesecake Factory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 08:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 08:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not LDS but more than willing to talk. PM me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 08:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BernieSandersnomics isn't working </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 08:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/syriancivilwar has a bunch of those types </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syria: A Federal Option (Gulf 2000) [5708x4253] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Puerto Ricos Governor Says Islands Debts Are Not Payable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Puerto Ricos Governor Says Islands Debts Are Not Payable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Puerto Ricos Governor Says Islands Debts Are Not Payable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The school may not have a legal office, but the office that does foreign students and the counseling center.  The foreign student office thing won't be able to give you legal advice, but they are a free source of advice and have probably dealt with this before many times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Puerto Ricos Governor Says Islands Debts Are Not Payable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Heartwarming Change of Pace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 04:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 04:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Atatrk is rolling in his grave.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah for some reason people get wrapped up in psedoscience when it comes to their pet issues. VT/NH have large amounts of gun owners, but much less violence than Chicago. UK has lots of knife crime. 

The consequences and rates of death from violence are higher with guns that knives, bur trying to ban guns rather than trying to fix our fraying societies in some urban neighborhoods is simplistic at best.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mama Mia!  Here we go againa. My my, why'd I ever let you go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But muh progressive messiah.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Caution:  He might try and exercise you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idaho Gold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Google it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was minor in rhe sense that he blew like a .085 and didn't kill anyone ore wreck a car. He got caught at a checkpoint.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Michel Thomas and Pimsleur language tapes are awesome to workout to, and are available free at your local library. I love sort of using time two ways and getting a lot more productivity out of the day like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Contacting the school may be a good idea. They have this happen all the time, and if OP was convicted they would likely find out anyways.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to be an "I told you so", but while OP is in the US I wouldn't drink at all (anymore).   The risk now is too high. 

I know people who have gotten kicked out of PhD programs for one relatively minor drunk driving arrest without even an accident, and while OP can probably plea bargain it down or get a diversion sort of program going, any subsequent arrest would be a lot more onerous and OP wonct have any of the first time get out of jail free kind of cards. 


I also knew a girl who had to return home because she got caught with pot.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is the secret at chickafila. Brine yo chicken in pickle juice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vous devez voter MLP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Freedom" is slavery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I disagree with rand paul on everything but like him on this issue" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 00:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I submitted this article because Americans have very few safeguards against pesticide use, and this article explores how corporations and the government collude to expose passengers to dangerous pesticides with unknown long term health consequences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Danger in the Air </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 00:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Activist Post: Airlines Spraying Fliers With Pesticides Inside the Plane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 00:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How This Very Popular Cereal Is Exploiting Americans   What You Can Do About It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 00:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 00:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama did this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 23:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The governor still shits over it occasionally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 23:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cashed out a lot of my IRA to support Bernie. 

We can do it if we all pitch in. 

I quit my job and am going door to door full time now 


We are just weeks away from Bernie eclipsing Hillary and leading the polls. 


Sanders has already doubled his support, and if he does it again he will be head to head with Clinton. I encourage you to educate yourself on the issues and read his policies.  He is very middle class oriented, and is against free trade (ie, pro middle class). 

/r/SandersforPresident


#FeeltheBern </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 19:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a gay man, please quit appropriating our struggle into arts and crafts you can repin on pintrest and tumblr and shit 


This isn't your life, nor is it your fight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 18:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am fearful of the cult of personality around him, with all of the saving kittens and saving people from burning buildings and stuff. It just seems incredulous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 18:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that presumptuous?  That isn't yout place to keep him out of the know about his own family.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 18:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How?  Race relations have soured because of obama. Disagreeing with you doesn't make someone ignorant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 18:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Devil would make 20/hr if bernie was erected president </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 17:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Busses use less energy, cost less, have better usage rates, and are faster. 

http://www.debunkingportland.com/max_vs_bus.html


Do you have any facts other than what you see in your suburban neighborhood?




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 17:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont. Dental insurance is a scam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 17:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TPP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 17:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The middle class is his economic plan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The right-wing senator who frequented prostitutes celebrated marriage equality with Chick-fil-A. Twitter wasnt impressed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 17:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 17:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please stop the damage control. He is a part of the lobbyist machine. 


We need politicians dedicated to public service, like Bernie is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 17:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seattle for two hours a day is not a lot of the time. You are taking your personal anecdote of a tiny amount of the transit system and subsrituting it for empirical data .... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 17:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We should have wealth in this country according to each person's humanity, not according to their profession" -Bernie Sanders </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 17:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a terrible idea. 


She is literally the same as bush on every important issue. She is anti gay, and you're being used by voting for her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 16:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds like George Bush's foreign policy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 16:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Publishing memoirs isn't an accomplishment. She startwd another war in Libya and her memoire didn't sell worth shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 11:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Region?  I am willing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
