<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1485</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These three politicians want feminism banned and gay people criminalised - another anti-J4MB hit-piece by the Mirror </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 16:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Making the Trolls Pay: How One UK Company Made 1 Million in Four Days from Furious Social Justice Warriors - Breitbart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 03:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Making the Trolls Pay: How One UK Company Made 1 Million in Four Days from Furious Social Justice Warriors - Breitbart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 02:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Falsely Accusing an Innocent Man, Lena Dunham Is Celebrated as a Rape Role Model </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 02:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC election coverage: Bigotry, bias and corruption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 23:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC's Chris Lewis sues ex-wife claiming she lied that he was the father of her son </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 20:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC's Chris Lewis sues ex-wife claiming she lied that he was the father of her son </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 20:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 14 April 2015: Women in politics - Mike Buchanan on the Stephen Nolan Show, BBC Radio Ulster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former BBC producer sues ex-wife for 350,000 claiming she lied to him for 17 years that he was the father of her son </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 15:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bigotry, Bias, Corruption - analysis of the BBC's attempt to sabotage the J4MB election campaign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 05:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 04:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should think we can guarantee that particular exchange was Mike's biggest mistake of the entire discussion, and yet its' the bit the BBC selected to air. Mike himself openly admits that Ray is the better performer of the two of them, yet the BBC have essentially banned Ray from the airwaves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 04:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet more BBC anti J4MB bias, not very subtle are they? Firstly note how the whole tone of the piece so negative and putting Mike up against his biggest opponent in the entire constituency. The whole premise is one of a feminist outraged with the very existence of a party supporting the human rights of men and boys. Plenty of people hate Labour or the Tories, but they don't simply restrict Labour in Rotherham to a grilling by a victim of the industrial scale child abuse there do they? Similarly even the BBC wouldn't put UKIP in front of a panel consisting 100% of Romanian immigrants

Where's the video showing him engaging with unemployed men or all the grandparents (male and female) denied a relationship with their grandkids? They're just constantly trying to put him under attack so he's on the defensive.

Mike also states that they interviewed his colleague Barry Barry, who is now a highly experienced and quite superb performer in such discussions. Naturally they shelved every minute of Ray's excellent performance and even give the last word to the feminist. 

(when they went back to the studio after this piece they even named check the feminist again and failed to mention J4M B or Mike or Ray) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Election 2015: Feminist meets Justice for Men leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 04:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 03:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet more BBC anti J4MB bias, not very subtle are they? Firstly note how the whole tone of the piece so negative and putting Mike up against his biggest opponent in the entire constituency. The whole premise is one of a feminist outraged with the very existence of a party supporting the human rights of men and boys. Plenty of people hate Labour or the Tories, but they don't simply restrict Labour in Rotherham to a grilling by a victim of the industrial scale child abuse there do they? Similarly even the BBC wouldn't put UKIP in front of a panel consisting 100% of Romanian immigrants

Where's the video showing him engaging with unemployed men or all the grandparents (male and female) denied a relationship with their grandkids? They're just constantly trying to put him under attack so he's on the defensive.

Mike also states that they interviewed his colleague Barry Barry, who is now a highly experienced and quite superb performer in such discussions. Naturally they shelved every minute of Ray's excellent performance and even give the last word to the feminist. 

(when they went back to the studio after this piece they even named check the feminist again and failed to mention J4M B or Mike or Ray) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Election 2015: Feminist meets Justice for Men leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 03:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 03:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Article is from 2010 but obviously it's highly relevant right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A look back at the last time the BBC banned men from the audience of a political debate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 03:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 01:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some studies show there to be more domestic violence in lesbian relationships than any other type. A shame that all these victims get ignored jut so feminists can bash men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brittney Griner, Glory Johnson and the WNBAs domestic violence problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 01:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brittney Griner, Glory Johnson and the WNBAs domestic violence problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 01:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brittney Griner, Glory Johnson and the WNBAs domestic violence problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 01:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 16:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A number of other avenues for letting your views be know are also available:

You can make an formal complaint here:
http://www.bbc.co.uk/complaints/complain-online/

Email addresses of BBC Nottingham management:
mike.bettison@bbc.co.uk (Twitter is @mikebettison)
philip.chapman@bbc.co.uk (Twitter is @PhilipChapman)

The feminist presenter who hates statistics/facts is:
sarah.julian@bbc.co.uk (Twitter is @sarahjulianotts)

Peter Saull, BBC Radio Nottingham political reporter:
peter.saull@bbc.co.uk (Twitter is @petesaull) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your chance to comment on the BBCs anti-male bias to the BBC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 16:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 20:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posting for non Uk Redditors who wouldn't have been able to access the BBC iPlayer link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Buchanan and other Ashfield candidates answer questions from an all-women audience  BBC Radio Nottingham (link works for international listeners) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 20:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 04:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must have missed shared parenting, genital mutilation, the entire justice system, domestic violence, suicide, and healthcare discrimination just to name a few. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 02:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the comments have a real go at the Mirror's "journalism" so that's great. Also there's no other MSM source covering the story really and some people only like to read MSM content.

If they close comments or start censoring them then I'll happily delete this post. Here's an archive link for those who don't want to give them traffic: https://archive.is/UEdn1
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 02:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologies for linking to the Mirror and a Mirror hit-piece at that, though it is at least MSM coverage of this story and I can't find anything else.

Obviously the article is pretty rubbish, not just in their bias but also in failing to challenge the BBC's misconduct. However, the comments are well worth a read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Men's rights' leader furious at having to address all-women audience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 02:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jury finds Shayna Hubers guilty of murder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 01:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The real victim of rape culture? Free speech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 23:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This guy has started legal proceedings for defamation against the feminist-run block-bot - please donate to his fund if you can </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 23:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goldsmiths University diversity officer banned white cis men from 'anti-racism' event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 22:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 15:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a day out, it was 8th March. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 14:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Mirror is a feminist newspaper (and a tabloid one at that), they are running a smear campaign against him. That's not to say he's perfect, but his party is 100 times more trustworthy and honest than this source.

Even teh headlines is nonsense - the main issue was that teh discussion was about women's issues and thus the BBC was again marginalising men. He'd happily discuss his manifesto in front of any audience of any gender, but the BBC were clearly attempting to stop him from doing so by rigging the discussion format. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 14:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  as it goes on it just gets more regressive, arguing for greater restrictions on abortion etc.

J4M B are pretty receptive to feedback. If you disagree with a policy area and have sources to back up your case then get in touch with them (and perhaps also mention which polices you also really like) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 04:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty obvious that there must be some hardcore man-hating feminists at BBC Radio Nottingham. Anyhow, some good comments on that Mirror article at the moment, keep them coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Men's rights' leader furious at having to address all-women audience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 03:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anxiety in Eldoret after NGO forcibly circumcises 30 boys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 02:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 02:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not hilarious when you're forced to do it though is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Army to review decision to have male cadets wear high heels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 02:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 02:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try doing the same to any other group and see how that goes.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 01:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I'm pretty sure they have to, though they conveniently "forgot" to invite Ray Barry (the other J4MB candidate) from the debate with a mixed gender audience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 01:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  they are not going to invite him back if they know he isn't going to stick to the format

They don't have any choice thanks to the way they're funded. I'm sure Mike wouldn't have done this on a commercial channel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 01:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except that's the only BBC debate to feature J4M B seeing as their other candidate wasn't even invited to the BBC debate in his constituency.

100% of BBC debates featuring J4M B feature all female audiences. Thus men have been banned from each and every BBC J4M B election discussion.

There is not a single opportunity anywhere for any man to engage with the party that represents them on the BBC. 

The BBC are guilty of interfering with the political process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 01:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It occurred on 9th March 2011. No male writers were allowed to contribute a single Comment piece to the Guardian. 
Udpate, it was actually 8th March 2011:
http://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2011/mar/09/cif-women-only-international-womens-day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 01:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure I agree with his tactic, though to be fair the BBC started all the trouble and he's just fighting fire with fire. I think his strategy could have worked with a little more practice.

The real battle is of course isn't that debate but in holding the BBC to account for what they've done here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 01:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wants to end special treatment at all stages, for example in training too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 01:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't his best performance, though he was under extremely unfair conditions. Listen to some more in depth interviews with him or alternatively Google Ray Barry who's the guy the BBC wouldn't even let take part. He's a excellent speaker with a huge amount of  compassion and sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 00:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Guardian even banned male writers for an entire day, so I'm not exactly exaggerating am I?

I should empahsise that as a private company they're entitled to do such stupid things,  and i support their right to be complete idiots. Completely different rules apply to the BBC, thus making this a significant scandal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 00:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a lie, all J4M B want to see is an end to all special treatment for women and for all recruitment to be based 100% on merit. Read the manifesto: https://j4mb.files.wordpress.com/2014/09/141228-v7-general-election-manifesto.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 00:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It does mean that media, in this case pro-feminism BBC, sets the rules, but I'm afraid there is no way around it.

Well the rules in question were almost certainly a breach of the BBC Charter and hence illegal. I'm sure he wouldn't have tried the same thing on a commercial outlet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 00:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that certainly isn't J4M B policy and I'm pretty sure they take the same view as almost the entire men's human rights community who simply want women to be treated as adults instead of as children as is presently the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 00:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely it's feminists who treat women as children thinking they always need special treatment and dont' ever deserve to go to prison? Parties such as J4M B want women to be treated as adults. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 00:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there's a real gap in the market that your party could fill here. UKIP have already adopted the J4M B policy on shared parenting, and they win over a lot fo men if they continued to cherry pick a few further similar proposals from the J4M B manifesto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 00:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in all fairness he was quite clearly shaken and upset by the blatant dirty tricks of the BBC. I think the point he was trying to make was that the BBC were attempting to marginalise men and he was just trying to do his own thing and not playing by their rules. I agree with your points though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 23:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May not work if you're not in the UK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 22:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the J4M B manifesto for all 20. A few off the top of my head:

* A sexist education system
* Almost zero support for the 40% of domestic violence victims who happen to be male
* Genital mutilation of girls is illegal yet is NHS funded on boys
* Different prison sentences for teh same crime depending on your gender.
* Zero rights for fathers, only responsibilities.
* Huge inequalities in healthcare spending based on gender, even on condition with the same number of deaths: e.g. prostate vs breast cancer

As for your point about men in Parliament, well its women who voted to put them there and simply democracy in action. Who voted for the BBC to ban men from their audience, I certainly wasn't asked and I doubt the candidates were either.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 22:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he was just extremely angry at being stiched up by the BBC. he has invested countless hours campaigning, fund-raising, writing the manifesto etc, only to have his biggest media appearance ruined by a rigged audience and rigged line of questioning. On top of all that his party colleague was completely excluded from the only other debate too. It's a complete scandal and the sort of thing you'd expect the Guardian to do, not a supposedly neutral broadcaster.

Update - Mike now reports that the BBC attempted to justify the all female audience based on the fact that 52% of the electorate is female

Second update - **The Mirror have picked up this story:** http://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/mens-rights-party-leader-left-5571931

**Link to BBC complaints page:** http://www.bbc.co.uk/complaints/complain-online/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 22:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably based on all the women who give up completely on work to raise a family (and men's tendency to work long hours and over-time).

Edit here's one article making the same claim: http://www.dailymail.co.uk/debate/article-2532461/Why-having-women-doctors-hurting-NHS-A-provovcative-powerful-argument-leading-surgeon.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 22:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have an anti-male bias in terms of how they run the country and the laws and polices they introduce. The genitalia of those formulating such misandrist polices is completely irrelevant - both male and female politicians are guilty of discriminating against the male population.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 21:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They wouldn't need to flip it around because men are already catered to by the establishment: 74% of candidates running for election are men

Politicians happen to be male, but male voters are outnumbered by females and politicians are notorious for pandering to female voters. J4M B outline 20 areas in which the state discriminates against men and boys, with no one able to provide a single example of the state doing the same to women. Thus reality is the complete opposite to what you describe.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 21:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will appear on the BBC website shortly (though often blocked for international viewers). Mike will almost certainly have it up on youtube and accessible to all within a few days.

**Update, it is now up on the BBC website:** http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p02pc3mc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 20:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll be able to listen to a recording of the broadcast here:

http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p02pc3mc 

Note that BBC Nottingham also failed to even invite the other Justice for men and Boys to the debate in his consistency, so their only chance to make their case was an an event discussing women's issues.

Also bar in mind that the BBC has a legal obligation to be neutral and fair.

You can submit complaints to the BBC here: http://www.bbc.co.uk/complaints/complain-online/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 20:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll be able to listen to a recording of the broadcast here:

http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p02pc3mc

Note that BBC Nottingham also failed to even invite the other Justice for men and Boys to the debate in his consistency, so their only chance to make their case was an an event discussing women's issues.

You can send complaints to Mike Bettison, I think his email is Mike.Bettison@bbc.co.uk  His twitter is @mikebettison

And if you're interested in J4M B as a result of the debate then you can read the manifesto the BBC is so afraid of here:
https://j4mb.files.wordpress.com/2014/09/141228-v7-general-election-manifesto.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC bans men from audience of the only election debate to feature the Justice for Men and Boys party. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 19:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC bans men from audience of the only election debate to feature the Justice for Men and Boys party. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 19:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC - Live Radio Nottingham General Election debate with Mike Buchanan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 19:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 19:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Program has started, Mike isn't taking any prisoners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 18:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **The debate starts in 53 minutes, tune in here:** http://www.bbc.co.uk/radio/player/bbc_radio_nottingham </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 16:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just posted the link, I'm not a member of J4M B. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 14:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An absolute scandal, they're not even trying to be fair now the election is getting close.

The guy in charge of BBC Radio Nottingham is Mike Bettison, **his email should be Mike.Bettison@bbc.co.uk**

Demand both an all male audience for a debate in future not to mention a full interview with Ray Barry before the election and also an apology.

You can also find him on Twitter.

Update, Mike reports that the BBC attempted to justify banning men **based on the fact that 52% of the electorate is female!**

Update 2, in addition to contacting Bettison **I strongly suggest people make formal complaints to the BBC. You can do so at the following link**: http://www.bbc.co.uk/complaints/complain-online/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC bans men from audience of the only election debate featuring the Justice for Men and Boys party. (and the host is female too!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 14:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NUS Conference Censor UKIP, Spin All Parties Invited </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 14:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 13:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The purpose of the suspension is to enable the rest of the committee to consider what action they should take. They are still to decide on this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 06:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and if a politician just told some nice racist jokes about killing black people that would be ok too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 04:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd only need to look at bank and credit card statements really. Such women often flaunt their purchases on social media in order to annoy the father. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Skye dads': The fathers who only see their children on a computer screen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 04:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 04:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  say the father pays $100 a month and the mother spends $150 of her own money on the child what happens to that $100? is that part of the $150 or is it not? 

As long as spending on the child exceeds the father's contribution then there's no major issue. I'm talking about when the child has to go without due to the mother blowing child support on a luxuries for herself, something that can sometimes happen just to try to spite the father.

It's very simple - the law needs to state that chils support HAS to be spent on things that benefit the child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 04:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the aspects of having that exact money solely being spent on the child is incredibly difficult to manage. 

No it isn't, the mother would easily be able to demonstrate that all the money (and more) went towards things for the child.

You're missing the point, there should be something in the law that states child support is to be spent on raising the child. If the mother has designer handbags and 100 pairs of shoes (and no job) and the child barely has any clothes, toys, books etc then there's something wrong and it should be illegal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 02:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you **please** delete that link and replace it with an archive. They don't allow comments so there's zero point in giving them any traffic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 02:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  child support is being paid, ultimately, to support a child

Child support is paid to the mother who's free to spend it entirely on herself. Ultimately, this woman did commit a genuine offence in failing to wear a seatbelt and thus could have avoided the situation easily. A walking cashpoint father who loses his job is 100% innocent of any wrongdoing yet can still go to prison and could have done absolutely nothing to avoid it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 01:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The video notes that these are effectively debtor prisons and that they'll supposedly take people to prison even quicker than for not paying child support. However, surely many of those failing to pay unreasonable child support demands are also in prison for being poor.

Why is going to prison for not paying child support implied as being OK and ending up there for other debts such a scandal?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 00:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the name of her party, the "Liberal Democrats" is the full name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 23:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So she just hates males now but doesn't actually want to kill every single one of them any more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 23:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For her to admit explicitly that she hates men isn't exactly backing down though is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 21:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, just trying to be fair and perhaps playing devil's advocate a little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 21:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only defence I can think of for the party is that they are known for being keen on due process. That said, senior figures could still easily have condemned the comments voluntarily instead of just burying their heads in the sand over this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 21:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well as a male she wants to kill me, so there's that for a start. This story is no longer about Noble anyway, it's now about how the Lib Dems deal with this issue and a lot of people are watching with interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 21:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please remember to follow some of the Twitter accounts she's given level one block bot rating to for no good reason. It's important that this sort of thing backfires. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 21:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about if they actually kick her out the party? Would that change your view? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whites and males have been banned from an 'anti-racism' event at a British university </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 19:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kill all men Lib Dem proud of hating men </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 19:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kill all men Lib Dem proud of hating men, abuses block-bot position to silence critics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 19:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kill all men Lib Dem proud of hating men, abuses block-bot position to silence critics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 18:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kill all men Lib Dem proud of hating men, abuses block-bot position to silence critics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 18:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kill all men Lib Dem proud of hating men, abuses block-bot position to silence critics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 18:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U of A Student Arrested for Lying About Sexual Assault </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 13:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 13:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I expect the main reason is sexism against men and that the concept of targeting female abusers simply wouldn't appeal to a bloodthirsty audience, many of whom don't like to think females can even be paedophiles (unless the victim is female too).

They may be other factors too though. For example, most female paedophlies I've read about tend to abuse people they already know. It wouldn't be possible for catch a predator to confront all the female predators in our schools, nurseries etc, nor all those sexually abusing their own children or children of close relatives, so maybe the pattern of offending is different?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Army ROTC program allegedly pushed men to wear high heels for 'Walk a Mile in Her Shoes' event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 02:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vandals target Ukip office in Mortimer Street in Herne Bay with swastikas and graffiti </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 20:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 20:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've submitted a complaint to the author and encourage others to do the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 20:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Male extinction is a complete myth, very poor journalism from the BBC:  http://www.techtimes.com/articles/6070/20140428/y-chromosome-study-suggests-men-arent-going-to-become-extinct-anytime-soon.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 20:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The stat in the article has been debunked and either complete nonsense or at best a massive exaggeration. At the current rate of change men would be extinct in many billions of years.

http://www.techtimes.com/articles/6070/20140428/y-chromosome-study-suggests-men-arent-going-to-become-extinct-anytime-soon.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Misandrist BBC pushing male extinction myths again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 20:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Men should stand up to feminists, not turn their backs on womankind </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 20:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help Me Get Back To My Dad - (x-post from r/videos) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 19:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 18:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't this the same Guardian newspaper which got a bunch of left wing Brits to contact random Americans to instruct them to vote Democrat so Bush lost the election?

http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/worldnews/northamerica/usa/1474828/Guardian-calls-it-quits-in-Clark-County-fiasco.html

(a campaign organised by a guy who now works for the BBC). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Babysitter accused of sexually assaulting 2 boys pleads guilty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 16:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 00:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it wouldn't be if the boys had a similar session the following week. However, I expect even if she a session existed they'd mostly be workshops on ho to stop yourself from raping and murdering females all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 21:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So being a racist shouldn't be a crime?

Supporting ISIS is far worse than being a racist. Your average racist wants to deport immigrants they don't like, not murder them using terrorist acts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 21:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  She's given responses for both in the AMA

Not aware of any responses about their domestic violence lies as I didn't realise anyone had challenged them yet. Also her prison's response was unsatisfactory so she need to be confronted again really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 17:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone ask about their sexist prison's policy please.

Also maybe ask why they lie about domestic violence on their policy pages too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dad falsely accused of 'satanic' abuse speaks of ordeal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 14:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Guardian Australia corrects domestic violence article </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 03:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 02:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't see the claimed explanation for their pricing policy. A very strange company.

Here's the original thread for those who didn't catch it the other week: https://www.reddit.com/r/MensRights/comments/31ragv/this_uk_gym_charges_men_60_more_than_women_for/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Update - Peak Fitness Gym statement on their pricing policy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 02:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 21:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has only been suspended. so that's still a real possibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberal Democrat executive committee member suspended over kill all men hate tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 19:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 15:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KotakuInAction is the go-to place on Reddit for block-bot related news. The Lib-Dem sexism angle isn't the only aspect to this story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 15:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but it can still be the straw that broke the camel's back. How they handle this is going to be very interesting to a lot of people and I do wonder how they would have acted had the gender's been reversed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 15:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it is indeed a "joke" within feminist circles then how come there are multiple feminist academics who genuinely want to eliminate most of the male population and are widely admired within feminist circles for their work?

And how come the rest of the Twitter feed contains contempt for men too? Is the entire feed and their role on 4 Lib Dem committees also just a joke? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 15:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It all depends on the outcome of the investigation really, though the silence from Lib Dem HQ may put equality minded people off voting Lib Dem too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 15:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This is a single tweet

There's at least 10 of them all along the same lines, and that's without even searching properly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 14:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Caving in when confronted by hysterical Breitbart witch hunts

The suspension occurred before Breitbart got involved - they're reporting on the suspension and didn't write anything prior to this action.

Even assuming the tweets are a "joke", then presumably is ok for other politicians to have joked about rape or cockle pickers etc? 

And if we're truly looking at things in context, then we have to include the wider context of Noble's very clear dislike of men and their human rights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 14:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He mentions her too much, but she's worth bringing up occasionally.

The fact that Labour left her out of a document of the history of women in politics in the UK tells you that feminists don't want anyone to remember her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 12:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In defence of some Lib Dem bodies, it seems that many were unaware of her views before this. The local branch have now acted properly (or at least started to process of doing so), as have the Secular and humanist Lib Dems.

The problem is the other two Lib Dem committees - other redditors have expressed concern about previous goings on at the LGBT Lib Dems in particular. The response of Lib Dem HQ has also been hopeless, all I can guess is perhaps they have to leave things to Noble's local party or something?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberal Democrat executive committee member suspended over kill all men hate tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 00:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 02:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **This story is currently the main feature article on the Breitbart London site!**

http://www.breitbart.com/london/

774 comments and counting!

also the 3rd most popular article on the whole of Breitbart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 02:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well with people abandoning the traditional players, they're certainly becoming pretty significant. I know there are concerns about the Breitbart US operation, but there's a hell of a lot of talent in their London division right now.

A lot of people moan when Breitbart links are submitted, but on so many stories recently they've been the only people actually doing the journalism and covering important issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberal Democrat executive committee member suspended over kill all men hate tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 01:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 23:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice to finally  see some MSM coverage of this story. Wonder when the BBC and Guardian will feature it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Kill All Men': Lib Dem Activist in Hate Speech Scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 23:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 23:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great to see some MSM coverage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Kill All Men': Lib Dem Activist (and block-bot admin) in Hate Speech Scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 19:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Kill All Men': Lib Dem Activist in Hate Speech Scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 19:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Kill All Men': Lib Dem Activist in Hate Speech Scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 19:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World's biggest men's rights leaflet campaign so far? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 18:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Authoritarian Activists Are Censoring Twitter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 17:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Authoritarian Activists Are Censoring Twitter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 17:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How authoritarian activists are censoring Twitter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 17:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Authoritarian Activists Are Censoring Twitter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 17:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long-term study finds no link between videogames and sexism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 17:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 16:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I note that coverage of this story prior to the suspension was dismissed by moderators here as "a farcical non-story" and censored form this sub.

Anyway, the latest developments obviously debunk such a claim 100%. It's great to see the Lib Dems taking some action against hate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberal Democrat executive committee member suspended over kill all men hate tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 16:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 13:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are some notorious misandrists working at Bristol university so this motion is no surprise really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Complementing women on handwriting is sexist according to Bristol student leaders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 13:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Labour  the nasty party in Ashfield </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 11:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton Presidency: We need to talk about Hillary and domestic violence claims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 10:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton Presidency: We need to talk about Hillary and domestic violence claims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 10:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 20:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's only on the policy committee so probably not even mentioned as its her least significant role of the four. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 20:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As we said before, it doesn't block abuse. In fact one of the admins is about as abusive a person you can find on Twitter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 19:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but people sign up to it assuming it does roughly what it promises to do. They're being duped. Some idiot at the BBC even did a feature on it which implied it was useful and legitimate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 18:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just send an email if you want to hide your accent, though in many ways it would send quite a powerful message if the scandal is now getting worldwide attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 18:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It claims to block sexism, harassment, hate etc, but in reality it's just a tool used to silence people they don't like for any reason whatsoever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 18:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only suspended at present, not booted out, and that's only in relation to one regional executive committee. She still sits on three further Lib Dem committees (and of course remains a member of the party too for now). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 14:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes but no one is censoring her political beliefs. "Kill all men" isn't much a real opinion or argument, it's the ultimate violent hate speech.

Furthermore, the Lib Dems are mostly quite a moderate party, so she's working for the wrong organisation. if she wants to make insane hate tweets she's free to try to get a similar role in the Green party or even labour where I'm sure she'd be welcomed with open arms.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 14:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She advocated genocide FF, all the tweets are blatant breaches of party rules.

It's not textbook SJW, I think we've been quite restrained. For one thing the SJW''s would definitely have reported her to the police by now (and they'd probably have arrested her) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 13:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I'm aware, they're not paid positions. At a guess they probably pay expenses at the very most.

People usually volunteer to work in such position in the hope of getting a more senior /elected role later (which would be paid).

Quite frankly, if she'd have deleted the tweets the moment we exposed them and apologised then she wouldn't' be in such a deep hole today and non one would have pursued the matter. She's the one who's left the tweets in place and continued along the same path. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 12:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just hijacking this comment to remind everyone to remember to contact the other executive committees who have yet to suspend Noble:

* http://lgbt.libdems.org.uk/en/page/executive
* http://hsld.org.uk/en/contact
* http://www.liberalyouth.org/people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 12:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please remember to contact the other executive committees who have yet to suspend Noble:

* http://lgbt.libdems.org.uk/en/page/executive
* http://hsld.org.uk/en/contact
* http://www.liberalyouth.org/people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 11:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30K+ people have read about this scandal, yet still not a single word from the MSM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 11:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully they're just following procedure to the book so she can't appeal on a technicality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 11:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's only been suspending to allow the investigation to take place. Doesn't guarantee she will actually be kicked off the committee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberal Democrat executive committee member suspended over kill all men hate tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 10:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberal Democrat executive committee member suspended over kill all men hate tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 10:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberal Democrat executive committee member suspended over kill all men hate tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 10:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Block-bot admin suspended from Liberal Democrat executive committee over kill all men hate tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 10:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberal Democrat executive committee member suspended over kill all men hate tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 10:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 23:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **NO**, that would be the typical feminist response and we need to be better than that. instead, simply debunk all the lies with facts and expose how sexist the posters are.

If the feminists have any decency they'll then take down their own posters out of embarrassment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Married womans fake rape claim after consensual sex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 15:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ABC misleads. No, its not more dangerous to be a woman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 14:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 01:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see much sexism at all by MRAs. it's true they complain about feminists a lot and that's fine so you're correct there, though it's unfortunate when either side confuses feminism with women. It's great to attack the former and not appropriate to do so with the latter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You Can't Trust Buzzfeed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 01:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 01:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we should just lie to kids now?

Amazing how sexism against boys gets spun into a good thing. Also I note the BBC didn't identify which teachers were the sexist ones. Did the report say anything further on this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 22:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many thanks, i thought you meant you'd posted it to her own Facebook wall. Totally forget that the web chat was today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 21:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, any chance of forwarding the link to this post please or providing a screen grab? We really like to thoroughly document every piece of evidence so that people fully trust our articles and work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man shaming and victim blaming: The A-Z of male suicide in the UK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 18:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review - No More Sex War: The Failures Of Feminism by Neil Lyndon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 18:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review - No More Sex War: The Failures Of Feminism by Neil Lyndon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 16:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice for Men and Boys 2015 General Election Manifesto </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 14:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man shaming and victim blaming: The A-Z of male suicide in the UK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 13:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man shaming and victim blaming: The A-Z of male suicide in the UK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 13:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC Panorama  A death in the family </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 13:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 04:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Working for the Guardian doesn't prove she's a man-hating feminist and you will occasionally see good articles from the paper, even about men. However, Bennett was a senior figure at the Fawcett Society, and hating men is pretty much part of the job description for anyone working there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 04:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a similar theme to the prisons question, I'd be interested to know the following. What is the Green Party's source for their domestic violence policy which states:

*"it is acknowledged that a large majority of cases involve abuse by men against women".*

The UK crime survey is considered by far the most reliable source for such material, and that shows 40% of victims were men, a pattern that's been seen for years in study after study. Furthermore, such studies don't even usually identity the gender of the abuser, again suggesting their statement is extremely dubious and this looks like more feminist sexist to go along with the prions policy.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 23:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Defending prison rape? Really classy. How the hell is getting raped in prison in any way the same argument as working in a somewhat inherently dangerous profession? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 22:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 2015 sexist feminists are the norm I'm afraid, and it's genuinely egalitarian feminists such as Christine Hoff Sommers who are the exception.

Feminism might have been about equality in 1960, but looking at the behaviour of most feminists then it's clear that isn't the case today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elmo banned from Witney Hustings with Prime Minster on Friday night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 22:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 21:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bennett seems to be the typical sort of sexist feminist, something that's all too common today.

If you read up on her background she worked for the Fawcett Society, an organisation synonymous with promoting special treatment and ever more privileges for women (whilst doing absolutely nothing to address any issues that impact men). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 21:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sceptical about a lot of these supposedly expert reports, and the most important thing is often to uncover any bias (or stupidity) of the author or research it is based upon.

They tend to be a mixed bag really, for example the Stern review into rape was fantastic by all accounts, whereas the Norgrove report into shared parenting was based on complete lies and has since been completely debunked, with a researcher taking issue into a completely false interpretation of her work.

I imagine this research is more Norgrove-like than Stern-like and at best it only tells half the story. For example it's absolutely true that an awful lot of women who are in prison simply don't belong there (tv licence evaders for example). However, what the various researchers and pressure groups fail to mention is that such prisoners are at least matched and almost certainly outnumbered by the vast proportion of female criminals who benefit from bias in the justice system at every single stage (and therefore should currently be locked up in place of the other women).

Up to 20% of peadophiles are women yet there number in prison is absolutely tiny. Similarly, women are actually more likely to initiate domestic violence against their partner than the other way round and at least 40% of domestic violence victims are men, yet the number pf women actually prosecuted for violence and abuse of men is still very small, and the actual number imprisoned smaller still.

The entire present narrative on this issue is essentially a complete lie. The idea that the justice system overall discriminates against women is the complete opposite of reality, and we have judges openly admittng they'd have given harsher sentences to female criminals had they been male. Philip Davies MP gave an excellent speech in Parliament a while back outlining this, which I'd recommend to anyone interested in the topic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 18:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a satisfactory answer from Bennett, there's absolutely no need to single out women if a term such as "parents" would be more valid.

 many are victims of sexual assault and domestic violence, many have mental health issues

All these things also apply to men, and men are subject to more violence overall than women too. I also note on the same policy page the Party blatantly lies about domestic violence, stating: "it is acknowledged that a large majority of cases involve abuse by men against women".

This is totally false - the UK crime survey shows that 40% of domestic violence victims are men, so the number of women who are victims is 60% at most. However, that survey ignores children  taking the number of women easily below 50% and that's still women abused by anyone. DV is particularly high in lesbian relationships so this amazingly specific crime of violence by men against women is smaller still. The Green Party i lying about domestic violence and then it uses this lie to attempt to justify it's sexist prison policy.

Anyway thanks for the link, I was already a firm believer that Greens needed to get rid of Bennett, and if she's also one fo those responsible for introducing such shockingly sexist policies then she really needs to go ASAP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 16:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems a pretty indefensive position. Surely this blatant discrimination will alienate at least  49% of the electorate once people get to know about this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sexist Green Party policy: "the only women who should be in custody are those very few that commit serious and violent crimes and who present a threat to the public." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 16:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 15:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The text in question is found at point CJ381 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sexist Green Party policy: "the only women who should be in custody are those very few that commit serious and violent crimes and who present a threat to the public." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 15:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 60 Minutes investigates: The Duke rape case (2015) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 15:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Florida man wearing Cookie Monster bag says theater discriminated against him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 08:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Florida man wearing Cookie Monster bag says theater discriminated against him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 08:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
