<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4298</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 23:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Fantastic at compiling fake job histories and references" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 23:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone posts the same question every other day it seems </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 23:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes people can. Would you like to be bound by something you said 2-3 years ago? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 23:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Polaris would have nothing to do with it, but yeah, they made it into a makeshift studio. Mark hangs out there a lot.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 06:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, none of that should take 20 minutes. And that's not even real editing, that's just overlaying text, and if that takes you 20 minutes, then you might want to consider a different field. Plus, if you use the same font and color every video (like the Grumps do) then you would have it saved as a preset, reducing a 2 minute job to 2 seconds. Keyframing text to fly in does not take a lot of time, though it would vary, it shouldn't take longer than a minute (and consider that it happens once per episode ON OCCASION) 

With the format of editing Kevin is given, using primarily presets and an assembly-line style of churning out episodes, there is no reason he should have messed up any of the times people have counted (other than laziness) The only time he's even responded to people's criticisms is when it legitimately wasn't his fault (an episode being six minutes long) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 19:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just because "it's the internet" and it's what people have come to expect, doesn't mean it should be that way and that nobody should focus on improving it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 19:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they brought in someone that was funny, I think it'd be better.

Plus, it's only Ross that's played with them, so you haven't seen them play off of anyone else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 18:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remove the last one, then replace Kevin with Holly and I'd watch it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 18:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be the best series imaginable! This was one of my favorite PS2-era games, I forgot it existed, I'm gonna go look up and see if I can buy it somewhere! Thank you!

(And like everyone else saying this: It would HAVE to include Dan, so either him on Grumpcade or a series on GG) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 16:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure VentGrumps has a good list going. Mostly from what I've seen, people say "Kevin edit this in" and he doesn't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 06:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every edit that he's missed or messed up on takes about a minute or two to complete.

Source: I'm an editor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 17:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh yeah, I forgot about that.... this might suck then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 10:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get it! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 10:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's just a watered down Pewdiepie to me. Neither of them are funny in any way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 10:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it's already been debunked quite a few times. Didn't even think it was still a fad. I'm amazed he's on it, considering that he seems to think of himself as educated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 07:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or he could just be at their office again.

God, I hope this guy is never on GG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 07:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think working on something with the Grumps and this project are mutually exclusive. It's not too distracting of a task to stop into the Grump office for two hours to be a guest on their show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 07:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he's not forced to do anything by a Multichannel Network, they'll just recommend certain collaborations and deals to him, likely providing him incentive to meet their requests.

He probably just hates Los Angeles, most people do, honestly.


But I agree with you, the Polaris collaborations are so pointless. Most people don't know the majority of their partners and most of them are kinda the same youtube channel, producing the same content under a different name. But I'm willing to bet this isn't a Polaris project, but a JonTron project that he requested Polaris's help in scheduling/contacting these other youtubers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 07:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> look, dude, I understand it's just a joke, but I can't suspend my disbelief entirely!

**At his job?** Seriously? Jokes have to have SOME sort of basis in reality here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 20:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, you gotta follow through with the setting and details: For example:

"In prison." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 20:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully this raises awareness enough for people to not put their fucking change collection in an unprotected container in a bathroom! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 20:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only funny if it's not a parent or a relative. Just some guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 20:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 20:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> probably some kind of "look at this neat trick I can do" video </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 19:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's some funny goat-related humor! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 19:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everybody shut up! This post has given me an erection! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 19:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it'd be more likely that he ditches it for his two bands and other projects full time, along with moving to Cali. But perhaps there's also an available physicist job out there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 03:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, I had a webseries in mind that was a parody of Dungeons Dragons type stuff that would use this joke.

This is the only sub where I figured I wouldn't get downvoted for using it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 01:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I created the joke. I always thought it'd be funny if some actual racist people in a fantasy setting referred to them as "Shadow People" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 01:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just a joke, dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 01:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, "I left mah lyrics at home, nigga!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 23:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're like people, but their skin color is the color of a shadow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 22:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda funny. Could've been a little clearer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 22:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they sink? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 22:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shadow People </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 22:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Argonians </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 22:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually want to hear the full song </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 22:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's black. Blacks (aka, the Shadow People) stereotypically abandon their offspring (mostly just the males though) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 22:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> E.T... phone Health Insurance Agency... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 22:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not enjoying it. It has some funny moments here and there, but I hate when they talk about the games, which they're doing a lot of here (unless the game is interesting, which Bloodborne does not appear to be.) I was actually thinking about getting it, till they started playing it and I realized how boring and repetitive it seems

Edit: Don't forget to downvote if you disagree with me, cumfaggots :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 06:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other than Dave Chappelle and Ron White, I don't like a single one of those or a single joke I've heard from anyof them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 05:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Write a youtube comment demanding that he come back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 05:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya know what bugs ME? Steel Panther is in it. God, they suck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 05:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then name me some funnier ones 

(This is not confrontational, I'd actually like to discover some if you happen to name any I haven't heard) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 05:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, that story is what sold me on Jim Jefferies. i saw bits and pieces of his anti-religion stuff, but when I listened to the album that one was on, I realized he can be funny with any subject matter. His TV show is pretty good too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 05:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The funniest Stand-Up Comedian Alive Today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 01:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And a shapeshifter (He's actually Danny in his spare time) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 15:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jon's getting a sex change operation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 15:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beej 2: The *coming* of JonTron </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 21:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as stoners like to THINK they are funny or interesting when they're high, they're not. I don't think a single one of them even smokes weed (excluding Danny, who used to) and despite Stout Train existing, none of those episodes were good at all. (And I LOVE alcohol, so I thought it would be interesting, at least if they discussed it)

I wouldn't mind a Drunk Grumps with just Dan and Arin, especially if it's Arin's first time being drunk, but it would have to be a chill, non-obnoxious episode and not act all stupid-drunk like Barry and Ross did. Something more along the lines of Toon Grumps would be interesting. (I mean, they can play games, but be FAR less into whatever is on the screen)

But stoned? Sorry, but I'd skip over an episode of them just laughing uncontrollably for no reason and talking about how hungry they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 20:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be the most horrible edition of Game Grumps in its entire history </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 17:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, played it last week. It's aged beautifully and I don't think a single Mario game has topped it since </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 17:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know when he'll be on Sleepy Cast? I'm more excited for THAT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 17:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, right!? How can they not know shit about the dude who invented **Salad!?** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 16:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> incorrect statement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 16:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Complaining can get annoying can't it?

Maybe now you understand why we don't like his bullshit with this game (An insanely easy game to master) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 09:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FOR THE LOVE OF GOD DON'T STICK THAT THING IN MY ASSHOLE!!! PLEASE!! I'll sacrifice the lives of my children if you leave my anus intact! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 09:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this look RARE to you!?!? This steak should've been mooing a little when you set my plate down! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 09:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuck, shoulda read the comments first. i posted the same thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 09:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Et Tu, Brute? .....and vice versa? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 09:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This doesn't suck at all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 09:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Your performance in this position has been unsatisfactory and I'm afraid we'll have to let you go"


"Whatever! Come at me, SCRUB-LORD, I'm Ripped!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 07:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Second Endless Ocean is my personal favorite. They're both at the top of their comedic game in that one. That's the first episode of GG I've rewatched (haven't finished it yet though. Been meaning to start it where I left off) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 05:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, dude, Game Grumps doesn't have a parent company and you're reading WAAY too much into them going on vacation. Do you know how much Starbomb albums have sold? They can afford multiple vacations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 18:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 is the only good one anyway. If he played the first one I can see why he hate it.

I'd like to see a Spyro game on Grumps. Danny seems to love dragons and shit like that, so that could stir up some passionate discussion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 18:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should get one or two stars from each, then fight Bowser </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 18:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My fellow Americans... this nation is------ **I'll be right back!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 18:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Well kids, sorry, but that's the seventh night in a row... you know what that means!"

"We have to eat the firstborn?"

"That's right... Cody, you get a 10-second head start. RUN!"



(Arin.... how do you **LIVE** with yourself!?!?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 18:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you watch Grumps for the gameplay, then something is seriously wrong with you.

However, it isn't entertaining if someone keeps making the same fuck-up over and over and over and over again and blames the game for it. Not because I'm watching the gameplay and I want to see progression, but because the conversation becomes stagnant, and it's just annoying to hear Arin ~~bitch about~~ er- "analyze" video-games.

Personally, I can't even stand when they talk about games at all, because for the most part, they aren't funny about it. But there were a few episodes recently where the fuck-ups actually were hilarious. Maybe they just need to learn to edit some moments out like that. If there are a bunch of fuck-ups that are funny, leave em in. If not, then just cut out that footage, and use the star selection screen as a point of transition, that way nobody knows anything was edited out

Just treat the show like a podcast that uses video-games to inspire discussion and it's entertaining. Otherwise, not so much. Arin and Danny are both super funny guys and I don't watch GG to see them beat games. It'd be better if they stopped playing them every time they weren't having fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 08:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't stop laughing at this! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 03:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, an illiteracy joke. Clever :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Subreddits From Earlier Periods In History, if the Internet Existed Back Then </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 01:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 00:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably not that far from their real-life relationship </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 23:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did this work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 23:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a copy of my resume... You'll find that I did some work for a little organization called "FoxNews..." so I have plenty of experience of instilling fear in the hearts and minds of Conservatives. I heard you have a lot of them down here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 23:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he's gonna find out... it's not easy being Satan's Toilet!

"Hey, Rob! Why do you always act like you're such hot shit!?"

"Ya know what they say.... You are what you eat!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 23:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm your Friendly Neighborhood Eight-Legged Arachnid Individual" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 23:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you believe we're in the EXACT room where Lee Harvey Oswald shot Kennedy!? How ROMANTIC! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 23:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Fuck It! I'll Write It Live!"

(confused look) "But, we can't read it! There's no words there!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 20:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> perhaps in real life? But no, Pewdiepie isn't to thank for this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 15:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gravity  (I want to fly) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 15:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some random guy named Jim from the 1500s.

Just to see the look on his face and how he reacts.

"I have to do WHAT? Why ME!?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 15:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breathe and Speak </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 15:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It transforms into cotton candy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 15:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Browsing Reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 02:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't have Bad Controls

Doesn't have Bad Camera

Doesn't lack level variety or design

"Same Boss Fight Every Time" is a recurring Staple of the Mario series </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 02:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's just that it can't be only Dan and Arin. Then it would be a Game Grumps serial </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 02:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's being edited. It's an actual project, not just a Let's Play. These things take time. Perhaps Barry is the editor and perhaps it got delayed because he felt overwhelmed by *real* editing work. Perhaps it's just a really huge/long project and they don't want to start uploading until it's all done.  

But Ross has answered posts like this multiple times with a resounding "yes, it is coming" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 07:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally the most plausible theory I've seen on the matter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 16:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and doing a bad impression of Jon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 08:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little do we know, that comment at the bottom was by Chris himself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 08:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why are the characters drawn like talking penises? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 08:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice guys finish last </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
