<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4218</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-05 00:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do an AMA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-04 05:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boondock Saints: Two misogynistic religious fanatics from another country execute countless American citizens without a trial; the public remains divided. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-01 20:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think an exact fraction has been named, but giving even half of the sale of your life's work to charity is pretty cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Lucas donates majority of Disney money to charity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-01 17:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For any VHS or Beta fans out there, they're playing a free 21+ show at the Magic Stick this Thursday! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-31 03:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also my band Plastic Fifth is opening, so shameless plug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-31 00:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-30 17:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Backstory: We thought a "cooking" picture would be funny, but the accidental grease fire was much funnier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 06:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're suggesting that his misspoke in all instances linked to above? Yeah, I guess that's technically possible. But I think it's more likely that all politicians feel comfortable with some degree of deliberate distortion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 06:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Merriam Webster definition of Lie: "to make an untrue statement with intent to deceive."

I doubt Obama was really trying to pull one over on us with that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 05:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you check out my links? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 04:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't hard to find comprehensive lists of any candidates' lies; check out many of Romney's [here](http://www.politifact.com/personalities/mitt-romney/statements/byruling/false/) and [here](http://www.politifact.com/personalities/mitt-romney/statements/byruling/pants-fire/).

[*edited to correct links*] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Halloween costume: "cooking" and "I am the danger" embodied a little too literally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 00:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-27 13:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's nuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-27 13:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Criterion's occasional mainstream releases often help finance their Euro/art offerings, and have the potential to spread awareness of the company's mission to a broader base. Provided they're able to craft a compelling package that makes a case for the films' cultural and artistic merit, it shouldn't matter if they're widely popular or not, hipsters be damned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-26 16:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you like pop rock, they definitely have a few gems--[Change your Mind](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P-mW_0TUSy4) is a personal favorite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-22 17:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't tell you how many times I've futilely started this film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-22 15:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't feel all that secure to me--living in Lansing, I'm seeing huge roadside signs for Rogers, Romney and Ryan everywhere. Swing state or not, they're fighting for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-21 16:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a pretty grandiose take on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mitt Romney's Bain Helped Get High Schoolers Hooked On Cigarettes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-17 03:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 07:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch good stuff/make bad stuff. That's how you get better at every creative endeavor ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 04:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It always seems strange when people do blatantly phony stuff like this for cameras, especially in this day and age--an olde timey photo op is not the only source of information anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-10 07:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ain't no "one of" here, Debando. You're fucking a hundred duck horses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-09 23:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While a very interesting and detailed read, I don't think there's much evidence that Caden committed suicide. The film is obviously surreal and obsessed with death, but it doesn't seem to be governed by anything so concrete--relatively speaking--as purgatory. My two major objections:

1) Caden dies at the end. I would argue that exploring a confused, subjective and decidedly purgatorial life and death is a simpler, more elegant and more meaningful reality for the film than literalizing that purgatory and necessitating an unfocused set of rules for leaving it. Basically, there's no sense in killing the poor bastard twice.

2) There is no afterlife. This film was conceived as a horror film, and deals with all the worst fears a man like Caden can suffer, right up to the permanent disintegration of his tortured but solipsistic ego. Death is absolute, impersonal non-existence, and that is why it is terrifying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-08 07:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or a therapist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My band Plastic Fifth is up to possibly play a gig opening for VHS or Beta! Go to the Detroit section, check out our song "I Am," and please consider voting for us! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-07 18:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [alt/pop/rock] Plastic Fifth - I Am :: My band is up to possibly play a gig opening for VHS or Beta! Go to the Detroit section, check out our song "I Am," and please consider voting for us! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-07 18:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-05 19:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. If strangers were excessively nice to a famous person on Reddit, then that would totally affect me somehow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-05 07:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate that. :) Enough time has gone by that it's fine now, but it really was a surprisingly hurtful, emotional experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-05 06:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hardly think this article qualifies as a comprehensive list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 23:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> home break-in actually, lost a ton of other electronics as well. still good advice though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 04:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks great! do you have any experience with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT Request: how to theft-proof a laptop? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 04:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few years ago my laptop was stolen, and it was pretty devastating. I quickly learned the value of backing up important files, but does anyone have any free/low-cost tips for physical laptop tracking and creating comprehensive backups on a multi-hundred gigabyte level? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 02:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *shhhhhhhhhhhh!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-03 02:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it was a house of cards built on illogical and implausible scenarios, I think it violates its own logic throughout the movie, and it panders to the audience with cliche "chance" situations.

Oy. That's a different disagreement entirely.

Ah well, stalemate it is. I've done my best to provide some examples of this movie's unique qualities as differentiated from similar films, but there's nothing to be done about different, subjective reactions to the film's objective novelties. I *will* invite you to consider how your own favorite "original" works fare by the standard you're applying here, but I do concur that we'll likely not agree on *Looper*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-02 21:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Losing a hand is one thing, conscious ongoing torture of a future person through mutilation of their past self is quite another--by the same token, time regulation is one thing and time travel as an exclusively criminal enterprise is another as well. All time travel movies will have some things in common, much the same way that all Westerns or slashers do. A creative genre picture is measured by what the author does within those parameters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-02 20:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where, if I may ask, have you seen the torture and dismemberment through time travel scene before? That's certainly a watershed moment. :)

I would also be interested to know where, if anywhere, you've seen the organized use of time travel for criminal executions, which is of course the sci-fi premise that distinguishes the movie. The only thing I see that Looper and *12 Monkeys* (1995) or *Frequency* (2000) appreciably have in common is time travel.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-02 19:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair though, you can make literally everything this side of *Arrival of a Train at La Ciotat* sound derivative by reducing it to its broadest elements. The implied gore of the disappearing fingers, the completely unexpected curve into horror territory, the brutal simplicity of the executions, the little things like the Rainmaker's henchmen wearing the same clothes as the character on the poster on the young boy's wall. For me, it adds up to one of the most clever, surprising movie-going experiences of the year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-02 18:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't be terribly surprised to see an Original Screenplay nod, that's where the edgy/creative movies go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-01 22:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's entirely possible to feel sympathy for the professor and overwhelming relief that no one was hurt, and to laugh because it's such a bizarre situation. Go green! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-29 18:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dinosaurs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-28 21:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **FUCK YEAH I LOVE THEM!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Paul Thomas Anderson's American Quadrilogy": How four great films capture a century of American counter-history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-26 23:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Paul Thomas Anderson's American Quadrilogy": How four great films capture a century of American counter-history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-26 21:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-25 15:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the point is that it's cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 20:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you can tell it's a classy joint as soon as you walk in and see the glossy gold painted walls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 20:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd just like to chime in in favor of signature flavor Sesquicentennial Swirl, a birthday cake and frosting flavor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 12:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welp, I'm convinced! Thank you, Bob Thompson! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 05:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By not giving a shit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 20:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **I BROKE IT**. Feminist avant-garde filmmaker/dancer/actress Maya Deren [has no Bacon number](https://www.google.com/search?q=bacon+number+maya+deren).

Finally, my degree in film pays off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 12:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> on 9/11, yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-11 06:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No disrespect to the Special Olympics, but if someone earnestly asked you if you were going to participate, you'd probably be a little offended too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-11 05:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I laughed at this, and then I thought the sentence "spaghetti is a lesbian," and then I laughed again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-11 02:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit dude, you must be starving.

Oh, you mean the picture? That's not so bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] Small TV with an HDMI/DVI/VGA input </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 17:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently moved, and couldn't take my old TV with me. I cover TV shows for my second job, and I'd like to be able to switch between cable programming and some sort of PC input. Any help is much appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-05 22:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You win? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 10:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fireside cats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-29 05:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This strikes me as a reskinned, better articulated version of the classic r/atheism facebook post. Harumph. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-25 04:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fine, I added three unessential words to the conversation. To be fair though, you added nineteen. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 19:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not *universally* wrong, but it's worth exploring how systemic socio-economic pressures shape perception of such opportunities, how effort toward "self-improvement" offers vastly different pay-offs depending on one's starting lot in life, and your own role in the cyclical, real-word social climate propagated through the trite dismissal of the disadvantaged as "lazy." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 09:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their [interview with Kubrick](http://paulnahm.blogspot.com/2010/06/playboy-interview-wstanley-kubrick-in.html) is another great non-boob related Playboy article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 23:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was made as part of the A.V. Club's Parameter short film contest, details [here](http://www.avclub.com/parameter/info/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Ballad of Oscar Homeslice - a semi-animated short based on 15 strange parameters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 23:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-19 04:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tl;rd: i don't like all these i-gadgets, but that Jason Mraz fella is pretty good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-19 00:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the Onion/A.V. Club video player is pretty flaky. Here it is on the contest's [YouTube](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6BlynQBynQI feature=plcp) and on my personal [Vimeo](https://vimeo.com/46409913). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 19:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's part of their Parameter short film contest, details [here](http://www.avclub.com/parameter/info/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 18:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 16:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wzqXggZU3eE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 16:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first experience with AFX CS6 camera tracking: a semi-animated musical short about a crayon-drawn magical astronaut, now featured on the A.V. Club! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 16:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-14 19:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming you're talking about the [tilt-shift](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tilt%E2%80%93shift_photography) effect, you can achieve the opposite by making your focus as deep as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-13 21:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe in plain speaking, foolishnesss. What does "look up Lisa Ferentz" mean? Her institute doesn't appear to offer a Master's program; are you saying that you know her personally, studied under her, or are actively pursuing a trauma certificate?

Regardless, it seems that we're talking past each other. You're describing a hypothesis, and I'm saying that there's no evidence for it. This is compounded by the testibly valid prevalence of false memory--something we both appear to acknowledge--to the extent that "recovered" memories, being indistinguishable to the subject from false ones, should bare no legal, medical or personal weight without objective corroborating evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-13 18:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, like a masters level class...

What, is this a hypothetical? What is your Master's degree in? What department was this class in at what university? Have you taken this class? Who was the instructor, and what are his/her credentials? 

With regard to your questions:

A) Compare the memory to the objective facts. *Conscious* memory has proven time and again to be surprisingly malleable; "repressed" memory has yielded no provable information to my knowledge. Citations to the contrary are welcome.

B) The brain is a magnificent organ, but it's understandably not great at gauging its own accuracy. Simple as that.

The description of repressed memories as things people "think they think" is reasonably accurate. We code our memories in fairly broad strokes, and unknowingly update the context and details in accordance with our changing understanding of events. When the friendly policeman or the authoritative Freudian suggests that the subject was abused by Satan, he/she slowly and unwittingly updates their memory to comply with their evolving perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-13 18:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what "counseling class" means, but my understanding from five or six psychology courses over the past few years is that A) there's significantly more testable evidence for fabricated memories than there is for repression, and B) *if* repressed memories exist, they're not reliably distinguishable from fabrications, and are therefore not useful in any real sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 15:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here you go!](http://imgur.com/9ENJ9) I'm of much the same mind here; I'd like to balance out the hundred of roadside signs everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lansing voters: Remember that Congressman Mike Rogers sponsored CISPA when voting this fall, and feel free to remind others </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-08 23:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michigan activists: Remember that Congressman Mike Rogers sponsored CISPA when voting this fall, and feel free to remind others </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-08 23:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> East Lansing Voters: Remember that Congressman Mike Rogers sponsored CISPA when voting this fall, and feel free to remind others </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-08 23:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michigan's 8th District: Remember that Congressman Mike Rogers sponsered CISPA when voting this fall, and feel free to remind others </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-08 22:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-06 16:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is there any answer in particular you were looking for? if I say "ur right no difference," will you give me an asker's best and 500 yahoo points? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-06 15:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nearly every single Beatles song by either is [credited to both](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lennon%E2%80%93McCartney). You are correct, however, as that verse is [generally accepted](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Getting_Better#Composition) as Lennon's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-06 03:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're getting a lot of shit, but people who think of him exclusively as "badassery and Jack Daniels" are looking at his career pretty selectively. What exactly is bad-ass about "[Daddy Sang Bass?](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NGUP8oc9Bgs)" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-04 21:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bullshit. This is about consumer sovereignty: if a business engages in a practice you strongly oppose, then you organize a public boycott.The average American citizen doesn't have a ton of of political power, but we sure as fuck have this.

You say "opinion" like these are a bunch of riled up Packers fans or something. No. This is about sending a legal, moral message that bigotry doesn't pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-04 21:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New protest strategy: serve free competitor chicken outside the store. Undercuts profits, helps the consumer, another opportunity to spread awareness. Not sure about food service regulation issues, but potential media exposure could balance it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-04 17:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The A.V. Club has a [weekly column](http://www.avclub.com/articles/cake-boss-evolves-on-comedy-bang-bang-and-the-bugl,83349/) on audio podcasts, not too sure about resources for video though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-04 08:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AAaaaa aaaa aass-fucked by debt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 14:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bit on the nose, eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-30 05:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's his [blog post](http://www.allegiancemusical.com/blog-entry/keep-myself-physically-strong-mentally-awake-and-morally-straight) on the matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-30 04:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm reading all of his comments in the spazziest, slurringest voice possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 05:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jimmy Fallon has joined Justin Timberlake in my Small Club of People Who Are Much Cooler Than I Initially Thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-28 21:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're right that the openness limits growth, and I think that that's completely fine. When "growth" trumps an open forum for provocative and edifying content, I'll leave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-28 21:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a monumental difference between supporting the right and advocating the message, one which Hines establishes clearly and is following consistently. I don't think his actions make much sense in the context of what Reddit is as a whole, but it's ridiculous to claim he is in any way opposed to "the right to free speech." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 20:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christopher Tin: How do you approach a new composition? Do you start with a melody, a general sound or instrumentation, a chord progression? How involved are project leads in the conception and shaping of your music? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-25 06:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If getting optioned in the studio system is the goal then I don't disagree, but you can follow whatever rules you want if you produce independently, which is fairly feasible these days. Study and criticism are hugely important to any creative endeavor, but breaking the rules doesn't have to mean "you're doing it wrong, rewrite" if you're willing to make a film yourself and good/lucky enough for it to make an impact on somebody. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-24 23:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That depends entirely on your goals as a writer and in life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-22 21:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chaplinesque </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-22 17:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It delivers on the theme of hope, for one, as Batman's memory lives on. As for doubting validity elsewhere, Ra's Al Ghul's ghostly appearance is almost certainly a tortured fantasy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-22 07:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One which didn't conflict with the clear, unambiguous depiction of him sitting in the cockpit four seconds before a nuclear explosion--I realize that people are saying it's a temporal shift or something, but that would be an unprecedented break from the film's established editing style and would be jarringly out of place. As it stands, Bruce either deliberately killed himself in spite of having fixed the autopilot, or is a god. Those last thirty seconds are an unfortunate bit of nonsense capping an otherwise incredible, amazing film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-17 14:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With respect to your addition: coercing someone into driving drunk *is* morally wrong by the exact same standard, and one could easily imagine a situation in which the coercer is found liable for wrongful death or guilty of manslaughter, particularly if they're sober. While conceivable, however, the idea of a sober person coercing a drunk person to drive for their own selfish interests strikes me as so uncommon as to be negligible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-12 19:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because no one understands what we do in western society besides other philosophers.

That is a massive failure on philosophy's part in no uncertain terms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-09 04:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This really drives home for me how old Redditors are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-03 19:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. I would still point out that Man *does* imply adulthood relative to Boy, which is the context Ardenfrost initially used it in. Also, I didn't mean to use the "pompous ass" label as an argument for or against any specific points, just as a friendly personal note on the tone of the discussion--that's why I separated it from my content-based arguments with "on a personal note." :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
