<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6825</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 02:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet losers like you oppose training courses at every level, unless it allows you to make it prohibitively expensive and inconvenient to own a firearm.

You're part of the problem, Chester. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 02:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Maher is an anti-vaccination lunatic.

He's a completely partisan hack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 17:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's off interest to people who are pro gun rights. 

Keep your friends close and all that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 16:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm only in favor of UBC's if they are conducted as follows:

Government-issued drivers licenses are conspicuously marked in one of two ways:

People who can legally buy a gun have an icon on their id of a little green circle with a pistol in the center. 

People who are prohibited from owning a gun have an icon on their id of a pistol with an international no symbol over it. 

When selling a gun, you simply ask to see the buyer's id. If you see the green icon, you're good to go. If you see the red icon you are legally required to decline the sale. 

This UBC method empowers gun owners to be the first line of defense in making sure guns aren't sold to criminals, requires no government bureaucracy, does not force buyers or sellers to have to waste time driving to an FFL, or waste money forcing them to pay fees to conduct a check.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To Counter Gun Violence, Researchers Seek Deeper Data : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 20:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why You Shouldnt Fear the Mass-Shooting Rise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 17:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 14:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assault kettles are black, have an external handle to make it easier to quickly pour the contents, the ability to heat the contents above 200 degrees F, and an internal capacity greater than 10 fluid ounces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 04:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a trick.

Get an axe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 13:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was, but it's still a great trope to break out when dealing with antis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 05:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By any chance is your ISP Comcast? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fact-Checking Feinstein On The Assault Weapons Ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 04:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 03:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. I'd like to thank the kind soul who gilded my link!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hypocrisy Gets You a Lighter Sentence? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 17:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pennsylvania: Gun Control Amendment Fails in Pennsylvania House Vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 17:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hawaii is the latest state to overturn gun restrictions on legal immigrants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 15:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Clinton attacks NRA in speech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 15:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Much Ammunition Should a Person be Allowed to Own? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 15:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 07:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red meat for the election season grist mill.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 07:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in total agreement with you; fuck people in wheel chairs. If they can't learn Krav, they deserve to be victimized! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 23:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GrC. 

I totally forgot about that place! 

The thing that's funny about them is that the rules are purposely designed to allow them to ban anyone. 

Most subs that cliquey just end up going private, but the folks at GrC seem to get off on engaging in a public circle jerk, which is really just kind of sad, when you think about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 14:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For your clothes, here's a pretty flower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 14:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anti-gun bigots extolling their fairness and compassion in 5...4...3.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI Releases Study on Active Shooter Incidents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 03:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI Study Finds 'Active Shooter' Incidents To Be On The Rise : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 02:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 20:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aside from political lobbying and such, the NRA is the largest organisation dedicated to offering training classes dealing with many facets of gun ownership, including four hunting, concealed carry and home defense. 

They are also one of the largest competitions shooting organizations, with NRA-sponsored shooting matches in every state. 

On top of that, they offer consultation on range construction, evaluation and grants for the building and improvement of shooting ranges. 

They also offer members insurance on their gun collections. 

That's just off the top of my head.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No Lawyers - Only Guns and Money: Now Why Would The ATF Be Asking About Internet Sales? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 16:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 14:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a very Spielbergian moment. He always puts nice little touches like that in his movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 13:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Kirkland fish oil doesn't have as much EPA and DHA as some other brands, so you might try changing it out for another brand.

There are some brands for sale on Amazon with very high EPA and DHA content, and even a couple for sale at Costco. Next time you shop there, compare labels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 05:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that a lot of people would see a correlation with race and assume causation, when that isn't the factor driving these injuries, but rather the culture of desperation that arises in economically and educationally depressed areas of the country, which tend to be disproportionately African-American. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 04:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Passing a law that allows people to be thrown in prison for merely owning a piece of optical gear is reprehensible.

I'm glad to see you oppose such onerous legislation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prosecutor Says White House Intruder Had 800 Rounds Of Ammunition In Car : The Two-Way : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 00:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 21:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great post. I've submitted it to r/bestof.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditor CBruce does a good job of demonstrating that statistics of childhood gun deaths are often over-stated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 21:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 20:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How, exactly, would they enforce this law? 

After all, federal law prohibits the government from retaining NICS check records for more than a week (iirc), so it would be impossible to prove whether someone did or did not submit to a NICS check. 

So this law is completely unenforceable and utterly useless, except to act as the groundwork for further restrictions down the road.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Onerous ATF rules threaten to put gun dealers out of business </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 19:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is North Carolinians Against Gun Violence holding a vigil for a convicted felon? - An NC Gun Blog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 19:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 19:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually worse than the headline makes it seem. 

What has the antis all up in arms isn't the gun itself, but the optical and electronic system attached to it. 

They don't want to ban the rifle, they want to ban the scope attached to it, which is just insane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 19:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's some grade-a trolling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 18:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The gun used was built on an 80% receiver.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 18:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Headline should read "Democrats try to regulate blocks of aluminum/spools of plastic."

I can't decide if this is more, or less, idiotic than their attempt to ban incandescent bulbs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 18:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a second there, I thought this was an announcement that Brady group had gone through yet another name change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interest in gun control | The View From North Central Idaho </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 18:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 20:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant User name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 19:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever notice how the solution to failed gun control policies is the institution of more gun control? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 19:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After California passed their state level ban on so-called "assault weapons" it turned out that they left a certain model of SKS off of the list.

Since the window to register them had closed, and they were now considered an "assault weapon " anyonewho had one was told to turn it in or have it confiscated.

I don't know how actively they pursued the owners of those rifles, but its my understanding that some forced confiscations did occur.

There is also a concerted effort in California to match gun registration information up against prohibited persons databases, and then they dispatch LE to confiscate the guns. I don't have a problem with this, at least for people with violent felonies, but they're also going after people who have mental health issues, and even family members who are legal to own guns, but who live with someone who is a prohibited person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 19:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask them if they would support instituting Australian-style gun control in the US.

If they say "yes" then they're lying when they say no one wants to take guns away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 18:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While this isn't strictly gun-related, I thought it was worth sharing because it shows that the world is more complex than most gun control fans think, and that it's completely possible that there are factors other than gun availability that play into violence and suicide. 

Given the revelation that high amounts of environmental lead were likely a large part of high crime rates through the 60s, 70s, 80s, and 90s, it seems plausible and reasonable that other chemical and environmental factors could be related to violent behavior or mental disorders.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inverse Correlation between lithium in water supply and suicide rates found </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 18:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Protesters blast embattled Albuquerque police over shooting contest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 18:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harvard: Millions of Dollars More For Gun Control </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 18:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 04:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always remember, the only reason gun control ever fails is because it doesn't go far enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas Appears To Step Back From Proposal To Sell Alcohol At Some Gun Shows : The Two-Way : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 03:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 02:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point, the NRA could come out in favor of puppies, baseball, and apple pie, and the mainstream media would have an aneurysm in response. 

It's freaking hilarious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Daily Beast flips out over new NRA ads. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 23:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 05:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't bother, they went out of business years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mother Jones and their latest 2 Minutes Hate directed at the NRA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 18:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moms Demand: Stay the course   fudge with the stats. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 13:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 13:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, yes, the old "some the people who disagree with me are mean, so clearly they're all mean" tactic of argumentation.

If you can't win on facts and reason, then slander your opponents in the public eye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 05:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone who thinks they know it all isn't interested in learning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gun Control Group violating Federal Law. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 17:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 15:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of your points matter to him because for him, gun violence is just the friendly cause he's using to mask hits actual hatred for all gun owners. 

You see, combat effective is both deeply fearful and wildly self-absorbed, and as a result, he believes that anyone who holds the capacity to kill him actually would do so given half a chance. 

As a result of this fear and paranoia, he supports laws that punish lawful gun owners for no reason other than the fact that they make him afraid and uncomfortable. 

This is why anti-gun people are so irrational, and it also explains why they added completely incapable of differentiating between someone who owns a gun for legitimate reasons, and someone who is a violent criminal. 

To him, deep down inside, we're all violent criminals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antis giving up on Assault Weapons Ban but going after all Long Guns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 15:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 04:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a purely political play to try to draw a comparison between the NRA, practical shooting sports, and police militarization/excessive force.

tl;dr: Cops practicing with their guns = ZOMG POLICE STATE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 04:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While some people get all up in arms about cops with modern rifles and pistols, I don't have a problem with it. The problem with police militarization is one of mindset (us vs. them) and not an issue of whether a cop has a wood or plastic-stocked patrol rifle.

As for cops practicing head shots, I'm fairly certain most police academies practice head shots, and have done so since time immemorial. The notion of criticizing cops for practicing shots that require precision is, frankly, utterly idiotic.

The problem is that the article is trying to draw a connection between a competition that will actually help cops have better and safer gun handling, and a militarized police state and/or cases of police using excessive force. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 04:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I understand it, Truth Out is a left-wing organization on par with Media Matters and the like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 23:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always remember, according to the left wing, only police and military are competent enough to be allowed access to firearms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Left wing activists flip out over NRA-sponsored shooting competition for cops. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 23:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington Gun Control Ballot Measure Would Criminalize Common Firing Range Occurrence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 20:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 20:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tl;dr: it's a trick, get an axe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prohibitionists Give up on Semi-Auto Bans? Not So Fast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 20:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 15:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After about the fifth season I started thinking the show would be awesome if Michael's monologues would start getting more and more bizarre, and the series finale would reveal that he wasn't a spy, but in reality just a really clever paranoid schizophrenic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 02:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, they've known that for years. The anti-gun crowd learned how to play the incremental infringement game starting in the 1900s. 

Now that much of the populace has gotten wise to their shenanigans, they're having to shift which strategy they use.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 17:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always liked this one:

http://www.theonion.com/articles/peace-activist-has-to-admit-barrett-50-caliber-sni,234/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 17:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From where I sit, the proposal to regulate semi-auto guns under the NFA, or requiring a permit to own one has two long-term goals: to invalidate the Common Usage litmus test spelled out in Heller (after all, if they make it more inconvenient to own a certain class of gun vs. another, most people will default to the easier choice out of sheer convenience.)

This will have the effect of making semi-auto firearms much less common, and therefore likely to fail the Common Usage test in Heller, which then opens the door to further regulation. (Oh, and hey, since you required registration to own those guns, it becomes much easier to pass new regulations governing who can own them and how they can be used!)

TL;DR: CAP to gun owners: C'mon, how about just the tip? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 06:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's interesting reading.

Of particular note is their prescription for requiring the registration of so-called "assault weapons."

Basically, they want to re-categorize semi-auto firearms as Title II NFA guns, and force you to jump through the same hoops for an AR15 that you would have to jump through to get a full-auto M16.

This doesn't mark a change of heart for the left regarding gun control; rather, it's just a change in tactics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Center for American Progress | Assault Weapons Revisited [PDF] (This is the paper that has resulted in a lot of media coverage in the NYT, WSJ, etc.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 06:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 21:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> requiring a license for so-called "assault weapons" is probably coded language for a plan to move to regulate then under the NFA. 

That was part of Feinstein's proposal to pass a new ban post-Sandy Hook.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 12:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's so Raven! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 Years Later, Parts Of Major Crime Bill Viewed As Terrible Mistake : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 23:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missouri Lawmakers Override Vetoes On Abortion, Guns : The Two-Way : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 16:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 15:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my experience, the vast majority of ardent anti gun people suffer from Narcissistic Personality Disorder.

Logical arguments don't hold any sway over them because the very nature of your gun ownership personally offends them on a visceral level.

Since their motivations are purely emotional and deeply selfish, facts, stats, figures, and appeals to logic and reasoned thinking will not sway them in the least.

It also turns out that this is a two-way street. Since facts don't have any power to change how they think, they will not consider fact-based arguments to be effective, so they emotionally lash out instead.

Ultimately, the name calling is just an attempt to outgroup you in order to make themselves feel better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 14:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Extremely well done, OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 04:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shitty website fails on mobile = downvotesville. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 01:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free to post the numbers of all of those working-class people who are dues paying members in anti-gun organizations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 15:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also worth pointing out that none of the gun control laws proposed within living memory works actually do anything to stop a suicidal person from getting a gun. 

Therefore it is completely disingenuous for gun control advocates to include suicide numbers in their gun death statistics in a cynical bid to make it appear that the US has a violence problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No Lawyers - Only Guns and Money: A Gun Rights Case From The Fringes Of America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 15:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 14:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Want buses to have more appeal? 

Then they need to not smell like pee, enforce a dress code, and have an open bar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 14:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yohimbine and green tea extract work well to take the edge off of a chronic compulsion to eat, but you still have to exercise some self-restraint.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 14:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly can't say if I do or not, I've never gotten blood work done, so my choice in supplementation is less than scientific. 

I'll check out the beta alanine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 12:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems a there is valid reason to be concerned about the safety of fully-autonomous weapon systems.

http://www.wired.com/2007/10/robot-cannon-ki/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 11:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't speak to the reputation of the university that conducted the study, but I don't see a reason to be outright dismissive of the tests they're conducting.

After all, it's not like antibiotics haven't come from novel sources before, including soil samples from the grounds of a medieval castle and bacteria found in hydrothermal vents at the bottom of the ocean.

Hell, there's even an antibacterial agent used in scientific testing that is only found in the blood of horseshoe crabs.

Unless the studies being undertaken are complete woo, or the university has a reputation for poorly controlled studies, I don't see a reason to completely dismiss this research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 07:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I know its baking soda.

No worries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 06:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'ge been working to be better at drinking plenty of water during the day. I usually drink at least 1 8oz glass of water before leaving for the gym, and consume a half liter container at the gym during warmup.

Not sure I follow on the acetic acid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 06:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evidently there is some evidence that it helps control acidosis.

http://examine.com/supplements/Sodium+Bicarbonate/

I figured I'd give it a try, but not sure if I'd do it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 06:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll oblige them by continuing to not purchase their horrendously overpriced soups and sandwiches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sodium bicarbonate + green tea + yohimbine + intense workout = puking? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 03:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been supplementing with green tea extract and yohimbine for a couple of months without any serious side effects.

Today I figured I'd try adding sodium bicarbonate into the mix, and about 3/4 of the way through a fairly intense workout, I started feeling nauseated.

Doses were 10g sodium bicarbonate, 800mg ECGC and 12.5 Mg yohimbine hcl.

Other supps are D3, zinc, and creatine.

About half an hour after, I had an intense bout of puking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CA Mayor Says Bloomberg's Gun Control Group Used His Name 'Illegally' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 19:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 19:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can see the key holes in the google maps photos if you pan straight up otter straight down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 18:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To make a crappy analogy then, it's sort of similar to having a computer with a really powerful graphics card. 

A normal human's vision system (graphics card) isn't all that high tech, so it just hands the stimulus off to the brain (processor), which is pretty to of the line, for interpretation. 

But in a mantis shrimp the vision system (graphics card) is a top of the line model that can handle a lot of that work locally without having to hand the stimulus to the primitive brain (processor) for interpretation, which probably cuts down on the amount of time the brain needs to make a decision as to whether it's seeing food (attack) or a threat (run). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 01:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably more than just Reddit. Lots of other gun forums will post announcements to vote on these kinds of polls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 00:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Shantel wants to make more, maybe she should take some initiative and find a new job or develop some marketable skills.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 05:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My, aren't we all testy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guns Boom In 2014 Campaign Ads : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 03:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 22:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops. My bad. I should have checked the date before posting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 19:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not if you'ge got an agitprop fetish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYPD brass to cops: Stop using Kahr K-9 semi-automatic pistol as an off-duty gun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 19:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 18:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bear in mind that so long as general population growth outstrips the growth of the segment of the population that chooses to become first-time gun owners, it is completely possible for the raw number of gun owners to grow, while their percentage as a part of the overall population gets smaller, which some people would interpret as a drop in gun owners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 17:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typical rent-seeking behavior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 03:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Improperly contained involuntary protein spill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I apologize for posting a meme, but it was too funny not to share. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 17:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another MAIG member arrested </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 16:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Castle Rock votes to repeal open-carry ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 16:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study purporting to show that most defensive gun use situations are actually am escalation of violence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 16:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are gun control supporters so violent? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 15:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fatal Shooting At Firing Range Sparks Debate About Safety : The Two-Way : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 21:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 15:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That subreddit is full of utter assholes. I'm not aware of another firearms related sub where anyone has anything positive to say about them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 05:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/shittynealdegrassetyson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moms Demand Action Supporters Advocate Crimes Against Kroger Customers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 22:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Writing on the wall for guns (article about the illicit gun trade in China.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 22:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 21:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bloomberg makes for a good villain because he is such a lunatic control freak, and had a tendency to say tremendously stupid things. 

Gates will be harder to go up against because he's done am exceptional job of building himself up as a humanitarian good guy. 

They won't be able to use the same tactics against Gates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 12:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once upon a time, surplus rifles and pistols were sold to citizens via the Civilian Marksmanship Program. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 12:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it, *Batteries Not Included?

http://m.imdb.com/title/tt0092494/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 05:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.lvme.me/enys03l.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 00:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obvious troll is obvious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 00:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christo is brilliant, and the project is temporary. 

I'd love to see this one in person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 17:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe some of the guys on the force are into those battle bot competitions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 17:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tl;dr: Inelastic Supply meets Increased Demand, they get married and have two kids named Increased Prices and Short Supply.

In the last few years there has been a massive spike in interest in guns and marksmanship among the general population.

This demand was enough to outstrip the manufacturers' abilities to make and distribute ammunition, even when running 3 shifts per day, and a lot of companies were reluctant to expand their facilities because its an expensive process and they were unsure if the elevated demand was a temporary thing or indicative of a more permanent trend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 17:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not aware of any legislative or courtroom victories won by JPFO.

The NRA and SAF, for all of the dumb things they've done, are the two organizations most directly responsible for the lion's share of pro gun victories.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 15:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While not strictly gun-related, there is some interesting info here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A sear hable database that shows what kind of equipment has been transferred from DoD to county law enforcement. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 15:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 14:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple of years ago, 500 round value packs were around $15. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 14:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least then they'd stop accidentally shooting innocent bystanders when getting into skirmishes over gang territory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 03:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once upon a time military surplus pistols and rifles were able to be sold to competition shooters under the auspices of the Civilian Marksmanship Program. 

Handgun transfers were ended in the 1960s, and the rest of the program was killed by Clinton, but resurrected as a non-profit, but will only last as long as stocks of antique Garands are still available.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 21:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In that case, you're not actually seeing infrared on your phone's screen, but rather infrared as filtered and translated to be displayed on a screen designed to display RGB.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 14:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does your list have Water World and Judge Dredd on it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 05:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started using a magnesium solution applied externally a couple of days ago. I really haven't noticed a difference as of yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 16:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If "the ends justify the means" is an integral part of how your party operates, intellectual honesty is an impossibility.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you call the cops in New Jersey for being stabbed in the neck, they will break into your gun safes in order to find something to charge you with. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 17:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sun Sentinel Editors have their genitals strangled over Silencers for Hunting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 17:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the "New NRA" Terrifies the Political Left </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 16:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 05:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The old saw about them being more afraid of you than you are of them is pretty true.

I haven't encountered a bear yet that didn't run from a bright flashlight and yelling.

If you feel so inclined, get some bear spray and keep it handy for when you let your dogs out at night, just in case. That said, it's unlikely you'll ever need to use it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 00:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I think it's a toss-up between the 47 or 15.

If you get the Compensator 10, though, be sure to get the optional ball-cupping heat-shield. Not only is it more comfortable, but it will keep you from sustaining burns on your testicles when you are busy compensating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 23:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HBAR AR15s are widely used for Service Rifle and National Match Rifle competitions. 

My guess is that there were probably some MD High Power shooters who were able to successfully make the case for their sport.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 23:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why, it's almost as if he held those views from the beginning, and only claimed otherwise so he could make a dramatic show of being driven away from voting for pro-rights candidates so he could foster internet drama! 

But that would imply that he's lying about changing his views, and I'm pretty sure no one lies on the internet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 23:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The version of me that lives in your head is highly amusing. 

If you feel the need to donate to Bloomberg supported groups, go ahead. I'm sure that as a member of the .01% he'll be duly impressed with your financial assistance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 19:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here you sit, reaping the rewards of slavery and land theft.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 19:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't soft-pedal it and claim you support regulation. 

At least have the courage of your convictions to state that you are in favor of outright prohibition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 19:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the thing. 

It's clearly obvious these laws easily circumvented and wholly unenforceable, and preliminary data has shown that to be the case. 

Frankly, if anything, gun control advocates should be even more in favor of repealing these laws than gun owners on account of the fact that these laws are so poorly written and unenforceable that they only serve to highlight just how absurd the gun control movement in this country is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 17:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So brave.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 14:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the antis are so in favor of the sale of smart guns, perhaps they should give a little, too.

-Industry immunity to protect from lawsuits like the ones in the story.
-Repeal the NJ "mandatory smart gun" law.


Heck, since the gun lobby can negotiate from a position of power on this one, maybe they should demand concealed carry reciprocity, and repeals on magazine bans, hollow-point bans, and other ridiculous gun control laws.

If the antis want smart guns on the market so badly, maybe they should compromise for once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 14:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He feels strongly about guns because he's deeply afraid of them.

Even worse, he's deeply afraid of the inherent symbolism they represent, which is individual autonomy and responsibility.

He's not interested in "saving lives," rather, he's interested in scoring points in a culture war where doing things that piss off people who aren't from his tribe makes him feel good.

*edited to add: the down votes are proof that I'm right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 14:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The enumeration in the Constitution, of certain rights, shall not be construed to deny or disparage others retained by the people.

-9th Amendment to the US Constitution



You kind of suck at this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 14:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's amusing that your perfectly reasonable statement of fact garnered downvotes from people who couldn't come up with a reply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 06:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The good is all on this side of the table. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hickenlooper wrote longfawning letter to former NYC Mayor Michael Bloomberg | Complete Colorado </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 06:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 06:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet you evidently have the right to say infinitely stupid things... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 21:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to wonder if he used little hearts to dot all of the i's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hickenlooper wrote longfawning letter to former NYC Mayor Michael Bloomberg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 21:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People Wonder: 'If They Gunned Me Down,' What Photo Would Media Use? : The Two-Way : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 20:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 15:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a new term coined by Bill Maher. 

If you hear them use it, you know you're debating someone willing to spring for HBO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 03:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harming animals is one of the items on the checklist for determining if someone is a psychopathic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 19:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We must ban temporal bullets. 

For the children.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 18:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that there's no way for the system to stop someone who's suffering from undiagnosed mental illness.

Your name doesn't go into the NCICS prohibited persons list unless you've been involuntarily committed or legally adjudicated as mentally ill.

In the case of a lot of states, they don't even bother to report those people to the national-level organization responsible for maintaining the NCICS list, so in some cases even people who should have a record in NCICS don't, and are still able to buy guns. (The Virginia Tech shooter is one example of that particular systemic failure.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 17:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not necessarily true.

There have been laws proposed that would put people on the NCICS prohibited persons list for having a mental illness diagnosis of any sort.

This, most notably, resulted in an outcry from people who believed it to be unfair that they would lose the ability to exercise a civil right for being stigmatized for seeking treatment for a mental disorder despite the fact that they were not violent.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No Lawyers - Only Guns and Money: Something To Start Your Day With A Smile (gun control buzzword Hinton.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 16:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 15:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There have been some stories floating around about the companies that run private prisons donating to certain politicians/causes in order to pass more laws, harsher sentences, or opposing things like legalizing pot because it's seen as harming the prison company's bottom line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 15:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IT'S ALL ABOUT MEEEEEEEEEEE.

Clearly the vapers are out to get you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 15:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Claiming something is "a right" is the pseudointellectual's version of "think of the children." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 21:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first picture accompanying the article sure does say a lot about this guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German gun designers quest for a smarter weapon infuriates U.S. gun rights advocates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 21:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 18:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But John Morse promised these kinds of things wouldn't happen if we passed his shiny new gun control laws!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goldilocks Gungrabber </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 15:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 14:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Columbine shooters didn't wear body armor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 03:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's a P8?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 19:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's an entire weird category that could for under "children's books used to preach about my beliefs." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Maher and Stephen Colbert  Helping to Sell Childrens Gun Books! #ClashDaily </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 18:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
