<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7377</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 17:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ate too much chocolate  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 17:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Hitler was vegetarian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 08:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd think so, but nah, they're fairly sturdy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 07:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess would be that physiologically, its the same reason.  Safety in numbers and all that, knowing is safe to fall asleep because someone is 'keeping watch'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 07:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its really not true,  Australia has dangerous animals but so does the rest of the world,  I've lived here my whole life, in a rural town, and have seen very very few dangerous animals.  But I spent a week in Alaska once and saw numerous moose and some bears, I feared for my life there on a few occasions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 06:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> notice Rogers cleanliness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kangaroos are machine washable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 06:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 05:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lyssavirus is pretty rare, but you're partner should have seen a doctor asap just in case.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 05:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah,  the last heat wave did kill a few hundred but that's out of a few thousand so there numbers weren't really affected  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 11:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of bats? I believe there's been a steady rise in the number of flying foxes, they're breeding up in the botanic gardens and surrounding areas with plenty of food available. But I'm not sure about the other kinds of bats, been hearing a lot of them at night though.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend sent me this with the message "i asked mum if she'd seen Pippin, she sent me this photo" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 09:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 09:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is pretty socially acceptable for men to have casual sex, sometimes even expected. 

The women in the picture are (probably) wanting to 'reclaim' the word slut, and the actions associated with it,  to say its OK
 want and have casual sex,  as often or rarely as you like, as men are allowed to do.  

There aren't words that are the equivalent of slut for men,  but women have plenty used to insult and degrade them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 08:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not about promoting any particular lifestyle, but saying that women shouldn't be treated poorly or judged for their choices, particularly when men act similarly and no one cares.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 16:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have this is Australia, online and over the phone schooling. I homeschooled part of highschool, but I would go into the nearest school to be supervised for tests. 
The curriculum was the same for regular schooling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 16:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a huge source of nutrients and vitamins beneficial for post-birth recovery.  many animals eat the placenta, I watched pet guinea pigs do it once, but its not generally socially acceptable for humans to do it. 

I guess its technically cannibalism, but no one was killed for it and it would be destroyed as medical waste otherwise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 12:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh of course,  very important.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 07:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this is just one country,  there are entire nations that will be completely underwater.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 07:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

On a related logic: why does human kind have to evolve in one specific region of the world, and then migrate to the rest of it?

It doesnt 'have to' but all the evidence we have suggests that it did.  Like most other life forms,  there are kangaroos in Europe and there aren't bears in Australia. Different regions create different things, its going to be pretty unlikely that the exact same animal will evolve in two separate locations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 07:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've lived 26 years in this time zone and its never caused me any inconvenience. 

But if it we do change it forward or back half an hour I would be fine with that.  

What are peoples reasons for wanting change? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 17:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And avocados trees take a long time to produce fruit, 5+ years from seed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 16:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, they're wallaroos, commonly shot for food along with reds and western and eastern greys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 15:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a female, the bald patch is her pouch opening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 03:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neat flacid shamrock.... sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 07:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be great if they could standardise that,  its super annoying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 18:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of gross, but they're beautiful pictures. 

My cousin used hair as a medium for a uni art project, but she included pubes and hairs from strangers so it kind of really put me off the idea of hair in art.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 17:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that the placement of the brake and accelerator is the same in both left and right hand drives to avoid confusion and potential accidents by people who may drive both.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 15:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no advice, but I'll cry for you.  Hope you get it sorted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 14:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are all so adorable!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 06:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So its still ok to abort before the heart starts beating?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 04:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doing thinks is challenging  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 03:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's so cute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 03:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And dogs are innocent, they aren't responsible for the situation they are in,  they didn't invent cars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 03:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Told my parents I hated them,  too many times. I was an angry child </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 03:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww :) 

But how did it get in there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 15:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vest? Tank top? I don't know what else they're called. Top usually made of cotton with thin straps worn under clothing for extra warmth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 16:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the alternative to a medically necessary c-section can be death  of the baby and mother, so it's maybe not easy but definitely preferable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 13:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When my sister was 3ish she refused to wear a singlet and told our mum "you be the little girl and wear the singlet"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 13:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think our looks and languages will grow more similar but still have regional differences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 13:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister was born. Hur hur hur </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 13:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhm... what is a dimbit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 13:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 13:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend was once outdoors pooping, a dog came up behind her and stole the poop before it hit the ground </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 13:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suddenly 40 and back in high school. 

I woke up on the verge of tears.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 11:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't have free speech here,  there are a lot of restrictions on what we can say publically. Any thing that is highly offensive, derogatory, racist, sexist etc is usually censored.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 11:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And talk to your midwife/ doctor, they will have all the information you need and once baby arrives they will help you begin and continue breast feeding if you are struggling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 08:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time is relative but the speed of light is constant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 11:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seconded </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 03:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last guy does not look at all impressed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 13:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh thanks.  I get you now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 12:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought they were the norm...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 12:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 17:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To amaze all the friends i don't have at the dinner parties i don't go to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 17:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bearded dragon doesn't react </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 17:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Immediately because your meat will quickly rot and be useless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 17:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing.  I think that anything I took would remind me of what I'd left behind and it would be too hard to ever look at.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 17:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't.  Stranger danger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 17:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want a dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 17:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost everything.  

My life doesn't suck,  its just so dull, I could have done do much better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 16:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dog breeding has caused loads of genetic problems...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 16:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an excellent plan. Why isn't that in any movie or book?  They always go into forests and get killed by zombies hiding behind trees.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 16:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea.  But i just can't believe it's been a year already. Time goes too fast.


Massive freakout now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 16:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stay inside and use the Internet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 09:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few different  species by the looks of it,  this is what I've always called a blue tongue but I've heard people  refer to what I know as sleepy lizards (shingle backs) as blue tongues too, they're related species. I'm not sure exactly what variety you have there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 09:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a blue tongue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 05:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I was getting so confused! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 16:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But not all brains,  maybe only one brain named itself and all the rest copied  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 16:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the difference between a head transplant and a body transplant?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 15:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing we could do about it,  not very likely it will happen, more important and realistic things to worry about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 11:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a word for needing a word for something?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 11:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hydrated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 09:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A shower is temporary, they don't take long,  if you spent a whole day in a hot shower you'd be pretty uncomfortable. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 04:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree.  Its the same blue and black dress with stupud gold lighting now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 03:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, Frozen was huge and is still really popular, with adults and kids.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 11:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My uncle speaks like "so i bloody uh got the bloody tractor bloody stuck and bloody uh kim came to bloody give me a hand to get it bloody out."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 05:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not only Americans who do this,  I'm Australian and we have 'famous' killers here.  
Ivan milat, John Bunting (had a movie made about him) and Ned Kelly (arguably)

Its morbid curiosity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 05:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard rumours. But I swear, us Ameristralians are just as patriotic as any one else.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 11:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is that?  
And can you adopt me?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 05:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What am I reading?  What are all those words?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 05:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And slavery still continues around the world with all races represented amongst the slaves. They overlook that a lot...or all the time.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 03:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The family was outraged, but sadly, nothing could be done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 21:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister got an f once in grade 5 for being too creative. I still remember the last line of the story... "and Barbara learned to love horses, she ate them every day at 1pm which was when the mental hospital served lunch." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 21:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is that bad? I get chocolate,  flowers, bath bombs and sex?! Sounds fine to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 20:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm baffled by how they're actually terrified by hypothetical people hypothetically using them maybe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 20:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know of someone who was 'that driver', it completely destroyed their life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 20:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My advice: stop thinking about it before your brain melts.  Its impossible for the human brain to comprehend time before time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 20:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hormones are the trigger, to dont need a specific sad thought.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 19:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the other species currently living and reproducing are successful because they are currently living and reproducing. 

We are more successful according to us,  but nature doesn't really care,  we aren't really better or worse than any other species.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 19:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their languages are English based Creoles, that most likely developed by the people in those places hearing english being spoken but having no formal learning of it,  so they didn't correctly learn English but made up their own versions based on what they thought or guessed to be correct, their native languages and slang.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 19:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can not figure it out.  

Edit: luckily, wikipedia had had it figured out before I had...had </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 11:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today I got of out of bed at 3.30pm, I kind of have no reason get up in the morning, but need one.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 11:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to unsubscribe from r/food. It doesn't help my determination to stick with the keto diet.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 11:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An assignment that was due yesterday and also making a hair appointment.  

Life is hard,  and I have all episodes of friends to watch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 11:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up in a rural area of Australia that has no signs of aboriginal habitation, there are areas that are remote, hilly, thick bush and its pretty possible that no one has ever been to some of those places.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 16:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Females are mostly only able to conceive about 1 or 2 days of the month,  a week at most,  so if you miss the fertile period you'll have to try again next month.  
Plus,  many men and women have fertility issues which can delay or prevent conception.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 11:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure many do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 10:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She didn't have any for the rest of the time we lived together but i don't see her much anymore so they may have come back and i haven't heard about it.  

It used to really scare her and she thought she would see ghosts of irish men. But yeah, after a diet change it all stopped.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 09:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A break from having to look after myself.  Where do i sign up?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 09:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> =get out of my nostrils you damn flys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 09:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not eating a big main meal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 09:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shut up you stupid loud jerks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 09:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 09:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Olives </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 09:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister used to get sleep paralysis, turns out it was a vitamin deficiency  (don't remember which vitamin), my parents made her take supplements and changed her diet a bit. Cured!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
