<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6084</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ebola outbreak: Congo becomes fifth country with confirmed cases. This strain is not linked to the epidemic that has spread through west Africa. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 20:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is a fungus that controls the minds of ants found in the U.S., and its life-cycle and mechanism of action are a little different than its well-known South American counterparts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 21:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the earwax in blue whales can form plugs as long as 10 inches (25 cm). Scientists can study the layers in them to get an idea of when certain pollutants were more common, much like tree rings can be counted to go back in time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 19:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 06:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all seriousness [this](http://informahealthcare.com/doi/abs/10.1080/15563650500514590?journalCode=ctx) is the only source for the Romans-eating-it stuff but it's behind a hefty paywall for me. If anyone has free access to it it would be fascinating what if any sources they had for ancient Romans doing this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 00:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about this one? If identical twin men have sex with a woman at the same time and get her pregnant with non-identical twins, there's no way of knowing if they are full siblings, half siblings, or even who their father is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 22:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This one?](http://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/2co5kb/til_of_the_dream_fish_a_fish_that_causes_you_to/). The link doesn't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 21:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Another story](http://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-28811232) on this beetle appears to have the answer, which is a little unexpected:

 Cyphochilus beetles are native to South-East Asia, where they live among white fungi.

 This new study proves that they have been optimised by natural selection to be camouflaged among their surroundings, while keeping the scales as light as possible - which is crucial for flying insects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that some plants can warn each other of incoming insect attacks by sending signals through an underground network of fungi. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 19:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A species of beetle is exceptionally bright white, because of its scales that reflect light so well. No human technology can match their brilliance using such thin material. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 17:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 17:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is a recent piece by that guy telling the story.](http://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2014/08/what-i-did-after-police-killed-my-son-110038.html#.U_NpBFHfu5k).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Real Reason We Yawn. Yawns are contagious, but they keep the brain working in peak form. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 17:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL there is a species of fish that can be hallucinogenic when eaten. The Ancient Romans reportedly consumed it as a recreational drug. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 17:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nature publishes a survey of scientists' use of social media. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 17:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crayfish can turn blood cells into neurons, regenerating parts of their brain. Understanding the mechanism could lead to new ways of reprogramming human cells. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 18:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 06:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the least insane posts I have seen in the last few months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 19:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people think that's the way natural right-handers *should* play golf, because the leading arm in a golf swing should be the dominant/stronger arm. The leading arm in a "left-handed" swing is the right arm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists Detect a Possible Signal from Dark Matter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 19:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 21:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a real Collector's item! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 17:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The paper is [here](http://www.cs.cmu.edu/~aldrich/papers/ecoop14-tsls.pdf) (PDF). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The World Health Organization is to reconsider its stance against the use of experimental, untested drugs or vaccines, in the light of the current ebola outbreak. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 16:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New programming language accommodates multiple languages in the same program. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 16:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in 2002 a study was published in the prestigious journal Science showing that MDMA or "ecstasy" was neurotoxic. However it was retracted the following year, after it was found that methamphetamine had been used in the study rather than MDMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 21:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Self-assembling origami robot is world's first Transformer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 20:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brief, acute psychological stress promotes skin healing in mice. The healing is brought about by glucocorticoids - steroid hormones - which are produced by the adrenal glands in response to stress. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 16:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 21:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's a video of them](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OaPYwlXOTzQ), probably from the 90s when the Indian authorities made some efforts to contact them (which they do not do any more). Amazing stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 18:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many times has a random stranger asked you to say "One does not simply ... (insert line here)"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 16:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is more accurate to say that 96% of the matter/energy in the universe is undetectable, but is predicted to be there by our current model of physics.

Either it is there and our current model of physics works for it, or it is not there and our current model of physics is wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 16:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not many. Don't shoot the messenger! I just pointed out that they have a rule and that it's strictly enforced. I'm neither endorsing nor disfavoring the rule.

^(The story in this post I find personally very interesting, however.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 15:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the [rules for submissions](http://www.reddit.com/r/science/wiki/rules#wiki_submission_rules):

 Every submission must be a direct link to or a summary of peer-reviewed research with appropriate citations.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 14:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has become clear that there is an important eukaryotic component to the gut microbiome of ruminant mammals, mainly in the form of anaerobic fungi and protozoa. However, when we talk about the human intestinal microbiome we always hear about bacteria. My two questions are: Are there eukaryotes in the human gut microbiome? If so, do they play an important role, with potential clinical implications? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A golden bat has been discovered in Bolivia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 17:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 17:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The process by which the medication was made available to Brantly and Writebol is highly unusual. It may have fallen under the U.S. Food and Drug Administration's "compassionate use" regulation, which allows access to investigational drugs outside clinical trials. Getting approval for compassionate use is often long and laborious. 

A sad fact is we're looking at years if not decades before this treatment is approved for widespread use after the requisite clinical trials, and even then it may be prohibitively expensive for use in Africa. I may be proven wrong, but I don't see it being distributed to the hundreds of sick in the current outbreak.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists discover why some people can thrive on less sleep than others. A particular gene variant is responsible, and those with it can also handle extended periods of sleeplessness better. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 17:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Many bees are lazy. About 20% of the bees in a beehive account for 50% of the foraging activity. However, the slacker bees step up if the hard working ones are removed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 15:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 18:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems to be so. Comments in the article and /u/arrc clear that up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 17:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad, I just trusted the article, including its headline. That's a pretty awful error on their part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 16:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if that's the case, a remastered release of the trilogy on next-gen while we wait, *please*! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 16:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All are good summaries but to clarify, the stop being negative one is in particular about other people. Quote:

 Needing to talk badly about others indicates low self-esteem. That means, 'I feel so low that instead of picking myself up I have to cut others down,' 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 16:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steer clear of the comments below OP's article, fellow redditor - it must have been linked by the Drudge Report or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Danish team achieves data transmission rate record: 43 terabits per second. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 15:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 21:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he's got an appropriate name if that's the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 20:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what you have to do when there's no bale of hay down there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 19:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dirty Rotten Scoundrels: An inside look at the lead up to the 2008 financial crisis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moose saliva contains a fungal toxin which enables them to be able to eat grass known to contain harmful fungi without any ill effects. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 17:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Kardashian index: a measure of discrepant social media profile for scientists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 17:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 20:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this is after one of Liberia's top doctors dies yesterday. This is sad and scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 19:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aussie and Kiwi kids have been doing this [at their schools.](http://www.news.com.au/technology/online/google-maps-still-shows-giant-graffiti-penis-graffiti-at-schools-many-years-after-they-were-drawn/story-fnjwnhzf-1226902303410). Heck, one kid drew a penis on the Google Street View *camera* itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 18:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [We need something like this for her.](http://i.imgur.com/Q0SqvwL.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 17:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This seems fitting, since marijuana legalization will do a great deal to reduce the incarceration rate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 17:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That last quote is actually paraphrased from this Hadith: 

http://www.usc.edu/org/cmje/religious-texts/hadith/bukhari/056-sbt.php#004.056.791 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 20:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Classic. [Here's what Justin has to say about that.](http://i.imgur.com/Gty6OM4.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 17:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [He died in 2012](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Maurice_Sendak) by the way, so it's not an is but a was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL there is a plant in Australia that grows completely underground. It even flowers underground. The "underground orchid" never sees the sun, instead it feeds on a fungus which grows on the roots of an outback shrub. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 16:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want a healthier life? Stop shaking hands and start fist-bumping. A new study shows that handshakes can transfer ten times the amount of bacteria as a fist-bump does. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 15:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 20:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The British were awful to the Australian Aborigines, no doubt about that, *but*, from OP's first paragraph:

 A number of historians point to **introduced disease** as the major cause of the destruction of the full-blooded Aboriginal population.

A similar thing happened to native populations in Central and South America upon arrival of the Spanish.

(edit: formatting) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 19:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh boy, that video is painful. The guy doesn't know he's in a hole and keeps on digging and digging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 18:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Also](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dick_Pound):

[CAN] Dick Pound </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 20:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's](http://online.liebertpub.com/doi/full/10.1089/ast.2014.1162) the paper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 19:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's something mildly interesting: Israel's [worst ever defeat](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Israel_national_football_team) in soccer was 7-1 against Germany. The exact same scoreline and opponent as Brazil's recent humiliation in the world cup, to which the Israeli gentleman was referring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 17:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, his imitation isn't bad. Needs more tongue out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neymar's brain activity while playing is less than 10% of the level of amateur players, suggesting he plays as if on auto-pilot, according to a study by Japanese neurologists. It is thought this applies to all elite players. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 17:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neymar's brain activity while playing is less than 10% of the level of amateur players, suggesting he plays as if on auto-pilot, according to a study by Japanese neurologists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 16:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The bacterium E. coli can build complex 3D formations out of the salt from dried salt water. They hibernate in these. When they are rehydrated, the bacteria are revived. There are implications for the search for extraterrestrial life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 16:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 20:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd bet the farm that the NHL is the least provincial by this metric. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 16:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  10 crew members were onboard. 9 were killed in the crash except the Navigator, 2nd Lt Wallace F. Kaufman. He was captured by the Japanese and executed. 

Sobering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 16:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This needs to be higher. FGM is only widespread in Africa and has little to do with radical Islam. I hate ISIS with a passion, to put it mildly, but this story doesn't make much sense. I'll believe it when they themselves publicize it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MH17 victims' mobile phones 'answered by others'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 16:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Chile has a civilian town in Antarctica, complete with a school, hospital, hostel, post office, internet, TV and mobile phone coverage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 21:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 16:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's what you're made of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 23:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Commander Glum

You can't make this stuff up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 22:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To paraphrase Hitchens: give that guy an enema and you can bury him in a matchbox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 16:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pilot who shot down the plane [gave an interview late last year](http://www.globalpost.com/dispatch/news/kyodo-news-international/131224/ex-pilot-says-he-performed-duty-shooting-down-s-korea-). He says he was following orders and has frequent nightmares about the incident, but these parts stand out, there are many coping mechanisms for the unthinkable or inexplicable:

  But some Russians still believe no passengers were on board on the Korean Air Lines' jumbo, including Osipovich's wife Lyudmila.

 Lyudmila, 67, told Kyodo News that her husband did nothing wrong, claiming the United States has woven a false story and that no passengers were on board.

 But Osipovich said he saw only the South Korean plane and no U.S. military planes, and that he is sure there were passengers on the plane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 00:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine the flight data recorder could in theory be used to determine the *direction* of the missile's impact, based on tiny differences in the times certain components failed. If this is the case, it could be very incriminating when combined with known locations of any surface to air missile sites in the area.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 19:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is an [AN-26](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Antonov_An-26). Can they be that stupid to confuse this with a 777? Apparently so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 18:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can find it at /r/undelete </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 18:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glenn Greenwald lives in Rio, you can add him if you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 18:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are Brazilians of every skin color you can think of. This comment is absurd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
