<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1446</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 14:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most definitely. They must have forgot they were supposed to be there when shooting and added them in for continuity sake. Although personally I think it would have been less jarring to just leave them out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 14:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reason they changed it originally was that they weren't allowed to show boobs. (Yes even cartoon boobs.) Funnily enough though they kept the boobs and just took away the woman. Censorship is weird.

And then the Halloween one is a female skeleton with boobs. Which was allowed.


So basically on television you are allowed dead skeleton boobs or floating boobs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 14:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Curb Your Enthusiasm has a lot including Paul F. Tompkins and Scotty Aucks himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 14:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially since he went to see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 14:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And of course Hollywood Facts. My favourite of Scott's fake quizzes was when David Cross didn't realise that Hollywood Facts was a bit and he started arguing his answer was right. I think that was one of the last ones. 


And of course: Alive Or Dead- Dick Wolf?
Answer: Dead. His dick was eaten by a wolf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is what it's like for the characters in a movie when someone bursts into song </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 12:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 19:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And in at least one you die in the next 5 minutes. Who knows which one it will be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 19:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, "trigger" trigger people who are sensitive to gun talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 19:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Below the what???? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to say the idea of Dan doing Minecraft videos is a very strange but also comforting feeling. Especially considering he seems to want to do Tutorials rather than Let's Plays. The fact that somebody who has a career in television still wants to take up a hobby in Internet entertainment tells a lot about the feeling doing that stuff does to people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 12:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. There are not yet any plans for the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 09:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was an extra for that season though, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I'm going to go with. She panicked and needed somewhere to hide the card so stuck it into a part of the van. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 16:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But just put the plastic over the top of the bottle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 10:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd watch a Weekend At Bernies type idea with the president. The president dies and the others politicians have to convince terrorists he's alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cops in America have been playing too much GTAV and now they think cops act like that </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 10:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 10:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I quite like If I Were You with Jake and Amir. Featuring earwolf guests like Ben Scwartz and Thomas Middleditch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 21:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like there is going to be an origin story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 03:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downcast tells you what day a podcast uploads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 02:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine if they did that though. New extreme if remake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 20:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this actually happen in real life to people? I've seen it in so many movies but I've never seen it in real life.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My summer hairstyles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 17:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 20:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you listen to the Season 3 writers room? I sort of want a weekly podcast where it's a new writers room for a different show every week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 16:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Art Of Discourse is one of my favourites. It has my favourite Troy and Abed plots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 14:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually have a genuine Torque question I want to ask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 02:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thing is going to be a lot UTU2TM references, which honestly I'm fine with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 02:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listening now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 02:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess they don't have it anymore. They've been saying there going to let us pick flair for a while now so soon hopefully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Cruise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 00:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comedy Bang Bang Season 3 and The Birthday Boys Season 2 should now be on Netflix </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 13:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone confirm? I don't currently have US Netflix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 11:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we have the plot for Justice League here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 23:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hitrecord.org could be an easy place to do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 13:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope second season. Bill Hader and Fourvel were the guests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 12:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He put vhs effects on the cuts but not the actual video. It's not hard to run a video through a vcr. All you need is a vcr, a DVD player and a AV to USB cable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 02:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh around the 20 minute mark. Unfortunately no uhh-ing but it is a little kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 01:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cmon it's Jurassic Park, there is more than one famous line. Which one do you want? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 01:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah maybe he got mixed up or he meant after they got the second season on ABC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 00:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Scrubs_characters#Recurring_characters

I can't find any characters missing from the 8th season on this. Are you sure it wasn't the 9th season? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 23:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I meant the best Lizzie McGuire one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 22:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's first year to the end of fourth year I think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 22:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The downvotes are especially rude considering she seems to be trying to answer as many questions as possible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 22:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard that the lines in the "kiss" scene in JW was improvised. Also that there were other versions of the scene. I was wondering what happened in them?

Also shoutout to /r/earwolf! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 22:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah you can have a cunt if it's a lighthearted one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 14:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the best fan theory I've ever read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like "NOT Farts" is going to be number 1 no matter what episodes come after this purely because of how much we loved Harris. Sort of like when the Oscars give an award for an actor who has died's last movie even if it wasn't really for that movie but the actor themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just made me realise my problem with Spontaneanation. It takes me a while to realise what's happening in the scene if I stop paying attention for a minute. Improv4Humans doesn't have this problem because of the short scenes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 00:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the stream went down as FIFA finally ended I lost it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
