<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7402</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 01:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, awesome video, thank you for sharing!  
  
  The visual aid aspect of his wave machine really makes a (kind of) obscure concept very easy to see, understand, and visualize.  

  

  Amazing how applicable it is as a teaching tool all these years later.  

  

  I'm going to forward this video to my boss, hes a rather avid HF / MF listener (grundig radios, big loop antennas, etc) but doesnt fundamentally understand the physics behind RF propagation /  resonance / etc. I think if he watches this vid, it will teach (even him, LOL) a bit more about the physics / magic behind being able to pull in RF signals from thousands of miles away..   
  
  Thank you again, infinite upvotes from me :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 04:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This KX3 auction.  
  
  ..I has it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 21:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because of the connections at the top, and jutting out the side, I want to say it looks like it might be an unreasonably huge triode, but I can not find anything on google (shrug)  

  

Cool piece tho, I'd hang onto it.. Thanks for posting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 21:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fly my parrots with random-wire attached to them.   
  
  If I feed them a little coffee, I can work 1/2wave 160m for 10 or 15 minutes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 23:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh.. Yeah, I remember the first time I saw that..  It blew my mind a bit. 
  
  (Names Jason here, born in July, heh) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It would be interesting to see "ghost" cars of your car... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 18:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Of previous commutes into work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 02:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the 8800 only does VHF / UHF (as does the 7900, sorry for the confusion.. My bad) I'm not too up on the 7900s specs. Sorry I cant help you more. Maybe someone can chime in with some better info? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 02:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason, I had 2 different FRNs associated with my SSN. the ARRL VEC didnt know what to do with that. Unfortunately, no-one got back to me to let me know there was a problem. I had to track down the lead VE, and ask him what was going on.  Oh well.. Glad its taken care of now :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 01:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still new to the radios, so hopefully someone can chine in and correct me where I'm wrong, but the FT-8900 (as I understand) is essentially an 8800, but with more bands. I'm only working VHF/UHF currently, and learning more before I plonk down the cash to dive into HF. The 8800 has glowing reviews (so does the 8900) and the cross-band repeat was important to me (I believe the 8900 does that as well)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 23:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually did pass my General on the same day as my Tech, so I called the ARRL back today, and they see the mistake. He said they'd be submitting my general creds to the FCC today.

As far as radios, I have the ubiquitous chinese HT, but I also picked up a Yaesu FT-8800. 

Going to be building a 2m cubic quad for the house this weekend! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After nearly one month, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 21:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I *finally* got everything squared away with the ARRL, and FCC.    
Call sign just showed up.  -KK6SFZ    
Cant wait to get on the air tonight.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
