<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4487</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 03:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 01:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, [but not $2,500 cool](http://www.gainesvillecoins.com/products/169751/2015-somalia-elephant-kilo-silver-puzzle-coin.aspx). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 23:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We hit the $14s back in late November, 2014. I believe it was on November 30th.  I distinctly remember it being the last day of the month and a Sunday as I hit an order at $14.72 that evening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 23:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not surprising on today's news, [Tech triumvirate propels Nasdaq, S P to record highs](http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/04/24/us-markets-stocks-usa-idUSKBN0NF16J20150424). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 21:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [minutes gauge isn't accurate](http://i.imgur.com/Nlg33Xy.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 21:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took several seconds and would like to tell you it'd be a much better photo if the big one was eating the small one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 21:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think about buying HAL today? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 19:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, shit, don't know what the problem is on this end...I'll give it a whirl at home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recreating the Birdman Opening Credits with HTML5 Web Audio APIs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 18:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://markmarkoh.com/birdman/

Is this fully working for anyone?  I'm not familiar with the opening credit sequence, but I think I know where the demo is supposed to go based on the opening which seems to work for me.

[I end up with a frozen screen like this](http://i.imgur.com/3woikQm.jpg).  I'm assuming it should continue to type/reveal itself based on the audio playing.

Have tried in latest chrome/firefox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DevTools Timeline: Now Providing the Full Story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 17:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 17:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, although it is unique and looks very good quality from [BGASC's recent video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BxUJHtekIFs). It isn't on my purchase list, but I can see it getting on others.  If it were a limited mintage, I would probably get a tube, but I haven't found any info on mintage, so I'm assuming they'll mint to meet demand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interdimensional - spatial scrolling Library. Scroll by tilting your smartphone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 17:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 05:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's their standard ASE ebay #, I've been seeing the green "You bought this item" banner at the top of their ASE BIN auctions since the beginning of this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 22:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suggest placing 1-2 inches of rigid foam over the lines as insurance.

I'd really look into some [heat cable/tape](http://www.homedepot.com/p/Frost-King-12-ft-Water-Pipe-Heat-Cable-HC12A/100032792) to go inside the foam for pipes that are exposed outside your house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 21:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It covers $2,500 of relocation costs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CSS3 Starbursts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 21:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 18:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rate at which the toolchain/frameworks evolves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 02:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi frenz, why you no love me like MD Pimple Popper? She no has Woods lamp light. I used to shine so bright in sky like stars here. Thank you for giving your valuable time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 23:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Foo Fighters free concert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 22:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our designer had an idea like this as well - with the exception that it went horizontally across the top of the page instead.

I actually made this exact thing, per one of our designers.  I gotta get that shit up on github, it'll blow up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 21:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kookaburra? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 21:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Others](http://24.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_lychkjAeFO1r7kviso1_500.jpg) [have done](http://petapixel.com/assets/uploads/2011/08/contact.jpg) [this](http://randomwire.com/wp-content/uploads/biz-card-back.png). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 19:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My motivation comes around every 2 weeks. This, for some reason, tends to coincide with a trip to the liquor store and a weekend of never leaving home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 19:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've reinvented the scrollbar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 16:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Where do you have these made?
* What do you provide as the artwork? (vector?)
* What is the cost/minimum? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 04:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is awesome, could you not have gone a little taller and 2 levels for other facilities?

Where is it physically located and what did you have to do for permits?

Are you going to be full-timing in this or is it for recreation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 01:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wanna buy but I'm holding out for a gold American Eagle/Buffalo sale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 21:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually wrote the order fulfillment algorithm that APMEX uses (patent pending).  You can get [a predictive outcome of your order by manually running the algo here](http://codepen.io/anon/pen/QbLYBw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 19:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if this has any correlation, but the [IMF just wrapped up a meeting in Washington DC, April 17-19](https://www.imf.org/external/am/index.htm). I don't know if there was any announcement that came out of this that would affect the markets this morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sprite animation with controls - CSS only </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 17:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 23:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> APMEX has the 2015 1oz on ebay now for $1,225.09, $20 over spot.

Item # [111559013753](http://www.ebay.com/itm/SPECIAL-PRICE-2015-1-oz-Gold-Canadian-Maple-Leaf-Brilliant-Uncirculated/111559013753?pt=LH_DefaultDomain_0 hash=item19f96f7579) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2015 Tokelau 1 Oz Silver Year Goat $5 Proof Coin In Cap   COA @ $24.95 (if you buy at least 3) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 23:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MCM on ebay item # [131232751917](http://www.ebay.com/itm/2015-Tokelau-1-Troy-Oz-999-Silver-Year-Goat-5-Proof-Coin-In-Cap-COA-SKU32031-/131232751917) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 21:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A buddy is looking to buy, just looked at a house that was on the market at $365k, ended up selling for over $400k. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 02:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear Dr. Fantasy Wife,

On a scale of 1-10 when it comes to severity of zits/pus/blackheads that you've personally extracted in your career, what would you rate this guy at?

Thank you and keep the videos coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 02:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emergency fund = cash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 21:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to piece meal it all together. jQuery and Knockout are libraries, not frameworks.

Knockout gives you two-way data binding.

jQuery gives you a x-browser abstraction for events, DOM manipulation, ajax and animation (high level overview, of course). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 20:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No back support = not designed for sitting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 01:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why you keep receipts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 01:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In theory, the benefits of everything that comes with either of those frameworks (MVC/structure, two-way data binding, SPA/routing, testing, documentation, etc).  I'm pretty adamant that right now is just the wrong time for us to do a new app in Angular given what we have to support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 00:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've actually used Knockout on a mobile app here, though it's a bit of a pseudo SPA.  I think what Knockout does, it does well, but it obviously is very limited in what it does do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you start a new project today with Angular 1.2? Assume you need to support IE8 in enterprise-land, i.e., glacial browser updates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 20:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a couple developers here who are throwing around the idea of rewriting an ~ 2 year old app in Angular. It's currently a JSF (Java Server Faces app). I don't think Angular 1.2 is a very good idea at this time and I'd like to hear opinions/justifications by those much smarter than myself.

**We have to support IE8** (we dropped IE7 last year, so not very long ago) and it looks like this would mean we'd need to use Angular 1.2. This is a minor version behind the *current* release of 1.3.

I've read the Angular team plans 1.5 - 2 years of support for Angular *1.3*, but we most likely wouldn't be able to update due to needing IE8 support.  This, to me means we'd essentially be hitting production with a deprecated framework.

As for when we could drop IE8 support and have IE9 as a baseline, that's pretty tough to say.  If 1.3 is supported for 2 years, I would guess it might be possible to upgrade any 1.2 app to 1.3 in 2 years, but then we're back to upgrading to a deprecated framework.

Upgrading from 1.x to 2.x is also a big unknown at this time.  I've read that is an unknown upgrade path as well as the angular team plans to work on an upgrade path.  With the fundamental changes in 2.x, it seems any 1.x to 2.x upgrade will be quite a bit of rewriting, if not mostly a full rewrite.

So I could see it being yet another rewrite in a couple years, which seems a bit ludicrous.

We've never built anything in Angular 1.x, either.  I've done a personal project in 1.3 but that was just to go from reading about Angular to actually doing *something* in it.  This is not saying much as I read and play with a lot of stuff just to go from a 50,000 foot view to a 25,000 foot view.

I've looked at Ember as well, which looks like we'd be topping out (with IE8 support) at [Ember 1.13. They also claim an upgrade to 2.x will be "relatively simple" when you can drop IE8 support](https://github.com/emberjs/rfcs/pull/45#issuecomment-93009469).

Ember looks like a better choice to me at this particular point in time, but I'd love to hear what you guys would do if you were in enterprise land, needed to support IE8 (for the next couple of years at least) and wanted to build some type of modern MV* app.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 16:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Portlanders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 16:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Batch job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL 27 of every 2014 tax dollar went to the military </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 02:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 01:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good passive aggressiveness on your part, though.  It's almost like you're from Portland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wish this guy all the luck in the world - anyone know of existing tiny house communities? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 21:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 21:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing it for the first time for months now. Make sure you go see Sheogorath, he's a hoot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 21:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not ashamed to admit that I know, just by looking at the thumbnail image, that's Kane Roberts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They want people who understand the language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 17:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     display:table != table </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts on HTML5, a Flash Developers hopeless rant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 16:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> wsky.js - a lightweight jQuery plugin for triggering CSS animations on scroll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 16:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CSS Vertical Align or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Display: Table </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 16:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 16:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on what you buy and sell at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 16:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic and unsafe modern staircases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 04:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought some RIOM last year, which is now [TAHO](https://www.google.com/search?q=tahoe+stock ie=utf-8 oe=utf-8#q=taho+stock). I'm currently up 2.3% on that. Not quite what my Apple is doing (I'm up 32% on that) but at least it's in the black. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL 73% of enrollees in Americas major public support programs are members of working families </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 03:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Many gold miners in dire straits despite costs cuts - around 50% of the gold mining sector looks to be lossmaking on its own calculated All-in-Costs basis at a $1,200/ounce </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 03:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the average lifespan of an S P company dropped from 67 years in the 1920s to 15 years today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 16:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 04:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife knows her place.

I order via an assumed identity in another country and use 3 re-shippers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL California agriculture accounts for 80% of the states water consumption, but 2% of the states economy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 02:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 02:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Impressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 20:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Kevin Carter](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lp9_Ng3wzt4), fantastic Manic Street Preachers song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 20:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ajax (what $.load() uses) needs to be run via a webserver (not the file protocol) and you'll want to be loading files from the same domain, or else you'll need to look into CORS (cross origin resource sharing), which is a separate set of issues if you don't control all the domains in play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 20:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I frequently see this from our back-end java and sometimes .NET guys, so I'm assuming the authors of that guideline came to the front-end via the back-end, i.e., they're your typical computer science guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 20:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, just setup a partial html page that other pages can consume and use jquery's load method.

    $( "#elem-on-parent-page" ).load( "path/to/page-to-load-into-parent.html" );

If you only want to load part of the page-to-load-into-parent.html page:

    $( "#elem-on-parent-page" ).load( "path/to/page-to-load-into-parent.html #container" );

Where #container is just the parent element you want to consume. When you have a space after the url, it acts as a jquery selector so the above is loading page-to-load-into-parent.html then filtering it down to just the element with the id of container. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 20:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So give them a full mockup for web, mobile, app, and a custom logo for the organization ... by tomorrow at noon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Golden Ratio: Design's Biggest Myth - The golden ratio is total nonsense in design. Here's why </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 16:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 16:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A collar but no ID tag? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 16:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said this in a recent thread about the same question and I'm going to say it again...You should *start* with ES3 as that is what you're probably going to be maintaining. There is a metric shit ton of ES3 out there.  Once you feel you have a solid grasp, move up to ES5, then 6. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 17:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Secretary of State under Wilson who quit as a result of the Lusitania sinking.  The Lusitania was carrying munitions which made it fair game for German subs. It was also carrying American passengers which of course drew outrage and ultimately drew us into WWI.  The German Embassy took out ads in US papers warning not to travel on the Lusitania. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 17:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi frenz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL about Tax Freedom Day - in 2015, the average American must work from January 1st to April 24th just to pay all federal, state and local taxes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 16:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 16:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and I'm now following up with scans of 3 of 10 coins I received

Since my original post I've ordered 20oz ASE from another vendor and all arrived without any visible fingerprints or other defects

I think this is key.  In your latter example you ordered a tube so you are most likely getting the coins as they left the mint. Some vendors may go through tubes and cherry pick what they think are the best to send out for grading but I think you have a much better chance with condition by buying in tubes.

What vendor did you purchase the 10 from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 00:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use a popular project name, then a dead astronomer, then validate, then DX (for Digital Experience).

* jQuery-Galilei-ValidateDX
* Angular-Copernicus-ValidateDX
* Node-Kepler-ValidateDX
* HTML5-Boilerplate-Newton-ValidateDX </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 00:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, [I would shed a single tear like that native American from the 70s](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uGu4AwL5Kho). Then I would put it back in the zip lock bag it came in. Then I would probably start drinking to be honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 21:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you carpet bomb it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL if you have no debts and have $10 in your pocket you have more wealth than 25% of Americans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 17:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 05:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I was not aware of that.  I think I'll start trying to edit the item number to turn it into a link after a comment is made. I wonder if having a comment would keep it out of the spam filter.

The item #s are direct links now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 04:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those posts get stuck in the spam trap, sometimes they don't seem to get fished out. Hence the item #s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When will we see the first *major* cyber attack (that affects most American's daily lives) and what would it look like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 04:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL according to the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau, 43 million Americans have overdue medical debt on their credit reports </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 03:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top 20 gold consumers: China still No. 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 03:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 03:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christ...Here I thought I grew up in a rural farming town. I've got nothing on these hicks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> APMEX ebay | tube of ASE @ $377 | 1 oz Gold Pamp Fortuna @ $1,222 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 03:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **ASE tube @ $377**

* Item # [141528111687](http://www.ebay.com/itm/141528111687? RILT=Main_Banner2_Silver_Eagles_Tube_eBay)

**1 oz Gold Bar Pamp Suisse Lady Fortuna In Assay (New Packaging)**

* $12 over spot
* $1,222
* Item # [111629423556](http://www.ebay.com/itm/111629423556? RILT=Main_Banner_Pamp_Suisse_Gold_Bars_eBay) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adobe Character Animator Lets You Animate With Your Face </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 23:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hamburger Menu: Handy Tool or Useless Icon? Adding the word menu increases engagement more than 50% </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 17:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 16:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Must be a tech hiccup.

Or maybe the end game is here...Quick, to the bunkers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 16:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 50 monster boxes. Anyone know what the premium per coin would work out to be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 16:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 16:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be a patent, see Amazon's one click button.  I believe they also have a trademark on one click.

I know Apple licenses the one click to purchase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 03:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure there are French people in Spain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 03:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consumer Price Index data from the US Dept. of Labor/Bureau of Labor Statistics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the price of ground beef has doubled since 2009 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 03:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 22:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I put my heart into everything I do

That's cute.  God, I remember when I was that naive. Those were good times, I was happy, kind, charming, sober and my cat respected me.

Also, it's *JavaScript* ninja, there, gaijin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 21:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's in frames:

     FRAME NAME="fr_top" SRC="top.pl?ww= w=stupid d=STUPID r=WStupid;Cstupid;" SCROLLING=NO BORDER=0 marginheight=0 marginwidth=0

    FRAME NAME="fr_bottom" SRC="/en/STUPID"

When you view the source of  http://www.wordwebonline.com/search.pl?w=stupid, click on the src links I've outlined above, and as they say in Spain, voil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 21:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lab Animal Technician </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 20:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You know things have really gotten out of hand when...](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1r8rJy2Q5p5QORYKcye93UECwOlSgFL24c5fyF7dqhaM/edit#gid=1607194899) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Realtime html + css = Darth Vader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 16:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 16:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are ten of the top 12 JavaScript

* Top 12 according to who?
* Why does it actually list 14?
* Also, the title says "Top 12+ JavaScript Libraries For Developers".

Lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 16:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Pro JavaScript Design Patterns](http://www.amazon.com/Pro-JavaScript-Design-Patterns-Object-Oriented/dp/159059908X) pretty much takes the GoF patterns to JavaScript.  Even though it came out in 2007, it's still probably the best JavaScript book I've read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 16:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Minimum skills:

* DunningKruger
* Bandwagoning
* Confirmation bias

Average day:

* Wondering if you're too old to join the army. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 16:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She wants me to replace some nice, clean elements on the site with a GoFundMe widget

God damned moron trying to facilitate business...Does she not understand you are an artist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know things have really gotten out of hand when... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 23:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 21:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened to the first two? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 21:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is done in Portland.  The tiny houses are basically parked in a "regular" house's back yard or somewhere on the lot.  In theory it works great until a neighbor starts to complain to the city.

You can do it but it's still a legal gray area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 21:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simple strategy, he's playing both sides.

$upporting = benefits of Hollywood networking/nepotism but not going full Jim Jones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 21:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used to work at an agency back in the 90s where I had one of those Power Computing Mac clones. They weren't available that long.

Fun fact: those PC clones stopped when Jobs went back to Apple. If I remember right Apple bought them to essentially shut them down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 19:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you aware the 2.0 version is not going to be backwards compatible with 1.x? There are major differences between 2.0 and 1.x. You might want to hold off until 2.0 is out before learning a framework (1.x), only to relearn it next year (2.0).

If you're just looking to do some sort of personal project in a JS MVC framework, I'd recommend Ember today. They embrace stability over stagnation.

If you're dead set on Angular because of the hype train, re-read my first paragraph and do some research on your own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Archer opening sequence re-created with CSS animations (full demo at bottom) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 19:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 16:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I own my home but no safe. Even with a safe I'd still prefer a safe deposit box. My home is not hard to break into and I don't want to invite trouble. How often do safe deposit boxes get robbed?

Ditto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 16:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that I need to start buying shirts and jackets whose sleeves are too short so everyone can see that **I HAVE A FUCKING APPLE WATCH, LOOK AT ME**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Resig annotates original jQuery source code </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 23:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 19:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's something I did last summer](http://www.yardshare.com/yard_pics/Patio%20Before%205-14-09%20004.jpg). It's very low maintenance, which is key when it comes to landscaping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 16:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a couple of good ES6 links:

* http://es6-features.org
* https://leanpub.com/understandinges6/read/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Majestic Silver's CEO - all in sustaining cost was $25 oz, now they are $11 oz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 06:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 05:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He could have stepped in a bear trap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silver expected to get a big rise in Japan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 05:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 03:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, I love those old Argosys and Airstreams.

How's the insulation in that?  I can't imagine it would handle Texas summers and Canadian winters well. Doesn't look like you gutted it down to the shell and did something like spray foam/insulation.  Windows original as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 03:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slabtown Customs? I actually like what the guy is doing because he does non-typical tiny house stuff. Does have at least one documented horror story out there, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 03:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think those dates are critically important other than the PR angle.  I think they have something like 30 days or 6 weeks to make the payments before they are considered to be in default, so we're talking mid-end May. 

Sure, the markets will react if they miss the deadline, but there is a grace period for the ape to get ready. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 02:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You talkin about this, Willis?](http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2015-04-06/key-events-coming-week) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we officially say the big dealer sales last week weren't foreshadowing a spot dip? i.e., myth busted (this time)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 02:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had a bunch of silver/gold sales last week, poor job #s were out, was it last Friday? Market was closed Friday as well.

Typically the theory has gone spot takes a dive a couple days after the big sales end.

What sayeth the peanut gallery? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 02:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO, you're making the assumption other opinions are invalid because you don't share them.

In the end, what you need is data supporting your rant. Do this repeatedly and she'll start to trust your suggestions/direction as it's backed by something tangible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 22:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you try implementing her suggestions/assumptions and actually test them in production to see how they play out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 22:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello from Portland.  If you end up going and have a smartphone, can you post up a video of your walkthrough as well as a general review of your experience? I'd love to see this as they've piqued my interest as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 21:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pick up a hooker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 21:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your best bet to determine if an old poured bar is fake is to melt it down.  If it turns out to be legit, you should re-pour it.  I have Photoshop and can help you make a mold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 21:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $.19 over spot.

Wonder if the bars are the style pictured or a variety. I know Englehard has several styles of 100 oz, APMEX usually has several varieties in-stock, though certainly not at this price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tiny Mountain Houses - west coast builders (CA, OR, WA). Starting at $39k </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 21:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 20:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, [there's one here](http://imgur.com/gYOww7z). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 18:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been using a local recruiter very successfully since 2008 (been placed 2x). Last time I looked around myself, [indeed](http://www.indeed.com/) seemed to be the best thing out there. Granted, it's been years since I checked it out but I still hear it brought up in casual conversation from other devs every now and then.

I never found any decent leads/gigs on Craiglist, but again, it's been years since I've looked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> web-bundle - pack arbitrary files into PNG and access them using JavaScript </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 18:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prerender  SEO for SPAs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 17:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Materialize - a modern responsive front-end framework based on Material Design </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 17:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 404 Animated Character in CSS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 17:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 16:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should start with ES3 because that's going to be what you're going to be maintaining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 16:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What should you do when you've completed a basic Java course, and can you get a job with Java?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 05:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a 10 oz Rarities bar, didn't pay too much of a premium for it.  Your 5 oz would probably fetch $100, IMO. That would be a "retail" price, i.e., to someone like the folks here. If you were to sell it to some type of retail establishment, you'd probably get $15-20 less, I'd guess.

I don't know if the 5 oz is particularly rare. I'd guess not so much but can't really speak with any authority. You don't see the Rarities bars much, but I don't think they're that collectible outside of being an older type of silver bar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Karl Lagerfeld claims his chic cat, named Choupette made 3 million euros last year from just two modeling gigs. Lagerfeld won't allow Choupette to do "foodstuffs and things like this. Shes too sophisticated for that." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 18:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 17:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as people have their air conditioning, cable tv and walmart, nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 23:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can understand this point-of-view.  I'm a big proponent of financial history, though, especially money and the institution of banking.  Don't get me started on The Federal Reserve. I won't even ask people about the 3 central banks that came before it in the United States.

Hey, look over there, Andrew Jackson, what a guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 22:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a ton of details, but I'd recommend checking out [knockout](http://knockoutjs.com/).

It's a MVVM library (not a framework), does pretty much one thing (2-way data binding), can be easily incorporated into any project and has a low learning curve.

I'd also recommend using knockout's mapping plugin which takes care of mapping your json data to your view model. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 21:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a Morgan Dollar, named after its designer George Morgan.  If you show that to most people, they will have no idea what you're showing them.  It's a bit of a shame there is very little knowledge of common US financial history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 16:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 oz Fine Silver - One Amero </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> StackHive - CodePen for full scale projects? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 23:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 20:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $18-$20 for 3-6 months is way below market.  You're going to burn through that for lunch in 3 days.

I will pay you $180-$200 for 3-6 months.  You're still going to run out of money to eat, but don't come crying to me with your problems during the 3rd week, we have a contract. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 18:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be sure to [check out the demo](http://pixelscommander.com/polygon/htmlgl/demo/filters.html#.VR1tSZOPyF4), crazy stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 18:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forget about launch, I get this feeling when walking into a project kick-off meetings with our marketing/UX team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 18:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd definitely look for the "about us" or "our team" page that has the most plaid. If they have Sasquatch in the firm name, perhaps with a logo of bigfoot riding a fixie, that would be the ultimate trifecta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 18:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under "breakdown of time", what's the difference between "companies" and "projects"? Assuming this is billable -vs- non-billable time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> R.I.P. REM, Viva CSS Reference Pixel! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 18:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 18:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canary looks very interesting, thanks much for the reply.  It's a shame they don't offer a discount for multiple cameras/units. http://canary.is is definitely worth checking out if anyone else is interested in this topic.

There's also https://getpiper.com/ which you can pair with open/close sensors for doors/windows (which is cool and something Canary doesn't offer), but I've read some people have issues getting those to work/sync with Piper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the 99%, familiarity trumps cleverness. Your typical line-of-biz web app is not going to succeed or fail based upon the clever, innovative UI youve invented </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 18:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Subdomains are bad for SEO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 17:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the latest/greatest/best bang for the buck home security internet-monitoring stuff out there that doesn't require $ubscriptions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 17:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would like to look into adding some home security where ideally I can monitor via my Android phone. I don't know what's really out there nowadays but figured a lot you guys do and are possibly using it or can recommend what to look into.

BTW, I don't have a static IP address at home, but could probably get one. I go through Frontier. I don't have a land line (phone).

Basically looking for the cheapest way to add some security/monitoring at home.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the latest/greatest home security internet-monitoring stuff out there that doesn't require $ubscriptions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 16:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would like to look into adding some home security where ideally I can monitor via my Android phone. I don't know what's really out there nowadays but figured a lot you guys do and are possibly using it or can recommend what to look into.

BTW, I don't have a static IP address at home, but could probably get one.  I go through Frontier.  I don't have a land line (phone).

Basically looking for the cheapest way to add some security/monitoring at home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HTML-GL - 60 FPS and amazing effects by rendering HTML/CSS in WebGL, framework agnostic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 16:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 16:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Value doesn't come from the page, it comes from the messaging.  Also more important, IMO, are error messages on the request level, but that's more geared towards apps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 04:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at the silver price over the past 5 years, I think I might go crazy later this month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 02:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's the best I've ever seen for a JM.  Monarch has .59 cents over spot on their 100oz bars, but not on ever make. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 00:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try again from home tonight, might be the corporate firewall I'm behind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 22:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Maggregor download button doesn't seem to work in Firefox, is there a FTP mirror somewhere? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 18:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But [a lot of the jobs suck](http://www.nytimes.com/2014/04/28/business/economy/recovery-has-created-far-more-low-wage-jobs-than-better-paid-ones.html) and wages aren't growing.

Also, [labor participation rate is lowest since 1978](http://data.bls.gov/timeseries/LNS11300000/) (change the from date up top to 1970).  Sure, you have a growing aging population, but I'm sure a lot of people are just giving up.

Do you really believe the [official unemployment numbers?](http://www.forbes.com/sites/louisefron/2014/08/20/tackling-the-real-unemployment-rate-12-6/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 18:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm digging on setting up my preferences to disallow custom subreddit styling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 18:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in London, but just yesterday I received an email from my recruiter for a "front end developer" titled/position that in the requirements also indicated full stack, 7-years of python, java and .NET (all of them, not one of them) plus dev ops responsiblities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Responsive Grid System - 2kb, Mobile First Grid System, HTML5 Boilerplate Head, 960grid like naming convention, IE8+ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 18:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 16:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The US economy is looking strong

Serious question, how do you figure this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 16:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IKEA catalog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 16:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why this has been down voted, it hits the nail on the head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The original name of the city of Atlanta was "Terminus" (meaning "end of the line) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 01:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 01:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a great score. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 22:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You probably saw it here:

* https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GLSxcLww2V4
* http://minimhomes.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $98,000 tiny house for your consideration - you could probably get them down to 96 if you played hardball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 21:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Loading CSS without blocking render </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 19:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Precise control over responsive typography - using calc() and viewport units </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 19:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advanced Performance Audits With DevTools - case studies on CNET, Time, Wikipedia, Google Play </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 19:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 19:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     p:nth-child(odd) {
        display:none !important;
    } </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 19:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus would use a Macbook and obviously vote Republican while turning water into wine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 19:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have to give mobile visitors the option of viewing the desktop version (in a responsive site), odds are, you're doing responsive design wrong.

That being said, I can still appreciate this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> interact.js - JavaScript drag and drop, resizing and gestures with inertia and snapping </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 19:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Triangulator - polygonal image generator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 19:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Triangulator - polygonal image generator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 19:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> netlify - builds, deploys   hosts your static site or app (basic packages free forever) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 17:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please stop with the stupid animated gifs, they do nothing but distract from the actual content.  I bailed on your article because of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 17:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Can't load a stylesheet properly" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 16:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By reading this commentyou agree to pay me $500 and provide naked photos of your sister. 

Enforcing that will be another question.  BTW, I already have the photos.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's see how long this lasts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 04:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/benbernanke

\#AskBen: Welcome To Twitter @BenBernanke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the grizzly bear is the official state animal of California. But no grizzly bears have been seen there since 1922 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 04:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 02:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a faction here that thinks when APMEX has sales like this, it's foreshadowing spot price going down.

So let's watch what happens this week. We're at $1,189.40 as I type this on Monday eve.

I'm not finding any silver deals from them, though I'm just looking very quickly, filtering down to bullion--silver--uncertified--1 oz.  I see they have a tube of ASEs for $411 but not much of a deal.  JMB has them for $400 shipped at the moment. Silver spot is $16.82 at the moment so if I'm missing any APMEX silver deals, please post it up for the record. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Craigslist scam tried to sell fake silver bars (Silvertowne 1oz bars) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 22:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 19:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Good](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/236x/76/f7/c6/76f7c6bc37625d26afac2fcd59f080a9.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dom-Animator.JS - show small ascii animations within comments in your dom, viewable in devtools (see chrome Elements tab) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 19:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 18:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just FYI, it's called a Mercury dime and it isn't a key date (which would make it more valuable). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turning Design Into Code: Tips for Designers from an Engineer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 17:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turning Design Into Code: Tips for Designers from an Engineer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 17:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 16:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Impossibru! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the average supermarket in the United States wastes about 3,000 pounds of food each year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 19:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scottsdale has 10oz Stacker bar for $181 shipped </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 23:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Item #141572249577

[Link to auction](http://www.ebay.com/itm/10-oz-Scottsdale-STACKER-Silver-Bar-Ten-Troy-oz-999-Silver-Bullion-A182-/141572249577) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 18:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you are here protecting you investments. 

You'd be much better off, IMO, if you would have spent that $ on semi-numismatics.  With those generic APMEX bars, you're directly tied to spot price.  Take a look at the price of silver since 2011 - it has crashed.  What if you would have been doing your research then? Would you still have jumped in with the doom and gloom dollar collapse scenario that proliferates from the silver pumpers? Do you really think you'll find yourself in a silver barter situation?

For someone who has done a "ton of research" and "endless research", yet makes a large first purchase of generics, I'd say your research is failing you. I'm not bashing generics as I have generics, but you really need to be aware of what you're buying. Diversification can be fun, but that doesn't mean it will yield you the greatest gains.

I would strongly suggest researching and getting into semi-numismatics where your silver won't be tied to the spot price of silver, which may not have bottomed yet.

Welcome aboard the silver train. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
