<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4094</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So there was a precedent, I don't see the same precedent for Ideis, however I believe he is a very talented actor so if he proved me wrong I wouldn't be surprised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 00:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was pretty suave in layer cake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While true it's in Chryslers best interest for their dealers to treat their customers right so they don't get pissed off and buy another brand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I thought this was a spoof of a Carly Rae Jepson song, putting tom hanks in the place Carly would be, not the actual video minus the music.  I don't understand the original music video at all after watching it.  Why use Tom Hanks?  I'm confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's some solid train of thought.  Don't surf for 2-3 weeks or endure pain for 8 months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a long shot op but I decided today I want to quit my Seo job and work freelance.  If you are interested shoot me a pm and I can share my resume and background with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His wording is fine your comprehension is lacking.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the common problem with really any sporting goods store.  Carry a lot of everything but not enough of one thing.  Their soccer selection is just horrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damnit I really am a c section baby, I feel like less of a human. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to think so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 05:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're a father now, congratulations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 05:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Squirrel, Vermont  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
