<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9503</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Paradox Of The Proof | Mochizuki has posted his papers, nobody understands them, theyre written in a private language, and he wont elucidate. Why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-11 05:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Controlled by Guns | "a category error, the same mistake the DeCSS advocates made when they believed that by revealing that the DMCAs slicing between code and speech was absurd that it would make the law go away, as if the legal system was a rampant AI you could shut down by shouting a paradox." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 07:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austerity Will Leave Us Crying 96 Tears | Extremely rich people dont send their kids to public schools, visit public parks or ride public transit. These wealthy folks dont need public services and resent having to pay taxes to support them. Austerity works for these wealthy Americans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 17:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Survival of the ... Nicest? | Corporate culture imposes uniformity, mandated from the top down, throughout the organization. But the cooperative is a modern institution that has much in common with the collective tribal heritage of our species. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-05 17:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Banks on the Run and the Homeowners Underwater | You cant talk about poverty without talking about the practices of the big banks, including their continuing refusal to stem the foreclosure crisis through mortgage principal reductions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-02 14:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Repeal the Sequester -- And the Insanity Behind It | Sure, we urgently need to repeal the sequester. But its even more important to repeal the insane thinking that led to the sequester. That means repealing the deficit babble that still dominates Washington. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-02 14:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Skeptics Guide to the Mind: What Neuroscience Can and Cannot Tell Us About Ourselves | A short summary review from Science-Based Medicine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 16:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> India is Drowning in its Own Excreta -- Can Science and Engineering Come to the Rescue? | Toilets and sewage disposal are among the least researched technologies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 17:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Krugman   Co.: Austerity's Failure Everywhere You Look | The Keynesians win every argument, say notable economists, so why does fiscal policy refuse to budge? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 16:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Does It Mean To Be An American Corporation? | Why do We the People even have laws that allow corporations and give them special benefits? The answer obviously is for our common benefit - why else would we do it? American corporations are holding $1.7 trillion in profits outside the country. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 22:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad beehaviour | The strange case of the bandit bumblebees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 21:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coding, Fast and Slow: Developers and the Psychology of Overconfidence | The key is that you first accept that making accurate long-term estimates is fundamentally impossible. How you can your dev team generate a ton of value, even though you can not make meaningful long-term estimates? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 03:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stop complaining about the lack of women in tech | No more complaining. No more calling people out for making mistakes unless were offering to help them fix it. No more negativity for the sake of it. But bring on the positive encouragement, because we can never get enough of that. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 02:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 15:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beat my age by 18. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 17:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Absolute Beginner English](http://esl.about.com/od/teachingbeginners/a/ab_beg_intro.htm) may have something you could use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breaking News Is Broken | Dont watch cable news. Shut off Twitter. Youd be better off cleaning your gutters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 04:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Physicist Proposes New Way To Think About Intelligence | "We basically view this as a grand unified theory of intelligence. And I know that sounds perhaps impossibly ambitious, but it really does unify so many threads across a variety of fields." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 04:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 02:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't at all mean to imply the person's evaluation changes.  Just that tense they use might.  Make it about the meal instead of the restaurant.  Would most languages make the shift from **I like** to **I liked** at the same time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 17:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two weeks!  Stay three months in NZ, join a [hostel network](http://www.bbh.co.nz/) and really see the country, both islands.  You won't regret it.  Then spend three months in Oz.  You'll barely scratch the surface of Oz in that time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 16:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an amazing lack of appreciation so many of these comments display for any sort of notion of the common good.  It's entirely possible to want less wealth inequality because of something other than wanting to take your money and put it in my pocket.  As though an increase in wealth equality takes something from you personally without giving anything back.  How about being able to live in a country with less wretched poverty? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Save Retirement (Its Simple, and Its Not Chained CPI) | A more realistic assessment reveals that the solution to Americas retirement crisis lies in the opposite direction-expanding Social Security, not cutting it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 01:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Not To Respond to the Boston Marathon Bombings | If we tell ourselves that nothing is ever going to be the same again, the terrorists win. Life is not going to change because some freak with pressure cookers and gunpowder wants it to. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 01:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 20:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had no intention of doing a corpus study.  All I want is to see whether knowledgeable people have commented on this phenomenon, if it exists.  This is a mild curiosity of mine, not something I can justify with evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Criteria for switching from the present tense to a past tense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 17:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an intuition that languages differ in their criteria for switching from the present tense to a past tense.  For example, when does 'I like this restaurant' shift to 'I liked that restaurant'?  Just before leaving, just ourside the door, after arriving home?  

Not knowing how to characterize this so as to research it, I keep running into prescriptive advice not to employ tense shifting, along with explanations of the various uses of tenses.  

My notion is that English is quicker to switch to a past tense than many other languages, such as possibly German, Spanish or Japanese.  How do I go about investigating this on the internet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 04:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recommend watching [Griefwalker](http://www.nfb.ca/film/griefwalker), a film that may transform your relationship to death and dying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: School Reform in 3 Major Cities Didn't Pass the Test | "The reforms deliver few benefits and in some cases harm the students they purport to help, while drawing attention and resources away from policies with real promise to address poverty-related barriers to school success" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 18:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 13 Spills. 30 Days. Nearly 1.2 Million Toxic Gallons. | A new infographic tells the toxic tale... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 18:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Parents Around the World Describe Their Children, in Charts | A fascinating new study reveals that Americans are more likely to call their children "intelligent," while European parents focus on happiness and balance. Here's why. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 18:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 01:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a Stein voter and it worked well for me.  My 1/129,064,662 of a cent went to the person I preferred.  I wouldn't have done that if I weren' t voting in a state safe for Obama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Avoiding Corporate Crime | "Theres little question that corporate crime -- pollution, corruption, fraud, reckless homicide -- inflicts far more damage on society than all street crime combined. Yet it is rarely talked about in the mainstream press." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 16:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Kings Two Americas Truer Now than Ever | Taken together, the sequester and other budget-cutting policies will likely slow GDP this year by 2.1 percentage points, costing the U.S. economy over 2.4 million jobs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 16:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Voters Forgive Obama for Cutting Social Security? | Self-righteous critics have portrayed Social Security as the profligate monster borrowing from the Treasury and sucking the life out of federal government. It's the other way around. The federal government borrows from Social Security. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 16:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 21:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recommend checking out [praise effort not ability](https://www.google.com/search?q=praise+effort+not+ability aq=0 oq=praise+effort+ sourceid=chrome ie=UTF-8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 19:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meant to use this full title:
The 40 Year Recession: The Modern Economy's Long Downward Spiral | How the "Long Recession" led to the "Great Recession" | "Between 1971 and 2007, real hourly wages in the U.S. rose by only 4%.  (Thats not 4% a year, but 4% over 36 years!)" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Between 1971 and 2007, real hourly wages in the U.S. rose by only 4%. (Thats not 4% a year, but 4% over 36 years!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 19:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 20:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh come on, you can paint with a more delicate brush than that.  I'm writing from Michoacn and there's plenty of peace here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Can Atheists Learn From Believers? | Jeremy Bentham would always ask of a proposition or belief, Is it true? By contrast, Benthams contemporary Samuel Taylor Coleridge thought What is the meaning of it? was a much more interesting question. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-28 16:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Digital Grab: Corporate Power Has Seized the Internet | The huge imbalance of digital power now afflicting the Internet is a crucial subset of what afflicts the entirety of economic relations and political power in the United States. We have a profound, far-reaching fight on our hands.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-28 14:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jim Hightower: Corporate Kangaroo Courts Supplant Our Seventh Amendment Rights | Since binding mandatory arbitration "agreements" are written by corporate lawyers, it's no surprise that they stack the deck in favor of corporations. But - wow! - the percentage of rigged wins is disgusting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-27 15:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Criticizing in Private Undermines Your Team | Leadership isn't about being comfortable; it's about being effective, even when you're uncomfortable. Smart leaders address ineffective team member behavior in the team setting when it occurs, or when the behavior affects the team. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 22:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> America Split in Two: Five Ugly Extremes of Inequality | Out of 141 countries, the U.S. has the 4th-highest degree of wealth inequality in the world, trailing only Russia, Ukraine, and Lebanon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 18:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Cleaning Is Not Always A Feminist Issue | If you tell me I have to do something that I feel is a waste of time, and don't care to see done, you're not striking a blow for gender equality. You're just imposing your vision of the world on another person. But don't call it fairness, or feminism. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 05:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Parenting Became a Blood Sport | Students are told their lives will be determined by how well they perform in school, and by which school they go to, even though research tells a different story. There is a multi-billion dollar tutoring industry that is pushing this myth really hard.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 04:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-22 03:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much everyone calls SS entitlements but it would be fairer to call them earned benefits.  The entitlement comes from their having been earned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Selling the Store: Why Democrats Shouldnt Put Social Security and Medicare on the Table | "...in fact the pie is larger than ever. Its just that those who have the largest and fastest-growing portions refuse to share it." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 15:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No More Steubenvilles: How To Raise Boys to be Kind Men | Our boys need to know that they will find themselves at a crossroads one night, or on multiple nights.  It is a young mans responsibility to listen to his partner.  Explain to your son what consent looks like (and doesnt look like).   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 03:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why bankers are intellectually naked | Banking is more dangerous than they dare imagine. Bankers gain vastly on the upside while shifting the downside on to others... We have failed to remove the causes of the crisis. Further such crises will come. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 03:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why bankers are intellectually naked | Banking is more dangerous than they dare imagine. Bankers gain vastly on the upside while shifting the downside on to others... We have failed to remove the causes of the crisis. Further such crises will come. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 03:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Capitalism efficient? We can do so much better | Workers self-directed enterprises would be far less likely to relocate production, far less likely to distribute profits among workers in extremely unequal ways, and to install technologies with negative impacts on the environment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 02:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wall Street Execs Should Face Criminal Consequences | Youre telling me that not one banker, not one executive on Wall Street, not one player in this entire financial crisis committed provable fraud? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 02:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Ultra-Conservatives Like the Sequester | Democratic pundits say that Republicans want to hurt the president, to show government doesnt work by making it not work, and to protect special interests from higher taxes. All true. But there is an additional and deeper reason. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 02:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sequestration: Washingtons Stupid, Destructive Game | The president could demand an end to the game. He could say that the sequester must be shelved permanently, right now, and then make the case for investment to heal our economy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 17:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Fed Could Fix the Economy-and Why It Hasnt | As QE is practiced today, money created on a computer screen never makes it into the real, producing economy. It goes directly into bank reserve accounts, and it stays there. The money power needs to be restored to the people and the government. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 17:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trouble with Austerity: Cutting is More About Ideology than Economics | Austerity fetishism is not economics; it is simply the latest expression of free market orthodoxy and, as ideology, impervious to evidence, never wrong. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-24 22:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Think Britain and the US Are Meritocratic Societies? Think Again | Those who have been successful either in business, the professions, academia or politics fall into two categories: either they consider themselves fortunate, or attribute their achievements to their hard work and relentless drive. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-24 22:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can the United States Heal Its Politics in Time? | This is a vital question, for not only must the United States get its house in order for the health and well-being of our people, but we need to step up and fill the global leadership vacuum left empty by decades of short-sighted self-interest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-23 17:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The babies who nap in sub-zero temperatures | Would you put your baby or toddler outside in the freezing cold for their lunchtime nap? Most Nordic parents wouldn't give it a second thought. For them it's part of their daily routine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 17:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clayton Christensen Wants to Transform Capitalism | Some industries right now that are either in a state of disruptive crisis or will be soon: Journalism, certainly, and publishing broadly. Anything supported by advertising. And then I think higher education is just on the edge of the crevasse.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-20 19:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scale Implosion: After Ruining America, the Era of Giant Chain Stores Is Over | Everything gigantic in American life is about to get smaller or die. The campaign to sustain the unsustainable, which is the official policy of US leadership, will only produce deeper whirls of entropy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-20 18:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Strengthening Social Security for All | Americans need Social Security more than ever, and theyre willing to pay for it. Rather than more cuts, we need higher benefits across the board. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-20 17:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cooperative Way to a Stronger Economy | My hope is over time, diverse forms of democratic ownership displace predatory capitalism as the foundation for our economy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-20 17:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wall Streets Misdeeds Cost Trillions, But Its Main Street Whos Getting Nickel-and-Dimed | Both parties are reportedly open to a budget agreement that would cut $130 billion in Social Security benefits for the elderly and disabled over the next ten years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-19 17:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Lamest Excuses Money Can Buy | Excuses for Inequality, for Bank Fraud, for a Dormant Minimum Wage, for Not Paying Taxes, for No Taxes At All. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-18 18:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Premises and Purposes of American Exceptionalism | That the US is objectively "the greatest country ever to exist" is as irrational as it is destructive, yet it maintains the status of orthodoxy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-18 18:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antibiotics and Antibiotic-Resistant Bacteria in Meat: Not Getting Better | This continued antibiotic use, and rising appearance of resistant bacteria on meat, is happening as the FDA has abandoned attempts to regulate livestock producers use of antibiotics,   has switched to a voluntary approach. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-18 06:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What it's like to uncover a $1 billion fraud | The moral of the story is watch your ass out there and don't be afraid to ask questions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-18 06:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sticking It to the SEC | Imagine - hundreds advocating for their clients with friends at the SEC - colleagues who themselves may be looking for a big payoff when they, too, leave government. No wonder the SEC has granted special waivers to business on some 350 occasions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-17 17:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 22:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that Social Security is an earned benefit, so it's puzzling that you characterize social insurance as "redistributive". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Are Proponents of the Chained CPI So Scared of Data? | This is just about cutting Social Security benefits. The chained CPI has nothing to do with accuracy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 17:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Great Wealth Robbery | The top 1 percent has captured 121 percent of the increases in income since the worst of the financial crisis, while the rest of the country has continued to fall behind. You rescued them. Now theyre drinking your milkshake. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 17:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The girls are not alright | We need to ask ourselves - those of us young enough to feel weightlessly innocent of the Magdalen and clerical sex abuse scandals - what would we have done to stop it, and what socially acceptable wickedness are we willfully not-noticing right now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 03:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Seven Habits Of Highly Effective Mediocre People | Being mediocre doesnt mean you wont change the world. It means being honest with yourself and the people around you. And being honest at every level is really the most effective habit of all if you want to have massive success. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 20:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quinoa: To Buy or Not to Buy... Is This the Right Question? |  The so-called quinoa quandary demonstrates the limits of consumption-driven politics. To address the problem we have to analyze the system itself, and the very structures that constrain consumer and producer choices.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 17:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theres Grief in Coming Home | We have to be in the culture making business, and soon. Real culture is not built on bad myths of superiority or inevitability or victory. The work of building culture is learning and remembering how things have come to be as they are. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 00:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Real Debt Issue: Its Not How Much We Will Owe, Its Who Will Hold the Note | Theres a dirty little secret lurking behind the Republicans debt and deficit hysteria. We the people will end up with more debt than if we dont, and fat cats and corporations will be holding the note. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 19:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 20:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, that's the point of the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Acts of God | Why do we think that private automobile insurance works, but insist on government health insurance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 18:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Increasing Social Security Benefits: An Idea Whose Time Has Come | Theres no reason not to make this change, starting now. No reason except one, that is - the refusal of our political leadership to see what must be done and do it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 18:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Sorry State of Our Union | Fiscal contraction slows the recovery, and the loss of public investment denies the government the very tools it needs to use education and infrastructure to help rebuild the middle class. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 18:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Relax! Youll Be More Productive | Strategic renewal - including daytime workouts, short afternoon naps, longer sleep hours, more time away from the office and longer, more frequent vacations - boosts productivity, job performance and, of course, health. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 06:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Repairing the rungs on the ladder: How to prevent a virtuous meritocracy entrenching itself at the top | The clever rich are turning themselves into an entrenched elite. This phenomenoncall it the paradox of virtuous meritocracyundermines equality of opportunity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 04:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bring Dark Money to Account | A long-dormant rule within the 1996 Telecommunications Act gives the FCC the authority to mandate disclosure of the funders behind political ads. It would let viewers know that an ad from Concerned Taxpayers of America is merely the creation of two multi-millionaires. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 18:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The US Should Grow the Deficit, Not Shrink It | The US economy is too fragile to reduce spending and raise taxes. Fiscal austerity is a recipe for worse pain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 17:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Austerity Cuts Coming to the States | Youd expect after years of austerity cuts to public services, state politicians would think of new ways to raise revenue from those who can afford it. Not so. Raising revenue from the wealthy is off the table for Republicans and Democrats alike. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 17:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Animal spirits | After you spend time with wild animals in the primal ecosystem where our big brains first grew, you have to chuckle a bit at the reigning view of the mind as a computer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 21:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corporate America: Saving the Twinkie but Not the Workers | Hostess Twinkies are likely to survive as a product, even though the company that makes them has gone bankrupt. The Twinkie brand will be sold off in bankruptcy to other companies who expect to be able to profitably market them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 17:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ten Virtues For The Modern Age |  Virtue needs rehabilitating. But also updating. Try this draft list of ten virtues appropriate to the modern age: Resilience; empathy; patience; sacrifice; politeness; humour; self-awareness; forgiveness; hope; confidence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 19:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smothered By Safety | American child safety laws and regulations go far beyond reasonable limits. Illegal in 19 states to leave a minor alone in a car, even for a minute. Connecticut mother charged with negligence for letting her children -11 and 7 - walk half a mile to buy a pizza. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 18:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Anniversary of Americas First Progressive Revolution | A progressive backlash against concentrated wealth and power occurred a century ago in America. In the 1880s and 1890s such a movement seemed improbable if not impossible. But it did happen. And it will happen again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 18:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Men Can Help Women Succeed in the Military | Are we willing to see a man who is at home with his children while his wife is off on the front-lines, as fully a man? We better be able to answer that question yes, or we are not going to see genuine female equality in the military or anywhere else. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-03 22:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Growing Wealth Gap Is Unsustainable | "A radical recalibration of capitalism is essential, not least because the wealthiest and least productive are in danger of allowing their own avarice to sabotage the very system on which they have become so hideously bloated." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-03 17:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Men Can Help Women Succeed in the Military | Are we willing to see a man who is at home with his children while his wife is off on the front-lines, as fully a man? We better be able to answer that question yes, or we are not going to see genuine female equality in the military or anywhere else. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-03 07:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Police Lie Under Oath | The fact that our legal system has become so tolerant of police lying indicates how corrupted our criminal justice system has become by get tough mantras and a seemingly insatiable appetite for locking up and locking out the poorest and darkest among us. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-03 06:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Valuable, Cheap College Degree | "The case for the 10K-B.A. is primarily moral, not financial. The entrepreneurs who see a way for millions to go to college affordably understand the American dream...the opportunity to build a life through earned success. That starts with education." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-02 17:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time to Take On Concentrated Poverty and Education | "As the United States increasingly regresses toward a Gilded Age of haves and have-nots-in terms of income, education, and opportunity-taking on concentrated poverty is critical." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-02 17:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The statistical significance scandal: The standard error of science? | Statistical significance is responsible for more idiotic ideas in the scientific literature than anything else - Charles Seife </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-01 18:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Economic Alternative to Exploitative Free Market Capitalism | The neoliberal market does not, paradoxically, grasp the purpose behind the commons. Our current system is one-dimensional and is designed to attach a price to everything. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-01 18:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 22:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well then, good luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Are Women Angry? Because 'They Still Have to Protest This Shit' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 18:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Think preventive medicine will save money? Think again | A 2010 study in the journal Health Affairs calculated that if 90 percent of the U.S. population used proven preventive services, more than do now, it would save only 0.2 percent of healthcare spending. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-30 18:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Treadmill desks: How practical are they? | "The health consequences of prolonged sitting... include not only obesity but also hypertension, hyperlipidemia - high cholesterol if you like - cardiovascular disease, certain types of cancer, poor or low mood, a predisposition to diabetes." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-30 18:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do What You Love? Screw That | "Passion is not something you follow. Passion is something that will follow you as you put in the hard work to become valuable to the world." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-30 17:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are Placebos Really Sugar Pills? | Drug companies manufacture their own placebos -- and aren't required to list the ingredients. One reason this is so disturbing is that drug companies are allowed to use (and do increasingly use) active placebos in their studies.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-30 17:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Gates: My Plan to Fix The World's Biggest Problems | Setting clear goals, choosing an approach, measuring results, and then using those measurements to continually refine our approach, helps us to deliver tools and services to everybody who will benefit.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 05:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 08:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There aren't a lot of photos of that kind on my subreddits, but I am bothered by sexist comments when I see them.  I'm also amazed by the comments here by those who don't notice it or don't care.  But then I'm an old geezer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 07:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just recently stumbled on the work of [Stephen Jenkinson] (https://www.google.com/url?sa=t rct=j q= esrc=s source=web cd=23 cad=rja ved=0CNYBEBYwFg url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.matrixwissen.de%2Findex.php%3Foption%3Dcom_content%26view%3Darticle%26id%3D703%3Astephen-jenkinson-culture-of-dying%26catid%3D118%3Ageschichte%26Itemid%3D98%26lang%3Den ei=ic0EUbmEK6jyigLuhYDoDg usg=AFQjCNGkomT_ohOGokpFWiaZItc1Bs8THw sig2=ldTK4Bm0_yjgABW4Tj2ElA bvm=bv.41524429,d.cGE) and I was blown away by the power of the guy and what he has to say.  Though everyone from 8 on up should hear him speak, I believe it has special relevance for you, both for yourself and for your relationship to your mom.  Uplifting and inspiring thoughts on a topic our culture considers a downer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 07:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see how you get *sole providers* out of that quote, or the article as a whole.  Anyway, chacun  son got. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 06:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article:
... men obviously also suffer violence, largely at the hands of other men, and every violent death, every assault is terrible.  But the subject here is the pandemic of violence by men against women, both intimate violence and stranger violence.  

Is this focus not allowed?  What makes it out of line? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 21:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a subreddit for discussion and conversation concerning the topics of equality in all subjects (such as racial equality, age equality et cetera) but mainly focusing on sex/gender equality.


So I didn't think it would be out of line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Longest War is the One Against Women | We have far more than 87,000 rapes in this country every year, but each of them is invariably portrayed as an isolated incident.  We have dots so close theyre splatters melting into a stain, but hardly anyone connects them, or names that stain.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 18:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Longest War is the One Against Women | We have far more than 87,000 rapes in this country every year, but each of them is invariably portrayed as an isolated incident.  We have dots so close theyre splatters melting into a stain, but hardly anyone connects them, or names that stain.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 18:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Last Calendar | Co-ordinating medical care for a dying father. "At the time, I was glad we kept the calendar because it helped us to cope with a difficult situation. Now Im glad for a different reason: it helps me remember small details about him, the little things that slip out of memory." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 22:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear brilliant students: Please consider not doing a PhD. | The thing about a PhD is that it's a criminally stupid way for highly intelligent people to train other highly intelligent people.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 19:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ownership, Full Employment and Community Economic Stability | Worker ownership works in the US, as well. Its not often realized that there are over 10 million Americans who work at jobs they also own-more than are members of unions in the private sector. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 18:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Letter I Wish Progressive Groups Would Send to Their Members | The leadership we need is certainly not coming from the White House or Congress.  The leadership we need has to come, first and foremost, from us. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 18:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The sorry state of neighbourhood design in America: a mother writes | Community is built by people passing each other in the streets, by NEIGHBORhoods, not strangerhoods. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 21:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our Dumb Democracy | These absurdities exist because our media has replaced truth, accuracy and reality with balance, false equivalency, and stenography and Democrats have been silent co-conspirators. Because the press is a wholly owned subsidiary of corporations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 17:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Powder Keg in the Pacific | Conditions are deteriorating in the western Pacific.  Things are turning ugly, with consequences that could prove deadly and spell catastrophe for the global economy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 17:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secret Ingredient for Success | No ones idea of a good time is to take a brutal assessment of their animating assumptions. But challenging our assumptions, objectives, at times even our goals, may sometimes push us further than we thought possible. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 19:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MLK Injustice Index 2013: Racism, Materialism and Militarism in the US | when machines and computers, profit motives and property rights, are considered more important than people, the giant triplets of racism, materialism and militarism are incapable of being conquered. - King, 1967 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 18:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martin Luther King Was a Radical, Not a Saint | He believed that America needed a "radical redistribution of economic and political power." He challenged America's class system and its racial caste system.  He was a strong ally of the nation's labor union movement. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 18:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Profits of World's 100 Wealthiest Could End Poverty Four Times Over | It is time our leaders reformed the system so that it works in the interests of the whole of humanity rather than a global elite. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 18:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interview with George Church: Can Neanderthals Be Brought Back from the Dead? | Computers made of DNA will be better than the current computers, because they will have even smaller processors and be more energy efficient. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 06:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can National Grassroots Push Depose the 'Billion Dollar Democracy'? | Elections are now awash in unregulated money and ruled by the nation's wealthiest, but can a grassroots effort stem the assault on democracy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-18 18:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Would a Down-to-Earth Economy Look Like? | How did we end up with Wall Street when models for a healthy economy are all around us?  Extreme individualism, greed, and violence are pathological and a sign of physical, developmental, cultural, and/or institutional system failure.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-18 18:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have We Solved 'Too Big To Fail'? | "No. Expectations of state support have risen threefold since the crisis began." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-17 18:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jim Hightower: Who's Behind Fix the Debt? | Unfortunately, they're using "fix" in the same way your veterinarian uses it - their core demand is for Washington to spay Social Security, castrate Medicare and geld Medicaid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-16 17:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pop Quiz on Standardized Testing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-16 17:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 22:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been buying [Acer Aspires](http://www.amazon.com/s/ref=sr_st?keywords=acer+aspire qid=1358283439 rh=n%3A172282%2Ck%3Aacer+aspire sort=price).  Good value. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 07:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are lots of [online sources](http://www.darntough.com/online-retailers.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teacher Bar Exams Would Be a Huge Mistake | School districts should be less discriminating in choosing new teachers, but more discriminating in deciding which veteran teachers receive tenure. This may seem counterintuitive, but for teachers, the best predictor of future results is past performance.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 07:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 02:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Unitarian Universalist community would provide a moral education and a respect for world religions without inculcating doctrines. Many UU members are atheists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 01:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not mine -- it's from the article, which is worth a look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charity, Accuracy and Being "Nice" in (Online) Debates | Demonising, character attacking, mockery and so on are indicators of knee-jerk responses that provides no insight into the debate itself. The force of your emotive replies jaggedly masks the rigid structure of proper argument. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 01:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What *Should* We Be Worried About? | That humans will be less and less able to appreciate what they should really be worrying about and that their worries will do more harm than good. Maybe one should try not to slow down anything but just to optimize a trajectory one does not really control. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-14 23:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What *Should* We Be Worried About? | That we are incapable of worrying about the right things, because we're (a) compelled by thrilling information, (b) discount the future, (c) tend to see our immediate troubles as our biggest, and (d) tend to think that the world is just.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-14 23:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-14 19:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are some interesting comments on [Hacker News](http://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=5054618). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Japanese Kids Learn To Multiply </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-14 18:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Five-Step Process to Cheat the Middle Class Worker | 1. Boost productivity while keeping worker wages flat. 2. Build up a financial industry that has no maximum wage. 3. Keep accumulating wealth created by the financial industry. 4. Tax yourself as little as possible... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-14 17:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Us and them | Oxytocin emerged as a promoter of ethnocentrism, in-group favouritism and escalating group conflict...  It induced them to see a greater emotional range in their own group, while having no effect on how they perceived the others emotional hinterland. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-14 03:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Situations Matter | I actually think the more context-dependent view of attraction is liberating. If happiness in relationships was really all about finding that needle of a soulmate in the haystack of the real world man, that's really the depressing or daunting proposition, isn't it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-13 02:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Soda and Violence |  In a study of 1,878 students at Boston public high schools, heavy soda drinkers were much more prone to violent behavior than other teens. That finding came about by accident.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-13 01:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Krugman: US Economic Policy Resulting in 'Vast, Unnecessary Catastrophe' | We should put aside our excessive focus on saving money, try to overcome political recalcitrance, and spend money to put America back to work.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 22:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corporate Gold on the Fiscal Cliff | A deal was struck that will extend the subsidies for Goldmans fancy new headquarters. In their 43 stories of glass and steel, and a footprint two city blocks long, Goldman Sachs reigns supreme - thanks to a system rigged by and for the powerful rich. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 18:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rework School Leadership | I just finished reading Rework. Although it has a business slant, there are many great links to school leadership. "Policies are organizational scar tissue. They are codified overreactions to situations that are unlikely to happen again." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 23:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zero Dark Thirty: Torturing the Facts | "The CIA did not first learn about the existence of the UBL courier from CIA detainees subjected to coercive interrogation techniques. Nor did the CIA discover the couriers identity from CIA detainees subjected to coercive techniques." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 18:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sick By Choice? US Health Worse Than Nearly All Other Industrialized Countries | 'We were stunned by the propensity of findings all on the negative side - the scope of the disadvantage covers all ages, from babies to seniors, both sexes, all classes of society.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-10 17:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4 Modest Wishes for New Treasury Secretary Jack Lew </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-10 17:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-10 01:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The the *overly non factual editorialized title* was supplied by The Guardian.  I agree that it's a distortion of progressives' views. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
