<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1529</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My DJ Crush: Flume </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 08:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 20:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's cloudy a lot. Seriously. Seasonal Affective Disorder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 10:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, fuckin' soccer players, every goddamn time. So hot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minorities and poor college students are shouldering the most student debt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 22:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minorities and poor college students are shouldering the most student debt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 22:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanderss plan to have Wall Street pay for your college tuition, explained </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 22:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Media coverage of gang violence sure looks different when the perpetrators are white </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 22:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Media coverage of gang violence sure looks different when the perpetrators are white </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 22:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany needs to calm down: The country's political left is hyperventilating over a string of spying revelations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 22:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greece says deal near, again: But same old barriers to an agreement with creditors remain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 22:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kayaktavists Take Over Seattle's Port to Protest Shell Oil's Arctic Drilling Rig </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kayaktavists Take Over Seattle's Port to Protest Shell Oil's Arctic Drilling Rig </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kayaktavists Take Over Seattle's Port to Protest Shell Oil's Arctic Drilling Rig </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kayaktavists Take Over Seattle's Port to Protest Shell Oil's Arctic Drilling Rig </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fossil fuels subsidised by $10m a minute, says IMF: Shocking revelation finds $5.3tn subsidy estimate for 2015 is greater than the total health spending of all the worlds governments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Supreme Court ruled Monday that San Francisco police cannot be sued by a mentally disturbed woman who was shot repeatedly during a 2008 confrontation, but the justices declined to rule on whether the officers involved were required to use less forceful methods. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Supreme Court ruled Monday that San Francisco police cannot be sued by a mentally disturbed woman who was shot repeatedly during a 2008 confrontation, but the justices declined to rule on whether the officers involved were required to use less forceful methods. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US residents' exposure to extreme heat could increase four- to six-fold by mid-century, due to both a warming climate and a population that's growing especially fast in the hottest regions of the country, according to new research. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. loses meat labeling case; trade war looms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders Wants to Tax Stock Trades to Pay for Free College </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU approves military force against smugglers: The focus now shifts to winning UN approval to take the fight into Libyan territory. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worker-rights groups are calling labor conditions in Qatar "horrific" and urging FIFA sponsors to take responsibility ahead of the 2022 soccer World Cup. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US officials are increasingly anxious about the potential for mass violence in Burundi, a small African country whose troops have received significant American support and play a major role in the fight against Islamist militants. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the era of college grads working at restaurants and cafes is coming to an end </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mission Unstoppable: From drone strikes to prison torture, the CIA has been pulling the strings of U.S. foreign policy since 9/11. And if history is a guide, the agency will be calling the shots in the Middle East for years to come. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mission Unstoppable: From drone strikes to prison torture, the CIA has been pulling the strings of U.S. foreign policy since 9/11. And if history is a guide, the agency will be calling the shots in the Middle East for years to come. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Captured Russian Special Forces Soldier Describes His Unit Fighting in Eastern Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Balancing China and the Realist Road to War: The argument for balancing against China rests on some questionable assumptions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Serial Didn't Tell You About Adnan Syed: The addictive public-radio series focused on his background. A broader problem is at play that hurts thousands of kids. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 01:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bus terminated its route at 8:30pm, and it was the last bus? Is this a true story? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bush didn't say Apple Watches should replace Obamacare. He said something weirder. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 01:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review Board Notes Rise in New York Officers False Statements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 01:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tajik Special Police Commander Disappears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 01:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Libya to Europe: Please Dont Come to Our Rescue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 01:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bush Just Nailed a Flip-Flop-Flip-Flop on the Iraq War </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 01:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five soldiers killed in fierce fighting in Burundi's capital </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 01:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indias Military Cannot Fight Wars Lasting Longer than 20 Days: A recent report by the Indian government points to an ammunition crisis in the India Army. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 23:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 04:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plenty of redditors don't like this quote in particular because the arms industry manufactures the firearms that they love. That's part of it.

The other part is that reddit doesn't like religion very much. The pope is a religious figure.

Another part is that the Catholic Church has caused plenty of deaths in its time, and is hardly a pillar of moral superiority.

Another is that it's just sort of obvious to most people.

That's why the comments are so hostile. Luckily, it seems that many more thousands of people think it's a fine quote, by the vote count. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The White House formally threw its support behind the USA Freedom Act Tuesday, fully endorsing a plan to end the government's bulk collection of personal data and replace it with a more tailored program that would allow phone companies to do the collection instead. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police in the central Florida city where George Zimmerman suffered minor injuries in an apparent road rage incident said the suspect in the shooting had two guns in his car at the time  and that Zimmerman also had a gun. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Madison, Wisconsin, cop who shot and killed unarmed teenager Tony Terrell Robinson Jr. won't face charges, the prosecutor said Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 20:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great write up, but just to point something out about the idiomatic phrase in the beginning, it's "makes my blood boil" not "makes me boil my blood." For future reference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moving the Drone Program from the CIA to the Pentagon Wont Improve Transparency: Generals arent better than spooks when it comes to reporting civilian casualties. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 22:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Syrian group opposed to the country's autocratic leader, Bashar al-Assad, says airstrikes by the U.S.-led coalition killed 52 civilians. The Syrian Observatory for Human Rights called the alleged killings a "massacre" committed under the "pretext" of targeting ISIS militants. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian warships force Lithuania to halt Baltic power cable construction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian warships force Lithuania to halt Baltic power cable construction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Norway Can Teach the U.S. About Getting More Women Into Boardrooms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraqi forces plead for help as Islamic State closes in on refinery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Monday, a group of Israeli veterans released sobering testimony from fellow soldiers that suggests permissive rules of engagement coupled with indiscriminate artillery fire contributed to the mass destruction and high numbers of civilian casualties in the [Gaza Strip] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Journalists Critical Of FIFA Arrested And Detained In Qatar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 18:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Journalists Critical Of FIFA Arrested And Detained In Qatar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 18:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas Governor Deploys State Guard To Stave Off Obama Takeover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 01:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A shocking number of mentally ill Americans end up in prison instead of treatment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 01:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
