<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3431</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have an economics exam in 35 hours and I only know like 50-60 percent of the material. I'm planning on doing an all nighter to study, any advice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 19:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the Earth was united into a single country, would it be good or bad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 06:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 19:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I either want to major in Music (been building repertoire for the past 15 years) or major in an IT-related major like Spatial Systems or CS... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crow says "Fuck you" to a guy who tries to mess with it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 09:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 03:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 18:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When companies usually state a BS as a requirement, would a degree like MEng, MPhil or PhD be overkill? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google is currently recruiting a Geo Data Specialist! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 12:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, who were the most underserving Nobel Prize recipients? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 07:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm soo friggin horny and can't stop thinking about sex with my GF! I can't get pass day 4, help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 05:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 04:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in a destructive relationship with my girlfriend who had a terminal illness and I just wanted to give up because I couldn't bear to see her slowly fade as the days went by but I persisted and was at her side even during her last moments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you're in an incredibly heated argument with someone, what are some things you could say that would just make them laugh uncontrollably? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 15:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is runescape dead? Too late to join? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 14:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While the human imagination is a mighty force, we cannot imagine a new colour. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 13:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what are the MOST POPULAR browser based online games like MMORPGs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 13:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why isn't 11 pronounced as onety-one like 21? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 13:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If women are gold diggers, how come I don't see any in African gold mines? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 12:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to start the violin but i'm 19... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 04:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, I really love the sounds of the violin and have tons of friends who are amazing violinists and i'm kinda inspired to be like them and learn the violin but... i'm 19... I feel as if i'm too old.

Now, while I don't have any unrealistic goals of ever reaching their level considering how they're already breezing through pieces like the Bach Chaccone, Mendelssohn Concertos, Caprices, etc. I don't know if it's the right move... will I forever sound like crap and be bounded to Suzuki-like-pieces? :(

I have some musical experience, i've been playing the piano for 15 years and have done my FRSM in music theory so I hope that can help a bit. I'm open to all advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 17:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She got tired after her laughing fit and went straight to sleep, leaving me alone, cold, lonely and very horny :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Completely new to the guitar, any tips? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 15:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, i'm going to go get a classical guitar to learn soon and was wondering if ya'll had any advice! 

I'm 18 and i've been playing the classical piano for 15 years and what I found with the piano is that at the beginning fundamental exercises like Czerny,Hanon,etc. are essential in building technique. Is there a similar thing for the guitar? 

I'm open to any advice, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by trying to talk dirty to my GF </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 12:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we were having a really hot make out/foreplay session and I (who was super horny), trying to be fucking suave, decided to just look her in her eyes to ramp up the hotness.

Our eyes lock on to each other and it was incredibly hot and beautiful and I decided to talk dirty. In the heat of the moment I said: "My tits are waiting for you". 

Let's just say the night ended there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know of fugues that have more than four melodies or a ridiculous amount of melodies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 06:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 05:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Impressive research, however through using Flaigocol mathematical derivations whereby the Hilbert spaces denote the Barnarch-Tarski paradox in equilibrium with the Fredhold theorem whereby the Erdos-nagy is 0, were can derive the Farrel-Markushevich in light of the Malgrage-Ehrenpresis if we denote the ZJ and Z* as the consant found in the Talor-Proudman. Thus:

Rasputin - Rasp[berry] = Utin[erry] 

Your mathematical rigour, though elegant, is flawed.

QED.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 07:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One year! Damn :(, so no hard boners during sex for a year? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 13:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How people often allude Patriotism to the military. 


I mean come on, I love my country and feel that there are tons of other ways to show this love OUTSIDE the friggin military!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 13:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My great grandmother calling me fat when I was already anorexic and around 49 kilos as a 175 cm male. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
