<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5937</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 08:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated an AMA on issues related to immigration. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 08:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated an AMA on issues related to trade issues. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 08:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated an AMA on issues related to exercise and ethnicity. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 08:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated an AMA on issues related to secrecy. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 08:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on issues related to current events. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 07:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on movies and impacts on society. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 07:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on issues related to extremism. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 07:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on Reddit related issues. Perhaps she can shed some light on how to word a post that makes sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 07:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated an AMA on issues related to subreddits. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 07:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on issues related to sales and marketing. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 07:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on issues related to Libya. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 07:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on employment issues. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 07:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on issues related to voting. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 07:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on issues related to football/soccer. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 07:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on issues related to international finance. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 07:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA  related to environmental issues. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 07:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on issues related to presidential candidates. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 07:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on issues related to finance and investing. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on issues related to ISIS. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on issues related to contagious diseases. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on issues related to crime. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on employment issues. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on issues related to same sex marriage. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on issues related to same-sex marriage. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on issues related to airline security. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on higher education issues. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on foreign affairs issues. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on security issues. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on Star Trek. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on pet ownership and care. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on issues related to pain. Perhaps she can shed some light on this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on corruption. Perhaps she can assist in this discussion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on abuse. Perhaps she could help shed some light on this situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on body piercings and other related topic. Perhaps she could shed some light here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on divisive politics. Perhaps we could have an AMA on this topic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on the "sex trade" profession.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 05:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Victoria facilitated several AMA on climate change  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> R*e-d.d,i~t in crisis: Chat boards hidden after popular staffer exits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 05:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 03:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [Brazen Bull](http://cdn8.openculture.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/brazen-bull.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the Brazen Bull was invented by Perillos for Phalaris, the tyrant of Akragas, Sicily, as a new means of executing criminals by cooking them alive in a bronze bull. Perillos was cooked in his own creation but released before death. Phalaris was killed in the Brazen Bull when he was overthrown. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 03:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 00:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I have a great interaction as a customer, I make sure I get their name, and then . . . 

- As I walk to my car I use Maps.Google.com to get the store/restaurant phone #

- I immediately call on speaker phone so I can do it NOW while I'm driving and it costs me no time

- I ask to speak to the Mgr, and say "Hey, you need to know what just happened with one of your employees . . ."

- As they brace for yet another complaint, I hit them with how fantastic Jane was (and why), and it's people like this that make me a loyal customer.

I guarantee: you, the manager, and the employee will all have a better day because you took the time. 

Edit: I thought about it, and I agree that an email, if you really will take the time, is even better since it creates a permanent record. I will now do both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 00:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  why you do bank on the hypothesis of a successful uprising

Did you even read my posts? I clearly stated:

"And, to be clear, Jang Jin-sung said the internal solution is "the forces of the market", not an overthrow of the government."

Attempting to converse with you is pointless. I'm out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 09:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the correction and additional info. 

I heard about this on a radio program and it was absolutely frightening. 

To be dismissed as dead, as you hear everything around you, with no way to break through, and to live that way for years, that would be crazy making.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 07:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a matter of pure statistics, it would be highly improbable that Trump would not present some positions now and then that actually make sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 07:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Go check yourself

I checked. Can confirm. Trump is an [ass-hat](https://sfcmac.files.wordpress.com/2011/01/asshat.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 07:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> black hole in my brain	

collider pushing limits

post tickling the edge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 05:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, right? Yet I get downvoted without . . . oh, why bother? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 04:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this is how the revolt began: 

"The type of robot that crushed the employee is usually kept in a cage. The man was working on the robot inside the cage when he was grabbed." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 04:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I skimmed the article, and here are some snippets: 

**Operation Uranus**: encirclement of the German Sixth Army to envelop German Army and Romanian headlong. Soviet troops were not without problems, due to commonly arriving late. Soviet forces on Axis forces, German reserves were not strong enough to parry the Soviet spearheads, did not react quickly enough to disengage. Soviet forces linked up encircling some men instead of attempting to break out of the encirclement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 04:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are more fired than a Mexican, drug-dealing, rapist, criminal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 04:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It, and he, are an **Ass-Hat**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 03:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yah - but just in case ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 03:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy is a walking **ass hat** - - in more ways than one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Being "boxed"**. That is being in what looks like a vegetative state, but you can hear everything that is going on, but you cannot respond in any way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Costco/Kirkland products are frequently made by big brand suppliers.

Ex: Kirkland coffee is supplied by Starbucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 01:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow - solid post. I was just going to post: "**I would smile**". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 01:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The woman police said Coleman shot and injured was Coleman's grandmother.

The sentence The Charlotte Observer printed Marusak wrote and butchered was Marusaks work product. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 01:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very timely. A group of a-holes have have been *"causing emotional distress" on the Internet* to me. I've been pretty well traumatized. Who  do I contact about [this crap?](http://www.legislation.govt.nz/bill/government/2013/0168/latest/DLM5711810.html?search=ts_act%40bill%40regulation%40deemedreg_Harmful+Digital+Communications+Bill_resel_25_a p=1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 00:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "So if you ~~at a govt job~~ owned slaves for 20+ years, and out of nowhere they change the ~~duties of your job~~ law to include something that may go against your morals. Do you feel they have a right to ~~fire you~~ take away your property? Have you ever heard of grandfathering people in?"

Interesting argument. I'll need to think about that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 23:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mechanic is expired.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 23:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  if they enforced federal law and raided pot dispensaries legal under state law ...

Like I give a flying fuck. There's this thing called Google. If you type in "DEA raids dispensary" you get:

- DEA Raids 2 Los Angeles Medical Marijuana Dispensaries

- DEA raids four Denver marijuana sites

- DEA raids 10 pot shops - LA Times

- DEA Raid Legal Medical Marijuana Dispensary...Again

- DEA Raids Washington Marijuana Dispensaries

BTW - I'm no "kid", as if that makes any difference in the veracity of my arguments vs. yours. Good day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 20:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, Mr. Bennett, we can totally tell that it's you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 20:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, pitching and catching . . . soon to become catching and pitching.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 19:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope several judges and clerks push the issue as far as they can. I would love to see federal marshals go in and enforce the law like a replay of "Little Rock Nine" in 1957. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 19:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they refuse to do their govt. job, then they should not have that job. I don't care if they are fired, or moved to another position. If they won't do their job they should be gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hilarious! I was trying to figure out how he'd be saved by this [lanyard](http://www.sportys.com/media/catalog/product/8/0/8096_2.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the US is due for a fascist dictator . . .  LIBERALS are thankfully preventing that

No, capitalists are preventing that. The wealthy and the corporations are in charge and have the most influence on who gets elected and on what policies are enacted. 

U.S. Politicians are much more like puppets than dictators.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My library even has a flier describing how to copy the file so it never expires . . . AKA piracy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The airline purchased an additional 23 safety lanyards following the accident and reinforced procedures for their optional use."

What are these "safety lanyards" and how would they prevent this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Military intervention? Covert ops? Peaceful dialogue between the two Koreas?

Do you really think any country is going to invade NK? And if they did, that NK wouldn't detonate nuclear bombs before facing defeat? In reality it wouldn't get that far since China would step in immediately. 

Covert ops? You don't think that was tried as NK was developing their nuclear program? It was. It failed.

"Peaceful ..." NK is still at war. There is no "peace" yet, and they have NO interest in pursuing peace. So, good luck there.

And, to be clear, Jang Jin-sung said the internal solution is "the forces of the market", not an overthrow of the government. 

I have no solutions other than shaming China into either owning the problem, or getting out of the way of others that want to "influence" the situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They would never go to prison. They would simply be charged, booked, and spend a few hours in jail before being released pending a plea deal (or, very unlikely, a trial if the prosecutor really wants to make an example of them - not likely). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  imprisoning people for their religious beliefs

For their beliefs - absolutely NOT.

For illegal actions ABSOLUTELY.

These clerks with convictions have 2 simple remedies: do your job, or work elsewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  there are alternatives for regime change

Please, do tell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 11:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well played, and very good point.

North Korea confounds me beyond any other country. I have no clue what the right approach might be.

I hate the regime, and my heart goes out to the people. 

From what I've read, I don't think an externally imposed solution makes sense. 

Given that, I see alternatives of (a) status quo, or (b) internal change.

I quoted Jang Jin-sung because I also believe that the change must come from within.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 10:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I had to vote right now - I would hold my nose and vote Hillary. 

That said, I don't trust her poll driven "convictions", and I don't think I am alone.

That is why I'm looking/hoping for viable alternatives to step up in the Dem party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 09:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I'll just let go, 'cause  . . .

Why did I have to act so mean?

Don't I know I'm human being?

Born of a mother with the love of a father

Reflections come and reflections go

I know sometimes I wanna let go

I know sometimes I want to let go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 09:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any publicity is good publicity as long as they spell your name right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 09:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jang Jin-sung says stop funding food aid:

North Korean exiles will tell you that the international community must stop funding food aid. We say this not out of spite with regard to a nation whose leadership invests in luxuries, nuclear tests and missile launches while the welfare of its subjects remains low among its priorities. We say this for pragmatic and humanitarian reasons, because the assumptions that lie behind funding food aid have hindered economic reform in our homeland, not helped it.

Today, the fatal threat for the regime lies not in the outside world, but within the country itself. More specifically, this is the jangmadang  an underground economy arisen from the ashes of economic collapse in the 1990s, and which consist of market activities taking place beyond the remit of the regimes control mechanisms.

In todays North Korea there are two rival forces in battle: the forces of the regime and the forces of the market. The formers interests are better served by the maintenance of existing party, military and surveillance mechanisms of control. The latter are equivalent to North Koreas progressives, who believe in a future that is possible beyond the absolute, stifling and structurally inhumane confines of the regime.

An international community wishing to assist the North Korean people should recognise that funding food aid is a channel of limited efficiency. The majority of North Koreans depend not on the regimes munificence but on market forces  they have already found this a more successful alternative, despite a disproportionate lack of international support or awareness.

Jang Jin-sung was one of Kim Jong-ils favourite state poets until he defected in 2004. He founded the North Korea news website New Focus International </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 08:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey OP - That's a lot of bull! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 08:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Chuck's got your back](http://leftwingnation.rocks/wp-content/uploads/2012/07/Chuck-Norris-Guns-Flag.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 08:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We blame religion . . .

I think that is in line with what Quasy1999 is talking about. But, whatever . . .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 07:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No surprise here:

"upheld a ruling that determined Apple to be the leader of an industrywide conspiracy among book publishers to raise prices of digital books." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 07:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was slammed by Reddit for saying this previously, but I truly feel that Clinton's toughest fight is against herself. She is just so prone to missteps, and actions that appear dishonest, that she will likely continue to alienate her base. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 07:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was slammed by Reddit for saying this previously, but I truly feel that Clinton's toughest fight is against herself. She is just so prone to missteps, and actions that appear dishonest, that she will likely continue to alienate her base.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 07:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I always thought it was: **Bail And Smack Earth** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 07:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please explain the difference between having diarrhea, and having "**active**" diarrhea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 07:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plot twist - that's why they need so much of our blood - - to make up for the lack of oxygen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 06:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  rip that department apart for an explosion

That escalated quickly. (that said, I agree with you entirely)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 04:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try to keep it positive. 

I'm tryin', Ringo. I'm tryin' real hard to be the shepherd.

The path of the righteous man is beset on all sides by the inequities of the selfish and the tyranny of evil men. Blessed is he who, in the name of charity and good will, shepherds the weak through the valley of the darkness, for he is truly his brother's keeper and the finder of lost children. And I will strike down upon thee with great vengeance and furious anger those who attempt to poison and destroy My brothers. And you will know I am the Lord when I lay My vengeance upon you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 04:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elizabeth Warren for VP !!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 04:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More than you know fellow Redditor . . . more than you know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 04:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The boy and his mother had been at the park since Wednesday morning, Richardson said. Police found them Friday."

Clearly a tragic situation and outcome.

But ... HOW? ... Did she sleep at night, then go back to . . .

Just scary to even think about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 04:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it hard to believe that **racism** and **hate crimes** are not involved here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 04:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yah, like I'm supposed to believe that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 03:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you are cherry-picking

So posting current YTD and prior year (past 18 months) performance fits your definition of "cherry-picking"?

As an investor, I respectfully disagree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 00:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put your feet in ice water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 00:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [And then the modification mutates even more](http://i.kinja-img.com/gawker-media/image/upload/s--OWCDFhU7--/c_fit,fl_progressive,q_80,w_636/193gdsf054vkejpg.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 00:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  if you don't like it, resign

I vote for "go to jail" ^and ^^then ^^^quit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2 dead after man sets self on fire on Japan train </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is an **ASS-HAT!** . . . No wait, maybe that's his hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for putting this out there. Schwarzenegger is an ass. Very successful, but still an a-hole. 

Judge Lloyd Connelly called Schwarzenegger's decision to reduce Esteban Nunez's sentence from 16 years to seven years distasteful and "repugnant to the bulk of the citizenry of this state," but within his executive powers as governor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Ronco Pocket Fisherman](http://c426092.r92.cf2.rackcdn.com/prod_images/500/21967.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Big Boy Night Light](http://i.ebayimg.com/00/s/MTIwMFgxNjAw/z/m4oAAOSwc0FUqkh7/$_1.JPG) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to say it, but I have come to believe that Europe and the US are going to let Putin take significant amounts of territory from the Ukraine - permanently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Cell phone cone of silence](https://llwproductions.files.wordpress.com/2012/01/funny-photos-cell-phone-booth.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is such bullshit! Another blow to freedom.

Judge Michael Mosman of the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Court ruled late on Monday that the Second Circuit was wrong and that the program could resume.

"Second Circuit rulings are not binding on the F.I.S.C. and this court respectfully disagrees with that courts analysis, especially in view of the intervening enactment of the U.S.A. Freedom Act," he wrote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flying kites at the beach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sounds were accompanied by a shock wave that knocked people off their feet and broke windows hundreds of kilometres away. The majority of witnesses reported only the sounds and the tremors, and did not report seeing the explosion. The explosion registered at seismic stations across Eurasia. It is estimated that, in some places, the resulting shock wave was equivalent to an earthquake measuring 5.0 on the Richter scale. It also produced fluctuations in atmospheric pressure strong enough to be detected in Great Britain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> World Asteroid Day - - now that is tempting fate. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm stocking up on spare bicycle tire tubes immediately! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Investor-State Dispute Settlement, or ISDS is [*The Trans-Pacific Partnership clause everyone should oppose*](http://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/kill-the-dispute-settlement-language-in-the-trans-pacific-partnership/2015/02/25/ec7705a2-bd1e-11e4-b274-e5209a3bc9a9_story.html) (By Elizabeth Warren February 25)

ISDS would allow foreign companies to challenge U.S. laws  and potentially to pick up huge payouts from taxpayers  without ever stepping foot in a U.S. court. Heres how it would work. Imagine that the United States bans a toxic chemical that is often added to gasoline because of its health and environmental consequences. If a foreign company that makes the toxic chemical opposes the law, it would normally have to challenge it in a U.S. court. But with ISDS, the company could skip the U.S. courts and go before an international panel of arbitrators. If the company won, the ruling couldnt be challenged in U.S. courts, and the arbitration panel could require American taxpayers to cough up millions  and even billions  of dollars in damages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
