<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7036</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 04:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know! Check [this](http://www.wired.co.uk/news/archive/2015-02/26/spotify-axes-apps) article. Looks like the apps took away from actually listening and discovering music aside from a few key players. Musixmatch was so popular they just integrated it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 03:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soundrop has been removed from Spotify as have most 3rd party apps. We used to use Soundrop at work but have not been able to since they decided to do away with 3rd party apps. Will have to look into plug.dj! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 00:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea ive been using their activity feed for a while and it's great. I'm hoping they make this live. For example: a listen with button or something of the like. Then you really are listening along with friends or artists. Totally at their discretion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spotify and social streaming services should have a feature where you can sync with friends and listen to what they are listening to in real time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 23:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next level social-music listening experience. I would love to see this happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> how was your commute today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 21:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NO SPOILERS] If you have access to consume GoT season 5 on its originally syndicated network but have already watched the leak, please do watch when they premiere. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 13:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 13:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We give it all a power scrub after each brew.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 02:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 32 ounces of pure bottled peace of mind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nice (supply) rack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 01:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AMA Request] James Dyson, the guy who invented the Dyson Airblade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 16:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am blown away every time I dry my hands in a bathroom with a Dyson Air Blade. I want to know how you came up with this restroom marvel of the 21th century. Thank you! Here are my questions.

1. How did you come up with the idea for the Dyson Air-Blade?

2. Who did you tell first about the idea to affirm your desires for a superior hand dryer and how did they react to learning that you wanted to make something that blows air out instead of being sucked in?

3. Do you think your invention has revolutionized modern bathrooms across the globe and if so, how?

4. Have you ever left a restroom using your own invention saying to yourself "Wow! My hands are so dry and that was fucking fun" just like we all do when we use your product?

5. What is your favorite type of chicken wing sauce?

Public Contact Details

* [Dyson Twitter](https://twitter.com/dyson)
* [James Dyson Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/pages/Sir-James-Dyson/165983500126482)
* [Dyson Contact Us Page](http://www.dyson.com/contact.aspx)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 02:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice purchase! I have Caress of Steel and a signed copy of Grace Under Pressure. They are my favorite band! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 23:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [chair](http://i.imgur.com/s5xdy7o.jpg) is as deadly comfortable as a real Zebra-Leopard would be in real life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 19:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you kindly! Those have since been moved to the other side of my room and leaned between bookends neatly. Many of my new additions are from my dads college collection. 

The table is great, I love it. Got it on sale at home goods. Very sturdy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 18:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Turntable: Audio Technica LP 120
* Now playing: Rush - '2112' [1976] Held up by a drum stick I caught at a show, speaker wire, 2 wall studs and 2 screws
* Receiver: Technics SA 303 (1980)
* Headphones: Audio Technica ATH-M50 (comes with a quarter inch adapter for receivers etc)
* Not Pictured (Acoustic Research Large Bookend Speakers) 
* CD liner note notebooks given to me by an old boss of mine. Features Led Zeppelin, Rush, MMJ and others

For Under 500 USD you can get your music room similarly set up. It really is very solid IMO! If I had my way I would have gotten better speakers but as long as you have music and a comfy chair (my great grandfathers leopard colored-zebra patterned is what I use) you are golden! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My humble bang for your buck, townhouse set up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 18:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teleman -- Strange Combinations [Alternative/Art Rock] (2015) Great and simple song with creepy dolls used in the music video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 06:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> perhaps but I feel that some genres still command a core following; a certain type of 'stereotypical' listener. Or it might just mean that music is more accessible and due to this people are listening to all different genres rather because they are all so easy to find. The internet is a global musical-ecosystem where all of these genres are floating around and is easy to access by all types of people. In contrast before the internet, it was much harder to find different types of music outside of what your community's radios were playing. That was why your spectrum of choice was mostly influenced by the radio and perpetuated to the other people around them and down the line to kids etc etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 04:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love Streetlight Manifesto. Huge into jazz also. I work for a company who work with tons of metal artists and when I hear about all the subgenres I cant begin to wrap my head around it. Huge appreciation for the musicians but I just cant seem to get into the music. I do like Meshuggah though. I also love some Girls Day. (K-Pop) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 04:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Enya. In grade school I had [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LTrk4X9ACtw) on repeat. Prob gunna listen to all of her stuff again now. Thanks
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 04:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all of my friends had a Sublime phase. I never had one. Nothing against them. It just was never really introduced to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 04:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> speaking of which, [footage](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IJ7qgrOyKQ8) from the pit is amazing. I am a trumpet player so I eat this stuff up. This bass trombone at the end is dirtyyyy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 03:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in every sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 02:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who is into both hip hop and system of a down I see nothing wrong with this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 02:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sang along to wicked last week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
