<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject138</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why fresh water shortages will cause the next great global crisis - Across the globe, reports reveal huge areas in crisis today as reservoirs and aquifers dry up. More than a billion individuals  one in seven people on the planet  now lack access to safe drinking water. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 23:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The European Union needs its own army to face up to Russia and other threats as well as restore the bloc's foreign policy standing around the world, EU Commission President Jean-Claude Juncker told a German newspaper on Sunday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 23:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Secretary of State Colin Powell weighed in on Americas ongoing struggles with race on Sunday, saying he was not that surprised by reports of racism in local police departments and asking law enforcement officials to do more fight against prejudice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 22:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Officials with the Florida Department of Environmental Protection (DEP), the agency in charge of setting conservation policy and enforcing environmental laws in the state, issued directives in 2011 barring thousands of employees from using the phrases climate change and global warming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 22:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 22:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely, but My argument is to be careful who is adding the context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huckabee Asked To Provide Example Of Negative Impact Of Marriage Equality, Draws A Blank - But rather than providing any specific examples, Huckabee dodged the question and fell back on old rhetoric. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 23:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At the Iowa Agriculture Summit on Saturday, former Arkansas Gov. Mike Huckabee (R) said that the U.S. needs to secure its borders to prevent people from entering the country who do not have the right intentions and who may just be crossing the border to exploit the Americas free commodities. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 23:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU foreign ministers showed little appetite on Saturday for stepping up pressure on Russia over Ukraine, preferring to give a fragile ceasefire a chance before deciding whether to apply more sanctions or even to extend existing ones. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 23:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ferguson Mayor Rejects Department Of Justice Report, Says There's 'No Proof' City Has A Race Problem - What theyve shown is that it has happened. Now, how often has that happened? I dont know. Their assertion is it happens regularly. Based on what? Im not sure yet, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 23:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 50 Years After Selma, African Americans In Alabama Say: 'Hell No, We're Not Going Back' - Just last year, courts found evidence of intentional discrimination against minority voters in Evergreen, Alabama. There, black residents were intimidated, improperly purged from the voter rolls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 23:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Four advanced nuclear plants are under construction in the U.S., but with ongoing shutdowns, the fleetonce the largest in the worldnow seems doomed to fade away, done in by cheap natural gas and policies that favor renewable resources such as wind energy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 23:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On the same weekend as the nation marks the 50th anniversary of the Bloody Sunday protest in Selma that represented a major turning point in the civil rights movement, protests have erupted in Wisconsins capital after a cop shot and killed a 19-year-old black man. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 23:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 22:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that all sides should be taught with the caveat that it's true. Ideas like manifest destiny and of a religious nature have no place in American history, i.e. intelligent design.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A single photo that tells the powerful story of the 50th anniversary of Selma - "If someone told me 50 years ago I'd be back on this bridge introducing a black president of the United States, I'd have said you're crazy," Lewis said as he introduced Obama. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 22:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 02:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a good idea to compare atrocities between nations during WWII as a defense for not teaching about an event. Robert McNamara developed the plan for the fire-bombing of Dresden, and later admitted that if the US lost the war, he would've been indicted for war crimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Friday, the West Virginia legislature voted to override their governors recent veto of a 20-week abortion ban, ensuring that the restriction will become law. Cloaked in the language of fetal pain, this particular policy continues to gain momentum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 00:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Complex Societies Evolved without Belief in All-Powerful Deity - The most immediate way to do this is to align yourself with a supreme deity and then make lists of things people can and cannot do, and these become morals when applied to our social behaviour. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 00:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Vietnamese citizens and a Canadian have been charged with running a massive cyberfraud ring that stole 1 billion email addresses, then sent spam offering knockoff software products, the U.S. Department of Justice said on Friday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 23:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crime In North Dakotas Oil Boom Towns Is So Bad That The FBI Is Stepping In - There used to be a saying that 40 below keeps out the riff-raff, said Steve Kukowski, a sheriff in Ward County, North Dakota. Thats not true anymore. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 23:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The trial of a 16-year-old boy charged with insulting Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan has been delayed shortly after it began, following his lawyer's request for new judges. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 23:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ferguson, Missouri, has fired three city employees and is pursuing other reforms to reach a settlement with the U.S. Justice Department after a federal investigation accused the city of illegal practices targeting African-Americans, the mayor said on Friday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 23:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Central Intelligence Agency will make one of the biggest overhauls in its nearly 70-year history, aimed in part at sharpening its focus on cyber operations and incorporating digital innovations, CIA director John Brennan said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 23:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attorney General Eric Holder declined to answer questions Friday about a possible corruption indictment against Sen. Bob Menendez, despite reports that he recently authorized federal prosecutors to file charges against the New Jersey Democrat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 22:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obamas Police Reforms - What is not discussed in the report is dialing back in any meaningful way the war on drugs, police militarization or the widespread use of broken windows policing that has led to the unnecessary criminalization of millions of mostly black and brown people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 22:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Inc (AAPL.O), the largest U.S. company by market value, will join the Dow Jones industrial average .DJI, replacing AT T Inc (T.N), in a change that reflects the dominant position of the iPhone maker in the U.S. economy and society. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 22:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 02:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good answers...as a society, the US public has placed barriers between itself and the dead. This wasn't always the case. If you currently live in an old house that has a parlor and dining room, the parlor was originally intended as the viewing room for the family of the deceased. More importantly, children were often tasked with the task of euthanizing a family animal. A good example of this is found in the book and film *Old Yeller*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red States Will Suffer - If funding Homeland Security is a problem for this Congress, why would one expect it to agree on a new health care regime? The complexity of such an endeavor alone would make final passage an unlikely event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 00:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Thursday, a trio of female senators announced the introduction of an ambitious piece of pro-choice legislation to safeguard access to womens health services as some members of Congress attempt to turn back the clock. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 00:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The NRAs New Low - But as far as I can tell, this is the first time that the NRA has taken a personal swipe at Giffords, mocking her reform efforts by directly invoking the shooting that nearly killed her. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 23:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big business rallied behind the gay marriage cause on Thursday as the U.S. Supreme Court scheduled oral arguments for April 28 on the contentious social issue that promises to yield one of the justices' most important rulings of 2015. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 23:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a literal application of the sharia law of an eye for an eye, an Iranian man convicted of blinding another man in an acid attack has been blinded in one eye, marking the first time Iran has carried out such a punishment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 23:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lockheed Martin's laser can stop a truck from over a mile away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 01:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9 Egregious Examples Of Racism In Ferguson Uncovered By The Department Of Justice - After telling the officer, you dont have a reason to lock me up, he claims the officer responded: N*****, I can find something to lock you up on. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 01:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three children shot in Houston: These werent accidents - Theyre the completely predictable consequences of criminally negligent behavior on the part of these kids parents and guardians, and they should be treated as such. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 01:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From eastern flank, Iran-backed force advances on Tikrit - It is also the clearest example of how Tehran, rather than Washington, is now playing a more important role on the battlefield in a war that sees both Iran and the United States supporting the same side against a common foe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 01:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even if Hillary Rodham Clinton's use of a private email server to conduct official business as secretary of state was not illegal, it violated Obama administration guidance and undermined his pledge of historic transparency. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 01:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Four patients at Cedars-Sinai Medical Center in Los Angeles were infected with a drug-resistant "superbug" bacteria during endoscopic procedures that may have exposed 64 others since last August, the hospital said on Wednesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 01:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Ferguson Report - "partly as a consequence of city and FPD priorities, many officers appear to see some residents, especially those who live in Ferguson's predominately African-American neighborhoods, less as constituents to be protected than as potential offenders and sources of revenue," </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 00:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Court justices split along ideological lines Wednesday in questioning during the latest legal battle over the Affordable Care Act, making the outcome difficult to predict. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 00:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tuesdays speech by Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu to a joint session of Congress seemed to have zero impact on the ongoing negotiations surrounding Irans nuclear program and may have even undermined the leaders efforts to scuttle a diplomatic solution to the crisis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 00:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why People "Fly from Facts" - But we find that people sometimes go one step further and, as in the opening example, they reframe an issue in untestable ways. This makes potential important facts and science ultimately irrelevant to the issue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 23:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A lower jaw bone and five teeth discovered on a hillside in Ethiopia are the oldest remains ever found that belong to the genus Homo, the lineage that ultimately led to modern humans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 23:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Hillary Clinton e-mail story just keeps getting worse for her - That level of sophistication speaks to the fact that this was not thrown together at the last minute; instead it was a planned maneuver to give the Clintons more control over their electronic correspondence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 23:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the first time in three decades, unemployment fell in every state and the District of Columbia last year. The last time that happened, in 1984, Apple was unveiling the original Macintosh. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 23:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 23:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> welcome  
  
But it's also correct that a WC in Europe is a toilet, or water closet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Senate failed on Wednesday to override President Barack Obama's veto of legislation approving the Keystone XL oil pipeline, leaving the controversial project to await an administration decision on whether to permit or deny it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 23:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 01:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 01:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Achy Breaky Heart - Billy Ray Cyrus. It's also the reason for M. Cyrus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 01:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubling up makes it twice as nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu slammed the emerging nuclear deal between the United States, Iran, and the major world powers during a drama-filled address to a joint session of Congress on Tuesday morning, but failed to offer any alternatives </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 00:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The House passed a bill Tuesday afternoon to fund the Department of Homeland Security for the rest of the fiscal year, sending it to President Obama for his expected signature. The measure will not target Obama's executive actions on immigration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 23:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Russian lawyer for Edward Snowden said on Tuesday the fugitive former U.S. spy agency contractor who leaked details of the government's mass surveillance programs was working with American and German lawyers to return home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 23:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. retailer Target Corp on Tuesday said it planned to cut several thousand jobs, mainly from headquarters locations, as part of a restructuring that will cut $2 billion in costs over two years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 23:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Gross Hypocrisy of Benjamin Netanyahu - Last Friday, campaigning in Israel, Netanyahu said he was coming here to lobby the only body that may prevent the Iran deal. The gist of both statements is obvious: Netanyahu doesnt like Obamas policy, so hes trying to use Congress to block it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 23:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu did President Obama an enormous favor Tuesday. Given the opportunity, on perhaps the worlds biggest political stage, to articulate the best possible case against the nuclear deal currently being negotiated with Iran, Netanyahu came up empty. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 23:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker (R) wants to end funding to a university renewable energy program that works to find ways to convert wood chips and grasses grown in Wisconsin into sources of energy. Walker is proposing to cut $8.1 million over two years from the Great Lakes Bioenergy Research Center </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 00:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate Change Hastened Syria's Civil War - A new study published today in Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences says drought in Syria, exacerbated to record levels by global warming, pushed social unrest in that nation across a line into an open uprising in 2011. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 00:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In response to growing tensions in Los Angeles over the police killing of a homeless man on Sunday, the president of the local officers labor union urged the public to reserve their judgment until an investigation was complete. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 00:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Palestinians plan to lodge their first complaint against Israel for alleged war crimes at the International Criminal Court on April 1, according to a senior official. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 00:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warren Buffett Says Elizabeth Warren Is Too Angry And Violent With Rich People - I think that she would do better if she was less angry and demonized less, he responded. I believe in hate the sin, love the sinner, and I also believe in praising by name and criticizing by category. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 00:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Barack Obama on Monday said he thinks there is no "plausible legal basis" for the U.S. Supreme Court to strike down a key plank of Obamacare, defending his administration's lack of a contingency plan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 23:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu warned the United States on Monday that the nuclear deal it is negotiating with Iran could threaten Israel's survival and insisted he had a "moral obligation" to speak up about deep differences with President Barack Obama on the issue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 23:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News has admitted, in answer to questions from the Washington Post, that host Bill OReilly did not witness any bombings in Northern Ireland or murders in El Salvador. The network said he saw only photographs of such atrocities. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 23:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A federal judge on Monday ruled Nebraska's ban on gay marriage unconstitutional in a decision that could allow same-sex couples to marry in the state within a week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 23:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Portrait artist says he painted Lewinsky reference in Bill Clintons official painting - Shanks said painting Clinton was his hardest assignment because he is probably the most famous liar of all time. So he added the nod to the Lewinsky scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 23:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Engelhardt, The Ten Commandments for a Better American World - And in the constant panic over our safety in situations where very little danger actually exists, our own barbarity, seen as a series of defensive acts to ensure our security, disappears in a sea of alarm. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 01:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Given a multiverse, does astrology work somewhere? - Is there a universe, for example, where astrology and homeopathy work? Or where murdering people gets you a divine pat on the head and a long-term ticket to paradise? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 01:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker says he opposes comprehensive immigration reform. He didnt always. - Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker on Sunday staked out a hard-line stance against a path to citizenship for undocumented immigrants, saying "flat out" that he has shifted on the issue since 2013, when he supported it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 01:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Abd-Rabbu Mansour Hadi accused his predecessor on Sunday of conspiring with Iran to scuttle a 2011 deal backed by Gulf states to transfer power to him in cooperation with the Shi'ite Muslim Houthi group. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 01:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On the first weekend after the legalization of marijuana in the nations capital, a sell-out crowd gathered in a hotel ballroom with the same basic mission: Learn how to capitalize on the economic opportunity thats headed for D.C., the so-called Green Rush. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 00:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How hunting with wolves helped humans outsmart the Neanderthals - The answer, she argues, was the creation of the human-wolf alliance. Previously they separately hunted the same creatures, with mixed results. Once they joined forces, they dominated the food chain in prehistoric Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 00:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We now know that the way we talk about race has no scientific validity. There is no genetic basis that corresponds with any particular group of people, no essentialist DNA for black people or white people or anyone. This is not a hippy ideal, its a fact. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 00:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State released 19 Assyrian Christian captives in Syria on Sunday after processing them through a sharia court, a monitoring group which tracks the conflict said. More than 200 Assyrians remain in Islamic State hands, said the British-based Syrian Observatory for Human Rights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 00:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> oris Nemtsov: tens of thousands march in memory of murdered politician - However, investigators appear to have ruled out the theory that he was killed for his opposition views. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 00:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamist militant Mohammed Emwazi, identified as 'Jihadi John', was a member of a network in contact with one of the men convicted of trying to bomb the British capital's underground railway in 2005, according to the government. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 23:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 02:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a no-brainer - it's [Michael Faraday](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Michael_Faraday), the inventor of the motor and the first person to understand that magnetic fields could be used as a power source. Everything in our modern world falls apart without Faraday's achievements, and he believed them so important that he refused to patent the processes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The identity of an Australian man killed in a motorcycle smash in Thailand has been confirmed by his colleagues as bitcoin entrepreneur Adam Tepper. Tepper, CEO of digital currency business Independent Reserve, died on Thursday, his colleague Adrian Przelozny said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 00:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Most Anti-Women Assertions At This Year's Conservative Political Gathering - I kinda have Fox X-ray vision, and I can see that some of you women, you dont even know it yet, but youre pregnant. Its not your fault. Its not his fault. The comment drew little laughter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 00:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mohammed Emwazi, the Islamic State extremist known as Jihadi John, was able to flee Britain and the scrutiny of the security services, despite being a member of a terror cell that was known to have links to the failed 21/7 attacks on London in 2005, the Observer can reveal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 00:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senator Rand Paul won a straw poll of conservative activists on Saturday, giving his potential bid for the Republican presidential nomination in 2016 a boost, and Wisconsin Governor Scott Walker came in second in a surprising show of strength. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 00:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police in the north German city of Bremen warned on Saturday of a heightened danger from Islamist militants and said they had increased their presence in the city center and stepped up protection of the Jewish community. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 00:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For six years, President Barack Obama and Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu have been on a collision course over how to halt Iran's nuclear ambitions, a high-stakes endeavor both men see as a centerpiece of their legacies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 23:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buffett: don't expect another 50 years of outperformance at Berkshire - Within 10 to 20 years, Buffett said, Berkshire's girth could require whoever then runs the Omaha, Nebraska-based company to consider steps he has resisted, such as paying dividends or conducting "massive" share repurchases. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 23:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Science standards that treat climate change as fact are no longer banned in Wyoming, now that a bill reversing the states ban has been passed by the House and Senate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 00:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-Israeli spy chief slams Netanyahu on Iran handling - Ahead of Netanyahu's contentious speech to US Congress, Meir Dagan said in comments published on Friday, that "the person who has caused the greatest strategic damage to Israel on the Iranian issue is the prime minister". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 00:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Officials in several Republican states that balked at participating in President Obamas health-care initiative are now revisiting the issue, amid mounting panic over a possible Supreme Court decision that would revoke federal insurance subsidies for millions of Americans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 00:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Authorities were expected to formally announce the arrest of Knights Templar leader Servando Gomez Martinez, also known as "La Tuta," later today in Mexico City. Reports citing official sources said Gomez was apprehended in the Michoacan capital city of Morelia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 23:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. House of Representatives voted to reject a stop-gap measure to renew Department of Homeland Security funding for three weeks, leaving no clear path for the agency to avoid a partial shutdown after a midnight deadline. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 23:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian opposition leader Nemtsov shot dead in Moscow - Boris Nemtsov, a Russian opposition politician and former deputy prime minister, has been shot dead in central Moscow, the Interior Ministry said early on Saturday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 23:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alien Life Prefers Circles - Because planets on circular orbits do not move toward or away from their star, their climates may be stable enough to foster advanced life. Our own solar system fits that pattern. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 23:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Big Brain" Gene Allowed for Evolutionary Expansion of Our Neocortex - This gene seems to be uniquely human: It is found in modern-day humans, Neanderthals and another branch of extinct humans called Denisovans, but not in chimpanzees. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 23:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A stand-alone U.S. Senate bill to block spending on President Barack Obama's November 2014 immigration order failed to clear a procedural vote on Friday after the provisions were stripped from a Department of Homeland Security funding bill. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 23:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Human Costs Of Chris Christies Attack On Planned Parenthood - The state legislature has repeatedly attempted to restore the funding cuts, but Christie has resisted every year. Senate Majority Leader Loretta Weinberg (D) has accused the governor of trying to drag New Jersey back to the 1950s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 01:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jim Inhofes snowball has disproven climate change once and for all - He referred back to the time that his kids made an igloo -- and then dropped his bombshell: "It's very, very cold out. Very unseasonable." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 00:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Big Picture: Buzz Aldrin's vintage selfie from space - Back in November 1966, Buzz Aldrin took a self-picture that will blow all Caribbean vacation selfies out of the water. Aside from the fact that it doesn't have a duckface in it, the photo was taken in space during the Gemini 12 mission. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 00:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pause in Global Warming Is Finally Explained - The oscillations have slowed the warming due to human activities for a while, but when that effect inevitably ends the oscillations will instead add to human warming, raising the rate of increase. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 00:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mossad's 'moderate Muslim' scorecard - The report describes Arab governments relying on what for all practical purposes are rental clerics, whose Friday sermons become paid mechanisms of political control rather than explorations of religious scholarship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 00:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. House of Representatives Speaker John Boehner on Thursday challenged an assertion by the Obama administration that Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu's upcoming speech to Congress about Iran's nuclear program would be destructive to U.S.-Israeli relations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 00:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas officials warn of immigrants with terrorist ties crossing southern border - In a report to Texas elected officials, the state Department of Public Safety says border security agencies have arrested several Somali immigrants crossing the southern border who are known members of al-Shabab </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 00:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A top Texas law enforcement agency says border security organizations have apprehended several members of known Islamist terrorist organizations crossing the southern border in recent years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 00:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Young Black Hole Had Monstrous Growth Spurt - Light from the black hole took 12.9 billion years to reach Earth, so astronomers see the object as it was 900 million years after the Big Bang. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 23:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can Eric Holder change the federal drug classification of marijuana? - This is what advocates believe is the catch-22: As long as marijuana is a Schedule I drug, there are limitations to conducting the extensive clinical trials required to take it out of Schedule I. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 23:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pediatricians Fight Back Against Anti-Vaxxers, Ban Their Kids - According to a national analysis conducted by an employee at the Vermont-based Physicians Computer Company (PCC), the majority of U.S. pediatricians will turn away patients who refuse to vaccinate their children. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 01:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shelter dogs are helping scientists sniff out worlds rarest gorillas - Theyre especially great at having jobs, and increasingly, researchers are realising their potential as wildlife scouts to help them track down the struggling species that (understandably) are doing their best to stay hidden. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 01:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Latest Selfie from NASA Mars Rover Shows Wide Context - The selfie scene is assembled from dozens of images taken by the Mars Hand Lens Imager (MAHLI) camera on the rover's robotic arm. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 00:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three men were charged on Wednesday with conspiring to support Islamic State, including two who planned to travel to Syria to fight on behalf of the radical group, U.S. authorities said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 00:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. officials on Wednesday questioned Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu's judgment and said his outspoken condemnation of efforts to secure an Iranian nuclear deal had injected destructive partisanship into U.S.-Israeli relations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 00:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This time, Donald J. Trump says, he really means it. The billionaire real-estate mogul  long amounting to a one-man circus sideshow in GOP presidential politics  said in an interview Wednesday that he is more serious than ever about pursuing a run for the White House in 2016. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 00:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austria's parliament has passed a bill amending historical laws on Muslim organisations which will ban foreign sources of financing and require imams to be able to speak German. The text aims to promote what conservative Integration Minister Sebastian Kurz called an "Islam of European character" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 00:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mitch McConnells real goal: The Senate majority leader isnt seeking to solve the crisis as much as win the next election - Seven weeks after pledging to make Republicans in Congress look less scary, Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell is just making them look rudderless. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 01:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Pro Life' GOPer Says It's Fine For Kids to Die in the Name of God - In a deeply religious section of Idaho, a Republican state representative says that the state has no right to protect children from their parents who refuse them needed medical treatment in favor of faith healing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 01:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rajendra Pachauri, chairman of the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC), resigned today following accusations of sexual harassment by a former employee at the energy think tank he heads in New Delhi. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 01:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nevada Lawmaker Says Cancer Is A Fungus, Recommends Simply Washing It Out - Nevada Assemblywoman Michele Fiore (R) wants to reform the rules of end-of-life medical care so that more cancer patients can simply flush out their disease using baking soda. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 01:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unusual Bacteria Discovered in Deepest Ocean Trench - Researchers from Japan discovered microscopic bacteria thrive in the canyon called Challenger Deep, which is the lowest point on Earth's surface and the deepest part of the Mariana Trench </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 01:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The gruesome waves of bubonic plague that began with the Black Death in medieval Europe and ended with the Great Plague of London may have been driven more by great gerbils than black rats, researchers claim. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 00:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Zimmerman, the former neighborhood watch volunteer who fatally shot Trayvon Martin in a 2012 confrontation with the teenager, will not face federal charges, the Justice Department said Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 00:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After West Virginia Explosion, Oil Trains Quietly Rerouted Through Virginia Towns - This is an issue thats been largely overlooked in the debate about the safety of oil trains: secrecy. Many people who live near railroad lines across the country want to know what trains are carrying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 01:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breastfeeding May Protect Babies from Arsenic Exposure - The powder and water used to make the baby formula may be sources of arsenic, which occurs naturally in the environment and in large doses is linked to serious health problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 01:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HSBC Holdings Plc has set aside $550 million more to cover potential fines for alleged manipulation of foreign exchange markets and warned it could face a $500 million bill to compensate U.S. customers sold debt protection products. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 01:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A US jury has found the Palestinian Authority (PA) and the Palestine Liberation Organisation (PLO) liable for supporting attacks in Israel more than a decade ago that killed American citizens. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 01:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Idaho Lawmaker Wonders If Women Could Have A Gyno Exam By Swallowing A Tiny Camera - Dr. Julie Madsen told him no, thats not possible, because items that are swallowed do not end up in the vagina. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 01:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker has always played to his political base: The Wisconsin governors current troubles were entirely predictable - In Walkers world, it matters more not to be seen as squishy than to worry about saying something that could ruffle liberal feathers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 01:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Harvard-Smithsonian Center for Astrophysics (CfA) has launched an inquiry into one of its researchers, solar physicist and global warming sceptic Willie Soon, following the release of documents that detail research funds he and the institution received from the energy industry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 01:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ecstasy Precursor Shows How to Reduce Alcohol Cancer RiskAnd Curb Drunkenness - This is the first time a problem caused by one broken enzyme has been solved by a molecule working on a different one, notes Thomas Hurley, a biochemist at Indiana University School of Medicine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 01:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In what world is naming a lipgloss Underage a good idea? - I surely speak for us all when I say I am eagerly looking forward to their Statutory Rape collection. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 00:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Illinois Rep. Aaron Schock, a rising Republican star already facing an ethics inquiry, has spent taxpayer and campaign funds on flights aboard private planes owned by some of his key donors, The Associated Press has found. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 00:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senator Lisa Murkowski (R-AK) threatened to cut thousands of park ranger and natural resource management jobs across the country  including in her home state of Alaska  escalating an ongoing fight with the Obama Administration over its plans to protect the Arctic National Wildlife Refuge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 23:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Can Peanut Allergies Be Prevented? - At age five all the children were given peanuts to test their reactions. The scientists concluded that early, regular introduction of peanut snacks can decrease the risk of developing peanut allergy by as much as 86 percent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 23:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Health Concerns Mount After Refinery Explosion Coats California City With White Ash - Spent catalyst is a substance that is powdery, and it has in it toxic things like vanadium, arsenic, heavy metals that are carcinogens, he said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 02:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What The Atlantic Left Out About ISIS - Ultimately, Haykel appeared to argue that effectively combating ISIS will require more than discerning what ISIS wants, theologically speaking. Instead, it also requires a deep, abiding dedication to providing what most Muslims in the region want </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 01:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Obama administration has proposed the first-ever safety regulations for drilling in the U.S. portion of the Arctic Ocean, where big oil companies have long been hoping to lay their claim. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 01:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Militants claiming loyalty to Islamic State said they were behind Sunday's twin bomb attacks on the residence of the Iranian ambassador in the Libyan capital and a rocket strike on the eastern Labraq airport. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 23:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. homeland security chief said on Sunday he takes seriously an apparent threat by Somali-based Islamist militants against prominent shopping sites in the West including the Mall of America in Minnesota and urged people there to be careful. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 23:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine said on Sunday it feared unrest could spread beyond territory held by pro-Russian separatists, after an explosion killed two people at a memorial rally in an eastern city far from the front line. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 23:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 23:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A reminder: the US supreme court ruled that black americans weren't really people but an inferior race that needed a paternal hand. The supreme court isn't "supreme" because it's not interested in the people's rights but that of corporate america. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congressman Defends Outrageous Giuliani Remarks: Obama Views America Differently - His evidence, Issa explained, was that Obama denounced the U.S. Supreme Court in the halls of Congress during the State of the Union for their decision in the Citizens United case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 23:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missouri Lawmakers Propose Banning Public From Viewing Footage From Police Body Cams - The bill, introduced by Sen. Doug Libla (R), would make all footage recorded by police officers, including dashboard and body cameras, exempt from the states open records law. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 23:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the worlds most prominent climate researchers publishing scientific papers that doubt humanitys role in climate change has received at least $1.2 million from the fossil fuel industry to fund his research and salary, according to documents revealed this weekend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 22:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The family of the codebreaker Alan Turing will visit Downing Street on Monday to demand the government pardons 49,000 other men persecuted like him for their homosexuality. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 22:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stuart Gulliver, the HSBC chief executive who has vowed to reform the crisis-hit bank, sheltered millions of pounds in a Swiss account through a Panamanian company and remains tax domiciled in Hong Kong. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 22:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 03:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Florida - come for the weather, stay for the crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 03:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because I gave you the context for my trashiness; I'm just saying I give people some slack because I've been there before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 03:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robert A. Heinlein short story that I never thought would get made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 02:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to enjoy the movie even more, Brian Greene does this wonderful series called [Beyond the Cosmos](http://www.primewire.ag/watch-2733300-Beyond-the-Cosmos-online-free) that explains in simple terms the relationship between time, gravity, and space. It blows my mind that the farther away from Earth that a person travels in space, time runs slower for them. The arrow of time runs in only one direction for humans, however, in physics and quantum mechanics the arrow of time is malleable and can move in both directions. It almost appears as if the writers of *Interstellar* wrote the movie after watching Greene's series. If you watch his series, Interstellar takes on a whole different level of pleasure and awe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nasa astronauts begin spacewalk to prepare docking port for shuttles - The work will prepare docking ports for upcoming flights by Boeing and privately owned Space Exploration Technologies, or SpaceX, which are developing capsules to ferry crew to and from the station </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 00:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Signaling little interest in entering the 2016 presidential race, Indiana Gov. Mike Pence said he is focused entirely on home state affairs, but the Republican refused to shut the door entirely on a White House bid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 00:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker's Latest Anti-Union Plan Is 'Cowardly,' Says Former Republican Leader - Wisconsin Republicans are forging ahead at breakneck speed with a bill meant to cripple the states unions. Gov. Scott Walker (R-WI) said Friday he would sign the right-to-work bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 00:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our Galaxy May Be Littered With Dying Earths - We all have our favorite doomsday scenario, but theres one apocalypse science tells us we cant avoid: The slow extinction of life on Earth as our sun grows hot and then flickers out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 23:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A prominent academic and climate change deniers work was funded almost entirely by the energy industry, receiving more than $1.2m from companies, lobby groups and oil billionaires over more than a decade, newly released documents show. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 23:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bloodied but unbeaten, the tobacco companies have plunged into another courtroom battle in an effort to stave off the humiliation of having to underwrite an ad campaign in which they brand themselves as liars. Oral arguments are scheduled for Monday before the U.S. Court of Appeals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 23:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nigerian forces backed by air strikes seized the northeastern border town of Baga from Islamist group Boko Haram on Saturday, the military said, a significant victory in an offensive against an insurgency affecting four African states. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 23:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 23:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not being trashy, that's being naive.  
  
For example, I grew up extremely poor and joined the military right out of high school. Because my family was so poor, I'd never eaten in a restaurant until a very pretty girl asked me to dinner at *Ye Olde Oyster House* in Boston. I was stationed with the 10th special forces group at Ft. Devens, Mass. and I was excited about my restaurant visit. She ordered a drink and I ordered an ice tea; when tea is served in the south it usually came pre-sweetened, but this Boston so it was without sugar. I promptly used every cane sugar packet on the table to make the tea sweet enough. The waitress brought cornbread to the table as a snack while we looked the menu over. The cornbread I'd grown up with was thin, bitter, and a type of hard tack, but the waitress had brought what appeared to me to be cake. Without saying anything to my date, I flagged down the waitress and told her she'd brought us desert before the meal and that we'd not ordered any cake. Both the waitress and my date assured me it was cornbread. As we ordered, I didn't recognize anything on the menu when I spotted a dish made with eggs that looked edible. So I ordered the quickee, which made the waitress giggle and my date blush. It was actually quiche, and I didn't eat much of it. After this affair I never heard from or saw my date again. While this may have appeared trashy to anyone watching, it was simple naivete.  
  
When I see poor people acting inappropriately, I understand the reasons behind their action.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iranian President Hassan Rouhani has dispatched his brother and atomic chief to Geneva to try to overcome hurdles in high-profile nuclear talks with the United States and five other major powers, official Iranian media reported on Saturday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 23:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 02:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the replies sound like things poor people do or wear, so I guess all poor people are trashy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Justice Department will seek an emergency stay to block a decision by a federal judge and allow eligible immigrants to apply for benefits granted under President Barack Obama's recent executive actions, the White House said on Friday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 00:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A senior Republican lawmaker has told President Barack Obama she was prepared to block foreign aid money if the administration did not provide fighter jets and tanks to Egypt and arms to other regional allies fighting Islamic State militants. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 00:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scattered across the ocean floor in the cold waters of the Arctic are nuclear submarines and reactors dumped by the Soviets up until the early 1990s. Now, as energy companies are seeking to drill in those same waters, the Russian government has shown an interest in cleaning up its nuclear waste. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 00:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 02:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The OK gop's stance on history is an attempt to revision the nation's past. It expected parents to agree with such a patriotic version of history, but miscalculated. Now its trying to walk-back comments made by a member by claiming the legislation was poorly worded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 01:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you believe in god? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It Was Perfectly Legal For This Doctor To Refuse To Treat A Same-Sex Couple's Newborn - Krista and Jami are not suing Roi, but mostly because they are doubtful they would have a legal case. Michigan has no law that explicitly protects LGBT people from discrimination </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 00:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attorneys for the accused Boston Marathon bomber on Thursday asked a U.S. appellate panel to override a federal judge and order his trial moved out of the city, saying an impartial jury could not be seated so close to the site of the 2013 attack. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 00:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doctor Refuses to Treat Same-Sex Couple's 6-Day-Old Baby - When they arrived at the medical facility, they were told that the doctor they had planned to see didn't even come to the office that day  she had prayed on it, and she won't be able to care for their baby. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 23:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ISIS isnt medieval: Its revisionist history only claims to be rooted in early Arab conquests - In this case, ISIS draws its ideological strength from an acute sense of what an invented past can accomplish for the present and how nostalgia can motivate immediate, violent action. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 23:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weird Winter Weather Plot Thickens as Arctic Swiftly Warms - This is where climate change comes in: the Arctic is warming much faster than elsewhere. That Arctic/mid-latitude temperature difference, consequently, is getting smaller. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 23:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recommendations Thursday from a government advisory committee call for an environmentally friendly diet lower in red and processed meats. But the panel would reverse previous guidance on limiting dietary cholesterol. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 23:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bush's Attack On Obama Over Iran Goes Horribly Wrong - Former Florida Gov. Jeb Bush (R) called on Congress to pass legislation that would trigger sanctions against Iran just as the United States and its European partners are consumed in negotiations over the countrys nuclear program. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 01:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here is the problem: election officials themselves also appear to be biased against minority voters, and Latinos in particular. For example, poll workers are more likely to ask minority voters to show identification, including in states without voter identification laws. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 01:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pig Poop Fouls North Carolina Streams - The farms generate so much waste that it would be too expensive to transport via pipeline or a truck, Wing said. So manure is dispersed via big pumps and sprayers that act like a lawn sprinkler," Wing said, and spread the slurry across fields. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 00:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An explosion and fire ripped through a gasoline processing unit at an Exxon Mobil refinery in Torrance, California, near Los Angeles on Wednesday, slightly injuring four workers and shattering windows of surrounding buildings, authorities said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 00:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Libya and Egypt asked the United Nations Security Council on Wednesday to lift an arms embargo on Libya, impose a naval blockade on areas not under government control and help build the country's army to tackle Islamic State and other militants. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 00:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Attorney General Eric Holder said on Tuesday he has given federal prosecutors a 90-day deadline to decide whether they can bring cases against individuals for their roles in the 2008 financial crisis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 01:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chelsea fans prevent black man boarding Paris metro train - (video) The unidentified passenger attempts to squeeze on to the train, only to be pushed forcefully back on to the platform at the Richelieu-Drouot station. The fans then chant: 'We're racist, we're racist and that's the way we like it' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 01:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge Illegally Fired Whistleblower Who Called Him Out For Preaching Religion From The Bench - As the appeals court explained, Pucci had a strong interestas a citizenin alerting the [state agency] to Somerss conduct on the bench </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 01:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After years of silence, Turkeys women are going into battle against oppression - In the past 10 years the number of gender-related homicides has tripled in Turkey. Between 2003 and 2013 domestic violence has increased more than 1,400%. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 01:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Egypt's public prosecutor has referred former President Mohamed Morsi and several officials of the banned Muslim Brotherhood to a military court, on charges of committing violence, state media has said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 00:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Barack Obama said on Tuesday he disagreed with a Texas judge's ruling to block executive actions that shield millions of illegal immigrants from deportation and said he believed the issue would be resolved in the White House's favor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 00:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chesapeake Energy Corp filed suit Tuesday alleging its founder and former chief executive, Aubrey K. McClendon, stole confidential company data during his last months on the job in order to launch his new oil and gas empire. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 00:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attorney General Eric Holder says he expects the Justice Department to announce before he leaves office the result of separate federal investigations into the Ferguson, Missouri shooting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 00:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 02:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew it wouldn't take long before the comparisons about safety between pipelines and railroads. This accident will be used by the republicans as an excuse to push the Keystone line for the Koch brothers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 02:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The early 20th century was a dark time in addressing mental health issues, with chemical and physical castration a common practice in its institutions. They believed the practice would keep homosexuality from spreading.  
  
edit: I'm arguing that US christians have already implemented a version of sharia law in this nation and it needs to stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 00:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not murder, but there was chemical and physical castration, imprisonment, and placement in mental institutions, all sanctioned by the government and the supreme court. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ben Carson, who is considering mounting a campaign for the 2016 GOP presidential nomination, said Monday that the United States should not hesitate to put boots on the ground to defeat the Islamic State  and that they should be free to fight them without any fear of prosecution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 00:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The head of Israel's election commission acted on Monday to limit any pre-election boost Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu may get from a March 3 speech to the U.S. Congress, in which he will warn of the threat from Iran's nuclear programme. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 00:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The head of Israel's election commission acted on Monday to limit any pre-election boost Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu may get from a March 3 speech to the U.S. Congress, in which he will warn of the threat from Iran's nuclear programme. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 00:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New ranking of U.S. presidents puts Lincoln at No. 1, Obama at 18; Kennedy judged most overrated - We also asked respondents which president should be added to Mount Rushmore, and Franklin Roosevelt was the overwhelming favorite. Almost two-thirds of respondents chose him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 00:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. National Security Agency has figured out how to hide spying software deep within hard drives made by Western Digital, Seagate, Toshiba and other top manufacturers, giving the agency the means to eavesdrop on the majority of the world's computers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 00:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 00:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't restricting access to rights shared by all Americans a form of punishment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 00:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You and me both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frances interior minister said several hundreds of tombs had been defaced at a Jewish cemetery in the east of the country, in what he called a despicable act. The country will not tolerate this new injury which goes against the values that all French people share, said Bernard Cazeneuve </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 00:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MI5 is facing allegations it was complicit in the sexual abuse of children, the high court in Northern Ireland will hear on Tuesday. Victims of the abuse are taking legal action to force a full independent inquiry with the power to compel witnesses to testify </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 00:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United Nations Security Council on Sunday demanded Iranian-backed Houthi militia in Yemen withdraw from government institutions, called for an end to foreign interference and threatened "further steps" if the violence does not stop. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 00:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Wisconsin Governor Scott Walker, a potential Republican presidential candidate, traveled on a trade mission to Britain last week, he brought along top officials from his economic development agency to help drum up jobs. It's a task they have struggled to accomplish at home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 23:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oil and gas companies wont have to pay for decades of damage to Louisianas coast, after a lawsuit filed against the companies in 2013 was thrown out on Friday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 23:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. aviation regulator proposed rules on Sunday for commercial drone flights that would lift some restrictions but would still bar activities such as the delivery of packages and inspection of pipelines that have been eyed by companies as a potentially breakthrough use of the technology. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 23:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The number of imperiled wolves found only in the American Southwest climbed to 109 in 2014, marking the fourth consecutive year that the population of Mexican gray wolves has risen by at least 10 percent, federal wildlife managers said Friday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 23:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Mississippi state lawmaker said he opposed putting more money into elementary schools because he came from a town where all the blacks are getting food stamps and what I call welfare crazy checks. They dont work. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 23:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Wednesday, a panel of the United States Court of Appeals for the Third Circuit upheld federal rules intended to ensure access to birth control, over a claim that employers who object to following those rules on religious groups should be exempt from them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 23:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biting cold and driving snow kept the U.S. Northeast in the grip of another major winter storm on Sunday that made February the snowiest month in Boston's history. Blizzards forced the cancellation of more than 1,750 U.S. passenger flights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 23:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Boehner, the Republican House of Representatives speaker, said he is willing to let funding for the Department of Homeland Security lapse as part of a Republican push to roll back President Barack Obama's executive actions on immigration. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 23:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
