<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6188</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slovenian retro-avantgarde rock group Laibach has announced it will become the first foreign rock outfit to perform in North Korea this August as part of their Liberation Day Tour. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slovenian retro-avantgarde rock group Laibach has announced it will become the first foreign rock outfit to perform in North Korea this August as part of their Liberation Day Tour. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's raining spiders! Weirdest effects of California drought. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Ottawa police tactical officer pleaded guilty to using his cellphone and email to store 63 sexual images after a Special Investigations Unit probe ordered that all tactical officers records be combed through by Ottawa police internal investigators. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Ottawa police tactical officer pleaded guilty to using his cellphone and email to store 63 sexual images after a Special Investigations Unit probe ordered that all tactical officers records be combed through by Ottawa police internal investigators. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australia's cattle industry has taken a sudden hit after Indonesia slashed its live cattle imports from Australia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australia's cattle industry has taken a sudden hit after Indonesia slashed its live cattle imports from Australia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Locals criticize commercial camping business in Waimanalo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea said President Barack Obama should dispatch all 535 U.S. senators and representatives to verify whether a pesticide research facility is being used to produce anthrax. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea said President Barack Obama should dispatch all 535 U.S. senators and representatives to verify whether a pesticide research facility is being used to produce anthrax. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Australian judge has accused WikiLeaks of "a clear and deliberate breach of the law" with its online publication last year of a suppression order issued to prevent world leaders being named in a corruption case. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rain and irrigation can make crops temporary bacteria farms: Researchers suggest farmers should consider harvesting when fields are dry, to prevent dangerous bacteria blooms from contaminating food. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> America's dirtiest power companies, ranked: A new report says carbon pollution from the power sector is declining, but not fast enough. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China's top graft-busting agency has lambasted the country's powerful state-owned industries as being riddled with corruption and nepotism, saying the origins of the problem could partly be traced back to the chaos of the Cultural Revolution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Saskatchewan woman fighting to prove she is in fact a Canadian is finally getting her citizenship papers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ontarios home-care system is changing how it delivers care to some clients, a move that will see an array of non-profit agencies take responsibility for services to tens of thousands of seniors who rely on regular support to remain in their homes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China will begin the trial on July 28 of a Korean-American missionary arrested last year over a non-profit school he ran near the sensitive border with North Korea, his lawyer said, in a case that sparked outcry from international Christian groups. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quebec's premier Philippe Couillard is holding a special meeting with his Alberta counterpart, Rachel Notley, on Tuesday, one day before all the premiers meet in St. John's Nfld: expected to discuss energy, oil pipelines and climate change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quebec's premier Philippe Couillard is holding a special meeting with his Alberta counterpart, Rachel Notley, on Tuesday, one day before all the premiers meet in St. John's Nfld: expected to discuss energy, oil pipelines and climate change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good god, you're like my evil twin in reverse!

I was born in Chicago and escaped to Hawaii as soon as I finished college. Have been going back and forth from Honolulu and Tokyo ever since! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've got waaaaay too much time on your hands! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 10:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This is a shit bot

I'm waiting for the Thisisashitbot to chime in in 5...4...3... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 10:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank goodness! 

? 

Maybe:~) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 08:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Or large predators!

?

Ever been in a club in Waikiki? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 08:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The hiking meetups are low-key and well worth your time to make.

If you suddenly notice a very strange new face in the next few months...don't panic. Just move away slowly and keep your hands and feet away from it's mouth:~) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 08:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's say I moved to Chicago and couldn't find a job. All I have to do is to pack everything in the car and drive to the next city over.

In Hawaii, your options are limited and it takes a pretty big chunk of change to get over there, let alone return back to wherever it is you came from if things bottom out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 08:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You can always check /r/hawaiijobs!

I'm there looking in three weeks so please fill this bad boy up!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 08:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that smoke from the burning pitchforks I smell?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 08:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  My RES

I'm afraid to wonder what you've got me tagged as! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 08:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lurked here at first because, as some of you may know, I've been living between Honolulu and Tokyo for quite some time now, but due to my family situation, most of that time has been spent here in Tokyo.

Don't get me wrong, I love Japan, it's just that I really prefer to be in Hawaii, *especially* when I'm not actually *in* Hawaii!

Yes, Hawaii drives me nuts at times, but that's the difference between living there and just visiting.

Coming here has helped to keep me grounded, still feeling like I'm part of the community.

Even though posting pics was kind of frowned upon when I first started coming here, thankfully, the community has become more open and flexible to most things Hawaii.

Now, a big change is happening in my life because, unless something majorly bad happens, I'll be coming back to stay from the first week of August.

Because I haven't actually been living full time in Hawaii, every time I went back there, I never went on the internet, spent most of my time in the water and/or walking around.

Now, I hope to balance things out a bit and I hope to become more of an irregular regular here. I want to give back those feel-goods to those of you who are lurking and wished they were actually in Hawaii.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for hermes1010 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 08:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for justin19821 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 08:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for eichhorn15 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 08:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Word of Windsor bar owners reward for patrons who dont drink and drive goes viral: John OKane wasnt comfortable with the sudden notoriety after becoming a hero of the anti-drunk driving movement, until learning the tragic tale of stranger in Washington, D.C. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fracking: Pennines residents mobilise to stop company drilling up to 950 wells in Thirsk and Malton. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deadly floods and record heat: Scientists say climate change made these recent extreme weather events worse: New studies point to the influence of human activity on events in Europe and Russia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 05:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May I play with them?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 03:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Well, if this just doesn't sound like a terrible idea with pretty transparent spin control.

Oh? This sentance...

"This information will then be passed on to hotels, restaurants, hospitals **and other institutions in Japan.**"

...doesn't raise any red flags for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for marouane446 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 02:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for Heryy143 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 02:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan will establish a system that transcends language barriers and smoothly provides omotenashi hospitality services to foreign visitors. Foreigners will be asked to volunteer personal information such as their religion, languages, food preferences and chronic diseases. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 02:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 02:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sharing:~) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 years ago, Canadian government made a significant environmental pledge to protect the countrys land and fresh water  and now efforts are falling behind the world average: Only 10% of Canadas landscape is protected, according to a report released by the Canadian Parks and Wilderness Society. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 02:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 years ago, Canadian government made a significant environmental pledge to protect the countrys land and fresh water  and now efforts are falling behind the world average: Only 10% of Canadas landscape is protected, according to a report released by the Canadian Parks and Wilderness Society. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 02:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 22-year-old man was arrested by the SQ on Monday in connection with the death of Samantha Higgins, according to Sret du Qubec spokesperson Christine Coulombe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fossils indicate human activities have disturbed ecosystem resilience. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The government's Levy Control Framework (LCF) spending cap for green power subsidies will be breached, according to new official forecasts from the Office for Budget Responsibility. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 15:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Well I am guilty of having 500 alter accounts.

UniGaseouspartdeux? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 15:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'd get north of a couple thousand hits on a top post.

Sorry, that was me. I...I...I like pushing buttons:~) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 15:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ah, trolls. XD

Not trolls, menehune! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 15:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  WE DID IT REDDIT!

These words strike fear into the fiercest of Warriors!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexican president expropriates indigenous land for highway: Activists expressed outrage and launched an online campaign after government trucks and construction vehicles entered this weekend protected lands of one of Mexico's indigenous communities in order to build a highly controversial highway. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hoping to promote transparency and credibility, the Evergreen Park(IL) Police Department will use body-worn cameras during a pilot program set to launch early this fall. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Big Water is trying to stop the National Park Service from cleaning up plastic bottles. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Obama has engaged in unprecedented spending on wind and solar power, and argues theyre key to getting the U.S. off of fossil fuels, but recent studies have raised new questions about just how much the so-called green energy sources will cost taxpayers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An illegal immigrant from Mexico, serving time in a federal prison for unlawfully reentering the U.S., will appear before a judge next week over his alleged involvement in the killing of a homeless woman 18 years ago in California. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fire marshal called to investigate Thornhill blaze. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hanging on by a thread': Fire department of Canadas most populated First Nation struggles to stay afloat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China's biggest carbon market in Guangdong province will allocate 408 million carbon permits to firms to help them comply with emission targets set for the trading year ending in June 2016, the same amount as the previous year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China's biggest carbon market in Guangdong province will allocate 408 million carbon permits to firms to help them comply with emission targets set for the trading year ending in June 2016, the same amount as the previous year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Underwater volcanoes found off coast of Sydney: Australia's new ocean research vessel Investigator discovers the four cones nearly 5,000m down while studying marine life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Underwater volcanoes found off coast of Sydney: Australia's new ocean research vessel Investigator discovers the four cones nearly 5,000m down while studying marine life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A scientific assessment on the impacts of hydraulic fracturing in California found that, in large part, the chemicals used are not being identified or tracked, and its nearly impossible to tell how damaging the process is to Californias water supply. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 07:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toronto Community Housing Corporation (TCHC) tenants owe millions in back rent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 07:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The HMCS Fredericton had an emotional return to Halifax on Sunday after a seven-month deployment patrolling the Mediterranean and Black Seas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 07:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 05:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I'm in Tokyo right now and it's 34c/93f and we've got about 67% humidity. I'll be back home the first week of August...so...is it possible to ditch the muggy air by then please!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biological predators being used to attack invasive species across Connecticut. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 03:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biological predators being used to attack invasive species across Connecticut. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 03:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for jschweiss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for DHSJSK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for lorena25 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for informadorin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for Sharla43 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for dadaras </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for kanishksingh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for bazaarbd </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for rabbi-schnitzel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for Chrisz713 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for sohailwali </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for pageinterest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for joe-site2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for SmidyTV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for Azedae </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for griangraf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for sanmob00 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fugitive in $3-million fraud case, Jennifer McTigue, arrested in Kaimuki. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you /u/moonpurr, /u/hawaiithaibro, and /u/fern420.

As you may already know, I wasn't born in Hawaii and didn't attend school here, so when I first moved here in the 90's, I did my best to read as much as I could about Hawaii and ask everyone as many questions when I could, at the proper times.

I don't try to "be Hawaiian", but I sure as heck try to "be local." And what I mean by that is taking some pride in the fact that my kids were born here, go to school here and we all need to be aware of Hawaii's past, so that we can have some sort of future here.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monsoon flooding that killed dozens of people in western India last month also hurt the worlds last population of wild Asiatic lions, according to a report submitted over the weekend to the federal environment ministry in New Delhi. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monsoon flooding that killed dozens of people in western India last month also hurt the worlds last population of wild Asiatic lions, according to a report submitted over the weekend to the federal environment ministry in New Delhi. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Norwegian renewable energy specialist Scatec Solar has struck a 52m deal to build West Africa's first industrial-scale solar power plant, the company announced in a statement on Friday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Norwegian renewable energy specialist Scatec Solar has struck a 52m deal to build West Africa's first industrial-scale solar power plant, the company announced in a statement on Friday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Staff shortages in Ontario jails lead to increase in lockdowns: 900 lockdowns in Ontarios provincial jails due to staff shortages last year, a figure that has more than tripled since 2009. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Staff shortages in Ontario jails lead to increase in lockdowns. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Suzuki rescues capsized canoers at Site C Dam protest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dust clouds the future of the South Asian monsoon. (Op-Ed) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservationists on Friday protested a U.S. decision not to prosecute a Utah hunter who mistakenly shot and killed a gray wolf that had gained an international following for being the first of its kind seen at the Grand Canyon in 70 years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 17:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title is directly from the story, it's the first paragraph. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 14:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure you'll be glowing after you spark this up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A judge ruled Friday that California regulators violated some farmers rights by telling them to stop diverting from rivers and streams, but the state said it can still punish those who illegally take water during the drought. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Struggling to save black rhinos, scientists are crowdfunding to preserve their DNA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Counterfeiter gets green card after evading US lawsuits. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a move aimed at strengthening efforts to prevent terrorist attacks on airplanes, Japan's Ministry of Land, Infrastructure, Transport and Tourism plans to implement a trial operation of full-body scanners in three major airports this year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2,000 Moldovans and Romanians call for reunification, scatter flowers over river border. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian officials are studying the impact of long oil trains on the integrity of the country's railway tracks, Transport Minister Lisa Raitt said on Friday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 12:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two women claim they were asked to leave an Ontario restaurant for breastfeeding a baby, but amid the resulting storm of criticism online, the eatery insists the trouble was caused by an unruly customer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 12:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Water from a public hydrant that Tom Selleck has been accused of stealing from in dry California was legally purchased, an official said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 12:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hawaiian Natives have been waiting since 1920 for promised land: More than 29,000 on list for acreage set aside for ranches and homes while corporations jump ahead in line. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 12:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK scraps zero carbon homes target: Treasury axes plans to make new homes carbon neutral from 2016, drawing widespread criticism from housebuilders and environmentalists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 12:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A South Florida family that made its fortune in real estate asked the state this week to drill an exploratory oil well in marshes just west of Broward County suburbs, marking the first time the search for Everglades crude has extended so far east. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 12:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 09:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do tell, where's this at? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The sun-powered Solar Impulse 2 aircraft has been grounded in Hawaii, its crew said Saturday, after a grueling five-day, fuel-less flight across the Pacific Ocean overheated its batteries. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservation groups are challenging new rules that expand cougar hunting in some parts of the state, arguing that the Washington Fish and Wildlife Commission disregarded scientific studies that show increased harvests dont reduce cougar populations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New law to battle ticket bots to even the playing field. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No need to worry, because we would *never* do that to /u/carmabound, right?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The head of a new organisation set up to tackle international wildlife crime syndicates has vowed to bring down the Al Capones behind the 86bn global trade in commodities from rhino horn to tuna. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
