<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7806</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 08:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea from all the comments i figured SMS and email are much better, will definitely use them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 08:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can do video streaming with the Skype shield in the 1Sheeld app.

http://1sheeld.com/shields/skype-shield/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 08:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I don't have a baby i just built the system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 16:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just used it for the sake of using Twitter you know, you're right notifications and email would wor better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 16:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Twitter is free, while most SMS services are at least nominally pay.
 

Yea you're right, I could use the notification, e-mail or SMS. They are all included in the 1Sheeld app. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 16:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I'm using the phone for that, I use the phone as a gateway to Twitter through the Twitter shield in 1Sheeld. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 16:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! You can find all the details in the instructable :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I built an automated baby monitor that tweets to me when the baby cries! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 13:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 22:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea the point is to leave a cheap smart phone inside the car, and this phone acts as a GPS, Accelerometer and GSM shield so you can talk to it and receive messages as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 20:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one is the easiest, you use 1Sheeld that connects to an old phone, the Arduino is connected to the master fuse so you can send it a message to stop remotely.
With the GPS and accelerometer in the phone, it sends you a text message with the location of the car.
http://www.instructables.com/id/Tracking-and-Controlling-your-car-remotely-using-A/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 08:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is the US link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 17:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! So what do you think of this tutorial videos: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7nf6lpsOrkI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 17:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool thanks for the advice! We'll get a new explainer video done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 20:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea it's for $55 but it has 36 shields and gets me access to stuff like voice recognition and text to speech in an easy way, check this one: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P35hSIyYltM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 20:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you are not writing the function itself as it's included n the library, and the good thing here is you don't get any tokens since you login from your smart phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 20:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea the beauty about it is that you access 36 shields on the phone itself, including voice recognition, text to speech, facebook, phone calls, video calls ... etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 16:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea the meaning here is this one line: 

Twitter.tweet("Plant is thirsty!"); </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
