<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5522</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. data hack may be 4 times larger than the government originally said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 03:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moroccan gay men to serve four months for posing close together for photograph </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 02:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Merck Birth Control Product Kills 24 Year Old Woman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 00:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These hackers warned the Internet would become a security disaster. Nobody listened. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 23:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 23:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The result was a culture within the tech industry often derided as  patch and pray. In other words, keep building, keep selling and send out fixes as necessary. If a system failed  causing lost data, stolen credit card numbers or time-consuming computer crashes  the burden fell not on giant, rich tech companies but on their customers.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Back in 1998, these hackers warned Congress that the Internet would become a security disaster. Nobody listened. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 23:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Children fleeing warzones being locked up at Yarl's Wood detention centre, investigation finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 23:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 22:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me the world we live in is a fusion of Brave New World, 1984, and Walden Two by Skinner. And I have an idea that Walden Two is even more determinant in shaping this present reality. The idea that people can be declared mentally ill because they fail to fit in. Ultimately everything ends up looking like Naked Lunch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prisons: Americas Slave Empire - Chris Hedges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 19:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This story hits home for me because I grew up there and used to walk all over the place from age 8 onwards. It really freaks me out how lame Americans have become towards overprotecting their children, and these parents should be applauded. They seem really sane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fearing Family Dog, Cop Accidentally Shoots 4-Year-Old Girl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 19:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free range parents cleared in child neglect case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 18:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 17:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In WW1, African troops were considered to be more resistant to mustard gas and forced to march through it in front of other troops. I don't know if there was any truth to their resistance or whether it was some myth based on racial assumptions of the day, but I do know that troops were brought in from West Africa to fight in France specifically for this reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US military admits it carried out secret race-based experiments to test impact of mustard gas on US soldiers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 16:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US military admits it carried out secret race-based experiments to test impact of mustard gas on US soldiers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 16:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Catastrophic food shortages, growing demand and riots: Government-backed researchers predict society will collapse  within 25 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 16:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Catastrophic food shortages, growing demand and riots: Government-backed researchers predict society will collapse  within 25 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 16:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State lays explosives in Syria's Palmyra ruins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 06:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China Is Building a Massive Railway Across South Americaat Significant Human and Environmental Cost </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 05:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 05:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not really a fan of her music but she seems to have a bit more going on upstairs than the average pop star today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taylor Swift shakes off Apple Music in open letter: 'These are not the complaints of a petulant child' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 04:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Embarrassing Sony secrets revealed in massive WikiLeaks dump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 01:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bradford sisters who left UK 'to join Isis' were radicalised by British police, relatives say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 22:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bradford sisters who left UK 'to join Isis' were radicalised by British police, relatives say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 22:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Orwell, Huxley and Americas Plunge into Authoritarianisn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 17:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Orwell, Huxley and Americas Plunge into Authoritarianisn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 17:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Souths Sordid History of Attacks on Black Churches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 17:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wikileaks publishes 60,000 secret docs of rare insight into Saudi royal family's lavish spending </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 17:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wikileaks publishes 60,000 secret docs of rare insight into Saudi royal family's lavish spending </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 17:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 17:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I get it. Because we're all drunks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Irishman died of spontaneous human combustion, coroner claims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 17:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earth is entering sixth extinction phase with many species  including our own  labelled 'the walking dead' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 15:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Nasa data map that shows the world is running out of water  because human beings are draining the Earth's underground supplies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 16:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Oliver thinks he's found a way to make people read a report on torture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 00:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 21:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very compelling. She is an extremely lucid and articulate speaker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 20:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Angels Don't Play This HAARP](http://www.westcoasttruth.com/uploads/7/0/4/9/7049688/adpthaarp.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 20:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HAARP is a very controversial subject to say the least. My simple understanding of it is that the ionosphere is heated by antenna arrays and the energy thus created is then directed downwards towards a target on earth. I posted a link to a PDF of Angels Don't Play This HAARP above. Here is a short video if you can deal with the Moog in the background: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MTpYwf7lBCA

Tesla pioneered this technology and nearly destroyed a town in Colorado. If I'm remembering right, he used a similar principle but instead of using the ionosphere, he obtained an accumulation of energy by bouncing electricity off the earth's crust on the other side of the earth... ie using the earth itself as an amplifier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 20:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot has been played down by the authorities especially the danger posed by the central core. I see a number of directions where cover ups seem to be occurring. Fish stocks in the Pacific are badly effected. Children in many parts of Japan outside of Fukushima are showing higher than normal rates of cancer. US naval personnel who assisted post tsunami have had some very unusual occurrences of leukemia and other illnesses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, I was just laughing at that. I e-mailed the article to my wife and now I'm probably on some fucking list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This wasn't a cumulative assessment. This was a year by year measure. The depressed economy has no bearing on the numbers. Take a look at 23 Thing they Don't Teach You About Capitalism for more info. It's not anti-capitalism per se, but challenges a few claims that are usually not addressed. As for IT or Bill Gates, no one is arguing that hasn't had a positive impact on the economy, but taken as a part of the larger economy, it hasn't been enough to lift productivity, real per capita income etc across the board. Zimbabwe is a terrible example. I used to live there and know a great deal about it. The land was ripped from the few and given to even fewer. It had nothing to do with helping the poor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just came across this. I don't know if I buy it, but it is interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Haarp Evidence for Fukushima Meltdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Not always" is the negation. The negation isn't the same as the opposite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Article about radiation contamination in Tokyo from Fukushima fallout: 

http://www.i-sis.org.uk/Tokyo_contaminated_and_not_fit_for_habitation.php </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 16:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Economic growth during the period from 1950 to 1980 in the United States was, by almost every measure, double what it was in the following period from 1980 to 2010. This happened despite high end tax rates during the earlier period that targeted the wealthiest Americans. We are way less productive as a society when these brainless elites are allowed to make all the decisions about what to do with our economy. Most of them are not producers but horders. They put their capital into government bonds at best (facilitating the endless expansion of enormous, enslaving debt) or else into off shore accounts where the money just sits doing literally NOTHING for anyone, serving as some kind of bullshit trophy/bragging right about how rich they are. A good book on the subject is Ha Joon Chang's 23 Things They Don't Tell You About Capitalism:

(https://mafhom.files.wordpress.com/2013/02/23-things-they-dont-tell-you-about-capitalism.pdf)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fukushima will likely go down in history as the biggest cover-up of the 21st Century. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 14:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 04:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (http://www.dailybuddhism.com/archives/670) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Graphene technology. This changes everything. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 01:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 23:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've done that before. Didn't say sorry though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 22:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you see Buddha on a smartphone, kill him. Or at least kick his ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a little reminder that Palestinians aren't animals, they're people... and cool people at that. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 20:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 20:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my problem. I can't believe this will not be turned against average citizens given enough time for the cops to learn how to game the technology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Navy Lieutenant Commander Thomas Narut in a speech in Oslo in 1979 claimed that the Navy had programs based in Naples, Italy to create mind controlled assassins. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 20:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you see Buddha on the road, kill him.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could filming cops really put an end to police brutality in the US? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about [Love Canal](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Love_Canal)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Appeal for UK family of 12 missing after Saudi Arabia trip </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police in the US have killed someone nearly every day this year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 15:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CIA torture appears to have broken spy agency rule on human experimentation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 14:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cartier boss with $7.5bn fortune says prospect of the poor rising up 'keeps him awake at night' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 22:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure none of these assholes give a shit about real issues. They're too brainwashed to wake up. Fucking lemmings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China's empty cities - Great video that shows how the fake property boom in China could bring down the global economy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 05:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 04:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My problem with full legalization is only that corporations would then be able to advertise. I want to see bans on advertising and some kind of quality control regulation. I do think legalization is coming sooner than people think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Youve Been Scammed! Going for Broke in Ponzi-Scheme America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 04:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 02:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely see drugs as a health care rather than a criminal issue. I also like the idea of decriminalization instead of legalization because that way corporations can't have the ability to market drugs. People need to be free to make their own mistakes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With a series of major hacks, China builds a database on Americans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 02:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Portugal decriminalised drugs 14 years ago  and now hardly anyone dies from overdosing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 01:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 01:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, I've actually been looking for some Situationist reading. And feel free to use the M word. Groucho is God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Portugal decriminalised drugs 14 years ago  and now hardly anyone dies from overdosing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 01:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 22:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Work stoppages seem to have helped folks in the fast food industry. Maybe we should all do our best to kill the Protestant work ethic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 21:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [May 1968 events in France](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/May_1968_events_in_France) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Graffiti from France May 1968 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 21:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 19:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess the problem is who is fixing the issues? If the same system that created these global problems in the first place is in charge of the fixes, then I can't see how that will turn out too well. I'm not 100% against GMOs, but I am against a system where Monsanto is in charge of them for example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 19:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first paragraph of the Unabomber Manifesto:

The Industrial Revolution and its consequences have
been a disaster for the human race. They have greatly
increased the life-expectancy of those of us who live in
advanced countries, but they have destabilized society,
have made life unfulfilling, have subjected human beings
to indignities, have led to widespread psychological suffering (in the Third World to physical suffering as well) and
have inflicted severe damage on the natural world. The
continued development of technology will worsen the si-
tuation. It will certainly subject human being to greater in
dignities and inflict greater damage on the natural world,
it will probably lead to greater social disruption and psy-
chological suffering, and it may lead to increased physical
suffering even in advanced countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do people on this sub think about this statement? "The Industrial Revolution and its consequences have been a disaster for the human race." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 19:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 18:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try this: [The New Atlantis - Secret Mysteries of America's Beginnings ](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KMhkf5mAGgA)

Also this: [The Secret Destiny of America by Manly P. Hall](http://www.bibliotecapleyades.net/sociopolitica/secret_destinyamerica/secret_destinyamerica.htm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 04:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read all his books. Now actually read the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carlos Castanedas Sex-and-Suicide Cult, and the Witches Who Disappeared </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 02:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Cusack: Barack Obama is 'as bad or worse' than George W Bush </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 20:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new age of internet terrorism: Who is hacking who, how long has it been going on... and what does the future hold for cyber warfare? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 19:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 18:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the fuck are you posting a link to a video that describes a sexually abused minor as a "sexy teen"? Seriously what the fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twilight of the Professors - The Neoliberal War on Higher Education </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 23:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be fun for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 17:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's so much stuff like this. The Belgians used to have safari parks with humans in them. In Spain, outside Barcelona, there was a stuffed African - I think he was a Koi bushman - up until the late 90's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Bernie Sanders is a Dead End </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 16:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The man who was caged in a zoo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 16:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guantanamo Bay detainee alleges CIA sexual abuse beyond original torture report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 15:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a US cyber attack on North Korea failed  because country has practically no internet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 15:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 21:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. It does sound harsh. And no, it couldn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 19:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was aware of that. The point is it isn't so well known now and articles discussing it should be passed around. Also people are more willing to let such a figure slip into oblivion if the victims were African because people in the West assume this is normal for Africa.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 19:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot to mention her cousin was working inside the Bush White House throughout the period and she had frequent contact with the White House. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 19:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think he's one of the most hated people around because I don't think the average person could tell you who he was. Also, I'm posting an article written by someone else. It's interesting and worth looking at. Doesn't mean all the words or thoughts are mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
