<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3651</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teens who use social media to quit smoking are twice as successful as those who use a more traditional method, according to a new study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drought, heat and insects have been responsible for the death of more than 12 million trees in California. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 22:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I don't think US should *support* them. I just don't think US should be trying so hard to stop them. Seems likely ISIS will lose anyway. Worst case scenario, ISIS wins and wipes out the Syrian government, the Iranian government and a few terrorist groups. As for the civilians, they're utterly screwed under both the status quo and ISIS, so we're not doing them any favors either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 22:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right, so those are bad things. But, like, everyone they're at war with is equally bad, and a bunch are actually kind of worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 21:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the USA should join Team ISIS.

Think about it. ISIS is trying to overthrow the Syrian government (that would be Bashar al-Assad's government, the one that used chemical weapons on its civilians). Meanwhile, ISIS is also at war with: Iran (the ones with the rogue nukes), Hezbollah (the ones with the rogue rocket strikes) and basically every failed state and terrorist organization in the region. Why are we trying to stop them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of Starbucks' new frappuccino flavors contains 102 grams of sugar. Thats 4x the recommended daily allowance, and roughly equivalent to drinking an entire one-liter bottle of coke or scarfing down about thirty sugar cubes all at once. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 19:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 19:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's an abstract from [the full study:](http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2015/150609/ncomms8352/full/ncomms8352.html)
Exceptionally preserved organic remains are known throughout the vertebrate fossil record, and recently, evidence has emerged that such soft tissue might contain original components. We examined samples from eight Cretaceous dinosaur bones using nano-analytical techniques; the bones are not exceptionally preserved and show no external indication of soft tissue. In one sample, we observe structures consistent with endogenous collagen fibre remains displaying ~67nm banding, indicating the possible preservation of the original quaternary structure. Using ToF-SIMS, we identify amino-acid fragments typical of collagen fibrils. Furthermore, we observe structures consistent with putative erythrocyte remains that exhibit mass spectra similar to emu whole blood. Using advanced material characterization approaches, we find that these putative biological structures can be well preserved over geological timescales, and their preservation is more common than previously thought. The preservation of protein over geological timescales offers the opportunity to investigate relationships, physiology and behaviour of long extinct animals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 16:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Death To Paywalls!! Here's a bootleg copy of the complete study: http://docdro.id/12xxp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fifty hospitals in the US are overcharging the uninsured by 1000%, according to a new study from Johns Hopkins. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Less than seven hours of sleep is "inadequate to sustain health and safety in adults," according to a new study. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least 55 diseases correlate with when you're born. Overall, people born in May have the lowest lifetime disease risk, and those born in October have the highest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Non-profit workers are dirty donut thieves, according to a 2006 study on altruism and anonymous donut sales. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 20:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 19:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> huh. that's a good point. we should really say "newly discovered species". A newly discovered species really can't be THAT new...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 16:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or reproduction in general has occurred in sync with El Nino Rabbis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 16:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By the way, here's the complete study (no paywall): https://peerj.com/articles/1011/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 13:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original study: http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0033589415000368 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rabbits have reproduced in sync with El Nino weather patterns across the past 10,000 years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 13:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seven new miniature frog species were just discovered in Brazil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 13:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
