<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1909</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 22:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are people getting mad at Coke? Get mad at FIFA, they chose where to do it, not Coke. Sure, they are a sponsor, but why are you blaming a major company, they had nothing to do with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 01:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i luv ur mum Steam Community: steamcommunity.com/id/train_subject1909
In all seriousness I love my dog. Whenever I go through hard times she is just so happy to see me and be with me. It makes me feel like I am important to someone. Even if she can't talk it makes me feel better. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 23:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you disable it? You do think fire is fun after all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 23:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 23:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lost Marbles please. Steam ID is [here](http://steamcommunity.com/id/train_subject1909) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 14:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game itself had nothing wrong with it. I am just salty they didn't use the old style of the game. As we saw with XCOM, if you keep to the classic formula, it would pay out. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 14:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SHITTY!? Syndicate was an amazing tactical shooter. They turned into a modern fps. It was just dissapointing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 03:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no... that is all one can say when someone says the Syndicate reboot is good... no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 03:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have lost all faith in humanity... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 23:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 69 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 19:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case you are unaware, this is a fetus, dressed up in a Snow White dress. This is a dry rotting fetus corpse, dressed up as Snow White, as her mother pretends she is alive and that there is nothing wrong with what she is doing. Ignoring what is there will not help you mentally, but make you not be able to accept this fact and deal with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 17:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, now I see it. Holy cow... that is all there is to say about this occurrence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 17:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not see it. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No, lets not read the article! Let's read a phone screenshot of the article! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 16:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 16:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, blame the bugs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 16:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, okay. Also, is 0s possible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apply here to be authorized to spread the glory of the button, and its noble truths. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 15:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 15:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats what I saw. I am pretty sure we haven't got to zero because that is the only post about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there 0s yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 14:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I saw that there were... if so... WHEN DID THIS HAPPEN!?!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 21:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gray for me. Did you try to press the button? If so you probably have one of the rare "cheater/glitch" flares. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 21:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, he did hit the rarest time. You will always know he *knew* that orange was the rarest. He is probably the orange prophet. Quick question, is you SO a virgin? If so I am pretty sure he is the pressiah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After that Feminism got split-killed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 06:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 00:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [PECKING ORDER](http://vignette3.wikia.nocookie.net/teamfourstar/images/7/78/Image.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20130527010752) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 01:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit Tyrone! I thought I could trust you!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [THEORY] Before the button ends, 60s will be just as honorable as red. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may be saying this because I am a salty April 1st 60s, but the tables are starting to turn. There are now more reds than purples. This means being purple is more rare than being red. Eventually people will want to get as early as possible. Because of this, the timer will go down, and it will end. Just an idea. Also, if there are more reds than purples, why are there more *active* purples? The statistics are mind numbing for someone unfamiliar with this type of stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, /u/train_subject1909 , accept that I am, as a Purple, superior to all other colors because of my Button-granted right. In addition, I accept the Hierarchy of Purple and swear that my ultimate goal is to allow The Timer to reach Zero.
Through all means, prove supremacy. Hail the Violet Hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 22:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This HAS to be influenced by animal crossing! It is too similar! Also, once I wen into the comments the score dropped by 3... wut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 20:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, probably right. I'm pretty sure ESO isn't cannon (just to piss of people) because it would make no sense to have 10,000,000 adventures all being the chosen of some prophesy or whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Elder Scrolls games are cannon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 20:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume all of them, but Redguard and Battlespire are quite obscure and no one has really played them. I LOVE the Elder Scrolls universe and have played the hell out of all the games but Daggerfall because I couldn't get DOSBOX to work with it. The old games a shit, I will admit, they were to ambitious for the technology of the time. So, which of the TES games are canon? edit: canon... jeez </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 03:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT THE SHIT! Fuckin' normie buzzfeed fags stealing pepe! REEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEe IF THIS GITS 1 UPVOTES THIS BECOMES A ANTI BUZZFEED SUBREDDIT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 02:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest I don't think they were console master racing. They just don't understand because they don't have a GPU inside a potato. They have fancy mold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 00:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did you type i wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 23:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't valid :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 22:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> added
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 22:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Added! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Loving Animal Crossing and Smash! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 21:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need some people to play with. Also play lots of other games. Friend code is 4828-6625-6360 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 21:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4828-6625-6360 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 03:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who knows? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 17:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> rekt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 06:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marvel Studios does not own the rights to Magneto. Marvel let Sony use Magneto for the X-Men films before Marvel Studios was created. Sony owns Magneto in film, even though Marvel COMICS created them. Since Marvel Studios created Avengers, they cannot include Magneto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 06:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just going to say something. I hope you guys don't hate too much on me. Why does /r/atheism have so much Christian hate!? This is about god not being real, yet we only focus on Christianity. Islam and Buddhism is just as stupid. Us saying it is bad for only Christians to be able to pray. All prayer is stupid. Why should we care? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 05:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUCK NO! I did something similar. Dick carpet burn. The pain... THE PAIN!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 04:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See! Everyone thinks I got a great card! Except that god damned cashier Linda! DAMN YOU LINDA!!! D: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 04:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was [pretty good](http://puu.sh/hHIwe/e398140176.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 03:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I guess it isn't foreshadowing, but it did hint that their relationship outside the Avengers would affect the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 03:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but the foreshadowing for them planning an AI since Avengers 1 was attention to detail. Just thought it was cool. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 03:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ? They said that lol. I dont think this clarifies anything or that anything needed to be clarified in the first place.

Well it seemed cool how they had Ultron planned since the first Avengers... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 03:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This explains how the talked about how they had been working on Ultron before but were unsuccessful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I guess you should expect that when you shop at Walmart... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 03:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 02:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! It's fine! At least you got it right! :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 22:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cell is called cell because, according to the wiki, "Cell is composed of cells from Goku, Piccolo, Vegeta, Frieza, King Cold, and according to the manga title page, a number of other lifeforms (in the FUNimation dub, it is also stated that he has cells from Krillin, Gohan, Nappa, and Tien Shinhan)." There are billions of billions of nuclei in the body, including Cell's. Also, according to this, "Cell Juniors (Jr.) are the seven offspring of Cell. They are asexually produced from Cell's tail, through cellular mitosis.[2] According to Cell himself, each Cell Junior has his power and abilities." Your statement isn't a theory but a fact. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 02:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/aww material right here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 23:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two words. Blue Penis... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 03:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I have a link to some info about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 02:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems to be a rip-off. There is no 3+ thing on the sunburn Elsa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 02:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain this to me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 22:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This could have ended in a much worse way... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 03:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wouldn't stab a guy with *glasses?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 00:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh... my.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 00:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why wouldn't the first person do this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 23:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would live in that. I don't need to leave my house. That house is pretty dank. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 22:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a 4chan omegle raid of the feminism tag. They were saying they were trans-niggers. was fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 22:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they made it a beer glass it would sell pretty well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 22:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit tails! That isn't a chaos emerald! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why NL was gone for a few days. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 22:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 22:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next he will start washing the damn windows. Fuck these type of guys.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 02:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preventing the inevitable 0s of the button once more, damn you reddit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 02:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, /u/train_subject1909, accept that I am, as a Purple, superior to all other colors because of my Button-granted right. In addition, I accept the Hierarchy of Purple and swear that my ultimate goal is to allow The Timer to reach Zero. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 02:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest... AWFUL game. Clunky controls, bad graphics, doesn't follow the show's plot. Not worth the download. Cool find though. Pretty rare game! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 01:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FIX: How to tell who farted at the table
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 01:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What pokemon are those. Kappa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 00:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there ya go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
