<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5306</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 08:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was always $550 here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 00:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh... I would totally watch that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 07:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it was Raiju </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 06:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No he didn't. He took several hits from fists and swords, followed by a direct hit by a nuclear bomb, before Gispsy's super powerful nuclear powered vortex turbine being fired full blast into his chest at point blank range finally killed him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 02:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 605 feet?

The new 2014 Godzilla is the biggest Godzilla has ever been and he's 350 feet. He was originally about 160 feet.

Godzilla certainly is more durable, and his radioactive breath and seemingly supernatural strength and healing abilities make him insanely powerful, but Slattern would still be a pretty worthy opponent for him. Plus we never really get a clear description of what exactly Slattern is capable of.

Due to Godzilla's radioactive breath and his ability to seemingly gain strength and power and heal himself whenever the plot requires, he'd probably be a Cat 6, but Cat 7 seems a little crazy and is downplaying the size of strength of Slattern a considerable amount.

Although it's really hard to put Godzilla and other Kaiju into the Pacific Rim class system because of how much their size and strength and abilities change from movie to movie.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 02:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slattern took a nuclear blast at close range and was pretty much fine afterwards  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 01:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeez what movie is this from? That's pretty graphic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 00:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-09 11:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell it to the judge, buddy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-09 09:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one said anything was wrong with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-08 14:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leo didn't win because he isn't good enough. He makes solid enjoyable movies and always gives a good performance, but he is rarely ever in the same league as the nominees he is up against. Just because he's cool and hip and his moves are usually the most widely accessible and fun among the usual darker, more serious (or 'challenging' or however you'd like to describe it) competition doesn't mean he deserves to win anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 11:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds horrendously depressing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 07:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, I guess it's just because of the size of the buildings in New York, but I would have thought the Millenium Godzilla was larger than Zilla.
 
Although it's hard to tell since Zilla's size changed so much in that movie anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 07:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How big is Zilla 98 compared to these guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 03:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also that is clearly Tom Wilkinson as Andrew Johnson, not 'Dennis Clark' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 12:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got the touch... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 08:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No King Ghidorah, Mothra, Rodan or Mechagodzilla? Not even Biollante? But Megalon makes the list? Above Destroyah? Booo, sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 13:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea who that is  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 22:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just a poster  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 10:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that all he said about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 10:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe Gareth Edwards is just a Slash fan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 08:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to IMDb that scene was only put in the movie for the sole purpose that it could be cut out to appease the ratings board, so that Scorsese could get away with the more important violent scenes throughout the rest of the film that he didn't want to cut out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 13:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, all the rumors were true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 10:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he's talking about the brony with short hair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 16:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a very common saying here in Australia unfortunately  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 07:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KkDFBVczcGY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 03:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes Drive Angry and Getaway look like big budget summer blockbusters. How can this look so bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 04:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something about pick up lines referencing God just creeps me out so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 04:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Subtly? Really?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 05:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping that too, but I think we all knew this was going to happen. CGI is just so much easier and cheaper these days, and having actual animatronics on location could result in too many problems to be worth it to them. It's a real shame and I'm gonna miss the awesome practical effects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 04:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that actually looks much better. Indy 4 had a really 'fake' look to it. Yours looks much nicer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 09:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jurassic Park is one of my all time favorite movies, and when I was a kid I absolutely loved all 3 movies. So I'll try to explain why, to me, the second two don't hold up anymore like the first one does.

Really boring stories, with no sense of wonder and discovery and science and wondering 'could this happen in real life?" Just generic stranded on an island with monsters plotlines. The Lost World has some potentially interesting ideas but didn't go anywhere with them.

Really dull and dreary tone. Jurassic Park was 50% fun and joy and childlike wonder, and then 50% terror and fear and tension. 2 and 3 were just bland, not very engaging, leaving us waiting for something exciting to happen.

Boring characters. Jurassic Park had fun lovable realistic characters, 2 and 3 were filled with pretty generic two dimensional dinosaur-meals. Even Jeff Goldblum and Sam Neill didn't seem like they were acting like their characters from the first. Pete Postlethwaite in The Lost World is an exception.

Didn't do anything new or interesting with the dinosaurs. Jurassic Park made the dinosaurs seem real and amazing, like we had never seen before. It was new and exciting and made them feel like real living animals, and brought on all the emotions of wonder and amazement, and then fear, that comes with that. In 2 and 3, sure all our favorites came back, and there were some new ones, but they just felt like monsters.

Frankly 2 and 3 just felt lazy and boring and uninspired. None of the cast or crew seemed very enthusiastic about churning out more cash-in installments. Acting was meh. Direction was meh. Story was meh. No emotions or excitement or fun or discovery or wonder. Just dinosaurs killing generic characters. The Lost World had a potentially interesting premise, and some of the action set pieces were alright, but as a whole it was flat and dull and pointless. And then Jurassic Park 3 felt like a lame cheap sci-fi tv movie.

Jurassic Park made you feel like you were there and captured your imagination. It was a new and exciting experience like never before. 2 and 3 were just excuses to watch more people get eaten by monsters for 90 minutes.

That's just my opinion anyway.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 04:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's creepy as shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 09:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I owned a museum I would totally hire this guy to make dinosaurs. These are insanely cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 06:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [oh my god I can't waaaaiit](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XwamV1fbYQk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 02:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude. It is your duty to be our secret inside man. Do it for all of us Jurassic Park geeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 14:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Godammit Ennis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 12:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen it, but I believe so. 

Dark Knight had the same thing where the 65mm IMAX shots and scenes were a different aspect ratio than the rest of the scenes. Most of the movie was normal widescreen, whereas the action sequences and shots of the city were more 'full screen' or 'square'.

MI4 had IMAX shots as well, but the aspect ratio was made to be the same as the rest of the movie. I guess it depends on whether or not the director wants that fluctuating widescreen effect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jurassic World to be shot on 35mm and 65mm film. John Schwartzman (Amazing Spiderman, Armageddon, Pearl Harbor) to be cinematographer. Shooting starts in April. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 11:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 09:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 35mm is the normal film size. 65mm is double size and is not so normal. Gives a much better quality, larger, richer, grander picture. Basically like bigger better resolution on your screen.

Sound of Music, Ben-Hur, Lawrence of Arabia, 2001, Samsara and recently The Master were filmed on 65mm. Chris Nolan uses it sometimes for special shots or sequences. It's a pretty big difference if you look at them side by side.

IMAX uses 65mm film as well, but I think you get a larger image due to aspect ratio... Or something... I don't actually know much about IMAX at all.

I'm guessing Colin will be doing this film Nolan style. Most of the scenes will probably be 35mm like a normal film, and then probably the big sweeping scenery shots of beautiful Hawaii will be 65mm, if not some of the actions sequences as well. (Hopefully)

Frankly it's great to see that it's being shot on film at all as opposed to digital. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Schwartzman (Amazing Spiderman, Pearl Harbor, Armageddon) will be the cinematographer on Jurassic World. Will be shooting on 35mm and 65mm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 08:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 06:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What every fuck is that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 04:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like the mountainous regions are a bit too big, making the city a little too small  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 01:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Octodaaaaaaaad

Nobody suspects a thing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 01:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to have a horse that was best friends with another horse at the local stables. They used to freak out whenever they were separated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 14:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like they're melting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 11:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't this movie come out in May? Whether or not this particular source is bullshit or not, surely we're gonna start getting new trailers or posters or details or whatever in the next month or so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 13:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cundy or Kaminski. Jurassic Park 3 was shot and lit like a cheap sci fi tv show. 

But it'll probably be a completely new guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 03:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw man this is fantastic

why was this deleted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 13:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a terribly written, impossible to understand, and hideously long title for such a well known repost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 13:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, so the 2xp thing I'm seeing isn't the Premium one? And it's not even working? Faaaaantastic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 08:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't run into the gate, it runs into the back of the cage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 01:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Danny Chan as Bruce Lee! Or Kwok Kwan Chan. Or Danny Chan Kwok Kwan. Whatever the dude's name is. Get him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 06:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eeewww </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 05:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know when the PS4 version is coming out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 09:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only like Quentin Tarantino's first three films. All the characters in his movies tend to be one dimensional cartoon characters and his movies never have any interesting depth or character development. It's just silly unrealistic dialogue, references and homages, and everyone trying way too hard to be cool. Django was alright as a fun silly bloody action movie but that's about it. Nothing special.

I don't like Jennifer Lawrence or Bradley Cooper or Ryan Gosling. Leo DiCaprio is alright sometimes I guess. The Departed was his last 'believable' performance.

The Dark Knight was great, but Inception was just okay, and Dark Knight Rises sucked. Unless he stops with the big budget action crap and goes back to smaller more personal thrillers I don't really care about Chris Nolan anymore.

I really don't like Marvel films. Or Wes Anderson films. They always both have great casts though I keep seeing them. I guess that's my bad.

EDIT: A lot of posts here are getting downvoted for having crazy opinions, which kinda goes against the whole point of the thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 15:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be nice if these were all in a chronological line, instead of separated into two rows </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 02:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like everything Mark Millar does then  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 13:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't HP Lovecraft have a cat named Niggerboy or something? Or was that just in one of his stories?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 10:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did your teacher molest you too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 03:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 14:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man thank you so much. Watching this little clip instantly gave me an insane jolt of recollection. I remembered this cartoon so incredibly clearly despite not ever thinking about it in years. I remember watching this as a kid and loving it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 10:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boogie Nights has always felt like the third in a trilogy along with Goodfellas and Casino.

Both Goodfellas and Casino, and now Wolf of Wall Street, show off what I think Scorsese is best at, showing us a crazy stylized alluring at first, but ultimately corrupt and doomed, fast paced get-rich-quick type scenario, that gradually falls apart as we see more of the horrible things that happen as a consequence, and how money and power corrupt the characters.

Scorsese is great at taking the classic rise and fall, American dream type movie, showing it in a twisted and corrupt light, and cranking everything up to eleven. Boogie Nights is so clearly aiming for the exact same motif, just in the porn world instead of the gangster world. PTA totally understood and reinterpreted and nailed everything Scorsese was going for.

American Hustle felt like it was trying for a similar vibe but just did not hit the mark.

Everything in Boogie Nights, the shots, the scenes, the characters, the cinematography, the pacing, the music, even the way the camera moves, is all dripping with Scorsese's influence. It totally feels like a twisted alternate-porn version of Goodfellas and I love the hell out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 06:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of hate for Aussies? How so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 05:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry things didn't work out between you and your sister, bro  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 09:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an honor to be murdered by that man. I'm sure your family will understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 07:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not out here in Australia yet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 05:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keitel has been in just as many Scorsese movies as Leo has.

And it's really weird that there's randomnly Cinematographers/editors/whatever for some and not for others. Most of these filmmakers tend to use the same cinematographers and editors for most of their movies, most famously the Coens and Roger Deakins, but instead there's a sound department guy.

But most importantly this is not what muse means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 12:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I choose to believe it was a martial arts induced seizure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 12:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you tell us anything else interesting? No spoilers of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 10:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow the hypetrain for this movie is insane!

http://www.slashfilm.com/early-buzz-gareth-evans-the-raid-2-sundance-2014/

There are some awesome twitter quotes there.

Also, apparently the movie had the be paused half way through because a dude passed out. Several other viewers took this opportunity to leave because the movie was too "intense" and "violent"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 09:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like that whole whymsical non sensical fairy tale-esque world was an intentional reference to Adventure Time. Just a much darker version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 02:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call me crazy, but I thought that the dude that H Macy talks to on the phone about car registration numbers or whatever was also played by Bruce Campbell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 02:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a shame that they don't do anything together anymore. They were clearly great friends in the 80s and 90s and loved working together. Although their careers have certainly gone in very different directions.

Joel was an assistant editor on Evil Dead. Joel and Ethan both wrote Crimewave, which Raimi directed. Sam Raimi had a cameo in Miller's Crossing. Joel and Ethan were credited as  'developers' for Darkman

Bruce Campbell was also in the Hudsucker Proxy, which Raimi co-wrote, had a small cameo in, and was the second unit director on.

Plus Raimi's A Simple Plan feels a lot like a Coen Brothers film.

And Sam Raimi and Joel Coen also both had cameos together in the 1985 Dan Akroyd and Chevy Chase comedy Spies Like Us for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 02:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice work man, congratulations! Your 'before' pic is pretty much exactly where I am now, so I'd love some tips. Especially with diet.

Also you looked like Timmy from WKUK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 02:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm both seething with jealousy and hiding a confusing erection.

What an offensively handsome man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 12:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This scene was so so awesome, and everything that a movie like this should be, I just wish it were longer. 

I feel like the whole movie was steadily building up to this big epic finale, and then this scene was over within ten minutes to make room for a much more bland and disappointing final fight under the ocean.

Also I did not realize that part with the office building was done with a miniature. That's insanely cool.

How did this movie not get nominated for best special effects? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 07:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turns out they were all hiding waiting to jump out, but then he pulled out his camera and started whining and saying how shitty everything and everyone was so they just waited for him to leave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 07:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing that seems to be different is I haven't seen any sort of vehicles or vehicular combat, which a huge part of what made Halo multiplayer so much fun for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 04:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope Jake Johnson isn't in it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 03:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This design probably has the slimmest thighs of all the Godzillas. (Aside from the  98 American version) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 03:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Colin Farrel has been going through kind of a semi come back since In Bruges  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 23:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's all I need to see to know I'm getting this day one.

Also, when's American Vampire coming back?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 05:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go go Godzilla </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 05:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, great interview! The secrecy around this movie is *killing* me. Still so far away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 11:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and my friend used to watch that movie aaaaall the time when we were younger. Thank you for reminding me that it exists so I can watch it again.

(It's called Road Kill here)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 07:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Raid makes Dredd look like Power Rangers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 06:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not for DVDs though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 02:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harvey Keitel deserves to be in this

EDIT: Also Frank Vincent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 07:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do all these crazy exotic super car show things keep happening? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 02:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoop, I misread your post and thought it said Asylum, not Origins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does the licensing for car games work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 02:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just wondering how do developers get the rights to use version cars and how complicated is the actual process?

It seems pretty simple, but then you have games that hardly feature any cars vs games with hundreds of cars, then a huge franchise like Forza not being able to use Porsches, then Need for Speed not having Ferraris for like a decade, but now their new game has them. Do developers pay to use a certain brand of car, and then use whatever they want, or do they have to pay by each car?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 01:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long Halloween is an absolute must. Read it right away. 

Arkham City is actually a phenomenal Batman story, a super fun game, and a great expansion and compliment to Arkham Asylum, so definitely get right into that as soon as possible. Don't bother with Arkham Origins.

Then just go through the recommended reading on this sub teddies sidebar  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 13:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Home is run no more  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 05:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like Thirst  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-01 15:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and my friends watch this movie together at least once a year. So much fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-01 14:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This whole trailer is definitely a lot 'softer' and less brutal than the red band trailer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 11:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neil deGrasse Tyson and Kevin Smith are the best ones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 10:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa this looks insane and huge!

The first one worked so well because of the simple, no bullshit, real time plot and structure, so I was a little worried that this one would have too many characters and subplots and just end up being silly. 

But this looks just as action packed and awesome as the first. One of my most anticipated movies of next year for sure. These guys know how to take what could be a relatively generic and boring martial arts action movie idea and make it insane and fresh and unique.

Although I'm a little bummed that Joe Taslim can't return, but even more excited that they managed to work Yayan Ruhian back into the mix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-29 02:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Audis are the sexiest cars in the world, but I really prefer them with silver trim around the grill and windows </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 16:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit Scotty, you weren't supposed to know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 15:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait for him to reach his final form and become SnoopLord </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 12:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The T-rex was not originally in the cargo hold. Watch again when it gets captured. It gets put into a cage, which sits on the deck of the ship. 

When the boat crashes into the dock, you can see the cage all busted up and broken open, and some of the chewed up crew members managed to lock it down in the cargo hold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 11:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 09:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Less than one minute of screen time? What does he even do in the movie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 08:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also that scene from DKR was clearly an homage to the opening scene in Licence to Kill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 08:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All he said was he didn't want to hype Louis CK on his show. Seemed more like a joke about promoting another comedian on his show rather than talking shit about him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 07:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've just found Louis CK's [apartment](http://i.imgur.com/tX3kPJM.jpg?1) now on Google Maps thanks to this comment. I feel creepy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 07:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just watched the Chris Rock episode yesterday and I didn't hear anything like that 

EDIT: It was the Carl Reiner/Mel Brooks episode and it just seemed like a joke about Seinfeld not wanting to promote another comedian on his show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
