<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5170</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 03:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Is Why We Need Obamacare: ...the kind of catastrophe facing people like Richard Streeter, 47, a truck driver and recreational vehicle repairman in Eugene, Ore. His problem isnt Obamacare, but a tumor in his colon that may kill him because Obamacare didnt come quite soon enough. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 03:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 20:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a former digg user who left and came to reddit for exactly the reasons you mention, I agree with you 100% about the likely sad end of this whole fiasco. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 20:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @crabnuts--sadly, I think you've hit it exactly, both the methods and the results of these political forums being destroyed by vocal minorities and easily cowed moderators. It's a shame the redditors are so naive. Just let the rest of us know where the good guys are headed, okay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 20:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do agree that eliminating all sources that build on other sources sacrifices analysis and additional insight from the secondary source, but with that caveat, I like your other suggestions. These mods should be acting as mods driven by a transparent policy, not wholesale censors of sources. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 20:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if the mods understand what journalism is. Mother Jones is a model of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 20:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, it has crossed from moderation into censorship. A political site that censors sources is worse than useless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 20:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree 100%--how can these mods not see that they are absolutely killing the credibility of r/politics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 20:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @synobal--If the censorship of legit sites doesn't end I'll be looking for a new political sub. How is USPOLITICS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 19:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strongly agree that opinion should be included along with news.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 19:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is that Obama needs to fight for his judicial nominees because these nominations have real-world consequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 18:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the kind words. I came to reddit after the demise of digg, where, for awhile, substantive discussion did seem possible. I can understand reddit moderators' efforts to prevent flame wars and self-promotion, but I think you need to be careful about banning news and commentary sources. It certainly makes you look biased, even if that is not your intent.

At the very least, the process of determining which sources are legit, and why, should be transparent. What are your criteria for inclusion as a source, and why? Anything short of that looks like prejudice or a hidden agenda.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 18:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Insurance policies not worth keeping </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 18:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Insurance policies not worth keeping </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 18:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A War on the Poor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 08:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Public Policy Polling: Republicans see Cruz as Party Leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 06:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Public Policy Polling: Republicans see Cruz as Party Leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 06:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 06:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, i use reddit to try to disseminate information I find valuable, in the areas of politics, health, tech, and women's issues. I don't think reddit should block access to any news source, frankly. It's members should decide the source's value, via upvotes or downvotes. I thought that was the whole idea of reddit -- largely unmediated access to information by its members. I don't want some redditor, whose agenda I have no clue about, making decisions about what I can see on reddit or what I can post from legitimate news sources. 

You may quibble about Huffpo --I'd disagree with you on excluding it -- but Salon and especially Mother Jones? Really? That looks to me like a conservative or libertarian bias -- and again, bias is just the opposite of what reddit should be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 01:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @Burkey -- Now it's starting to make sense. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 01:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @asdjrocky-- Very well put. Agree 100%. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 01:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @catmoon-- How does banning legitimate, award-winning political journalism sites improve quality standards? Seems to me to harm the quality of the subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 01:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @montreal01--Not an open system with this type of censorship going on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 01:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To quote the article, "Its the /r/politics moderators who dont understand Reddit or comprehend their role."

WTF is going on here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 17:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @Turicus--But the boots helped, as the other anecdote about the silk shell demonstrates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 17:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "One thing I've learned is that one person's illogical belief is another person's survival skill. And nothing is more logical than trying to survive."

Great insights in this piece, which deserves a wider audience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where is the outrage over employer-sponsored coverage in the rate shock debate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 16:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the iPod President Crashed: Obama's Broken Technology Promise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 23:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the iPod President Crashed: Obama's Broken Technology Promise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 23:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I'm showing my son mercy:" the story of an Oklahoman's abortion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 23:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LA Times: Another Obamacare Horror Story Debunked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 23:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Uproar Over Insurance 'Cancellation' Letters: Republicans were apparently furious that government would dare intrude on an insurance companys freedom to offer a terrible product to desperate people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 23:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Foxs Greta Van Susteren Does Actual Journalism On Junk Insurance Story, Showing a Cancelee That Her Old Cancelled Policy Was No Good </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 15:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans are treating Obamas if you like your plan you can keep it pitch as ... the original swindle. But the focus-grouped deception they hope to perpetrate against seniors is far more egregious. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 14:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newt's Revenge: Child Labor Makes a Comeback -- ...over the 50 states, one of the things you see is how concerted an effort it is, and how cookie-cutter the legislation is  and how much its not being driven by individual legislators, but by a national corporate lobby. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 14:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Libertarians in 2013: The Even Whiter, Wealthier, WASPier Bastion of Republican Party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 14:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP Gov. Kasich Says There 'Seems To Be A War On The Poor' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 16:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 20:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @brotherwayne-- I agree. I just wanted to hear how he articulated it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the New Economy, Everyone is an Indentured TaskRabbit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 20:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 17:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @EducatedHottentot--Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Miners deaths arent a Halloween thrill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 16:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOPs Obamacare conspiracy: Sabotage from the inside--Eight ways Republicans tried to sabotage Obamacare -- and intentionally undermine the law of the land </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-26 22:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ross Douthats right-wing fairy tale: What the New York Times columnist misses about Obamacare and the Republican war on the poor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-26 22:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The fallacy of the Republican moderate: Stop being nostalgic for the right </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-26 22:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul May Place Hold On Yellen Nomination </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 17:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans: Immigration Reform Must Die Because of the Shutdown! Republicans now say they are going to refuse to do anything on immigration reform, not because they oppose it, but because they're feeling spiteful toward President Obama: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 17:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harry Reid: 'We're Not Going To Have A Grand Bargain' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 02:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black Barneys Shopper Says Cops Asked Her What Are You Doing Here in Manhattan? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 01:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AR-15 Reported Stolen fFrom GOP Rep's Unlocked Garage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 15:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Fix the Glitches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 15:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Durbin: House leader told Obama 'I cannot even stand to look at you' - The Hill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 15:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 19:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great piece on the government's counterproductive Enterprise IT practices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 19:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great article that puts the messed-up launch in its bureaucratic context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AG Holder: Number Of Mass Shootings In U.S. Have Tripled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 05:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 19:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A great article, and scary, in that there doesn't seem to be a readily apparent route to thwart the combo of Tea Partiers and big money guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican Collapse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 17:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Houston Chronicle Expresses Regrets For Endorsing Cruz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 05:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bittman -- Should You Eat Chicken? Salmonella at the Source </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-16 16:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No, there isnt a New American Center </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 21:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anonymous targets town that forced out alleged rape victim and her family </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 05:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anonymous targets town that forced out alleged rape victim and her family </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 05:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anonymous targets town that forced out alleged rape victim and her family </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 05:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IMF Chief Calls Out Republican Debt Ceiling Truthers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 05:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The delusional and dangerous Paul Ryan: First he was the linchpin of a GOP deal with Obama, now he wants the birth control coverage mandate out of the ACA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 21:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blue-state nation: Maybe its time for cities to secede </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 20:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Georgia Tech fraternity creates disgusting guide to luring your rapebait </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 07:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 23:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The stand by conservatives that led to the current crisis was the outgrowth of a long-running effort, waged by a galaxy of well-funded groups, to undo President Obamas health care law." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dems move to force Republicans to reopen the government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 17:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP House Can't Claim to Speak for America: "The ACA is law. End of story. The House Republicans' attempt to nullify a duly-enacted law violates the norms of our constitutional system. It is reckless economically and an egregious affront to our democratic form of government." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 17:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox and Friends host thinks Hispanic colleague grew up on tacos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 06:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 19:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article:

"Ive seen no conservatives, anywhere, actually question the morality of debt-limit extortion." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boehner: Obama Stubbornly Refusing to End the Crisis I Created (Borowitz) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 21:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas fundamentalists pushing public schools to teach that Garden of Eden is science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 15:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corporate money is the power behind the Tea Party and that corporate money has one goal -- the creation of a...subjugated population grateful for whatever scraps fall from the table. To accomplish this, the corporate money...had to disable the institutions of self-government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 07:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cruz warns shutdown could lead to terrorist attacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 07:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama's Debt-Ceiling Dilemma: Which law should he obey? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 04:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Boehner Could End Shutdown Today If He Wanted To </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 03:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Ten Republicans Who Shut Down the Government: Here are the "Terrible Ten" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 03:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> R.I. GOP under fire for gun raffle, even in own ranks/ Poll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 00:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ...the crazier a Republican member of Congress is, the less they have to worry about political consequences...the only question...is which candidate in a Republican primary is the most extreme, hates Obama the most, and can talk with the most contempt about liberals and government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 00:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Krugman: The Economics and Politics of Chaos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 06:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the normal course...in a constitutional and democratic republic, parties win elections on the issues that matter to them. They pass laws or repeal them by majority vote. The tea party could not muster such a majority...Do what we want, they said, or we will render the country ungovernable. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 06:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Krugman: The 1% has created a monster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 01:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An anxious Fox News blames the shutdown on Obama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 01:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 23:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a great read. It is written in the style a reporter would use if the shutdown were happening in another country--no euphemisms or false equivalencies==the Tea Party Republicans are an "extremist rump." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 21:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hypocrisy, thy name is Republicans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't blame the Tea Oarty for the shutdown- blame Boehner: the majority "leader" needs to lead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 20:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 19:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @infinitejest -- You are either very naive or very dishonest. The same bill that the Republicans stripped the food stamps from contained huge subsidies to agribusiness, which they had no trouble spending money on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What kind of world do these [Republicans] live in? ...prepared to bring our entire system of government to a halt in order to prevent sick people from getting access to treatment? What hallucinating, self-serving monsters have you become? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 18:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOPs most shameful shutdown moment:NH Republican Rep Compares Obamacare to Brutal Fugitive Slave Act </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 17:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those Banana Republicans:"Many House Republicans do not want the government to shut down and would probably vote for the Senate's clean bill if given half a chance. Their unwillingness to speak out against the extreme faction in their party is shameful." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 16:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The House GOP.s Legislative Strike: Republicans are careening towards a shutdown, and possibly toward provoking a sovereign debt crisis after that, as the inevitable product of a conscious party strategy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 08:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Threatening to destroy America is no way to negotiate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 19:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atul Gawande: Obamacare and Obstructionism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 17:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rebrls Without a Clue in the House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 17:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudi cleric says women who drive risk damaging their ovaries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 17:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your False-Equivalence Guide to the Days Ahead: ...any story that presents the disagreements as a "standoff," a "showdown," a "failure of leadership," a sign of "partisan gridlock," or any of the other usual terms for political disagreement, represents a failure of journalism... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 06:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All the Older Single Ladies in Poverty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 05:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All the Older Single Ladies in Poverty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 05:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Are These Men Taking Up Too Much Space On The Train, Plane, Supreme Court Photo... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 08:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Millennials, unite! You have been cheated. Do something about it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 07:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Subsidizing farmers but not the poor still evil: "The special value of the farm debate is that by combining the GOPs opposition to handouts for the poor with its support for handouts to the nonpoor, it exposes the partys deeper moral views. I find them quite ugly." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 18:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Popular Science: Why We're Shutting Off Our Comments--The cynical work of undermining bedrock scientific doctrine is now being done beneath our own stories, within a website devoted to championing science. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 09:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Cruz Fauxlibuster Includes Nazi Reference Because Ted Cruz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 05:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sorry, the latest anti-Obamacare article to go viral is totally wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 18:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nauseating Health Care Idiocy from Forbes: Forbes' most-read story of the day (with over 26,000 Facebook shares and 3400 tweets as I write this) is simply false. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 18:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm young and healthy, and having health insurance saved me $200,000 when I got shot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 20:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NRA's LaPierre on Navy Yard Shooting: 'There Weren't Enough Good Guys With Guns' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-22 22:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The GOP's "Hunger Games" vision of America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-21 20:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elections used to have consequences </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-21 20:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Horrifying anti-Obamacare ad warns that Uncle Sam wants in your uterus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 15:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Horrifying anti-Obamacare ad warns that Uncle Sam wants in your uterus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 15:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans: We were too nice to the hungry, but we've fixed that </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 15:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Koch-Backed Conservatives Go Pro-Cervical Cancer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 06:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Men Dead In Michigan Road Rage Shootout, Police Say; Both Had Concealed Carry Permits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 06:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Same Company Did Background Checks for Aaron Alexis, Edward Snowden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 05:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obamas bold but dangerous 2nd term philosophy: YOLO! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-16 18:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Men Parade Around Wisconsin Farmers Market Carrying AR-15 Rifles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-14 01:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three GOP States Block Same-Sex Spousal Benefits For National Guard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 18:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even the Police Chief Is Afraid of George Zimmerman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 07:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reflecting on the Colorado recalls - Public Policy Polling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 06:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Summers Dossier and Why He's a Bad Choice for Fed Head </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 19:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Krugman: The Wonk Gap -- Why GOP reps literally do not know what they're talking about </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 19:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas business creates decal of woman bound and tied to bring in new business </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-08 18:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Great Divide: Why Janet Yellen, Not Larry Summers, Should Lead the Fed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 17:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mother Jones: Snowden disclosures finally hit 12 on a scale of 10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 06:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Intervention in Syria is like walking into a bar in a foreign country, seeing a brutal fight and saying: Why not hit me instead? ... Already Shiite forces in Iraq are aiming to hit American targets; we will endure terror at home, and surrender freedoms to the intelligence-surveillance state. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 18:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Krugman: Years of tragic waste </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 17:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McCoonnell's created an Obamacare Frankenstein's Monster, and it could end his career </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 17:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The American Jewish Cocoon--Peter Beinart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 04:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marco Rubio Demands That HHS Cancel Obamacare Advertising </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-04 16:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These Documents Show What an Attempt to Sabotage Obamacare Looks Like </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-04 05:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Signing people up for Obamacare? House Republicans have some questions for you: Health and Human Services described the letter as a shameful attempt to intimidate groups doing Obamacare enrollment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 01:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Signing people up for Obamacare? House Republicans have some questions for you: Health and Human Services described the letter as a shameful attempt to intimidate groups doing Obamacare enrollment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 01:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Friedmans bizarre fantasy: Heres who he needs to meet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 18:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge Who Gave Light Sentence to Teens Rapist Wont Resign Despite Protests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 06:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
