<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8959</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 18:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If people would vote with their money instead of voting for an article on Reddit maybe Verizon and AT T would listen. If you upvoted this link from a Verizon device you are directly contributing to the problem. "I don't have a choice" doesn't fly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dexter Morgan vs. Hannibal Lecter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 05:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dexter tracks Lecter to a busy hospital before realizing Lecter is hunting him. Only one of them leave the hospital alive. Who survives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The more you weigh, the stronger and more intelligent you become. All other health risks remain the same. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 03:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 17:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genie wishes Galactus can only sing Backstreet Boys songs, nothing else. Match over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which superhero or villain would have the most popular reality television show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 22:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Genie (Aladdin) vs. Galactus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 19:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genie is completely free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm stuck in line at a grocery store and I've already loudly complained that they need to open more registers. What else can I do to show everyone how valuable my time is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 07:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superman vs. Dr. Manhattan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 05:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Implied powers from comics and movies included. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Link with the Master Sword vs. Jon Snow with an iron broadsword and his dire wolf. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 18:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Random encounter in a deserted forest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 19:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bruce Wayne. Not Batman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Bride from Kill Bill vs. Bruce Wayne </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 16:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cage match. Hanging throughout cage is one katana, one bo staff and one small knife. No other weapons or armor allowed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silver Surfer vs. Wonder Woman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 16:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> City street fight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every canine in the world versus every feline in the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 02:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All breeds, including in the wild, suddenly go to war. Who wins? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 08:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White guys were the OGs of illegal immigration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rambo vs. Bourne </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 08:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two square mile deserted wooded island, only one leaves alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "In many states, particularly since 2010, Republicans have passed new laws requiring voters to show identification cards and restricting early-voting hours, arguing that these methods would help prevent voter fraud." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 02:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All living and nonliving things in the universe exist only when you are physically observing them in some manner. Otherwise they completely cease to exist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 05:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Batman vs. Sagat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 04:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Street fight, opponents run into each other unexpectedly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 17:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of states don't require permits for conceal carry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> W.Va. Senate Approves Bill to Not Require Handgun Permits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 05:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles and Master Splinter vs. unarmed Bruce Wayne </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 04:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Street fight, Wayne has no Batman gear to utilize and no formal weapons with him. Turtles and Splinter have their respective weaponry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 04:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saudi Arabia dictates virtually the entire economy of the western world. By the simple act of refusing to reduce production, OPEC smashed the profit lines of every single western energy company and has so far, since October 2014, sent numerous shale oil producers into bankruptcy in the US alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United States, Canada, Britain, France, Australia, Japan and Germany vs. Russia, China, Iran, Saudi Arabia, Egypt, Mexico, Venezuela, Pakistan and Turkey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 09:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All other nations remain absolute neutral with no involvement. Documented military capability only, no assumptions. US team is A, Russia team B. Who would win in this WWIII scenario? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tetsuo Shima vs. Wonder Woman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 15:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WW travels to Neo Tokyo for vacation and is attacked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every fictional character Brad Pitt has ever played form a team. Can they defeat Batman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 10:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 11:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.yale.edu/ynhti/curriculum/units/1980/2/80.02.07.x.html

If you ever want to educate yourself on the subject you are clearly completely ignorant of, start here. Then debate it. While your approach of arguing without facts is unfortunately growing in popularity, I'd advise against it personally. But to each their own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 10:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd also like to point out, these were uncovered with a mortar and pestle, several knives, source flint and a large knapped flint piece over a foot in length within a three foot spot as we were uprooting a dead tree. I cleared the debris, photographed and labeled the site with compass and GPS detail and stopped digging. The historical society is sending a contact to the property to assess and continue excavation. Thanks to the person who commented, I felt I should add that information less I am confronted by another baseless accusation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 10:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did document the entire dig and have since turned it over to the state historical society. Congrats, you're quick to wrong judgement and failed miserably. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Incredible Hulk vs. An army consisting of one of every type of Pokemon, all max evolved </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 10:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confrontation in downtown New York, Hulk is surrounded in a surprise ambush by the Pokemon militia. Could they defeat him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As an anthropology student, I spent years searching for Paleolithic objects. I finally made my first find. I found these buried on my fathers property while assisting with landscaping. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 09:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 16:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not sure if serious.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ozymandias vs. Lex Luthor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 10:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If each of them developed a plan to destroy the other, who would most likely survive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 08:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Running a sweatshop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charlie vs. Mac vs. Dee vs. Dennis vs. Frank (Always Sunny Death Match) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 06:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fight takes place in Paddys Pub, to the death, using anything found in the pub on more than one episode. Who survives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 04:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Bourne would decimate Ali so badly ancient ancestors of Ali would simultaneously feel blinding pain.
2. Same
3. Same
4. Same
5. Ali would last longer because Bourne would kill Wayne before the bell stopped ringing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 04:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mac OS mech would look the best but it's tight jeans and scarf would cause it problems. Windows Mech would crash repeatedly.

Linux would harvest their souls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 04:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ayn Rand loses at life. Outmatched in intellect by the metal dog, she blames everyone else for her failures and flees leaving only the others playing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 04:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Action wins. Pens and paper burn by the action of arson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ryu vs. Bane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 04:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mountaintop fight  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the Weapon X project infused a kryptonite mix into Wolverines adamantium, could he defeat Superman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 21:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rudy Giulianis sad self-destruction: How Americas mayor became just another GOP sidewalk lunatic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 19:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silver Surfer vs. Darkseid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 18:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superman vs. Professor Xavier, Phoenix, Magneto and Quicksilver </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 07:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superman ambushed in city street, does not know any of these people or what their powers are in advance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deadpool and Wolverine vs. Wonder Woman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 01:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fighting in open field </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every time you get something you want in life, you lose something you love. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 23:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tyrion Lannister vs. Frodo Baggins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 21:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To the death battle in a forest, no assistance from outside characters, Frodo does not possess the Ring for this fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Telekinetic Stephen Hawking vs. Pyrokinetic Nancy Grace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 02:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fight takes place in Times Square on New Years eve </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Phoenix and Wonder Woman vs. Magneto and Brainiac </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 08:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fight takes place in Brainiacs ship </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wolverine and Storm vs The Fantastic Four </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 19:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fighting takes place in desert scenario </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Batman vs Spiderman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 16:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One day to prepare, fight is in a city street </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lobo vs Ultron </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 04:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superman and Wonder Woman vs Iron Man and Hulk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 01:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 team street brawl, no advance preparation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Manhattan vs. Galactus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 16:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every Jedi from Star Wars vs every wizard and witch from Harry Potter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 16:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The cast of Super Smash Bros vs The Avengers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 04:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> City street brawl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I try to appreciate the genius of Kanye West but I accidentally keep realizing he has no talent. How can I stop being racist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 16:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bert vs Ernie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 06:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To the death, cage match </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All religious people throughout the world suddenly turn into zombies, hunting the still living non believers. Do the living stand a chance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 04:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tony Soprano vs Walter White </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 05:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pikachu vs Jake the dog from Adventure Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 04:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fighting in an open field, no rules </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas governor rescinds order protecting gay state workers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 01:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why hasn't the automotive industry found alternatives to rubber tires? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 20:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like every asp[ect of the car has evolved, but the tire has remained essentially the same for decades. Environmental concerns aside, they are dangerous in that they can explode, flatten etc. It seems like someone would have developed an alternative to this. Is there a reason we haven't changed to some other form of tire? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pennywise the Clown vs. Freddy Krueger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 07:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 17:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found what appears to be a preserved trilobite? Will exposure to air damage it? Can anyone tell me what it is and why it preserved this way? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 02:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every Captain from every Star Trek series in a Battle Royale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 04:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To the death, only one can survive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservatives want to rewrite the history of the Crusades for modern political ends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 16:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daenerys Targaryen and Drogon vs. Hiccup and Toothless </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 03:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arena match, gladiator style. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 07:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any other info? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The cast of the Mortal Kombat series vs. the cast of the Street Fighter series </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 06:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Open air street brawl, characters forgive storyline rivalries to work together, everyone in at once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Packing tape should whiten when stressed or ripped so I can find the end of it without endlessly running my fingernail over the surface. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 20:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 05:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If people are only allowed to discuss what they are considered "expert" in, New ideas would practically cease to exist and innovation would die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 05:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Climate change movement". That's like saying "Round earth movement" or "gravity movement". Science isn't a movement. The idiots that dispute it, however, are certainly one in my book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 05:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is propaganda to rally support around sinking the one act that protects us from paying for another bank bailout. The Dodd Frank act is not anti gun. It's anti bank bailout. The fact they are going this far to get people to turn on it does it's working.

Before believing this crap and knee jerking to it, think about it. You are being played right now. I'm a firm supporter of gun owners rights and I see through this B.S. immediately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do people continue to dispute mans impact on global climate despite what appears to be absolute and certain evidence? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 00:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 22:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calling me a conspiracy theorist for believing oil is a factor in war is like calling me a conspiracy theorist for believing water sustains life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 07:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your comment has more edge than a U2 album. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 07:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When drinks cost more than dignity, theaters have gone too far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 07:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is brilliant. This has absolutely never been done by millions of people every day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 07:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching Dexter doesn't make you a forensic expert. And meat packing plants undergo health inspections constantly. Human blood would be detected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 07:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This will never work in a venue worth visiting. Ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 07:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My experience, scummy people work at Dunkin Donuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wolverine vs. T-1000 model Terminator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 20:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They run into one another in a subway station and start fighting. No rules, no one helping either of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 01:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dignity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dwayne 'The Rock' Johnson vs. Vin Diesel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 01:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Street brawl, anything goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Presidents Jimmy Carter, Ronald Reagan and Mikhail Gorbachev all said that they believe in UFO's </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 22:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 18:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I think these responses appear to be incorrect. Groupon is actually not making money. It's losing money on a massive scale. But that fact aside, they do not charge marketing fees up front, and advertising is an indirect profiting mechanism. They typically promise businesses an increase in revenue in exchange for a cut of the revenue they bring. There is a significant problem with this business model, they don't pay up front meaning businesses provide the service, Groupon collects the money and businesses do not get the money immediately. 

Businesses essentially front the service and are paid by Groupon in lump sum afterwards. For some businesses this is fine, for others, this is difficult to manage. The criticism lately is that often businesses find the increase in customers does not cover the loss of revenue between fronting the service and the decreased rate of said service provided.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I went for a walk in the woods as it snowed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 18:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 06:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, if they are fed enough Kardashian in between news breaks, I think they'll go along with anything at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 20:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably? You either have facts specific to your claim or you don't. Which is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 20:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on what data? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 20:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Virginia is open carry and you don't see that anywhere. It's a responsibility that could be abused, sure, but the facts show it isn't. Dumbasses with drivers licenses concern me far more. A drunk college student with keys in his hand is a much scarier scenario. Any responsibility can be abused. Living in fear of that possibility or placing unnecessary restrictions on the whole to try and prevent these abuses is absurd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 19:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "to stupid"

My sides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 18:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meant to address to the tisajc alt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 18:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it not true? Is Boehner not doing this? Is it made up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 18:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the same thing. They prevented Obama from helping the majority of this country for 6 years, 4 of which they based their principle behavior on the act of absolute obstruction and now they pledge themselves at the feet of a foreign leader? It honestly does sound treasonous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 18:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 18:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. I'm a democrat. I'm liberal on many things, like protecting myself. I'm confused why this is even an issue - people should have that right. Someone who intends to rampage with a weapon is going to do it whether the weapon is legal to possess at the time or not. Those of us who would prefer to have the chance to survive the rampage should have the option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 18:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And privatize the remains, yep. But he apparently feels appeasing interests of US citizens is second to appeasing interests of a war-mongering leader of a foreign country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boehner, Netanyahu conspire to push war on Iran </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 17:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's something a person can admit to that will forever give you a negative impression of them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 05:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 02:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 00:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Average 7 year old is around 50 lb. As strong as he is, he couldn't survive a pile-on. If they just started swarming him, what would he do? His ethics alone would make him hesitate to strike first, so they'll definitely get the first moves in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Completely unarmed/uncostumed Bruce Wayne vs. 100 7 year old girls with sharp pencils </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 23:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cage match. Everyone in at the same time. Wayne has nothing, the swarm of girls have writing instruments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 23:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They blocked our President for 6 years and are now promising legislation to the leader of a foreign power. I can't find any precedent for this ever occurring in the US. Or any other country for that matter. It sounds almost  like a form of treason when read in plain context with no fluff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Congress invites Netanyahu, Obama blindsided </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 21:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 16:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The new title is stupid as shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 08:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being dropped in a pool of acid would be quick but would also suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 08:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read that the brain can continue interpreting signals for up to 30 minutes after a beheading, so that kind of scares me. I do not want to sit in  some basket thinking "this sucks" for thirty minutes before I go... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 08:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds....absolutely amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 08:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assassination. If someone has to go through that much trouble to cut me off quickly, I did something really awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your preferred means of dying? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 08:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 20:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not know that. I'd think that's pretty telling... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 20:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd think he would be a huge disappoint to his donors as well. I could be wrong, I don't live in LA, but from the perspective of one who lives in the north east, he has achieved nothing but negative sentiment and only appears to get a headline when he has something outrageously stupid to say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 04:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ego. Like Romney, he honestly thinks he has a chance. He surrounds himself in yes men, only watches Fox News and has constructed a house of mirrors around himself. It's really pathetic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Bobby Jindal has stolen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 04:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 02:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Homeschooling is making a great deal of sense to me all of a sudden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 02:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see the educational system is still horrible a decade after I escaped from it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
