<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5807</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drunk fish convince sober ones to follow them around. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 08:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 06:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for letting me know. Looks like it was published in Nature Photonics.

Link from the bottom of the article:

http://www.nature.com/nphoton/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nphoton.2014.95.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists discover how to turn light into matter after 80-year quest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 21:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 18:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adorable. I wonder if she also stepped around Mrs. Peabody's azaleas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gluten intolerance may not exist: A double-blinded, placebo-controlled study and a scientific review find insufficient evidence to support non-celiac gluten sensitivity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 15:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Archaeologists think they've found the wreck of Christopher Columbus' flagship, the Santa Maria. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 15:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers induce lucid dreaming in subjects by applying electrical current to their brains. The technique could potentially be adapted to allow PTSD sufferers to control frequent nightmares. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 15:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research explains why Antarctica is not warming as much as the other continents. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 21:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New species of metal-eating plant discovered in the Philippines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 00:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new analysis in PLoS ONE finds that female genitalia in the animal kingdom are massively understudied, which likely stems from aged sexual stereotypes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 16:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers image the spread of pesticides in snails and shrimp in order to understand how they are affecting these aquatic species. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 18:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Public science funding generates substantial returns to the private sector, a new report claims. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 01:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are You Really Gluten-Intolerant? Maybe Not. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 17:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chiropractors' spine-chilling warnings about computers, phones and pancakes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 20:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A review of archaeological records shows that Neanderthals were just as advanced as humans, making it increasingly likely that they were assimilated into our species through interbreeding, not driven to extinction. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 23:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study shows the first functional replacement of muscle tissue in humans. Surgeons implanted extracellular matrix derived from pig bladder into wounds. Over time, muscle grew around it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 23:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have built an 'off switch' for the brain. Their technique uses light sensitive proteins to shut down neurons. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 16:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Birds in areas with high radiation contamination around Chernobyl produce more antioxidants. It's the first known example of wild animals adapting to chronic radiation exposure. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 20:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 01:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see your point and raise you a "shit ton."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have long wondered why our atmosphere has so little of the noble gas Xenon. They've just found a whole bunch of it in Earth's core. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 21:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arecibo Observatory Detects Mysterious, Energetic Radio Burst </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 17:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 16:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like the link is at the bottom of the article: http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature13027.html

The research is in Nature, so it's paywalled, obviously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A possible cure for ebola virus infection has been discovered. A molecule called BCX4430 rescued 17 of 18 monkeys after they were infected with the virus. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 15:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another reason not to use Apple Maps... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 02:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 23:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure thing! Sorry, I didn't read the new rules. Whoops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ten things you might not know about particle accelerators </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 17:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would You Have Sex with a Total Stranger? An Inside Look at the Study That Found Out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 15:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have shown they can rapidly produce large quantities of graphene using a bath of inorganic salts and an electric current. It's a step towards mass production of the wonder material. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 15:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Intravenously Administered Ketamine Shown to Reduce Symptoms of Chronic Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 21:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cannabis use is quantitatively associated with nucleus accumbens and amygdala abnormalities in young adult recreational users. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 21:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astronomers Find First Earth-Sized Exoplanet in Habitable Zone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 20:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Men's beard fashions may be guided by Darwinian selection. Both beards and clean-shaven faces become more appealing when they are rare. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 18:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Positron emission tomography, a type of brain scan, could help predict if patients will wake from a vegetative state. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 03:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> By tracking brain activity when an animal stops to look around its environment, neuroscientists at Johns Hopkins University believe they can mark the birth of a memory. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 23:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For a Happy Marriage, Stay Well Fed: Low blood glucose levels correlate to greater levels of aggression and anger between spouses. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 21:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two research teams have unveiled a quantum-information analogue of the transistor, a major step towards the development of practical quantum computers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 04:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If he looks stupid, he probably is: In a new study, both males and females were able to accurately evaluate the intelligence of men simply by viewing photos of their faces. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 16:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Positive Association of Video Game Playing with Left Frontal Cortical Thickness in Adolescents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 23:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 69% of respondents support extending disability protections to obese individuals, according to a new survey. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 20:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study reveals the power and scale of Earth's cataclysmic collision with a 30-mile-wide object some 3.26 billion years ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 19:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10 of the Greatest Myths in Psychology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 16:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study highlights that people are often mistaken in how spending our money might benefit our lives. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 04:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
