<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8395</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 17:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Swear down. It isn't built yet and there were two Croatian men building it. We asked and they said it was ok. I can provide proof if needed but they are filming GoT in Dubrovnik right now. I also met Brienne today so check my profile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We found a Game Of Thrones Season 4 set piece in Dubrovnik, Croatia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 17:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The famous "Margherti" scene from Inglorious Basterds is a reference to the director of "Cannibal Apocalypse" Antonio Marghereti. He is also a character in the game Dead Island. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 14:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 12:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was a solid summer blockbuster and was surprised at how much I enjoyed myself. I had read a few reviews and the concept interested me so I gave it a watch. The plot, characters and setting were able to hold my attention throughout the film and I thought the ending was probably one of the best Disney have ever done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never tried this position when gaming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-05 13:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL A man died when playing a game of Russian Roulette with a automatic pistol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 23:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 15:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The room is pitch black, the only light shown is from the computer monitor. A large dark figure is at the chair, light gleaming off his glasses while he types in a large red font "Half Life 3 is not going to happen"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schindler is going up in the world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-12 22:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-12 22:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yo mama so fat that Obi Wan Kenobi said "that ain't no moon... that yo mama". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 16:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you not scared of your flat being possessed due to it being over a Mexican burial ground?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
