<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4000</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your stance on movie remakes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 13:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you love em, hate em. What's your opinion on this growing trend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the farthest you've gone to maintain a lie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 08:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 08:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I blame peter molyneux, he just kept over-hyping his game, setting the bar too high. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 08:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a fan of Final Fantasy, I don't think FF7 is a great as everyone says. Apart from graphical improvements and stuff like mini-games, it played just like the others. The magic system was creative but not that special and open world aspects had been in the other entries. The story wasn't bad, it was good, but not that special. I still think its a great game, I still play it to this day, but I don't think it's as game changing as others have called it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What video games do you think don't meet up to their reputation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 08:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 15:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now I'm afraid I have somewhat of a mess on my hands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 13:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude the people who look at you with disgust, fuck those guys. When i was 15 i used to have a small red-afro, people used to call me carrot-top. You just have to learn to ignore it, and then you don't hear it anymore. I used to be introverted too, I'm still afraid to order a pizza over the phone. You just need to realize your special, there's no one like you, and there never will be. Just knowing that will help you be more outgoing. I'm doing this, and the girls are starting to swoop in for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the beginning of promising trilogy... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 13:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 12:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buck Naked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 12:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah make society your bitch, if you're into that sort of thing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 12:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I do think it's a shame they shutdown LucasArts, that doesn't mean the end of Star Wars games, they can still license. Some of the the best games were developed by others. Jedi Outcast, Jedi Academy, Empire at War, Battlefront, and Knights of the old Republic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 12:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While you make good points, I still think it is. The license system is deep and while it matches the sphere grid I think it takes the idea to a new level. But I don't think it's perfect, example is Vaan. You could take him out of the whole game and it wouldn't change much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 10:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why'd you delete FF12? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 09:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy shit you're me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 09:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won't lie, Bioshock is a great game, so are the sequels. But I never understood all the hype. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some movies where you are rooting against the main characters/protagonists? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 09:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and it doesn't just to have to be movies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 08:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shenmue, if you don't it you really should youtube it. Final Fantasy series, even though I don't favor the new entries I do respect how amazing the graphics are. Knights of the Old republic, one of if not the best series of Sci-fi RPG's. Heavy Rain, while I liked Indigo Prophecy I actually cared about the characters in Heavy Rain with all my heart, so much so I had trouble getting a sad/"bad" ending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 08:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "you will sit here, and you will f*cking watch this!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 08:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star Wars:Jedi Knight. the old games still have the best lightsaber action so I would love to see what they can do now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 08:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is about my dad. I wanna love him, but he wasn't and isn't part of my life that much, so I have trouble loving him. I think he's trying, but i'm not the first kid he wasn't always around for.

P.S. I know the title should be "What's" not "Whats" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats a horrible truth you have in your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 08:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 07:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [dude those it just suck being you?] (http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aeFuq5Q0OXo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 06:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2001: A Space Odyssey. There's so many interpretations out there ranging from the minor details to the overall plot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 06:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first i was like, yeah! Then it asked for money and I was like, Sorry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 01:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Topher Grace? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 00:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4, 5, 2, 3, 6. You don't need 1 because the elevator scene in 2 I think brings you up to speed and almost no plot is carried over. And with this you don't lose the shock value of the Darth Vader father reveal in 5. After that you can consider 2 and 3 a long flashback for how Anakin become evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 12:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was/is your dream job? Unless you always wanted to be a security guard, I'm not saying it's a bad job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 12:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> relax bra, :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 12:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sequel to Office Space </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 12:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Parenthesis, Exponents, Multiplication, Division, Addition, Subtraction. Solve in that order </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 12:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "PC LOAD LETTER? The fuck does that mean?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 11:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Queen - I Want to Break Free </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, What superstitions do you believe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 09:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 07:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wish more people would realize this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 06:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep Shenmue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
