<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9572</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 19:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does it suck?  Is it not accurate?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 01:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good explanation, but how does mutual annihilation result in a Higgs boson (vs. two gamma rays)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 19:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bears ... Beets ... Battle Star Galactica! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 16:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see how this European law can possibly be implemented in a reasonable manner given the number of requests that will eventually be submitted along with their subjectivity.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 15:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is dark energy and how does it work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 20:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Granted the "dark side" of the moon is an incorrect term (should be far side or opposing side), but it's a term that is generally accepted and understood ... and it makes a great name for an album. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 19:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gold is inert to all chemicals it encounters inside the human body, which is probably why it is used in this application. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 16:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead, the [near-infrared laser] light excites the free electrons on the gold nanoparticles and causes them to heat up and generate energy, eventually making the cancer cells to explode.

Your guess is probably correct. The expansion/explosion of the cancer cell is likely caused by liquid within the cell that is heated by the gold particles and turned into vapor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 20:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes KAM1KAZ3, thanks for the link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 20:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are the ISP speed ratings from Netflix: 

http://ispspeedindex.netflix.com/usa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 15:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to Street View scene: 
https://www.google.co.uk/maps/@55.973489,-3.172656,3a,75y,50.01h,62.08t/data=!3m4!1e1!3m2!1sJdIklfy2tDmAMlP8j6dbmg!2e0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 16:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 15:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If all else fails, you can watch using Safari on an iOS device running 4.2 or later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 18:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good idea.  Think I'll send him a tweet with that recommendation for when he visits LA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 19:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess is Apple will be on this very quickly.  It's not good press to let this issue linger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 19:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could it be due to this?

http://www.macrumors.com/2014/05/25/apple-software-update-invalid/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 15:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This method may have been used to get in a quick and easy fix without requiring a restart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 22:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 03:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good editing showing the optical sensor scanning the scene to determine a landing location. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 20:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brand new look?  Reminds me of 50's SciFi space suits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 00:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends a lot on what you want to get out of the meet-up, but yes to all of the items you mentioned for Tom's meet-up.  I think this is one of the many methods Tom uses to build a strong community.  For me its a chance to meet and talk with people who are interested in technology.  Generally I find a connection that I didnt expect to make with a few people, and its not always about technology.  That's what makes these meet-ups interesting.  Tom was a very gracious and engaging host and Jennie was very good at introducing each attendee to the group. 

I asked my wife who also attended for her response to your question and this was her reply: 
 
 Definitely meetups are informal and are what you choose to make of them.  Expect to introduce yourself to people and try to find things you have in common. If you go expecting people to start the conversation for you, you may be disappointed. You dont have to imbibe in alcoholic beverages - some will, some wont but its non-discriminatory. 
 
 The subjects in which we engaged last night included:
 
 * Star Trek
 * Captain America/Agents of Shield
 * A guy walked by with an xkcd shirt on so that made for easy conversation
 * Whether to add an SSD to your computer
 * Whos still using XP (through no fault of their own)
 * The future of journalism (and what does it even mean)
 * Youtube subscriptions vs. Podcast subscriptions (and is it too hard) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 19:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Photo credit to @charltonweb (taken with Glass) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 01:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point regarding the mass of this body more likely putting it in the rogue planet vs. brown dwarf category. It appears the mass threshold for deuterium fusion is not precise and is more of a rule of thumb.  

From http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gas_giant:

 The 13 Jupiter mass (MJ) cutoff is a rule of thumb rather than something of precise physical significance. Larger objects will burn most of their deuterium and smaller ones will burn only a little, and the 13 MJ value is somewhere in between. The amount of deuterium burnt depends not only on mass but also on the composition of the planet, especially on the amount of helium and deuterium present.[5] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 23:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a good diagram showing the closest systems to our Sun including WISE's recent brown dwarf discovery.

http://www.nasa.gov/sites/default/files/pia18003-full_0.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 06:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Question: Is it correct to call a prop driven by electricity a jet engine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 06:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any place that has a good, clear view of the southern sky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 06:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can see it on the east coast as well, but pretty early the morning of April 15, ~1:00 - 3:30 am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 20:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point Rene Ritchie is trying to make is *not* that Apple won't have another product that becomes a hit, but that they won't (at least in the near term) produce a product that has dominated the market and their bottom line like the iPhone has. As Rene puts it, 

 But there will be many, many things that, taken together, make the iPhone much more valuable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 06:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mods, please allow this one to remain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 16:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, comets travel at very high speeds, but so do all the other bodies in space.  A comet's trajectory can be accurately projected for a rendezvous with a spacecraft, until/unless it comes close to the sun which may change its trajectory.  After a close encounter with the sun (if the comet survives) the trajectory will stabilize and can be recalculated. In any case, it is an impressive feat to land a probe on a comet.

Comets are significant in a few ways.  They contain information that sheds light on the formation of our solar system.  Many scientists believe that comets colliding with the Earth during its formation brought much of the water we have to our planet. There are also theories that comets may have brought life or the building blocks of life to the Earth since organic molecules have been detected in them.

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Comet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 05:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evidence of primordial gravitational waves is the leading contender for the announcement.  
http://www.theguardian.com/science/2014/mar/14/gravitational-waves-big-bang-universe-bicep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 16:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a summary of the paper see this article: 

http://phys.org/news/2014-02-massive-neutrinos-cosmological-conundrum.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 16:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Astronomers detected an exploding star in the M82 "Cigar" galaxy. It is most likely a Type Ia supernova, but yet to be confirmed. Type Ia supernovas are created when a white dwarf star collects so much matter from a neighbor that it becomes unstable, collapses upon itself and explodes in very predictable manner.  

Type Ia supernovas are used as "standard candles" to measure distances to very distant galaxies and how fast they are receding from us to determine the rate of acceleration of the universe's expansion.  Since M82 is so close, this is one of the rare Type Ia supernovas that can be observed by amateur astronomers. 

Here's a link to a related article in ARS Technica that might load for you: http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/01/astronomers-rush-to-study-new-nearby-supernova/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 16:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No announcement or release of a 4K Apple display? Apple has a prime opportunity here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 17:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh thephantom, you haven't heard of the emerging Big Band model where various states of matter and energy are represented by harmonics produced by a large collection of saxophones, trumpets and trombones? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 15:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's an article on the exoplanet discovery that's a bit easier to digest:

http://www.geek.com/science/new-impossible-exoplanet-is-11-times-heavier-than-jupiter-1578981/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 07:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh, that is interesting.  CNET changed the article since my original post but didn't note their edit.  I (and CNET) stand corrected. 

Edit: CNET did acknowledge their edit: 
Updated at 9 p.m. PT to correct that the company has ceased sales of the testing kits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 07:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's the other way around. They have stopped selling the kits (to comply with demands made by the FDA) but will continue to provide analysis results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 06:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read replies above to the same question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 05:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom has tweeted that he will not continue with FrameRate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 05:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom's "replacement" will be Mike Elgan.
http://twit.tv/2013/12/05/changes-twit-part-2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 05:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The post from Leo stating his decision to let Tom go was from today.  Tom will remain with TWiT/TNT until the end of December. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 04:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well stated Bishma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 19:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a more technical explanation of ISON's fate.  
http://www.isoncampaign.org/potw-dec02

Bottom line is that ISON was sheared into smaller pieces as it passed through the Sun's corona.  Although some of the larger pieces could be seen exiting the corona, those pieces continued to evaporate/disintegrate (still pretty hot there) and nothing sufficiently large to observe as a comet now remains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-30 01:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now behind a paywall. Any other sources? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-29 16:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two fairly good articles below:

http://earthsky.org/space/big-sun-diving-comet-ison-might-be-spectacular-in-2013
http://www.cnn.com/2013/11/29/us/ison-comet/

Summary: it appears some piece(s) of ISON survived, but how much of it survived and how bright it will be is unknown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 04:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious, what browser and version are you running? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 16:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good on ya Tim Cook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 02:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why am I still not seeing this Google doodle in the US?  Anyone else?

Edit: It finally arrived in the US, two days after New Zealand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 02:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the Doctor moving to the location you've selected?  If not, select a square you want the Doctor to move to.  If there are no blocks, gaps or robots in the way, once a square is selected and outlined in yellow, he will move to it.  If there are obstacles, you need to manipulate the game using the available levers/knobs to make a continuous path. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 16:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this was live test 6.  Doing it once is impressive, but six times? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 16:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this was live test 6.  Doing it once is impressive, but six times? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-10 22:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOCE is expected to begin disintegrating at an altitude of about 80 km.

http://www.spaceflightnow.com/news/n1311/10goce/#.Un_ztJQadzs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-10 20:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's another site that offers satellite tracking info, including for GOCE.  

http://www.satview.org/decay.php

At this moment in time GOCE's altitude is 138.7 km and falling.  Projected to re-enter between 1:30 pm and 7:00 pm EST today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-10 01:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point aero_space.  As orbital decay gets going in earnest, the orbital prediction will become increasingly less accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 23:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, still working for me at this link: 
http://www.foxnews.com/science/interactive/2013/11/08/track-europe-falling-2000-pound-satellite-in-real-time/

Possibly a location dependent block? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 19:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The odds (as of Saturday morning) on the GOCE satellite crashing down on different continents according to British gaming company Ladbrokes:

North and South America: 6/4

Russia and Asia: 2/1

Africa: 4/1

Europe: 5/1

Australia: 10/1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 19:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The odds (as of Saturday morning) on the GOCE satellite crashing down on different continents according to British gaming company Ladbrokes:

North and South America: 6/4

Russia and Asia: 2/1

Africa: 4/1

Europe: 5/1

Australia: 10/1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 19:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm completely sold on it.  For me it's been very reliable.  I feel more secure now that I use a passphrase (e.g. for unlocking after restart or changing security settings) rather than a four digit passcode.  I want all of my future iOS devices to have Touch ID.  I only wish Apple would open up the API to developers.  Maybe over time they will.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 02:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The link takes you to the answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 19:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with your assessment, but I suspect Sony was not pleased with the outcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 15:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Air is largely composed of Nitrogen (~78%) with most of the remainder being Oxygen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 18:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had my black leather iPhone 5 case for about a month and it appears to be holding up well, so far. Here's a photo: 

http://i.imgur.com/flItOH0.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 06:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 13:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A GRB would require the collapsing star be 40 solar masses and meet other special conditions. See http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Supernova </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 05:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can observe supernovae much more often than once every 50 (or even 30) years, but it's very rare to have one occur within our own galaxy. Which type are you referring to, internal or external to the Milky Way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 18:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's just hope it's not too close. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 22:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that is subtle - didn't notice it.  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 19:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just noticed the TM rotating arrow still appears during backups in the Finder window sidebar.  Don't always have a Finder window open, but I can adjust.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 19:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was mildly distracted when I heard my external drive getting accessed, but this feature helped to nullify the distraction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 22:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently (as the earnings call occurs) AAPL is down by 2.59% to 516.14 relative to today's close in after hours trading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 18:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's implied given that it's not feasible to determine the mobile phone habits of all children in the world.  Of more significance is the sample size and margin of error.  From the report:
 This report is based on a nationally representative survey of 1,463 parents of children age 8 and under including an over-sample of African-American and Latino parents. The survey was designed by Common Sense Media and conducted by GfK from May 20 to June 12, 2013. ... The margin of error for the full sample is +/- 3.5 
percentage points.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 18:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a little more info from Fox about the series. 

http://www.fox.com/programming/shows/?sh=cosmos---a-spacetime-odyssey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 19:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 16:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, will remove. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 20:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need to use an Apple thumbdrive.  Any standard 8 GB or larger USB flash drive will work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 19:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Phil Schiller is DM'ing the OP?  Really?  I'd like to see the entire direct message thread including the OP's original message.  This is still not convincing, although I'd like it to be true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 16:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does this message not show up on Schiller's Twitter feed?  Looks suspicious.  Would be more credible if you posted the link to the tweet rather than an image capture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 16:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't direct message someone on Twitter unless they follow you (I doubt Phil Schiller follows you) or they enabled the feature to allow DMs from those who don't follow them (I doubt Phil enabled this feature). The fact that your reply has an error shows he doesn't follow you.  Let's see your original DM to Phil where you called him out for saying Black Knight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 04:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These directions worked for me:
http://www.gottabemobile.com/2013/10/22/perform-clean-install-os-x-mavericks/

Similar to a Mountain Lion disk image, but a couple differences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 19:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I first read the title as working on a James Bond submarine car vs. on a working James Bond submarine car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 17:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus you have to swipe rather than lightly press to get your fingerprint to register. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 20:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I originally posted this based on a post from Twitter assuming it was true.  Later, based on reading the comments on this post, I did the analysis showing it is not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 20:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get a free copy of the paper at the prl.aps.org site using this link 
http://prl.aps.org/pdf/PRL/v13/i16/p508_1


Unfortunately Reddit's version of the link doesn't support the pdf download.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 20:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I suspected this might not be the F, A, C, E musical notes. Many of your comments motivated me to analyze the notes since I don't have perfect (or even decent) pitch.  See this image for a visual of my analysis: http://i.imgur.com/O8JwHHK.png

Thanks to scottjenson for the Facetime ringtone which I used for this analysis.  

First I copied the ringtone into Garageband to visualize the notes in the time domain.  I suspected the first two notes were different from the rest in timing and pitch (maybe the F and A?).  Garageband showed me the timing of the first two is different, but of course nothing about pitch.  

Now to the frequency domain.  I downloaded a free app called iSpectrum which analyzes sounds played in real time through an audio input to your Mac.  I then played the Facetime ringtone and adjusted iSpectrum to focus on the frequency range from 1.0 kHz to 2.6 kHz.  I used the waterfall display where audio amplitudes (highlighted in magenta) are plotted as a function of frequency in the horizontal axis and time in the vertical axis (similar to what sonar operators use).  You can see I played the ringtone six times.  The magenta highlighted areas on the left are the first two notes (short in duration) and the highlighted areas on the right are the note pairs for the remainder of the ringtone (longer in duration). 

Unfortunately, the frequency resolution is not very good.  However, it's good enough to see that the first two notes are around 1.6 kHz while the trailing pairs of notes are around 2.45 kHz (+/- 100 Hz). 

I then went to the phy.mtu.edu site to see how musical notes map into frequencies.  I could not find any F notes that are close to 1.6 kHz nor could I find any C notes that are close to 2.4 - 2.5 kHz.  

My conclusions are 

* The Facetime ringtone notes do not spell FACE
* I'm spending way too much time on this

I'm out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 16:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My thoughts exactly.  I'm guessing more info will emerge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 15:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume you're referring to the statement: 
 There is a bit of a discrepancy regarding what to call the planet, as some astronomers demand that the definition of planet be considered a mass that is tethered to a sun.

The article is not well written.  I think the author should have stated that being tethered to a sun is one of the requirements some astronomers believe a planet should satisfy.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 03:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks hokie_u2 - that is helpful.  

I don't agree with Tyson's tweet "Mysteries of #Gravity: Why we enjoy a SciFi film set in make-believe space more than we enjoy actual people set in real space."

I've thoroughly enjoyed actual people set in real space over the years including the Moon landing, Felix Baumgartner skydiving from 128 kft (almost space) and Cmdr. Hadfield performing Space Oddity from the ISS, to name a few.  Knowing it's real makes it that much more interesting and enjoyable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 05:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But these quarterly results will include a significant increase in sales of Apple's leading money maker. We'll see how this translates into revenue and profit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 15:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the problem is that Misek is assuming Apple will react to other mobile phone manufacturers' trends when they have not shown this behavior in the past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 15:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SpaceX says "we have no reason to believe there was an explosion of any kind" on the Falcon 9.  

http://www.businessinsider.com/report-explosion-on-elon-musks-spacex-rocket-falcon-9-2013-10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 04:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If not, a serious omission.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 23:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 15:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Birchman is correct, you can export the HD video using AirDrop.  Surprisingly, you can also Message the HD video to anyone, including yourself.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 01:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why make this comment on this post?  Seems like my post on r/apple might be a more appropriate subreddit.  

But since you commented, I'm a long time Apple consumer and happy with their products but I'm not their PR.  Believe me, I would love Apple to pay me for my comments, but no luck.  

Regarding posting to two threads quickly, I do that all the time.  It has nothing to do with pretending - it is due to the limited time I have to review reddit and make posts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-22 16:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doctored.  This is Section 3 from Apple's EULA for iOS 7.

 Transfer. You may not rent, lease, lend, sell, redistribute, or sublicense the iOS Software. You may,  however, make a one-time permanent transfer of all of your license rights to the iOS Software to another  party in connection with the transfer of ownership of your iOS Device, provided that: (a) the transfer must  include your iOS Device and all of the iOS Software, including all its component parts, original media, printed materials and this License; (b) you do not retain any copies of the iOS Software, full or partial,  including copies stored on a computer or other storage device; and (c) the party receiving the iOS  Software reads and agrees to accept the terms and conditions of this License. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 21:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was 12th in line at my local AT T store and had no trouble getting a 32 GB Space Gray, very efficient operation.  They only carried Space Gray (no Gold or White) but they appeared to have many more in stock.  I've been hearing from friends that very few stores are stocking the Gold/White today and those are in very short supply (~5/store).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 21:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been using Touch ID extensively for about 2 hours now since I've had to reload several 10's of apps.  The function is very accurate and responsive with the 4 fingers/thumbs I've used thus far.  I'm sold.  Can't wait until the API is provided to developers.  

One item I wasn't expecting is the passcode is still required after a restart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 21:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only way I was able to update was through the iTunes store.  OTA was just not working.  Note you need to first download iTunes 11.1 before downloading/installing iOS 7.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 19:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let us know if you're successful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 23:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad - here's the Kickstarter link to Occipital:
http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/occipital/structure-sensor-capture-the-world-in-3d?ref=search </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 18:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I can't imagine this thing will actually take hold with most people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-14 07:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although I am a long-time Apple consumer, I stopped posting anything positive about Apple on r/technology long ago.  They don't want to hear it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 23:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ironically, NASA says that although Voyager 1 has entered interstellar space, it hasn't yet left our solar system.  Apparently there is an overlap of the two regions from the Heliopause through the Oort Cloud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 22:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See post from a couple minutes ago.

http://www.reddit.com/r/apple/comments/1m4jva/apples_september_10th_keynote_is_now_available_to/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 22:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also available under Apple Events on the Apple TV.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 21:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Further indication that McAfee is living:
https://twitter.com/officialmcafee/status/377142571740315648/photo/1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 21:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Further indication that McAfee is living:
https://twitter.com/officialmcafee/status/377142571740315648/photo/1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 20:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given McAfee's recent Twitter post, this may be a hoax or just misreporting.  
https://twitter.com/officialmcafee/status/377115874655612929 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 20:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given McAfee's recent Twitter post, this may be a hoax or just misreporting.  
https://twitter.com/officialmcafee/status/377115874655612929 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 17:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The DJI Phantom is a good prosumer entry level quadcopter for very light weight cameras (e.g. GoPro).  To get decent arial footage, I recommend you get a gimbal to stabilize the image.  Although it's a bit of a hack, the Zenmuse H3-2D gimbal works well with the Phantom.  Realize that this can get expensive pretty quickly - what is your budget? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 08:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing a rescue attempt of some type will be in the plot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 20:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although not confirmed by Apple, WSJ's AllThingsD has confirmed the Mavericks release. 

Mark Gurman at 9to5Mac reports, and AllThingsD has confirmed, that OS X 10.9 will not launch this month, but next.

WSJ/ATD is about as close to a confirmation as we'll get without an Apple confirmation.

http://allthingsd.com/20130906/apple-likely-to-ship-os-x-mavericks-in-october/?mod=atd_homepage_carousel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 03:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Favorite line: "I think there's this profound and enduring beauty with how much we're able to get away with, and we push that ... as far as we can." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 03:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure, but it may have to do with the presence of water/ice on Mars and the possibility of finding some evidence of life on Mars.  The chances of finding signs of life on Phobos would be much smaller.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 03:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you.  I also think r/space is an **awesome** subreddit.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 18:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're referring to its odd shape, it's not Phobos' fault.  There is something called the "potato radius" above which objects in the universe become sufficiently massive to form a sphere.  That radius is ~200 km for icy objects and ~300 km for rocky ones.  Phobos has a radius of only 11 km, so it has no hope of becoming spherical.  
http://arxiv.org/abs/1004.1091 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 04:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, I didn't know about the Island of Stability.  Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 04:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that the case with most things that are "discovered"?  I think the word has taken on a different meaning in these contexts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 16:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a confirmation of an element that was initially discovered in 2003.  The element's temporary systematic IUPAC nomenclature is Ununpentium or Uup.  The element's name will change with its confirmation.  
http://www.webelements.com/ununpentium/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 15:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Airplay is not related to networks so an "Airplay-app" doesn't make sense, unless I'm not getting your question.  Airplay is an Apple app supported by newer Macs and iOS devices that allows you to send whatever you are viewing on the device to your AppleTV and view it on your TV (known as mirroring).  

For older Macs that don't support Airplay, I use AirParrot ($9.99 US) to perform the same function. Doesn't perform quite as well as Airplay (likely due to running on an older Mac) but it gets the job done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-21 04:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does it only have 2 stars in the App store? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 16:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been there. Next time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 04:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good work kbuis. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 15:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hadn't heard about Bluetooth Low Energy technology until this article. As I was reading, it hit me: BLE would be perfect for the iWatch (or whatever Apple chooses to call their wrist-worn personal device).  This revelation assumes that Apple will not stream music from the iWatch or place other high data rate requirements on the device.  

Below are the paragraphs from the article that got me thinking:
The tradeoffs of choosing BLE over standard Bluetooth are that BLE only supports very low data rates, so you wont be streaming audio via BLE any time soon  but you can send small files if youre creative, and it works extremely well for small data packets sent from sensors.

Devices built with energy efficiency in mind can achieve battery lives of several years running off coin-cell batteries like the CR2540. This makes them ideal for wireless devices that stay in one place and would be annoying to recharge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 15:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just realized the last sentence is similar to the Wizard of Oz's message to the Scarecrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 05:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that is what I would call a really bad day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-03 18:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but if you're a Dexter fan, it's a big deal. This is how to encourage torrenting the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-03 18:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fortunately we are in an area that also has FiOS.  We are switching in the next few days, not just because of this (which will be resolved soon I'm guessing) but because the up/download speeds are pretty snappy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 20:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least those of us who don't pay for the WSJ can read a summary of the article at BGR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 17:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, there are conflicting reports, but WSJ is usually accurate with their Apple reporting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 15:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a video of the event

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FM8lQlMVI1k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 16:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you'll see Retina iMacs this fall.  I've seen no credible reports to indicate there will be but I'd be happy to be corrected here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 06:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a good example of Cosby's work from a few years ago. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-tf1K1P2Skw[1] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 06:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a good example of Cosby's work from a fews years ago.
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-tf1K1P2Skw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 22:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe she picks up where Cmdr Hadfield left off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 13:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the post again, slowly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-28 13:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can take a tour of the island on Google Maps Street View here:
https://www.google.com/maps?ll=32.628992000000004%2C129.73861300000002 cbp=%2C80.06%2C%2C1%2C-22.949997 layer=c panoid=W9OeMqdw-o94Il7EoQWSFw spn=0.18000000000000788%2C0.30000000000000676 output=classic cbll=32.628992%2C129.738613 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 05:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... but you would then need to take the stairs.  Now that's a workout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 15:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The prices are at the top of the embedded tables which may not be available at the mobile site.  Can you see the tables? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-31 23:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually it is both.  The super-massive black hole is still there (http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sagittarius_A*), but there are additional postulated smaller black holes orbiting the big one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-27 18:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds a lot like what Tim Cook said to the U.S. Senate a few days ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-27 13:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very close to the Newton.  The circular shape on the watch face would suggest the Newton.  But 1) the circle on the face in the ad is proportionally larger than the Newton's, 2) the watch face in the ad is missing the bezel that surrounds the Newton's watch face and 3) the watchband in the ad does not taper outward to match the size of the watch as the Newton's band does.  This looks like a 6th gen square nano with a different watch face applied, possibly for obscuration? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-25 18:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They actually play this song (and many others) and are accomplished harpists, although I'm sure this recording is "finger synched" given the environment they're in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 22:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, that's the problem - your density is way too low.  A neutron star has a density of between 3.710^17 and 5.910^17 kg/m^3, which is about 14 orders of magnitude higher than the density you're using.  The material about to compress into a black hole would have an even higher density than a neutron star. Try the neutron star density and see what radius you get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 22:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you get that density? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 21:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what density you assumed, but your radius looks way to large to be the minimum radius required to form a black hole.  You may have used the density of iron that we observe here on Earth.  However in the process of forming a black hole, iron atoms are highly compressed so that the nuclei are nearly in contact with each other.  This is a form of iron that is many orders of magnitude more dense than what we observe on Earth.  The much higher density allows the minimum radius for black hole formation to be much smaller than your estimate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-18 04:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time for me as well.  I looked for an original post but couldn't find one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 05:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say a pretty good production ... FROM FRICKEN SPACE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 05:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can only hope that was a joke. If so, good on ya.  If not, heaven (or what ever your belief) help you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-12 03:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Symbols are color coded and organized by alliance, with Luke Skywalker and Darth Vader as far apart as they can get
* Each element uses the small template to organize information about the first appearance of the character, initials of the actor or actress who played the character, and the cast order
* Initials and numerals are all coded in a Star Wars inspired font and code, which are explained in greater detail on Disney's website http://etckt.com/2013/05/07/elements-of-star-wars/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-12 03:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Symbols are color coded and organized by alliance, with Luke Skywalker and Darth Vader as far apart as they can get
* Each element uses the small template to organize information about the first appearance of the character, initials of the actor or actress who played the character, and the cast order
* Initials and numerals are all coded in a Star Wars inspired font and code, which are explained in greater detail on Disney's website http://etckt.com/2013/05/07/elements-of-star-wars/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-04 16:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like his rendition of 'Chain Gang' with a nice beat at 1:21. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-01 20:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recommend getting in touch with Allison Sheridan at http://podfeet.com.  She has been producing the NosillaCast Mac podcast for 8 years.  In addition she has produced a 12-part series companion podcast called Podcasting on Podcasting which is focused on helping people create their own podcast (http://www.podfeet.com/wordpress/podcasting-on-podcasting/).  

Allison learned from other generous podcasters and loves to pass on her knowledge to others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 02:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Microsoft is maintaining the tradition of releasing a problem OS on every other major rev. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 15:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that you Pat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 15:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's look of minimalism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 18:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty creative, except it violates one of the main design features of a manhole cover - they are usually circular so they cannot accidentally fall into the hole they're covering.  Any other shape, including this one I think, will allow the cover to fall into the hole if correctly (or incorrectly depending on your point of view) oriented. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 01:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but it's a first step (of many). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
