<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3533</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 02:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teemo is such a butt turd licking butt. I want my oracles back ;-; The only pure enjoyment I have when fighting against a Teemo is killing him. 

(My boyfriend and I have a great relationship. :P He hates it when I give him skins, too much pride in that man. We just both dislike Teemo...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 19:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you get gifted with a skin on sale lower than 520 with a higher base price, you'll get a refund. So, technically you're not allowed to get gifted skins on sale. :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 19:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gifted my boyfriend two teemo skins... He hates me and our relationship is in ruins. Thanks teemo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 02:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it me or is the PC one only listing the base price with no sale? I've been wanting this expansion for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 02:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANK YOU! I didn't know which kind of tutorial video to watch :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-25 05:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So should I just build around where I originally spawn? How do I navigate these hills? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New to Gnomoria, completely lost! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-25 04:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought the game during the Steam Community Choice sale and I'm having trouble. Any tips for a complete newbie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 07:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> assassin master yi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 22:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone notice how when Hurt's about to press the big red button, 10 and 11 are standing side by side with Clara behind 11 and "Rose" behind 10? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
