<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4544</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 04:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Samurai Champloo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 04:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't agree more with you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What anime has the most confusing ending? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 04:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's Paranoia Agent.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 03:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically you don't even need nx. You can buy meister cubes or master craftsman cubes but those cost A LOT of money. Theres an option to craft it yourself but you need meister level smithing which is a pain in the butt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 02:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always upvote /u/Poem_for_your_sprog
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 21:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try asking /r/manga or /r/anime.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 20:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not really funded would it be okay if I use 70% scroll because clean slate scrolls cost a lot of money.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 20:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have sympathy towards those who constantly complain about their problems and manipulate others into feeling sorry for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 06:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seryu Ubuquitous from Akame Ga Kill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 05:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is kind of late but is it better to scroll your CRA gear with spell traces 70% rather than spell traces 30%? I know spell traces 30% gives a higher boost but theres also a huge chance of failure... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 05:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First thing that came to mind was League of Legends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 04:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anime. Lots and Lots of Anime. Although like many other pleasurable activities, you are temporarily pushing the problem aside while immersing yourself in a fantasy world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 03:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never stick your dick in crazy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 03:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was suspended in 3rd grade for raising my fist at a kid who wouldn't let me play with him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some of your real life horror stories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 03:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 03:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was in the Walking Dead I think back in Season 4! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 03:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You Found Me - The Fray </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 03:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You must therefore be content to slubber the gloss of your new fortunes with this more stubborn and boist'rous expedition"

*Othello* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 21:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you remember Wyoming but not New Jersey, Pennsylvannia, Massachusetts or any other major states? NO ONE CARES ABOUT WYOMING. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 06:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same for my school! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 19:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But did you try turning it off and back on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who do you despise the most right now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 18:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your favorite T.V show while growing up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 04:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 20:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suicide doesn't take the pain away... it only passes it to someone else. Even though right now it may be tough, life always does get better. Tthink of all the opportunities you're missing out on life if you decide to end it? Think of all your friends, family, and colleagues that your death would affect. Good luck dude, just remember there's always a light at the end of the tunnel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 05:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Type 8008 on your calculator. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 05:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't have said it any better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 05:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You truly are an optimistic robot lord. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did you and your best friend grow apart? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 05:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do people do that irks you the most? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 03:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 05:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I see. I would do Root Abyss but it's too hard even on Normal as my main probably can't even solo Gollux on Easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Selling Crystal Ilbis - Scania </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 05:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on Scania. I'm selling some Crystal Ilbis for 70m, if anyone is interested please contact my Dark Knight, xDKnightzx1. Yes I know Crystal Ilbis are selling for ~100m but I just want to make some quick money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 04:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All Mods

How do you guys earn your money? I know /u/icephoenix21 sells crystal ilbis and balanced furies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 03:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm more of an anime person but yeah I agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 03:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Swap the Taj Mahal with the Eiffel Tower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 03:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anime. Most people assume anime is for little children but they're very *very* wrong... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 02:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant it as a joke.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 04:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 90% of statistics here are wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 04:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most mothers are cheating cunts because apparently nearly everyone I've met while playing video games claimed to have "fucked my mom". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 03:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Camden, Bronx, Baltimore, pretty much all the ghetto uneducated and impoverished communities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 22:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom asked me what the stain on my bedsheet was, I told her I drooled a lot when I sleeped. Not sure if she belives me.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 05:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wanking off actually is a great way to fall asleep as it helps to relieve stress and to take your mind off of things. Other than that I watch anime until I get tired...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you guys get motivated to get up in the mornings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 05:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 22:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for answering! One last question, is making crystal ilbi's your main source of income or do you go on gollux runs and stuff too? At first I thought about making money off of Gollux but my damage is so bad I can't solo it even on easy so thats why I need some money to get better gear and stuff.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 21:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long did all the prequests take? What level do you recommend someone should  be before they start making crystal ilbi's? How long does selling one take?

Sorry for all the questions but I think I might try to make crystal ilbis now when I have a chance. At first I thought it was incredibly annoying to make but looking at it now, it doesn't seem that hard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 21:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I know, I wasn't asking specifically if you would make one for me but rather if I can accompany you while you make them or work on my own set while you're there. I'm also on Scania btw also, I used to play ms five years ago so my guild has been inactive for a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 21:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I probably won't be going on maplestory for today but whenever I have a chance I'll add you. My username is xDKnightzx1. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 04:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if I recalled the drop rate for the badge's weren't very high and also don't you need 100 dark crystals to make one set of balanced furies? Oh and what server are you on? If it isn't too troubling for you can you help assist me in making one set :D? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 04:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? Care to explain or perhaps teach me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 04:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They both are quite hard to make as they require a lot of exepensive materials and a lot of time spent on the prequests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 03:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's like asking why does your arm hurt when it's broken or fractured. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 03:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was placed in Bronze 5 in League of Legends and I only cried for two days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 03:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waking up in the morning.... I think that goes for everyone though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help with Gollux runs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 03:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone wanna do Gollux runs with me? I'm on Scania and I have a lvl 140 Dark Knight. My damage isn't that great so I can't solo it even on easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 16:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm clutching my scrotum right now, oh god, I feel really bad for you it's extremely painful for me to even think about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 16:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got your priorities straight! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 16:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you get stabbed right when you open the curtains and you start crying like a little bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
