<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1473</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 21:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably has a Mercedes engine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 20:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it kind of bizarre to see 67 ads for DeSotos and 132 for Volgas on the same site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Check out these Cuban car classifieds. Lots of strange stuff and some cars that look surprisingly decent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 20:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 19:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hand built, expensive materials, fine wood and leather, state of the art technology and entertainment system, complex engineering, and custom options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tell us your depreciation stories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 19:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 19:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Infiniti G25x/35x/37x should be available in that price range has AWD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 18:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could probably buy something 5-15 years old with under 100k for $9,000 or less if it belonged to a senior citizen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 14:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1980-83 Lincoln Mark VI. A smaller, boxier derivative of the earlier Mark V. It was the first and only Mark Series available as both a sedan and a coupe. Today, they are among the rarest of the Panther platform cars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 06:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honda Fit, Toyota Yaris, Mazda 2 would be a few more options. A 150k modern car can still be reliable and if you are just driving to the train station, mileage shouldn't matter as much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 05:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A number of Cadillacs look RWD when they are actually FWD. The DTS, XTS, 1994-99 DeVille, 1972-78 Eldorado, and 1979-85 Eldorado. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abandoned Mercedes Gullwing found in Cuba </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 05:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 05:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget about the old non-American made vehicles there, Soviet and European mostly. Not sure how big the market for 70s-90s Soviet vehicles is in the US, but if you want a Lada 2101, Niva, Volga, or Chaika and are in the U.S., I would imagine that importing one from Cuba would be easier than from Europe since it's closer. They should be cheap when all the other collectors are in a frenzy for 50s American cars. There is also that rumor about a Mercedes 300SL Gullwing sitting under a banana tree. If the Gullwing isn't too far gone, that should be a seven-digit car.

I also wonder how cars from today, or even 20 years ago will seen to a Cuban who has been driving an old jalopy all their life. Going from driving a 57' to even an 87' car is a big change, so a 2015 model may feel space age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good ways to celebrate renouncing my U.S. citizenship? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 03:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am planning to renounce my American citizenship within 10 years. I originally planned on going on a trip to Cuba to celebrate no longer being American, but seeing as Cuba may become open to Americans by the time I renounce it, I would like some other suggestions. I am looking to celebrate by doing something that U.S. citizens cannot do, and likely in a place where U.S. citizens cannot go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 18:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dodge St. Regis, Merkur XR4ti </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the oldest car you have ever used as a daily driver? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 15:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 15:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1979 Pontiac Bonneville Brougham </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 03:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How highly illegal is it there? In the US, most traffic violations are considered low tier misdemeanors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 02:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crown Vic, Mercury Grand Marquis, Lincoln Town Car, W body Imapla, Taurus/Sable, Saturns, 10-15 y/o Buicks. You might be able to get something a little nicer if it was built in the 80s or 90s. Aim for cars owned by elderly people, as they tend to be well maintained with low miles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 02:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 80s Quattroporte is blander, http://www.curbsideclassic.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/IMG_0306.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some other places besides Cuba where old cars are kept alive by any means necessary because of poverty or a lack of newer cars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 02:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 02:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They say desperation is the mother of creativity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 01:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean because boxy 70s-80s American cars are colloquially known as "boxes"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 00:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the Toyota Hilux seems to be the truck that has become stereotypically associated with Middle Eastern terrorists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buy These: Malaise-Era American Iron Immortalized in Awesome 1:43 Scale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 00:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 23:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 70s-80s RWD,boxy, full-size American cars. (E.g. Caprice Classic, LTD Crown Victoria, Chrysler Fifth Avenue). Most enthusiasts disregard these cars as bland and stodgy, but I actually think they should be looked at on the same level as W123s and Volvo 240s. Just like those European cars, these cars are also boxy, conservative, slow, un-sporty, and simple to work on. I like the earlier oversized versions too, but these seem to be more notably made fun of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most bland exotic car? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 23:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 21:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it ironic that these terrorists would choose to use a Ford truck if they are so vehemently anti-American. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Were French cars popular in Quebec and other French speaking parts of Canada when they were sold in North America? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 15:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 23:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, both are cars sold in Canada, but never the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out of all the cars you have ever owned, which was your favorite and least favorite, and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 15:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 13:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mercedes-Benz 560SEC and 1979 Lincoln Town Coupe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 05:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP didn't specify the type of title, but I guess this Passat could have come to that point where minor damage can result in being totaled because of its low value. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 01:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! Never thought a running car that cheap could be anything other than a 35 year old, dirty, beat up, unreliable POS that makes the owner look like they live in the poorhouse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New petition to create an independent public committee to study the 25 year import ban and enact new legislation. A different approach since previous petitions didn't work. (Re-post from r/autos) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 01:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 16:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chrysler R-Body cars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 05:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GG Allin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Were 15-30 year old cars a common sight on the road decades ago? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 23:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today it is not unusual to see a 1980s or 90s car in regular use depending on where you are, but how common was it to see cars continue to be used at this age in the past? For example 30s cars in the 50s or 50s cars in the 70s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 02:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mercedes E class coupe 4Matic, Toyota Supra and Celica Alltrac, Nissan Skyline GTR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 20:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chrysler 300 and Mercedes W126, 1990-93 Infiniti Q45 and 1992-94 Ford Crown Victoria, 1980-89 Lincoln Town Car and Rolls-Royce Silver Spirit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What cars have a resemblance to each other that it seems like only you see? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 20:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 23:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1996 - Either Brabus 7.3S W140 or Brabus E V12 W210 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You can have any car, as long as it is American and was built between 1974 and 1984. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 22:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the era when most on this subreddit say there were few, if any good American cars to choose from, but I dissagree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What car makes you feel old when it is referred to as "classic"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 16:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 20:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As well as it's stablemates, the supercharged Olds 98 and LSS, and the supercharged Pontiac Bonneville SSEi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you had to choose one infestation or the other, which would it be? Roaches or Mice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 20:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 16:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - 40s 1941 Cadillac Model 62 convertible
- 50s 1959 Chevrolet Impala coupe
- 60s 1963 Pontiac Bonneville coupe
- 70s 1979 Pontiac Bonneville Brougham coupe
- 80s Mercedes-Benz 190E 2.5 16V (or 560SEC)
- 90s Toyota Century
- 00s 2000-03 Toyota Crown Athlete V
- 10s Mercedes-Benz S65 AMG
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 13:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Late 60's Olds Toronado or Cadillac Eldorado </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 05:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does seem like cars of this type are very easy to find with low miles and there are likely more nice examples than there is demand. These late 70's land yachts don't have the same cache or icon status as those from the 50's and 60's. I have noticed many are now being exported to Europe, possibly for their lower prices here and uniqueness over there. At what point in the future, if ever might this be considered an appropriate price?


Here's another similarly priced 79', but MJC cars are typically way overpriced, http://www.mjcclassiccars.com/1979-pontiac-bonneville-landau/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 12k mile, ultra clean, 1979 Pontiac Bonneville for $19k at RK Motors. Have the prices of late 70's full size Pontiac survivors really gone up this much or are they dreaming? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 04:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 04:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Olds Cutlass Supreme diesel was pretty dreadful even for it's time, especially in sedan form. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: The Felony Murder Rule should be abolished. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 03:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What new car looks like it could be 10+ years old? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 20:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have seen quite a few "what older car still looks current/has aged the best" threads, so what about the reverse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 03:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mercedes C65 AMG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 16:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1960 Chevrolet Impala Sport Coupe, Toyota Century, Mercedes-Benz E63 AMG S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 20:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Malaise era American cars. They will be easier to get going again than new cars and by then there will not be anyone alive who remembers how bad they were when new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most surprising car you ever saw historical/classic plates on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 20:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 20:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 1.8l 90hp 4cyl engine in the R32 Nissan Skyline GXi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has the number of cars imported to the US using the 25 year rule increased dramatically in the past 4 years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 19:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems that way, especially since R32 Skylines and E30 Tourings are now legal, with more coming soon. I have seen companies claiming to have imported hundreds of cars using this rule. In say, 2004, when 1979 cars became legal to import how much did the number of 25+ year old foreign cars being imported to the US compare to the current numbers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 17:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a shame the Olds Diesel was such a terrible engine, because diesel-powered full sized American cars seem like a good idea. How are there any still running? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 20:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, Lexus is really stepping up their game, but having to put a front license plate on is gonna suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 17:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually it is because when I go into Queens and Brooklyn, I tend to see a lot of dilapidated 10-20 year old MBs, BMWs, and Lexuses that seem to be driven by people who don't have the money to maintain them, so they just become beaters and eventually lawn ornaments. Small parts for a ten year old S-Class Mercedes can go for hundreds of dollars, or at least a very high amount compared to a 10 year old midrange car. I can see the cost of parts and service, as well as gas causing a lot of problems for the low or even average income owner of an older, high mileage luxury car. Those who know better avoid these cars because of their running costs which makes them dirt cheap to buy for people who know nothing about cars and don't do research before buying. I always think of different questions that I can post here or other subreddits while I am bored or daydreaming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who bought a particular car because it was a cheap way to get a prestigious badge (new or used), how did it work out for you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 16:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the most common first cars for teens and young adults where you live currently or when you were younger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 16:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favorite and least favorite things about the date of your birthday? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 00:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the minimum amount of horsepower required to keep up with traffic on today's highways? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 21:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 02:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There seems to be far more ten year old cars that still look up to date today than there were ten years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 19:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> G25, Q45, LS430, W220, DTS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 19:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Acura TL, VW Phaeton </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 04:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - BMW 3 Series
- W203/204 C-Class Mercedes
- Infiniti Q45
- 2002-08 Acura TL
- First year Jaguar XFs are getting cheap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 03:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard about them too. These are actually US market Pontiac G8s, GTOs, and SSes that have been rebodied as utes/Maloos or converted into Commodores. They have all that is needed to comply with US regs. Everything from the Australian cars fits right on to one of the US cars since they are all rebadged Holdens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 23:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The R34 is one that will not be importable until 2023, but yes, the early 90s includes some of the most sought after forbidden fruits. This is the list of federalization-eligible cars, some of which are now over 25 years old: http://www.nhtsa.gov/CARS/RULES/IMPORT/elig101012c.pdf. I once remember hearing that in 1995 less than 300 cars were imported this way. There is a W210 Mercedes with out of state plates which appears to be euro spec that I have seen around these parts from time to time. Not sure if it is a legal import, illegal import, or US model that has been converted to look like a Euro car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How common is it for non-US vehicles to be federalized by registered importers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 22:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> C30 CDI AMG: Just learned these exist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 07:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron Swanson tries to copy Stalin's look, what if a TV character tried to copy Hitler's look? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 01:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the most common wild animals in your backyard? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 22:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 04:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I mean with the same characters and setting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if That 70's Show had become "That 80's Show" after the decade ended? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 04:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why hasn't anyone in North America ever decided to convert their C-Class or CLS sedan into a wagon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 08:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shooting brake CLS and all generations of the C wagon except for the W203 are not available in the US or Canada. The CLA shooting brake is not planned to arrive on our shores either. I mean "convert" as in bring over a wagon body, take the sedan body from the US spec car off the chassis, and replace it with the wagon body. Though this may sound very hard to do and far fetched, I'm actually surprised I can't find any evidence of anyone here doing so. There is a company in Colorado that converts the Pontiac G8, GTO and Chevy SS into a Holden Ute (Australian pickup car) by doing this and I have seen pictures of S-Class sedans with SEC/CL front clips, as well as a W124 with a W210 front. With this Colorado company claiming to have done over 30 conversions and having stumbled across all sorts of Mercedes frankencars online, it surprises me that I haven't found this yet. I'm sure a CLA45, C63 or CLS63 AMG converted to a wagon would probably be a major attraction at any Cars and Coffee or European car meet over here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you guys think of Carter era GM diesel cars with a Cummins or Duramax swap? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 06:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen W126s and W123 diesels with Cummins swaps in them, so why not put them in cars like the late 70s-early 80s Chevrolet Caprice, Cadillac Fleetwood Brougham, or Buick Regal. The factory diesel engines were terrible, so a Cummins or Duramax should make the cars run better than ever and be kind of badass. They are already set up to run on diesel fuel, so it shouldn't be that hard to do this kind of swap. They would make pretty cool/ironic tow vehicles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 22:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have thought about moving to Canada because of the import laws, but then I do more thinking and realize I have to choose between 15+ year old imports and more rust, colder weather, and a higher cost of living or 25+ year old imports, less or no rust depending on location, warmer weather, and a lower cost of living. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If parts and maintenance for older Mercedes-Benzes are supposedly so expensive, than why are they so common in poorer countries? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 01:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ever seen a car and thought "what the heck is that thing" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 21:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 23:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does that mean I should remove it from here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korean documentary about poverty in America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 23:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been noticing an increasing number of ratty and/or poorly customized W220s,W210s, and W203s. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 06:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some differences between the car culture the "lower 48 states" and that of Hawaii, Alaska and the territories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 00:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can hermaphrodites impregnate themselves? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 19:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why doesn't public access have closed captioning? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 18:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 22:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you in Quebec, because I once saw a picture of a terribly rusty Mazda 3 with Quebec plates somewhere. It was stated that such rust on 5-15 year old Mazdas there was not uncommon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 20:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my neighbors had a Hyundai that was smashed to oblivion and looked like it would fall apart any minute when it was only four years old but still drove it because he says his ex wife was a really bad driver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the newest car you have ever seen in "beater" condition. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 20:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone here downvote other posts in order to move your own closer to the top? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 20:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do shemales have such big feet? Has anyone else noticed this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 04:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 23:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks so 80s. Cars with trendy, loud styling don't usually age very well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 19:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it really that dated looking? I actually think it has aged better than most cars of its age. It would have guessed that the M45 was an 08' at newest if I knew nothing about it, which is very impressive considering that the design is now 15 years old (available in Japan before the US). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What car sold new in your country is most likely to be mistaken for something that somebody imported on their own? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 20:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 05:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, NY Metro area </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 22:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mercedes E and C Class, BMW 3 Series, Honda Accord are the most common. Saw an early 90s Lexus GS300 today for the first time in years here. I used to often see a 1978 Chevy Malibu that was a daily driver. Never saw another one around here, it was in really bad condition and I think it died a few months ago. 

Edit: Just remembered once seeing a Lexus LFA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 22:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Soviet W123 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 22:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1971-72 Cadillac Eldorado </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is "AUDM" the next JDM? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 17:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have noticed that in recent years, Japan has been producing less and less cool Japan-only cars. At the same time, a U.S. based interest in certain Holdens from Australia has developed. This has led to some Pontiac G8, Chevrolet Caprice PPV, and Chevrolet SS owners applying Holden badges and parts to their cars. A smaller number have even gone to great lengths to do full HSV and Ute conversions. I have also noticed a small but growing number of Australian classics for sale in the US, including Ford XB Falcons, Holden Monaros, and 1950's Chevy and Ford Utes. So will AUDM in North America keep growing and potentially have the kind of popularity, industry, and silliness that JDM has or is it just a minor fad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found out that the Holden FB and EK were sold new in Hawaii but not in the mainland US. Are there any other cars that were sold new in Hawaii or an American controlled territory such as Puerto Rico but not in the contiguous United States. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 07:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 22:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - 1990 Ford LTD Crown Victoria - http://newjersey.craigslist.org/cto/4747768670.html

- 1978 Ford Granada http://newyork.craigslist.org/lgi/cto/4742909019.html

- 1995 Chevy Van (just had to put this in because it looks so creepy)
http://newyork.craigslist.org/lgi/cto/4750291349.html
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best/most desirable versions of otherwise bad or mediocre cars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 21:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are Malaise Era cars really as bad as people think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 21:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1980 Oldsmobile Holiday 88 Coupe. There is something mildly interesting about very un-sporty cars with sport options. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 14:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mercedes-Benz 220D crew cab pickup from Argentina. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 03:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is velour no longer used in car interiors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 22:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the longest number of years you've kept driving the same car for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 01:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it true that Harvard is considered more prestigious in the UK than in the US and Oxford is considered more prestigious in the US than in the UK? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 17:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 13:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The drinking age </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most nondescript car? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 03:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one who thinks old Australian cars look like alternate universe or video game versions of old American cars? Do Australians ever think the reverse of this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 03:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the most common older daily drivers in your area? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 19:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Older " means 20+ years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 02:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Malaise era cars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do horror movie monsters create a stronger trigger of fear than the dangerous beings of real life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 23:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I mean is why does an image of Chucky or a horde of zombies create a stronger initial feeling of terror than images of serial killers or large, vicious animals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one who thinks it is gross and unsanitary that we wear shoes that were worn by multiple other people at bowling alleys? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 17:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 22:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Daily Turismo
- Petrolicious
- Japanrse Nostalgic Car
- Old Parked Cars
- The Street Peep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best looking stock wheels of all time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 04:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 15:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll start by saying the Mustang II would be Scrappy Doo. Both are smaller derivatives of something iconic, unloved, and the result of misguided marketing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would cars be if they were fictional characters? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 15:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Name some things that are the ______ _______ of _______ ________ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 15:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> e.g. McGill is the Harvard of Canada, Fred Phelps is the GG Allin of evangelists.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Name some things that are the ______ _______ of _______ ________ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 15:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the cars that you are embarrassed to admit you like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 00:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 00:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 1M is already appreciating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guesses of future "blue chip" classic cars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 23:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just regular future classics, what are the cars of 1990-now that will sell for stupid money in the way that muscle cars often do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 21:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 25+ year old imports are legal in CA but are not smog exempt. It would be very hard, or at least expensive to make this car comply with CA smog regs. Some get inspections done at shops that will falsify results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 18:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a Japanese grandma car, but still might get noticed by the most hardcore of Skyline fanboys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 17:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many have done RHD conversions with their Honda Civics and Acura Integras to make them look JDM. Like what this Buick owner did, it is a good way to waste money on something only 2% of the population will pay attention to. Conversions like this are interesting to see, but not necessarily practical to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 06:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1999-02 Mercedes E55 AMG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 06:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have also seen guys who put Skyline badging on their G35s but keep the Infiniti emblem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is a Buick Regal which has been thoroughly converted into an Opel Insignia. Know of any other examples of cars with "foreign appearance" conversions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 05:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Assign the surname "Bitchson" to anyone who is chronically rude or aggressive. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 05:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 04:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The W123 interestingly seems to be one of the few slow cars that is a regular topic on car enthusiast forums and websites. Not that there's anything wrong with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 04:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just theoretical. Used or modified cars would be acceptable. I have read that there are tuning companies who can manufacture chips and other parts that will make a 10-15 year old AMG or M car have HP and torque which is in some cases far higher than the Hellcat. Such a car could be purchased stock and clean for $10-30k and have $5-10k worth of upgrades done. It would be less expensive to buy and might beat a Hellcat on a track, but would be a maintenance nightmare. Still, would be interesting to see something like this happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cars that are faster and less expensive than a Charger Hellcat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 04:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would it be possible to or has anyone ever "cornered the market" of a particular car? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 02:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are most of my wet dreams about watching porn? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 04:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Use death row inmates as crash test dummies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 02:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 17:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of these commercials http://www.adweek.com/news/advertising-branding/ad-day-dead-mice-act-out-plays-strangest-pest-control-ads-ever-160615 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What car did you hate when it first came out, but started to like later on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 00:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Re-animate" fish and other dead sea animals by putting them in a tank of formaldehyde and implanting them with animatronics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 00:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Offbeat guesses of future classic cars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 19:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For how much longer will 1990's Hondas still top the list of most stolen cars in the US? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 18:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 90s Civics and Accords continue to routinely top the list of most stolen cars, but I'm starting to see less of them on the road and most of the ones I do see are getting increasingly ratty. Will they still be frequently stolen in 5-10 years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 04:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And hermits aren't too far removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Live like an animal. This way you don't have to work, go to school, pay bills, or give a shit about anything. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 03:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone here who had their car scrapped in Cash for Clunkers or a similar program and regretted it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 03:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pissed at someone and sick, don't start a fight, sneeze on the mofo and make them get sick too. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 03:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 16:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got two old American land yachts for the price of one,

- http://newyork.craigslist.org/lgi/cto/4711162340.html - 1965 Chevy Impala Sport Sedan $2250 81k, a bit rough.

- http://newyork.craigslist.org/lgi/cto/4678456768.html - 1988 Lincoln Town Car $2500 68k miles, the closest you can get to mint in this price range.

- and $250 left over. 

The Metro NY craigslist is also littered with rough, high mileage 70's-90's German Cars
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did Hyundai and Kia succeed, while Daewoo faded away? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 04:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Korean car brands, Hyundai and Kia during the 1990's-early 2000's were seen as cheap and boring, but today make competitive cars. Daewoo had a similar image but instead, practically dropped of the map in 2003 (unless you regard the Chevy Aveo as one) rather than getting any farther. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 17:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Fronternac (Canadian only version of the Ford Falcon)
- Dodge Royal Monaco Brougham
- Mercury Cougar Villager station wagon
- Oldsmobile SportOmega (the first American car with plastic fenders)
- Nissan Axxess
- Isuzu Axiom
- Kia K900 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Name cars that are rare but not valuable or desirable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 16:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 13:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - BMW M550d
- Mercedes-Benz CLS Shooting Brake
- Toyota Crown
- Toyota Century
- Holden Ute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your least favorite thing about life in the country where you live? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 03:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 00:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Velour, "Brougham" packages, more expressive colors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will the 1920's still be called the Roaring Twenties in the 2020s or will the next decade be the new Roaring Twenties? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 23:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 23:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Particularly the ES models </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think is the cheapest looking luxury car? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 22:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As in a luxury car that has the styling of something you would not expect to be all that luxurious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 18:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How bad are Rovers really, I'm an American so I look at them on the surface as a European version of Acura. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the Hyundai Equus the next Volkswagen Phaeton? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 16:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have noticed some striking similarities and differences between the two.

Similarities

- Both are large luxury sedans from non-luxury brands.
- Both have trouble holding their value and like the Phaeton, the Equus will likely be a huge bargain after it is discontinued.
- Both have relatively conservative, anonymous styling.
- Both have been slow sellers.
- Both are relatively obscure compared to their competition.
- both were intended to be halo cars.

Differences

- One is from an experienced manufacturer of luxury cars, the other isn't.
- Hyundais are generally more reliable and cheaper to maintain than Volkswagens.
- One has a V8 as it's largest engine, the other has a W12.
- Hyundai has established a "cheap" reputation with many, while Volkswagen has established an "affordable" reputation.
- The VW is hand built, the Hyundai is not.
- The material quality of the Equus may not be as good as the Phaeton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are cars aging better than they used to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 16:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While automotive technology and safety is changing quickly, it seems that cars are also aging better. 10 years ago, a 20 year old car had a harder time blending into modern traffic and was often more decrepit looking than most 20 year old cars today. 40 years ago, a a 10 year old car was probably on it's last legs and the difference between it and a new car was like night and day. Today many, if not most 10 year old cars still feel modern and have plenty of travel left.

For example, imagine a 1999 Lexus LS400 with 80,000 miles today vs. a 1960 Chevrolet Impala with 80,000 miles in 1975. Both are 15 years old, but one still looks and feels relatively modern if in good shape and will last a few more years, while the other seems ancient compared to a new car and isn't too far from hitting the junkyard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 15:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Full size 70s and 80s American Behemoths (Think Lincoln Continental, Chevrolet Caprice Classic) - Everyone seems to think they are ugly and uninspiring. I rarely see them features by the mainstream automotive media. But I think they are quite attractive and interestingly many are somehow ostentatious and conservative at the same time.
- BMW E23 - Seems to be the least loved 7 Series and least loved BMW of its era. 
- JDM luxury cars both new and old (Think Toyota Century, Toyota Crown, Nissan Cedric). I can remember Jeremy Clarkson ragging on these, as well as my first category quite a few times.
- Boxy 1980's JDM mid-level luxury cars and sport sedans, especially the ones with turbos or superchargers. Similar what I said above, but while cars like the Century have a distinct appearance and presence, most non car people outside Japan would probably assume a 1980-something Toyota Crown or Mark II GT Twin Turbo is just a regular old Camry.
- Every generation of the Mazda Cosmo.
- Hyundai Equus - It's big and looks super elegant but loses value real quickly. I could see it becoming the next VW Phaeton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
