<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject64</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 18:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes me feel torn, said Rep. Keith Ellison (D-Minn.), chairman of the Congressional Progressive Caucus. **The bottom line is military spending is government spending, and in the absence of any sort of other stimulus for the private sector, we need to get it where we can**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 17:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you try to write your comment w/out profanity and then resubmit.  Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-28 18:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you want an endless war, sure, let's keep afghanistan in a perpetual state of domestic conflict and completely ignore the eerily similar events of history.

Intervention by foreign powers has caused all of the problems you're referring to.  What Afghans do in their own country is not now, nor has it ever been, the business of the United States.

You have to understand that you have been brainwashed by your employer with these phony arguments in order to get you to kill people who have never posed any threat to you or your country.  I'm sorry your life will be perpetually scarred by the immoral acts you participated in while serving the interests of some politicians and the arms manufacturers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-28 17:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The war is lost.  There is no sense in losing one more Afghan or American life.  Any "mature" observer of the situation would agree with this assessment and counsel the same course of action: bring the troops home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-28 17:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moreover, some 70,000 people, most of them Muslims, have been killed by other Muslims in the Syrian civil war, **which the U.S. had nothing to do with**  although many Muslims are now begging us to intervene to stop it.

I guess he doesn't read his own newspaper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-28 17:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exaggerated reports of coalition casualties, vows for revenge, and glorious victories against great odds

I think you're actually thinking of claims made by the U.S. military.  The U.S. lost the war many years ago.  It's time to admit that fact and bring the troops home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-28 17:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, peace would be a terrible thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-27 16:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But NATO insists that the war is being won, with US General Joseph Dunford, head of the International Security Assistance Force (ISAF), saying on Thursday there was "indisputable" progress towards the goal of a stable nation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-27 01:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm sure the murderous Japanese Imperial system could have been sustained for the last 70 years or so in all of those countries.  How long did the U.S. military last in Iraq again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 23:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, what the Japanese military did was none of the U.S. Govt's business so long as it didn't threaten America.  The only reason the Japanese attacked the U.S. at all is b/c we had forcibly acquired colonies in Hawaii and the Philippines (and Guam, American Samoa, etc.) in contradiction to the principles the country was founded on.  If we mind our own business, people tend to leave us alone.  It's not a complicated theory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 22:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 20:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out the comments section of the story.  Unbelievable ignorance and stupidity.  Examples:

My new favorite oxymoron: Ron Paul Think Tank

Intent on studying why black Americans won't vote in support of slavery and racists? Because that's just not obvious so let's spend time and money figuring it out...

The Ron Paul Institute for the Peace and Prosperity of Slaveowners and the Operators of Segregated Lunch Counters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 18:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously, there is a coordinated effort to try to discredit the Ron Paul Institute.  How soon before Rand distances himself from his father's think tank? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 20:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RUSH:  So the meme is we did it, the United States.  We are responsible. Michael Scheuer, who... I'll refrain, but to me, **no credibility there whatsoever**

Does he even know who Michael Scheuer is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 19:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being targeted with violence is a major cost of war and aggression. It's a reason not do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 00:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he still is against targeted killings and especially unwarranted drone surveillance.

Just give him a few more days.  He seems to change his mind on a whim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 19:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just fucking w/ you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 00:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great comment.  Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 22:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's try this a different way: "Americans who distrust [Jews] are likelier to back [concentration camps]" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 02:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't order the strike. He didn't have anything to do with the story in the article you just linked.

So I guess the drone's just operate independently of any human input, right?

What hoops you partisan Obama lovers will jump through to absolve your murderous hero of any guilt.  You're pathetic.  Grow up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 01:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 17:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A female E-4 who police said confessed to shooting BBs at passers-by for fun, was charged with assault but will not be arrested, the prosecutor said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 19:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not his father.

And I want to keep reiterating that point so people aren't fooled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 18:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While the Deer Team was with the Viet Minh, the Japanese surrendered and the Viet Minh declared Vietnam an independent nation, using language from the Declaration of Independence. Ho gave his American friends a message to forward to President Harry S. Truman asking him to support the Viet Minh against France, which had lost its colonies to Japan during the war and was fighting to take them back. Mr. Truman never replied. The United States backed France.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 22:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You still haven't provided an alternative contender for that title.  Please let me know when you come up with one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 21:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Partisan = Insane, in this case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 20:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Translation: I surrender

Not a "surrender," just a waste of time presenting facts to a partisan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 20:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have time to refute all of your false statements about the greatness of the American Empire.  Maybe you should try reading a few books in your spare time to educate yourself.  It's obvious reading isn't currently one of your favorite pastimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 19:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give me another contender. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 18:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do yourself a favor and start thinking for yourself for a change.  Your govt is and has been the most evil and violent force throughout the world for decades.  Grow up and start questioning the nationalistic mythology you've been spoon-fed since birth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 18:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice comment.  Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 18:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the US does not 'target' civilians, only enemy combatants

Tell that to the people of Hiroshima, Nagasaki, My Lai, Baghdad, Wazirastan, Kabul, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 21:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blowback? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 17:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's easy to forget what life was like when the decision was made."

04/15/13: [Iraq Attacks Leave 36 Dead](http://www.thestatesman.net/index.php?option=com_content view=article id=452170 catid=37) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 18:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Establishment figures called it unfair that Rick Santorum won caucuses in states like Iowa and Minnesota but then Paul wound up controlling the delegation because his supporters organized better for the conventions that pick delegates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 18:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rand Paul wing

Seriously? When did Rand Paul get his own wing of the GOP?  Obviously the activists protesting the rule change are left over from the Ron Paul campaign and probably have nothing to do w/ Rand.  Nice "reporting." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 23:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, Obama is innocent of any wrongdoing.  Bush and Cheney are making him order the drone strikes that have resulted in the deaths of thousands of innocent men, women and children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 01:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess that's why I'm not a Republican. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 16:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the Comments section:

She should have been executed for treason. Now the good Lord is doing the job.

Sorry, she is a traitor and as such should rot in hell - better yet: keep her in prison!

It's too bad we can't help her along her cancerous path with a little "Neck Stretch Therapy"... Treason should get what it deserves.

I do pity her, I would not wish cancer on anyone. However, she did deserve a firing squad.

And they wonder why no young people will join the Republican Party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 18:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the crowd was supportive of Rove, giving him a standing ovation as he walked on stage and applauding when university police officers escorted one protester out of the room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 18:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if he would have been charged with a crime if he had run over a child in Afghanistan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 17:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as Taliban begin spring offensive

So it's all the Taliban's fault? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 18:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Led by Sen. Rand Paul

Huh? A neoconservative leading the libertarian movement?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 16:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I'm sure it was the Hungarian troops who were responsible for the airstrike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 01:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there something untrue in the headline? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 23:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Ronald Regan (Grenada), or George H.W. Bush (Panama, Iraq, Somalia) Bill Clinton (Haiti, Serbia, Kosovo, Iraq, Afghanistan) or George W. Bush (Iraq, Afghanistan, Pakistan, Yemen, Somalia) or Barack Obama (Afghanistan, Pakistan, Yemen, Somalia, Libya). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 22:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USA! USA! USA! USA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 17:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The military has done what it needs to do, sending a clear message that there will be severe consequences for compromising classified information. Now, it should accept Manning's guilty plea, **send him away for 20 years** and move on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 16:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama did bomb the hell out of Libya, so what's your point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 23:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We know that the men and women who wear the uniform of the U.S. military are the greatest fighting force and the **greatest force for good that the world has ever known**.

Even better than Jesus? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-28 23:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing a good marketing campaign can't alter in a week or so.  Americans love to dominate and subjugate "inferior" peoples (for their own good, of course).  They don't tend to reflect too much on the trail of fetid corpses they leave behind in their wake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-28 21:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't know Americans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-28 17:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's probably what the Iraqis thought too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 18:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He can say whatever he wants and I'm free to point out how anti-libertarian it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 17:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe not, but he also doesn't scaremonger about its use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 17:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't want anyone to be fooled into thinking Rand Paul is a Ron Paul-style libertarian b/c he's not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 17:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taking a quote "out of context" by simply stating exactly what he said?  Once again, Rand Paul is trying to have it both ways:  He's pro-Drug War but against having pot smokers of certain age groups go to prison for violating laws he supports.  If pot is "a bad thing to do" and thus there s/b laws criminalizing its use, why shouldn't a 13 year old kid go to prison for using it just like someone who is 35?  

Pot "takes away your incentive to work?"  That's a Newt Gingrich level of drug hysteria propaganda.  Truly pathetic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 17:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Explain to me why smoking pot is "a bad thing to do." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 21:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bush is a monster but this death goes on Obama's tally, not his.  If you're being honest, and not simply a partisan, then you would have to admit this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 23:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This poor guy still doesn't understand why he lost the election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 23:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Railway police said the soldiers were acting up on a Dongducheon-to-Incheon train on the night of Feb. 2  playing a boom box loudly while dancing and shouting  when a Korean woman in her early 20s asked them to quiet down.

That prompted the soldiers to verbally and physically harass the woman, while taking video and photos of her, police said. During the confrontation, one or more of the soldiers may have touched her breasts, they said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-13 17:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Jeb Bush: 'History will be kind to my brother'](http://firstread.nbcnews.com/_news/2013/03/10/17257330-jeb-bush-history-will-be-kind-to-my-brother?lite) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-13 17:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Gary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 18:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the language of the DoD, not me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 16:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Remote Warfare Troops" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 15:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So The Surge didn't work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 23:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He said dozens of families have already moved out of his home village of Deh Afghanan because of alleged mistreatment by the special forces and their Afghan partners. He alleged that both "beat people and make our lives miserable."

"This is no life for us or for our children," he said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 18:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Earlier on Monday, police in Kabul said two civilian lorry drivers were killed and one wounded when they were fired on by an Isaf convoy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-10 02:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should have spent more time on the piece if he didn't want to be misunderstood.  Just my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-09 23:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But how do you "misspeak" when writing an op-ed for the Washington Post?  He could have ended the sentence with "no American should be killed by a drone," yet he continued.  Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-09 20:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-09 20:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [N]o American should be killed by a drone **without first being charged with a crime.**

This language is intentional.  He's saying he's for execution by drone so long as due process is followed.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-09 20:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [N]o American should be killed by a drone **without first being charged with a crime**.

This language has to be intentional.  Clintonian way to be on both sides of the issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-09 01:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I knew this was why I was doing it," said sculptor Greg Marra. "**It was divine inspiration**."

Well, at least Jesus approves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 17:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $33 million seems a tad excessive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-06 22:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure you watch the video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 16:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it's a good thing then that the Soviet Union disintegrated two decades ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 18:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Afterward, his wife, Rebecca, told reporters the incident has made life awful for her family and nearly wrecked them financially.

She said she was proud of her husband, who now works as a firearms instructor, for standing up for himself. "We didn't do anything wrong. We don't have anything to apologize for," she said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 17:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're supposed to worship these guys, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 21:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you kiss your Mother with that mouth?  Try to learn how to debate w/out using gutter language every other sentence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 19:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You *did* have another option: not voting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 18:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound like Sean Hannity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 18:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seriously think I supported Mitt Romney?  He would have been a murderous monster, just like Obama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 18:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One morning recently, a teenager named Bacha Zarina was collecting firewood on her family's small farm in eastern Afghanistan. About 30 yards away, as family members recall, two Taliban commanders stood outside a house.

A missile screamed down from the sky, killing the two men instantly. Two chunks of shrapnel flew at Bacha Zarina and lodged in her left side.

Her family raced her to the nearest hospital, a half-hour's drive away, but she died en route, an accidental victim of the rapidly escalating U.S.-led campaign of drone strikes in Afghanistan. **She was 14 or 15 years old.**

Yes, your hero kills children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 18:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The use of armed drones is likely to accelerate as most of the 66,000 U.S. troops in the country are due to withdraw by the end of 2014. **The remotely piloted long-range aircraft, which kill targets with virtually no risk to American lives, carry an unmistakable attraction for military commanders.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 17:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you know that?  Do you really think Obama would hesitate to order someone's death just because that person happens to be w/in the confines of U.S. territory? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 17:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Furst-Ramdohr says the group couldn't understand how the German people had been so easily led into supporting the Nazi Party and its ideology.

"They must have been able to tell how bad things were, it was ridiculous," she says </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-21 16:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drone strikes, President Barack Obamas signature tactic for killing suspected al-Qaida and other extremist fighters, have been very effective, said Graham. It's a weapon that needs to be used. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-18 17:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "truths" we're taught to believe from birth - whether nationalistic, religious, or cultural - should be the ones treated with the greatest skepticism if we continue to embrace them in adulthood, precisely because the probability is so great that we've embraced them because we were trained to, or because our subjective influences led us to them, and not because we've rationally assessed them to be true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-17 01:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats when it crystallized: Rand Paul and Hillary Clinton are very similar in that they are both very smart, unlikeable people who are not above unethical actions if they think it will get them what they want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 19:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Rand Paul persists on going demagogic on Hagel, he will have established beyond any serious doubt that regardless of who his father is, he is Bill Kristol and Jennifer Rubins boy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 05:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, you say. But todays war is entirely different: no front line, no end in sight.

So what? **Its the jihadists who decided to make the world a battlefield and to wage war in perpetuity. Until they abandon the field, what choice do we have but to carry the fight to them?** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 00:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We meet this morning in the eleventh hour ..., said Committee Chairman Rep. Buck McKeon, R-Calif. Now it appears that this self-inflicted wound is poised to cripple our military in just a few days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-13 16:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Along with the civilians, four insurgents were killed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 22:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So that makes it right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 21:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U.S. foreign policy is aggressive, reckless, belligerent, and meddling. We dont need a foreign policy that strikes a balance. We dont need a foreign policy that we can afford. We dont need a foreign policy that is like Reagans. We dont need a foreign policy that is less interventionist. We need a wholesale repudiation of the past century of an evil and murderous U.S. foreign policy.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 18:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quote begins around 4:35 of the video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 17:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 00:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only problem w/ your assertion is that I didn't write the headline.  If you had followed the link, you would have noticed that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 00:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USA! USA! USA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 20:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't state in that clip that he would be the sole judge of whether an actual rape had occurred.

Have you ever read the newsletters?  The language in them is typical of what was being said by the Right after the LA riots and hardly "racist."  In fact, he has said on numerous occasions that he has some moral responsibility for what was published.

I am not a cult member.  If Ron Paul ever veered from his libertarian non-interventionist beliefs, I would abandon him immediately.  My guess is that you cannot say the same w/ respect to Barack Obama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 17:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for posting the link.  Ron Paul is simply stating that there has to be some evidence of an actual (he uses the admittedly more clumsy word "honest") rape b/f he would *personally* agree with any measure to stave off a pregnancy.  He didn't say he would send in stormtroopers and put the hospital staff and woman in prison.  You're reading what you want to into his statement and not listening to what he actually said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 04:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the link.  I'll believe the quote when you post it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 00:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you talking about?  How about you post a link to the comment you're referring to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 16:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're supposed to worship these guys, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-03 23:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that in American patriotism = support for endless war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-02 02:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You noticed he didn't say, "Why do we have to pay *Israel*?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 22:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a real article.  Follow the link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 21:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder who wrote Inhofe's speech for him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 20:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before he even made his opening statement, Mr. Hagel faced a blast of objections from the ranking Republican on the committee, Senator James M. Inhofe of Oklahoma, who told Mr. Hagel that he would not vote for him because of his position of **appeasing Americas adversaries.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 18:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dangers to the economy of across-the-board budget reductions

Huh? So that money won't be spent elsewhere in more productive areas of the economy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-28 17:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US itself is the world's leading cyber-aggressor. A major purpose of this expansion is to strengthen the US's ability to destroy other nations with cyber-attacks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 18:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paul, who has not been coy about his interest in running for the 2016 Republican presidential nomination, perked up when the interviewer framed a question by saying, lets say you become President Paul at some point in the future.

I like the ring of that, Paul interjected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 00:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So b/c women weren't allowed to kill Afghans and Iraqis, the male soldiers thought it was okay to rape them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 22:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is the responsibility of every citizen to protect the nation, Panetta said shortly before signing a new policy memorandum that directed the armed services to integrate women fully. Every citizen who can meet the qualifications of service should have this opportunity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 22:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a creepy totalitarian-like statement.  You can just imagine Josef Stalin saying the same thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 18:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USA! USA! USA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 18:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, there are U.S. troops on the ground and they've been there for [many years](http://www.mg.co.za/article/2006-11-15-fearing-terror-threat-us-goes-back-to-basics-in-mali). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 00:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How original.  You're the first one to ever post that quote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 00:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democracy does suck.  Just look at its results: Obama, Bush, Clinton, Bush, Reagan, Carter, Ford, Nixon, Johnson... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-18 18:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Defense.gov only posts combat deaths.  They do post a report of suspected suicides every month but they do not list names even of confirmed suicides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-17 19:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "For the life of me, I don't know why the hell people have to have assault weapons."

The why is he sending them to Syria, Mali, Somalia, Yemen, Iraq, Pakistan, Afghanistan, etc.? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-16 17:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bin Laden wasn't defeated by superheroes zooming down from the sky; he was defeated by ordinary Americans who fought bravely even as they sometimes crossed moral lines, who labored greatly and intently, who gave all of themselves in both victory and defeat, in life and in death, for the defense of this nation.

USA! USA! USA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 23:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US is not committed to spreading democracy and freedom in the world. "Freedom" and "democracy" are concepts it exploits to undermine regimes that refuse to serve its interests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 23:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you're just a partisan who excuses and justifies murder b/c it's done by your guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 23:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What real difference does it make whether it's happened once or multiple times?  Obama ordered an innocent American to be killed.  He can do it again whenever he wants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 22:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then what did you vote for? Peace and non-violence? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 22:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean like the [16-yr old Denver born American](http://www.businessinsider.com/alwaki-son-yemen-16-drone-2012-10) he murdered in Yemen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 22:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the piece.  He rips Romney for being a murderous warmonger also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 21:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to think of Obama ordering a drone strike on your wife or husband, or your lover, or your children -- or you. Imagine it in every detail. Then tell me how "accepting" you are of this monster. Then tell me how you justify having voted for him, if you did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-06 15:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about we [disarm Obama](http://news.yahoo.com/drone-attack-pakistan-kills-least-10-intelligence-sources-082455837.html)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 23:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Well sadly, I think I'd rather open a business in [the United Kingdom] than the U.S.," he says. "The U.S. isit's a minefield. Open a business in California? You must be joking. The lawyers, the taxespeople talk about high taxes here. Well, yes they are high, but in America, in the places you might really want to open a businessNew York, L.A.you've got state taxes, city taxes, state income taxes, city income taxesyou add that lot up, you're paying more over there than here." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 17:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Department of Defense contends that anti-suicide programs installed throughout the armed services soon will curb military suicides  and that such initiatives already have helped douse mental-health stigmas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 18:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then maybe we should leave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 18:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they are non combatant troops

I think you're being a bit naive to believe that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 18:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The withdrawal plan always included leaving some troops in Afghanistan

Then it was never a "withdrawal" plan.  It was a try to leave the U.S. military in Afghanistan plan.

Also, don't you think 10 years is enough time to train the security forces? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 20:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Care to explain your comment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 17:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps an easier, less violent solution would be to end America's pointless, unwinnable wars.  What do you think?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 17:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please explain.  Are you denying Obama is responsible for these deaths?  If so, why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 00:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem like the angry one, not me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-30 22:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the better question would be: How much will it help the rest of the world? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-30 22:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I mean like you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-30 21:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody likes a narc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-30 17:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "surgically removing insurgent leaders"

Gotta love those military euphemisms.  Sounds so clean and precise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 18:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like he could find a better stress-relieving activity... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 19:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pot being grown in Bong County? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-27 17:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That 90% figure is ridiculous.  The majority of Taliban are simply Afghan citizens who want the U.S. out of their country.  They are fighting just like you would if, say, China was occupying America and killing your friends and family.

You killed multiple human beings for no justifiable reason, that makes you and your comrades mass murderers.  A govt-issued costume doesn't exempt you from the laws of morality.

You should check out www.ivaw.org to get a different perspective from fellow veterans.  Or, just peruse antiwar.com or reddit.com/endlesswar on a daily basis to read arguments from the other side.  Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-27 16:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case you weren't aware, bin Laden was found in Pakistan, not Afghanistan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-27 01:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are already defeated b/c this war could never be won.  If it makes you feel better to believe that you were part of some glorious military victory against a bunch of pre-industrial third-world tribesmen, then...whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-27 01:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You endanger my freedom.  You do nothing to enhance it.  You have fouled the air I breath with the smell of a miles-long trail of dead corpses.  If you think otherwise, then you are simply brainwashed and delusional.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-27 01:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's war propaganda.  Nothing else.  We won't know the true extent of the damage inflicted on the Afghan people until our army withdraws in defeat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-27 00:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've "accomplished" nothing other than destroying millions of lives.  If it helps your psychological balance to think that you have, then so be it.

Every man I killed, if given the opportunity to come to America, would have comitted acts far worse than the tragedy in Connecticut.

And you're calling me ignorant?  You're just spouting a warmonger talking points.  Yeah, you killed those people so women could learn to read.  If you really believe that bullshit, then you probably still believe in the Easter Bunny and the Tooth Fairy.  Jesus, grow up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-27 00:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anything, you put my life in danger.  You keep no one safe by invading countries and killing people who don't threaten us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-27 00:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You participated in an unjust, unconstitutional war against a nation that never committed any violent act against America.  You can't use self-defense as an excuse b/c you never should have been in Afghanistan to begin with.  Every person you killed was an act of murder.  You're no different morally from the Newtown killer or any other mass murderer.  To me, it's actually frightening that you and your comrades sleep well at night after committing such horrifying acts.  I guess that's what psychologists refer to as psychic numbing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-26 23:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that what you mean when you say you're "protecting our freedom?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-26 23:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No Afghan ever threatened this country.  You *murdered* Afghans for absolutely no reason**.  That's something you'll have to live with for the rest of your life.

**Sorry, just b/c you were wearing a sand-colored camoflauged uniform you don't get an immorality pass.  The Ten Commandments don't have a list of exceptions.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-24 20:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a different issue

Please explain the moral difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 00:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama's killed a helluva lot more people than Bales.  Will they seek the death penalty for him also? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 00:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a free society, you would be able to buy a rocket launcher.  And if you never used it to harm others, I would have no problem with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 16:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an anarcho-capitalist, not a leftist anarchist.

Panetta has been responsible for the deaths of thousands of innocent people as head of the CIA and now as Secretary of War.  Stop supporting a mass murderer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 05:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, yes I am an anarchist.  And Leon Panetta is the war chief.  Nothing he does is "defense" related. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 05:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although they functioned as members of Petraeuss staff, they said they did not want to be paid. There are actual patriots in the world, Fred **Kagan said. It was very important to me not to be seen to be profiting from the war.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 05:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Kagans said they continued to receive salaries from their think tanks while in Afghanistan. **Kim Kagans institute is funded in part by large defense contractors.** 

At the August 2011 dinner honoring Petraeus, Kagan thanked executives from two defense contractors who sit on her institutes corporate council, DynCorp International and CACI International. The event was sponsored by General Dynamics. All three firms have business interests in the Afghan war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 03:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one likes a snitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 16:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet he gets more time than [Sgt. Robert Bales](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Bales). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 16:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The children of north-west Pakistan, it seems, are not like our children. They have no names, no pictures, no memorials of candles and flowers and teddy bears. They belong to the other: to the non-human world of bugs and grass and tissue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 20:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What difference does it make WHO planted the landmine?  The reason it's there is b/c the U.S. military invaded and destroyed Afghanistan.  Obama could have ended this atrocity on the day he became president and removed any incentive to plant IEDs.  And these girls would in all likelihood still be alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 20:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm blaming him for accelerating a war that should have ended the day he became president.  In case you're unaware, Obama is responsible for the deaths of thousands of innocent people in Iraq, Afghanistan, Pakistan, Somalia, Libya, etc.  His trail of death and horrific carnage far surpasses the evil deeds perpetuated by all of these lunatic child killers combined.  If you think that what Obama does on a daily basis is any different morally from what was done in Connecticut or Aurora then you're not being honest with yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 20:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bush should. Mitt never became president and thus had no opportunity to perpetuate an aggressive war against innocent people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 19:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great answer.  Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 18:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the difference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 04:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As expected, after it opened it was elbow to elbow, the history says. The comfort women ... had some resistance to selling themselves to men who just yesterday were the enemy, and because of differences in language and race, there were a great deal of apprehensions at first. But they were paid highly, and they gradually came to accept their work peacefully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 22:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if he weeps over the children HE kills every day in Afghanistan, Yemen and Somalia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-08 04:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You liberals is so smart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-06 18:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, killing thousands of innocent people in aggressive, undeclared wars is certainly no war crime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-03 23:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great comment.  Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-24 22:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect he isn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-23 18:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not news, but it does seem to be the [neocon talking point of the day](http://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/charles-krauthammer-why-was-there-war-in-gaza/2012/11/22/c77582e8-3412-11e2-bfd5-e202b6d7b501_story.html?hpid=z2). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-23 17:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So only tax increases, not spending cuts, will solve the debt problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-22 20:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If an American citizen really wants to advocate for neutrality on the ground that both sides are equally horrible and they're sick of the whole conflict and wish it would all just go away, then the place to begin with that advocacy is US government policy which, as unpleasant as it might be to face, has long been, and remains more than ever, a key force that drives the bloodshed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-20 18:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with being "anti-war"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-19 20:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When we met with Karzais staff it was clear that the Afghans are tired of being treated like servants in their own country, Tina Foster said. Symbolic gestures are not going to cut it anymore. They want the keys to the prison, and the ability to determine the fates of the prisoners held there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-19 17:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rand Paul will be far more of a force in the Republican Party in the coming years than his father ever was. Thats a problem for conservatives who hope the GOP remains a bulwark of common sense about national defense and foreign policy. It will also mean that one of the partys most prominent spokesmen will not be someone who will be viewed as reliably pro-Israel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-18 01:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However respectfully the views of friends are considered, **the ultimate decision over peace or war must remain in the hands of the president.**

I thought Congress was supposed to have a say, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-16 16:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, Rush has often used that term when referring to Ron Paul. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 17:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am going to be honest with you dad. I have killed a lot of men and children. Some that didnt even do anything for me to kill them. Also some that begged for mercy. I have a problem. I think I got addicted to killing people. I could kill someone go to sleep wake up and forget that it ever happened. It got normal for me to be that way. I never wanted to be this way. I just took my job way to serious. I took things to the extreme. Anyone can tell you that I changed. It is like being a completely different person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-08 18:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't imply that nor ever would. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-08 17:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your hero kills innocent men, women and children.  Grow up and deal with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 16:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [A Global Force For Good](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h3wtUCPWmeI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-30 16:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American politicians never tire of extolling the virtues of the US military, which is now commonly hailed as "the finest fighting force in the history of the world." This claim appears grotesquely at odds with reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-26 16:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Mistakes" like killing Afghan children every day for 3 and 1/2 years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-24 17:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the primary reasons war - especially protracted war - is so destructive is not merely that it kills the populations at whom it is aimed, but it also radically degrades the character of the citizenry that wages it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-21 18:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what's your Dad wrong about, Rand? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-18 17:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first step should be to impose an immediate curfew on all US military personnel, but the only real solution is the removal of all US bases from Okinawa prefecture. As long as they remain here, these crimes will continue," said Miyoko Ashimine, the member of a local womens rights group who advises female victims of sexual crime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-15 20:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, that should have been Sailor, not GI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-09 17:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dr. Ron Paul was the last chance for the GOP to reform, redefine and renew itself. Paul was sidelined and ignored. As a result, Republicans may be marching towards irrelevance and unimportance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-09 16:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perpetual War = Perpetual Employment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-09 00:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-08 18:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So horrific is the human suffering brought about by such sanctions regimes that some are beginning to argue that killing Iranians with an air attack would be more humane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
