<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6381</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 04:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't planning on doing any red. I did plan on some orange but I decided against it because of a background i may put on it in the future </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 03:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! :) like I said im really indecisive about it right now which is why im waiting to make a decision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 03:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I changed my mind! I decided im going to add more the the background on the piece, likely some blue/pink/orange tropical flowers. So its actually going to be a larger piece now rather than just the bird on its own. Perhaps. Not truly decided yet which is why im waiting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 01:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Her name is Lisa dowling she works from her home in the GTA. She's been tattooing for 20+ years so I really trust her with my pieces! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [UPDATE] had the final sit on my Quetzal thigh piece today, i'm really happy with how it turned out and I'd like to give a big thanks to Lisa Dowling for her amazing work! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 00:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 02:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My next sit is February 6th, so i'll post one soon enough! :) i actually found it to be the most painful of any of my tattoos, i have 3 others which are all black and white, this is my first colour piece. I found the most painful spots we're the top of the wings near my butt and the back portion of the bird. But definitely the wings were the worst.

Considering it is the largest piece i've had and also the longest sit at 3.5 hours i feel that was part of the reason it began to hurt quite a bit. It's also a lot of shading and colouring in one spot, but definitely a sensitive area to get a large piece like this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 00:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When my tattoo artist was positioning it she was actually talking about how important it is that the lines follow your natural curve. I agree with her, if not it makes your body look off. Im really stoked she played good attention to positioning! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 21:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She doesn't, she has a group on facebook but I believe it's closed now and only previous clients can view it. She hard to get! The wait right now is about 6 months... PM me and I'll see what we can do! Btw hi from Whitby as well :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 20:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She used to work at sinful inflictions in Whitby but ended up getting a great client base and left to work from her home! She now has a studio in her house, fully licensed and whatnot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 19:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I found it originally as a chalk drawing and loved it! Searched up the artist and saw the blurb and then was of course sure to switch it up and give my artist her own personal freedom on the piece. It translated into a tattoo really well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 18:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im thinking orange and some mauve as well. Like a tropical colour theme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 18:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you! I gave her the basic idea and said to get creative with it and she honestly hit it out of the park! It looks like a pastel/watercolour which I find really amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 17:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! On the next sit she'll be adding some orange into the blank areas and colouring the tail feathers. Im also considering adding some drop shadowing, but im not sure yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One 3 hour sit down and one more to go! Pastel coloured bird done by the ever so talented Lisa Dowling from Toronto Ontario. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 16:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 17:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How come a girl can't just like a hairy man? i hate the concept of manscaping, i think men are meant to be hairy and i don't expect him to remove his natural growth! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
