<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1598</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 01:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  or better dexterit

Might try that. I de-set the kit a few weeks back, it's cased up and waiting to be set up in my new house (will be re-skinning as well). The Zil-Bel I might return to putting it on top of the china (felt, china, felt, zil-bel, felt, wingnut). 

I have a pearl icon rack in the picture, but too many things to rack everything (it already carried the four high toms and most of the cymbals). 

You're correct on the china - I only use the tip on the right hand one. I could invert the left one, not sure if there is much advantage though.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 01:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bass drum of my Roland TD-8 has become quite unresponsive sometimes - any tips for making it work properly again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 01:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember flams are ultimately used for accent. Little things like "bass-bass-flam" work well inside longer fills. Or starting fills around the tom's on a flam (or ending on one).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 01:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Total agreement here. I haven't gigged in a few years - so the kit has grown. If I got a band back together (which I intend to do now I'm building myself a music room in my basement) then I'll probably go down to 3 toms, 2-3 crashes, ride, hi-hats, snare and bass drum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 01:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would like to get a picollo snare for the left of the hi-hat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 01:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bit of it is perspective. The four crashes are almost touching each other. Their height is eye level, which suits me well. Perhaps this picture will make it a bit easier to see:
http://i.imgur.com/mll48ib.jpg
The smallest roto-tom is awfully positioned, but it was either keep it there and balance the other two, or just remove it - it doesn't get in the way even if it is almost untouchable. Agree with your point though.

12" drum is perspective again, you could almost put a ruler along the top three toms and it would lie on all the skins. 

China's are actually the normal way round - but many people prefer them upside down. I don't - since I often play them with the stick tip in the middle. 
Floor tom's are touching, but there is a cramping issue which is why the 16" tom is a little too far to the right for comfort. 

Appreciate the thoughts though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 01:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hehe, I bought some Quick beats a few years back and sold them within a week. I do like my New Beats - had them for about 10 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 01:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps buy better sticks. Otherwise watch the technique. Swipe the cymbals rather than "slapping" them. Let your fingers and wrists bounce your strikes off your skins (and don't angle the drums to sharply). Go for accuracy on rimshots not power (i.e. to hit rim and skin perfectly together) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 01:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably the cymbals I'm most careful with. I used to invert the 14" China, but changed back a while ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 01:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I've played small venues I've been loud enough to hear over the band un miced
If I've played a bigger venue they've tended to mic the drumkit out of course. 
You can play loud without breaking sticks. Hitting cymbals in a swiping motion, keeping hands and wrists supple on skins, and going for accuracy rather than power in your rim shots. 
If you hit the kit too loud you'll just dull the sound of the drums/cymbals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 17:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good technique, particularly on cymbals, and you can get a big noise without damaging your sticks. Saves money too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 17:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I like to have it so I can use the tip or shaft of my sticks. I've only broken one stick in 15 years of playing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 15:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 16" Tom is in an awkward position. If I'm running round the tom's or playing I tend to turn towards it, but I use the 14" floor tom much more.

The small roto-tom is the only thing there almost impossible to hit due to the hi-hat rod. I keep it on the kit to help balance the bigger roto-tom on the bar that holds all 3. I need to find a solution to that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 14:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reuploaded and deleted old one since photobucket is rubbish and won't allow full size image links - used IMGR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's growing out of control aaaahhhh (pic) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 14:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 11:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steep angles tend to result in dented heads and worse resonance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cold War in Six Parts (.... in MS Paint) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 17:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My 15-yr old self's interpretation of the bible using MS paint! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 17:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone work out how to play beat at the end of Dislocated Day by Porcupine Tree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 17:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a clip of the beat: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4ZX72C2MTRE

http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v108/londonprophet/Dislocatedday.jpg is my best guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 17:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would only ever recommend Roland V-drums (having played both Roland and Yamaha). 
They also need to be a "high enough" series of V-drums to have the mesh pads on all drums. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 17:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't play too loud and have fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 17:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> K's are darker, A's are brighter, but every cymbal (even identical make and models) can be slightly different.

I prefer the A Customs, but I used  mix of A, K, and A Custom (I think I prefer the A's the most). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Debates go live across the UK on animal research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 18:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big Animal Research Debate Live at Imperial College London - Starts at 7pm UTC+1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 18:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Debates on go live animal research across the UK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 18:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 18:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Science communication </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-16 16:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moreover. Teachers are underpaid. Overworked. And the government in the UK is constantly berating them accusing them of not working hard enough. They are regarded as mid-level jobs. Why should top students be teachers as we set the system up now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-16 16:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I quit teaching after 3 years (I came in through Teach First, the UK's version of Teach For America). I don't regret doing it, but my entire life became about teaching. 

Now i get paid more and have more time to do other things i enjoy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 16:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure about responsible people, but some people who aren't PETA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Debunking the claims that animal experimentation cannot mimic human conditions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 13:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fukushima industries to name new mascot "fukuppy" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 15:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazing flaming sambuca picture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 11:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 16:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was surprised this hadn't been posted already </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Week of Animals in Research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 16:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stop motion ninja battle in lego </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 11:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Next week, 30+ universities in the UK debate whether or not to ban animal research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 11:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forget the shutdown, the sequester is still damaging modern research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 10:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using celebrities is different from using facts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 15:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 12:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair argument </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The yeast, cows and GM mice behind the Nobel Prize </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 17:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PETA pursue efforts to discredit UW-Madison after accusations found without merit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 16:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 15:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shouldn't doesn't imply moral reasoning. 
Britain shouldn't keep pumping pollutants into the atmosphere

If the reason we should or should not do something is scientific in nature, then the argument is not necessarily a moral one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biggest Debate on Animal Research Ever - 36 universities involved (plus more schools). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 12:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 12:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Baby: http://www.nature.com/news/grafted-ovaries-lead-to-successful-pregnancy-1.13845
Glands: http://www.newscientist.com/article/dn24303-mice-get-replacement-glands-grown-from-scratch.html#.Uk6UpYYm3hd
Chemotherapy: http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-24346541
Stem cells: http://www.newscientist.com/article/dn24315-neural-stem-cells-pulled-from-rats-brain-using-magnet.html#.Uk6RRoYm3hd
Jetlag: http://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/body-clock-reset-button-discovered-by-scientists-8858326.html
Botox: http://sciencenordic.com/gastric-injections-botox-might-curb-obesity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Week in Animal Research - October 1st </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 16:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unicorn in my beer - call the clergy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 13:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Primates in Medical Research [Free Ebook] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 13:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dozens of universities to debate the future of animal testing over 4 days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 12:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's a unicorn in my beer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 12:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who do you think will win the Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine - check out the top picks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 16:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2013 Nobel Prize Predictions for Physiology or Medicine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 17:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not breaking news: many scientific studies are ultimately proved wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 12:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girl who feels no pain could help treat those who do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 11:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany and Japan have poorest 50 year growth predictions across whole of OECD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-16 11:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need a couple of good evolution-information links to wean someone off Intelligent Design </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 12:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My uncle persists in believing ID. He attacks the gaps in Darwin's tree of life (despite the fact many of those gaps have been filled since Darwin and the tree itself has changed), and has now cottoned on to the arguments of Stephen Meyer. I wanted to send him TWO very good links that would help debunk the common arguments of ID proponents and provide a good show of evidence supporting evolution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Debunking the science in Breaking Bad [BBC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 15:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 15:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is the other dude? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Double Life of Dr. Hansen - the animal rights activist who also conducts it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 11:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Problem with Stark's House motto is... (Game of Thrones) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 12:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The problem with the Stark's House motto... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 12:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Depressed fish could help in the search for new drug treatments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 14:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists unveil neuron maps for mouse and fly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 11:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 11:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Spend a lot of time analysing background data
- Get all the walls neatened up with displays </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 10:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Italians have gone off the rails on science issues lately - they just introduced legislation banning breeding animals for research
http://speakingofresearch.com/2013/08/02/a-bad-week-for-medical-research-in-italy-but-science-is-fighting-back/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-05 14:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Basel Declaration had some pretty interesting papers on suggestions for improving transparency of research:
http://www.basel-declaration.org/basel-declaration/improving-the-publication-standards-of-research-involving-animals/

http://www.basel-declaration.org/basel-declaration/open-access-to-maximize-the-value-of-animal-research/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advancing Medicine through Experiments on Animals: Room for Improvement? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-05 14:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Animal Research advances this week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 18:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 17:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Likely to be very nice. Polite kids. I expect the department will have clear resources. 
FYI - Private schools are often called Independent or Public schools over here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Eye of Sauron is seen in London </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 16:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 15:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the school - what area is it in - Britain is a very diverse place.

Read the National Strategy for KS3 English. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First ever Mouse model of Hep C will reduce reliance of chimps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 12:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 10:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chemistry at Oxford </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 10:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Torture is a ridiculous dramatisation of animal research. The laws are far stricter than pet ownership, farm animals, or almost any other industry bar nuclear weaponry.
Anaesthetics must be used to reduce suffering wherever possible. Alternatives must be used where viable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 10:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the opening to the article - it echos that sentiment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MPs are making parliamentary motions based on pseudoscience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 18:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 15:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the ridiculous EDM: http://www.parliament.uk/edm/2013-14/263 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MPs fooled into signing pseudoscientific parliamentary motion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 14:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crocodiles may need their fruity five-a-day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 13:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diabetes pill has anti-ageing effect in mice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 11:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dead cell removal process gives hint about Lupus causes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 11:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Lifesaving CV of the Laboratory Mouse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-29 13:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lifesaving CV of the Laboratory Mouse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-29 13:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-29 10:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to The Times article, the drug Cisplatin (who anti-tumour properties were discovered in mice) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We have pretty much 'cured' testicular cancer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-29 10:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A week of scientific breakthroughs in pictures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-26 16:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World Hepatitis Day this Sunday - diagnosis is up around 40% in UK in last few years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 14:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taiwanese news covers the royal birth complete with pandas, robots and hover cars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 17:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 17:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 16:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It comes from Taiwan's animated news network NMA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Royal Birth - Complete with Robots, Hover Cars and Pandas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 16:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some financial literature is bad. Some of it goes beyond. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 17:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 15:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The stats are not remotely related. It's like saying that First year TFA turnover is close to 0%.

Find the stats for retention of teachers after their first two years in a single school and you'll probably find it remarkably similar to the TFA. Lots of teachers want to move on after 2-3 years to find another school with new challenges.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 15:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certainly graduating from an Ivy league doesn't automatically make you a better/worse teacher - but these are top graduates who have got into top schools and these kids can benefit from that. 

First year TFA teachers are ill equipped to go into the classroom, nonetheless studies in Louisana showed TFA'ers were "statistically significantly more effective":
http://www.nctq.org/docs/TFA_Louisiana_study.PDF
There are various other state studies as well. 

Now you point out cost, which is an issue - especially when long standing teachers experience is sorely needed (and as noted, TFA'ers often have lower retention). I do think some schools do pick TFA'ers as a cheap option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Solving the Brain: Animal research at the frontiers of Neuroscience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 11:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interactive map of Syria's rebellion (Al Jazeera) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 11:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 11:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you evidence the idea that 86% (100-14) of new traditional teachers stay at their initial placement for more than 2 years. That stat wasn't in the link you provided. 

Also, there is higher turnover at high poverty schools where TFA'ers go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 10:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why wouldn't we want the most able students to go into teaching? They weren't going so much by traditional routes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 17:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I started, around 60-90 hours

Before I quit it was more like 40-60 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 17:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The evidence that the Swedish model is not all it was cracked up to be is making Michael Gove (Education Sec) follow the Singaporean system. This is a bad move. If there was a model to follow it is the Finnish, who don't test their students until 18 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 17:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The UK has its own TFA program called Teach First. Occasionally it's attacked, however it's very popular with senior politicians.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
