<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8998</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to screw the world over with organic kitty litter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 19:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 15:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A parallel with the invention of cameras. What a coincidence.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 19:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a 22 on my mac. Definitely going to try on different screens and in different light.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to stop people from pressing the button? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 18:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we develop a strategy to prevent individuals from pressing the button, we could solve a lot of world problems. Temptation and the desire to screw someone over are just so appetizing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dax Riggs- Evil friend. A new favorite. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 03:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 20:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like taxing negative externalities and efficient energy sources...but what about the private property? What about the harsh economic impact (specifically fewer jobs and expensive infrastructure?) 
What about the environment being an bipartisan issue?
etc.
Does anyone had ideas on technological advances? or just out of the box whacky ideas? Anything!  Like photosynthesizing humans are a great answer. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My policy teacher asked me this question today: What is the answer to climate change? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit, I'm curious? What do you think the answer to climate change. You don't need to know how to get there, but what is your answer? No need to be practical.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
