<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject893</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US doctor Kent Brantly contracts Ebola as sick government official carries the deadly virus to Nigeria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 10:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hamas rejects 4-hour cease-fire extension in Gaza </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 21:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Child star Jennette McCurdy posts on a subreddit about her and explains why she and other celebrities are not roll models. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 01:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most beautiful college campus I've ever been to. Santa Barbara City College. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 09:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How in shape do you need to be to be an EMT? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 07:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I start college in the fall and they offer an EMT training/certification course. It's something I'm very interested in but I'm pretty out if shape. Lifting wise it's not that bad because I've been lifting for about 5 months now, but cardio and BF% wise I'm waaay out of shape. 237lbs, 5'9. But I have lost about 10lbs so far! Anyways would it be better to take the class and get certified once I'm more in shape or would I be good to go now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unlicensed weed dealers of Colorado, it's been about six months since recreational dispensaries officially opened, how's business? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 03:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I passed my MSF course today! However, my instructors recommended that I practice braking, clutch control, and a couple more essential skills before I actually start going for rides on the streets. How should I go about doing that? I don't have a nearby place to practice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 03:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Special thanks to /u/CongratsOnYourBike (and the rest of rideit) for [his advice](http://www.reddit.com/r/motorcycles/comments/2b5hl0/why_cant_i_use_the_clutch_properly_its_so/cj201cr). To be completely honest, I was about ready to write off motorcycles as a lost cause, but today was so fun once I got the whole pressing thing.

So I'm wondering how I can practice more. My instructors recommended that I come back and take the intermediate rider training or practice for awhile before I really try to hit the streets so I don't stall out in an intersection or something. I can work on all that friction zone stuff at my house, but to practice braking my issue is that the nearest large empty parking lot is a few miles away. Any ideas on what I should do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can't I use the clutch properly? It's so frustrating. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 21:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just finished my first day of my MSF course and they've got me on a GN125. I can't get the clutch right. I'm either rocketing off the line uncontrollably or I stall out. I get off the line correctly about 50% of the time and the rest I'm just having trouble. Do you have any tips or tricks? The parking lot we're using is weird because it's sloped a bit so you have to apply more throttle depending on ehat side youre on. I need to improve clutch control because I really do not want to fail tomorrow and have to pay another 200 dollars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have any of you seen this movie? How is it? - Why We Ride </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 08:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a study comparing motorcycle related fatalities and dangers and bicycle commuter fatalities and dangers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 03:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iirc the most dangerous place for motorcyclists is actually within the city, specifically in intersections. Which makes me wonder, why doesn't cycling have the same reputation as motorcycling? In the city a bicyclist is basically a slow motorcyclist with less protection.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 295 killed after Malaysian airliner shot down in Ukraine - US intelligence has confirmed that the plane was shot down by a radar guided missile. The origin of the missile is currently unclear. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 23:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Jen Selter's ass actually a product of all those exercises she does and how much is genetics coming into play? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 21:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/awt1S (NSFW) 

She's an instagram fitness model famous for the belfie (butt selfie) 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> KKK Gives Out Goodie Bags to Recruit New Knights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 16:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any drawback to removing the lower fairing of an EX500? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 06:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of like the look of [this bike without the fairing](http://oi44.tinypic.com/2wnd2f6.jpg)

Specifically the bit I circled in green [here](http://i.imgur.com/OEYnVqk.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does modafinil/armadafinil effect social interactions? As a socially clumsy person would using afinil for parties or dates help me with small talk and witty banter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 09:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tl;dr: Would it work as a social lubricant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that at the peak of his drug addiction Eminem was taking 40-60 valium and 20-30 vicodin a day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 08:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are KTM's really as unreliable as people seem to imply? I want a dual sport commuter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 09:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found a 2000 KTM EX250 for $1825, but I can't tell you how many times I've seen someone make a joke about getting their buddy a tool kit with their KTM. It would be my primary mode of transportation, 20 miles round trip per day on highways and surface streets. Plus however much I ride trails.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that 1522 Medals of Honor were awarded during the Civil War. That makes up almost half of all awarded Medals of Honor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 07:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in 2012 the Brighton, CO police department swore in their youngest officer, a 12 year old boy with terminal cancer that had dreamed of becoming a cop. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 03:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bartenders of reddit, what are your funniest fake ID stories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 02:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you help me choose some motorcycle shoes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 04:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm looking for a sort of casual shoe/boot that could work with most outfits. I'm not the type of guy that wears kicks or leather boots. I primarily wear Nike frees, vans, and topsiders.

I kind of like these

http://images2.revzilla.com/product_images/0070/9488/sidi_gas_shoes_zoom.jpg

And these

http://images3.revzilla.com/product_images/0069/6378/dainese_merida_shoe_black_zoom.jpg

I'm open to suggestions though. I'm buying my first bike, a GS500E in a couple weeks. It's a standard/naked.

Edit:

Here's a bunch of different shoes and boots for motorcycling. I'm not looking to spend more than $150

http://www.revzilla.com/motorcycle-boots#v2-page=1 page_size=48 sort= tab=all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL of the Hunter V. Farmer Hypothesis which argues that ADHD, specifically the hyper focus aspect, may have originated as a beneficial trait in Hunters when we were nomadic hunter-gatherers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 21:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No matter how little the chance of the condom breaking, it's still a possibility </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 10:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Awhile ago a user suggested a motorcycle jean alternative for kevlar to the RevZilla guys, anyone remember what that material was? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 22:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They posted a couple videos of tests that included a drag test and holding the material up to some kind of spinning metal wheel thing. It seemed to out perform kevlar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm looking on Craigslist for my first bike and I came across this listing. It's a decent deal for my area but I can't tell if these are red flags. Please help a newbie out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 09:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So here's the listing. It's a ninja 500

http://eugene.craigslist.org/mcy/4528619780.html


The alternative being this GS500

http://eugene.craigslist.org/mcy/4558114417.html

I know these prices aren't great for these bikes but the local market isn't great either. To get cheaper prices I'd have to go to Portland and then ride the bike through portland and on the interstate for 2hrs which I'm not sure I'd be comfortable doing right off the bat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cleavage-tastic new instagram pic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 08:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can hear music coming from downtown or the university district from college hill. What's the deal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 07:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Soldiers often report having tunnel vision while in combat. Why does this happen? Wouldn't the use of peripheral vision be help in a combat situation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 06:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *be helpful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is a 1997 GSX600 streetfighter a poor choice for a first bike? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 08:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was on Craigslist looking for bikes and I found a GSX600 streetfighter and I think I came when I saw it. 

http://i.imgur.com/b3mGlJ2.jpg

It looks like sex. How are these things when it comes to acceleration and all that jazz? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to play rage cage/guacho ball [video] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 04:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I liked this sub better with inactive mods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 04:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll start off by saying that I mean no disrespect to you, /u/WNW3. I think you're doing a fine job, but I liked the vibe of this sub when we governed ourselves. I do think that we need a mod to update the sidebar and post meetups and whatnot, but beyond that I think they should be hands off. Experimentation with subreddit dynamics is, in my opinion, a poor idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Camden police save two with heroin antidote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 09:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSV: I workout twice a day and eat salad on a regular basis now! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 09:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> M/18/5'10/SW:247/CW:???/GW:150

So six months ago I wouldn't touch a salad with a ten foot pole and the only time I did anything that would get me out of breath was when I went up stairs quickly. 4 months ago I started a strength and conditioning class at my high school which got my mile time from a ~16:40 to a ~13:15, which is great! but I wasn't progressing fast enough! So, I go to the gym twice a day now! In the early afternoon I go do a 40-60 min cardio/light lifting workout, and on the way I stop and pick up a cobb or caesar salad and a bottle of water. Then in the evening I go do a 40-60 minute light cardio/heavy lifting session. I haven't been completely keeping track of my calories but I think I'm eating around 1800-2000 per day. I've been supplementing creatine and whey protein so that I can continue to build muscle mass while in caloric deficit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is transgenderism treated with drastic surgery while other personality disorders are treated with medication and therapy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 06:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there ANY benefits at all to a detox/tteatox/juice cleanse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 07:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of want to try a [teatox](http://www.bootea.com/products/14-day-teatox), partly to prove to myself that I can, partly because I'm hoping that it'll clear my mind, and partly because I think a strict plan will help me cut calories.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ++AB and Yodi not giving a fuck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-06 20:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would it be possible to work as an EMT basic while attending college full time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-06 08:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm starting at a CC in California and I noticed that they offer an EMT course and it got me thinking. Would it be possible to work as an EMT Basic and attend school full time? The primary ambulance company in the area is AMR btw. I figure I could take the EMT course this coming term, get fully certified over spring term and start working over the summer, assuming there's a job opening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which ambulance/EMT companies and fire houses service Isla Vista? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-06 04:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which ambulance company/emt service operates in Isla Vista? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-06 02:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Santa baby </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 20:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Many of us will be first time college students soon, what are some good tips and tricks for making a good impression and getting along with our new roommates? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 20:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kate Upton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 08:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kat has been working on dat booty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 05:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do war torn countries like Afghanistan have the same rates of PTSD as countries that send their fighters abroad and then have them return? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 07:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is modup.net no longer considered a reliable supplier? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 02:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been away from the reddit nootropics community for awhile, but last time I was here everyone seemed to recommend modup.net as modafinil/armodafinil vendor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a nootropic that somebody with ADHD can use that will give a similar effect as adderall in somebody without ADHD? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 02:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any adderall-esque nootropics that will work on somebody with ADD/ADHD? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 00:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were to start a street gang based on your username what would your gang symbol be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 21:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First time I've ever seen a Motto Guzzi in the wild </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 21:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She said that it would help my skin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 20:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your opinion of liquid cleanses like juice, tea, smoothies, etc? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 07:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking about going on a cleanse for multiple reasons, one of which is to sorta kick start my weight loss because I've been stuck for a while, but also to feel more energetic and happy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your opinion of liquid cleanses like juice, tea, smoothies, etc? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 07:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jen Selter looking hot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 06:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jen selter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 03:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jen selter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 03:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever created a subreddit? How's it doing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 00:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another album </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 00:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bikini </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 00:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mini skirt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 00:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Puppy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 00:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jen Selter Album </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 00:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/Jen_Selter - A sub for sharing pictures, videos, and info about fitness model, Jen Selter! Unlike /r/Jenselter posting isn't restricted to the mods. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 23:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in the event of Sacramento being evacuated, Chico becomes the capital of California. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 09:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best annual or recurring music festival you've ever been to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 04:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a movie you've seen thet was advertised as a comedy but ended up being a sucker punch to your feelings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 09:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nicola Peltz, the new Transformers girl. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 08:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] How much would the damages caused by all of the battles in Transformers 4 cost to repair? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 07:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who have chosen popular or "fad" baby names for their kids, why did you do it? Conversely, people that have chosen obscure or "weird" baby names, why did you do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 07:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nicola Peltz, the new Transformers girl. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 05:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Because I said I would. Here's to you Capt. David Van Camp! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 04:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sacrificed yourself in the line of duty for the sake of others. That is the ultimate sacrifice. So for that, here's to you, Capt. David Van Camp. May you forever rest in peace.

http://imgur.com/a/jSOAJ

Context

http://www.reddit.com/r/cigars/comments/29d5ny/smokedrink_one_for_captain_dave_tomorrow_please/cijwryb?context=3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would a '72 Norton Commander 750 fair as a first bike? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 22:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found one for 3k and I'm tempted to pull the trigger. Would it be too powerful or too unreliable or anything like that? Im 5'9, 230 lbs, riding experience is limited to the MSF course. 

Side note, most if the bikes I'm looking at are 70's/80's motorcycles, primarily British and Japanese, are old bikes just a bad idea in terms of reliability and safety?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the Church of Scientology has a compound in CA called Gold Base that is guarded by snipers and armed gate guards. It houses a prison that practices torture, and a paramilitary training school. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 08:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is PE a graduation requirement in American High Schools? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 07:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meg   Dia -- Monster [dubstep/house] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 06:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It feels like it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 23:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does your gym have a place to do deadlifts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 08:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been to two gyms in my town (a YMCA, and a local athletic club) and neither have had an area to deadlift, nor have they had the big bumper plates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: When wild animals like bears, wolves, sharks, etc kill a human why do we invest so much effort into finding and killing it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 21:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An American reviews a McDonald's in Hong Kong. "It tastes a little bit like children's toothpaste" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 02:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GG KFC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 00:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So this picture popped up on my instagram. Wild looking bike. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 21:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favorite romantic comedies that can be enjoyed by the girl AND the guy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 05:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why does my android phone (GS5) have to split up SMS texts if they go over a character limit while iPhones can send and receive long texts without having to split them up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 02:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rescue Me: A NYC firefighter that his haunted by the cousin he lost on 9/11 struggles with alcoholism as he tries to balance the job, his family, and the family of his cousin. This show is exciting, heart wrenching, and hilarious at times. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 09:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside Combat Rescue. Helmet cameras on Air Force Pararescue Jumpers in Afghanistan document their harrowing rescues, and the medical procedures that they must perform in helicopters as they race back to the on base hospital. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 09:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that soaking the leaves, branches, and flowers of a marijuana plant in alcohol will make a THC infused alcoholic beverage called Green Dragon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 02:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Obama to Award the Medal of Honor to Sgt. Ryan Pitts For His Actions at the Battle of Wanat in the Kunar Provence of Afghanistan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 01:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Healthy options at fast food restaurant? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 22:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Often times I'm in a rush and have little money so I'm forced to go to McDonald's, BK, or DQ. What are some healthy options from drive thru restaurants? I always skip the soda. Usually at mcdonalds I'll get the 10 pc mcnuggets with medium fries. At DQ I'll get the 6 piece chicken strip basket. At BK I'll get a burger and medium satisfries </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I DB press without wobbling all over the place? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 09:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've been bench pressing for about 4 months, and in that time I've also tried DB press at least once a week, but anytime I'm using dumbells that are actually hard to lift I have trouble balancing them and keeping my wrists from wobbling and keeping them in control through the rep. I don't  have this problem when I'm bench pressing. Any tips or advice?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I DB press without wobbling the dumbells all over the place? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 07:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How does it work when I view an image from google images, click on the source page, post the link on reddit, but then when you click the link it redirects to a website or another image? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 05:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just looking at a post I recently made and when I clicked the link, which when I posted it lead to a picture of a jacket, it redirected to a porn site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Loseit, what are your favorite low calorie recipes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 04:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite breakfast of champions is:

[1 scoop of Optimum Nutrition Oats and Whey](http://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/B002DYJ0K2?vs=1) - ~200 calories

10 oz of 1% milk - 125 calories (12.5 cal an oz)

1 banana - 105 calories

Blended all together gets you a surprisingly filling ~425 calorie chocolate banana breakfast shake. Toss it in your shaker and mix occasionally to prevent the protein powder from settling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favorite foods and recipes for when you're cutting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 04:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite breakfast of low BF% champions is:

- 1 scoop of Optimum Nutrition Oats and Whey - 200 calories

- 10 oz of 1% milk - 125 calories

- 1 banana - 105 calories

Blended all together gets you a surprisingly filling 435 calorie chocolate and banana breakfast shake. Toss in shaker and mix occasionally to prevent protein powder from settling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's Next for Isla Vista? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 00:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If everybody shopped at Goodwill nobody could shop at Goodwill. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 17:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harley-Davidson Reveals Project LiveWire(TM), The First Electric Harley-Davidson Motorcycle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 17:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in 1996 Mark Harmon (Gibbs on NCIS) saved two teenage boys from a burning car wreck by using a sledge hammer to break a window, he then pulled them out of the car and dragged them to safety. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 09:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How soluble is creatine supposed to be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 03:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I purchased ON creatine monohydrate and instead of dissolving it settles on the bottom of my shaker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Macklemore ft. Allen Stone -- Neon Cathedral [hip-hop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 02:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Macklemore -- Otherside [hip-hop] This is the remix of Macklemore's otherside that was never released on an album. In my opinion it's far better. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 05:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What gym do you go to and what do you think of it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 03:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm between gyms at the moment and looking around. I'm especially interested in the snap fitness by market of choice on Willamette </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> T.I. -- Memories Back Then ft. B.o.B., Kendrick Lamar [Hip-Hop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 01:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need help choosing a beginner/intermediate lifting program </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 18:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've been lifting for about 3.5 months now and I'm at this kind of weird inbetween stage where I could really do either a beginner or intermediate workout. I'm looking for something that I can do 5-6 days per week. My primary goals are strength building, fat loss, and muscle growth. 

I'm so confused by the different workout plans and I have no idea how to decide. I've looked at a [P/P/L Routine](http://forum.bodybuilding.com/showthread.php?t=149807833) but it seems like it'll leave you with an underdeveloped lower back. I've looked at [Cory Gregory's program](http://www.bodybuilding.com/fun/cory-gregory-fitness-360-lifted-up-training.html) and that one also looks good but I would probably have to sub out day 6 for a rest day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any thoughts on Coolcicada's Push/Pull/Legs routine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 19:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking about starting this now. This would be my first legitimate workout routine, previously I've just been following a loose list of lifts set up by the weightlifting teacher at my high school but I've just graduated so I figure I should start a legit program. My goals are fat loss, strength gains, and a bit of bodybuilding. 

Here's the workout:

http://forum.bodybuilding.com/showthread.php?t=149807833

I'm concerned about underdevelopment of the lower back woth that program but I figure I can just do the variant that includes deadlifts. 

I'm also eyeing this program, but it might be a bit much. If I did it I think I'd sub out the 500 and 1000 rep days for cardio days.


http://www.bodybuilding.com/fun/cory-gregory-fitness-360-lifted-up-training.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any gyms in or near IV that are a better deal than the rec cen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 05:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is the moment that solidified my attraction to her </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 04:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GoPro Hero 3 Inside Crab Trap. Visited by a starfish. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 21:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much water should I aim to consume while on creatine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 03:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a lot of bodybuilder bro science that says 1-2gallons per day (how is that even possible???) But I'm having to dig pretty deep to get a legit answer. Anyone know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bisexuals of reddit, do you prefer dating one gender over the other for any reason? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 18:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using protein powder to lose weight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 06:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would using protein powder work to help me lose weight? My plan is to use it as a meal for breakfast and occasionally other meals if I'm in a rush. The stuff I'm looking at is 120 cal/24g protein/1g sugar per serving so I figure it's healthy enough and the protein will fill me up nicely while also help in me take a nice chunk out of my calories. I do lift and have been doing so for about 4 months.

Edit: 

Secondary question,  for meal replacement would it be better to use whey or casein? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can creatine work at all if taken on an irregular basis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 05:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to lose weight but I don't want to lose my gains. Would it work for me to take creatine for a week every once in a while or a few days a month so that I can pack on some muscle without getting the water weight side effect of regular creatine use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creatine as a cognitive enhancer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 10:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone have a clip of the sex scene from "A little help" with audio? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 04:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My meds don't seem to bw working as well anymore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 04:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My doctor put me on 150mg of welbutrin about 3 months ago and it worked for a while but it seems like my depression is coming back. Not as badly as before but it's definitely there. I'm going off to college im two and a half months so do you think it'd be best to ask my doctor to bump me up to 300mg or to wait and ask the college medical center? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clavicle hurts after doing modified dips. M/18/2 days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 21:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was doing modified dips yesterday, feet up on a bench and hands on boxes on either side of me, and after the first rep my collarbone started hurting like a bizatch. I could only do one more before the pain became unbearable. It hurt for about ten minutes afterwards and then went away and I continued my workout, even doing bench press with no problem. I chalked ut up to me being heavy and not having trained for that exercise before. Today though my left collarbone has a slightly dull pain when I move my left arm or head. Can DOMS occur around your clavicle after dips or do I have another problem?

At the time of the workout the pain was probably a 7/10, now it's a 2 or 3/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is clavicle/collarbone pain normal when doing dips for the first time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 21:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was doing modified dips yesterday, feet up on a bench and hands on boxes on either side of me, and after the first rep my collarbone started hurting like a bizatch. I could only do one more before the pain became unbearable. It hurt for about ten minutes afterwards and then went away and I continued my workout, even doing bench press with no problem. I chalked ut up to me being heavy and not having trained for that exercise before. Today though my left collarbone has a slightly dull pain when I move my left arm or head. Can DOMS occur around your clavicle after dips or do I have another problem?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nina and her friend at the beach </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 18:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: There has yet to be a ban on same sex marriage that is ruled constitutional. Is it possible for one to be and if not why can't they overturn them all at once? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 07:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need protein powder help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 06:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm looking for a low calorie/carb/fat/sugar, high protein powder that I can use to supplement small meals. My goal is to cut weight. Here's my problem though, protein powder brands are confusing as fuck. I've been told that muscle milk is straddling the line between a genuine protein powder and a full meal replacement powder. That's the only brand I actually know of and I'm wary of consuming powders from a ranfom source.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EMSK: How to choose the best protein powder for your needs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 17:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Election results here - unless I'm reading them wrong it appears that Bill Brown has ben reelected as sheriff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 05:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> KORENGAL - a film by Sebastian Junger (official trailer) - Korengal picks up where Restrepo left off. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 21:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the best idea you had without knowing that it already exists? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 06:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is the quality of IV Screen Printing shirts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 08:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Material,  graphic lifespan, etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why hasn't any of that land around LCC been developed into student housing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 08:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been doing this awesome bench press exercise but I don't know what it's called. Can anyone help me out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 05:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a modification of your standard bench press sets. I put my usual BP weight, 25 each side, on the bars using 5lb plates. I do 10 reps for each set, and remove 10lbs after every set. For the last three sets I increase the number of reps by 5 so that on my very last set I'm doing 25 reps with just the bar. My friend that showed it to me called it a burnout but I've come to learn that a burnout is something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best diet for both maintaining and gaining muscle and losing weight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 20:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been lifting for about 3.5 months now. Gained a bit of muscle, haven't lost any weight. I'd rather lose weight than gain muscle but doing both would be a huge plus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The paddle out should be an annual thing. (Repost, somehow I accidentally deleted the original post.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 03:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk if you guys saw but the Daily Nexus released a list of all the Guachos that died this year. 11 total. It also makes me wonder just how many Isla Vistans die every year. I think that every year on either may 23 or may 28 we should have a paddle out to honor all those that fell on that tragic day and all those that die each year in Isla Vista. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EMSKR: How to safely lift weights without a spotter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 03:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They're selling IV strong shirts and the proceeds will benefit the families of the victims. One problem, they're only being sold for pickup in IV, no shipping. Is there any way we can organize a system to send them to out of towners? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 04:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.hashtagfifty.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any gyms open today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-26 19:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both the DAC and the Y are closed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something for all of us to remember. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-26 05:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I mean, they say you die twice. One time when you stop breathing and a second time, a bit later on, when somebody says your name for the last time."

Let's not give that monster what he wanted. Let his second death happen when the last reporter utters his name. However, let's make sure the people that died at his hands live on forever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are the shibes up for a bit of charity? UCSB's official Facebook page just uploaded a link to donate to the victims of the Isla Vista spree shooting and their families. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 22:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone want to get the ball rolling on this?

https://www.sbfoundation.org/islavista
Here is an article on the shooting:

http://www.nbcnews.com/storyline/isla-vista-rampage/gunman-kills-least-six-uc-santa-barbara-shooting-spree-n113931

Summary: A SBCC student tired of being rejected by women decided to have his "day of retribution." He stabbed his three roommates, ~~all believed to be chinese exchange students~~ two of whom were exchange students and one was an American, and then went on a shooting spree in Isla Vista where he intended to kill sorority girls. He ended up killing two sorority girls and one male UCSB student. 7 other people were wounded either due to bullet wounds or being hit by his car. The shooter wrote a 140 page manifesto detailing his hatred of women and outlining his plan to get revenge on society. He also posted a video on YouTube which is essentially a condensed version of his manifesto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When will we learn the names of the other three victims? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 08:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three bodies have just been pulled out of the apartment of Isla Vista spree shooter Elliot Rodgers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 00:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This fucker... Saw his comment while reading an article on the shooting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 21:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When will we see a complete victim list? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 19:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Since back and spinal injuries are so dangerous and surprisingly easy to get wjy do we instinctively use our back to protect ourselves? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 07:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to suggest artists to AS for extravaganza next year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 21:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't mind a bit of dropkick murphys or blink 182.  And Radical Something even has a song about us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think I may have seen a light at the Hilyard-Amazon/E 30th intersection go green while the light for the cross street was still yellow. Anyone else notice this at that particular intersection? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 06:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's with the obsession with the girl in green shorts that danced with Diplo at extravaganza on UCSB confessions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 02:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't go, anyone got pics or vids so I can see why I too should be obsessed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whenever my land line rings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 22:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone got pics of their jeeps without the roll bar? I'd love to see, especially if it's a TJ unlimited! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 06:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Samsung Galaxy S4 has a pink line running down the right side of the screen and the touch screen is unresponsive. What do I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 07:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only way I could get it to turn off was by removing the battery which I've done twice but that didn't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I get a summer job on a ranch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 09:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to work on a ranch next summer doing work like mending fences, digging irrigation, herding cattle, but I've got no experience in agriculture. Honestly, I kind of want to do this because being a cowboy sounds like a fun adventure, even if it requires doing a lot of dirty work. Next summer will be after my freshman year of college, what kind of part time work can I get to help build my resume for this? Currently I've got a line on a construction job. What websites advertise these jobs? I'd prefer to work in Wyoming, Montana, or Colorado at a larger ranch. Thanks for your help! And I apologize if the answers seem obvious to you guys but this whole industry is confusing to a kid that grew up in a city.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were given unsupervised access to a spy satellite for one hour what would you look at? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 00:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the most recent picture of you became an internet meme what would it be used for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 21:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IE: scumbag steve type posts, bad luck brians, good guy gregs, etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Probably a stupid question, but if for a forearm tattoo does the bottom go on the wrist side of your forearm or the elbow side? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 01:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was telling my friend about a forearm tattoo I want to get that has lettering and he was saying that typically a forearm tattoo has the bottom facing the wrist and the top facing the elbow which seemed counter intuitive to me because I wouldn't be able to read my own tattoo without putting my arm in an awkward position.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the best prom proposal at your school? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 06:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most offensive thing you've ever said or done accidentally? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 19:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just found a dead friend's LinkedIn profile. Do you have a plan for your various internet accounts when you die? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 04:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the best/coolest subreddits with less than 10k people subscribed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 18:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Check out this awesome full body work out I found! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 17:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/inspiredcrowd explains to a skeptical redditor how alcoholism is both a choice and a disease by sharing a quote from his father. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 17:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the worst/most awkward date you've ever been on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 07:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A girl I know just posted this on instagram... hnng </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 05:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What has your experience with bike commuters been like in Eugene? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 03:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that we're considered one of the most bike friendly cities especially due to the bike lanes they add whenever they repave streets, but it seems exceedingly dangerous,  especially because a lot of bikers don't follow the rules of the road. I've seen one biker get hit in my years here, and I've been in and seen plenty of near misses. Just today I was walking on the bike path by SEHS and I saw some kid fly into the parking lot at 10-15 mph and nearly get hit by a car that didn't see him.

Until Eugene expands the bike path a bit more I'm afraid that I'll always view them as a bit of a nuisance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Death of Isla Vista? - Have you guys read this yet? I'm especially curious to hear what the alum think of past IV compared to the IV of the past three years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 06:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Undercover Police Issue Citations at House Parties - The Daily Nexus is covering the story IVFP story and they even used one of /u/CeeJB's photos! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 20:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do the college students party? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 03:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never really been on campus at night but last week I was driving around campus at 11 o'clock on a friday night and I was surprised that I didn't see any house parties during my travels. I'm obviously nit planning on dropping in, but I've heard that there's one street that has a bunch of parties.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone identify this jacket? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 05:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Running kills the left side of my back, what's the best alternative? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 04:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm a fat ass but I've started taking a strength and conditioning class to get in shape and lose weight. Running hurts my back like a bitch. I think I need to lose more weight before I can actually run. Should I use an elliptical, or bike, or some other stationary machine instead? 

Lifting is no problem although I did jack my back up doing SL deadlifts but it's almost back to normal now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York police end Muslim surveillance program </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 03:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sebastian Junger has made a sequel to Restrepo called Korengal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 17:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any drive thru restaurants in Eugene that aren't along the lines of McDonald's, BK, Carl's jr, etc? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 03:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically are there any that are not massive fast food chains? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a common misconception that you always see in movies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 21:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
