<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1727</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 01:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch:

[CULTURAL MARXISM: The Corruption of America ](http://youtu.be/gIdBuK7_g3M?t=2m30s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 01:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this gets more infuriating every time I see it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 21:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silly Snowden..... doesn't he know all good in the world springs forth from government and if we didn't have our wise betters in Washington loyally toiling for the public good that we would all be savaging for worms in the ground and living in huts!? That 5-year-olds would be working in mines!? That our toasters would explode and our homes would collapse!? Think god for our benevolent public servants! I can eat a ham sandwich with piece of mind now! /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 20:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ever time i ever posted anything there its got dogged.... I think the last comment I got was:

more crap from the Mises Institute clogging up the interwebs...

...so your comment is encouraging...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 20:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i heard this a while back, that illegal voting blocks have the numbers to determine close elections but as libertarians I really think we should really be welcoming these people. Not just because the statist idea of borders is an initiation of force but because most of these people are fleeing failed socialist regimes. Contrary to popular belief I bet illegals hold fundamentally libertarian beliefs. Its the Hispanic Americans that are mostly leftist...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 13:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pay around 58% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 13:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes they are called progressives... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
