<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2843</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 02:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want to see your shawls! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 02:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many people don't stuff the puffs as much as I do, so mine is going to be super heavy. I get cold really easily so I think it will be perfect!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 01:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are an inspiration!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 01:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm shooting for 400. But you can make a small quilt with 250-275. Thank you so much!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 23:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope! I use my 4s for all of them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 23:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I plan on doing Sailor Moon one day!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 23:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too! I'm on vacation and there's this amazing yarn shop nearby! I'm planning on getting at least four new yarns for this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 23:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I first started it took about 1 hour and 15 minutes to make one. But, now I can crank one out in about 50 minutes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 23:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow! I loooove your pattern! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 23:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually only stuff them with scrap yarn or cheap red heart yarn. I think it works so much better than fiber fill or poly fill. Less messy too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 23:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooooo! I'd love to see that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 17:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not yet. I'm debating whether or not to crochet them all together. It looks really neat but it spaces them out more. I like how they look all touching too, so I need to figure out what I like more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 16:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've used all different weights to make mine. The key is to keep the larger ones surrounded by medium sized ones, and then the smallest ones around the medium sized ones. I used every size yarn. Lace, fingering, worsted, and even bulky. That fuzzy one in the picture is one of the largest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Working on my Bee Keeper's quilt while relaxing in the mountains. I have 112 Hexipuffs now. Anyone else working on these? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 15:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 13:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 5'6 1/2". Gotta add that half in there. Haha. What's really weird, is when I was big, I was taller. I was 5'8" according to my doctor for about four years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will do! Keep an eye out! Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It took a year for the first 70, and I've been toning and working on my distance running this year, and I've dropped another ten. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eat less move more. Lol. ;) I'll be posting an update on my progress to /r/progresspics soon. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be posting an update of my progress in a week or so. I've lost 80 pounds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 01:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually do have some stretch marks, but they are very hard to see. I went to see a dermatologist and I was prescribed trinoin cream and had red light therapy. Thy are only visible if I stretch my skin a certain way in specific lighting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
