<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject770</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blue eyed chocolate labrador. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 14:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm just gonna jog across the street while the light OOOOOHHHHH SHIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIITTTT!!!!!!!!!!!! - [0:09] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 13:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What I wouldn't do.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 13:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I felt last night after mexican take-out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 12:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what is the nicest random act of kindness you ever witnessed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 23:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it had to be when I saw this kid, must of been like 12 or something, come out of the store with his dad holding a pack of cookies. He looked really happy with them. Then he saw a homeless guy and his dog sitting near the entrance of the shop. 
He stopped, hesitated for a second and then went up the guy, giving him his cookies. He also asked if he could pet the dog, I could see the dad wasn't to excited about that but let him proceed. He then walked away with an even bigger smile, as if he knew what he had just done was nicer then wat I'de say 75% of adults would ever do.
Really brightened up my day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Picture of my cute athiest cat who just turned 420 on Christmas! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 17:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More reddit then you'll ever need.

Disclaimer: age might be exaggerated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 16:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a belgian, AMA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 16:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAE trees?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I found old stuff in my basement, upvote for nostalgia and 90's! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 01:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm so shy. Here's me taking a random redditor's [f]ootlong up my ass. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 01:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 00:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's far from perfect but hey, who's first one was? Still kind of proud! For anyone wondering, it was either my friends that used to roll or me with one of those machine-thingies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been smoking for years but never rolled myself, this is my first one! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 00:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-27 18:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Thanks](http://i.qkme.me/3rskp7.jpg) 
 
Kidding, didn't notice that indeed but hey, this is IGTHFT, not a spelling contest :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What God tought when creating the world.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-27 14:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [DON'T UPVOTE THIS!!] I'm trying to look genuine! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-25 16:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But srsly, upvotes to the left cuz sweet karma AMIRIGHT?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-25 00:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there's one person 'X-P-special' in the room, it's her. Good lord, so bad.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-22 21:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ctrl+F 'fuck himself' was not dissapointed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-21 21:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this out on EU or just NA? 'Cause I can't seem to find it :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 21:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the replies! Going to see it tonight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question: Can you follow the Hobbit without having seen the LOTR trilogy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 21:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if this is the wrong subreddit, didn't know where else to ask this. All tips are approciated!! Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 17:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Mars](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iODdvJGpfIA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 10:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damnit, just realised what a bad timing this is, US is asleep right now.. Oh well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans, what are the stereotypes about your country you would like to set straight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 10:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

I believe most of you are well aware of some of the stereotypes the rest of the world has about the United States of America. I would like to hear your point of view about these things and what you think about them! 
Also, people who visited the US, what surprised you? What did you except to be completly different?

Thanks!

Ps:apologies should there be any mistakes, English is not my native language </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, if you could have one talent, one thing you could excel in, what would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-15 23:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As asked above, what would it be? Would you be world's best dancer? Be able to pursuade/manipulate people like no other? 
Preferably something realistic, so no superhuman powers and such..:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iTunes 11 refuses to open, help please! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-15 00:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,
So I recently upgraded to iTunes 11. Everything went great for a day or 2 but ever since then, iTunes just doensn't open anymore. I tried everything, re-installing, opening as admin, giving priority, deleted iTunes and all sub-components, cleaned registries and reinstalled. Same problem tough, just doesn't want to open..

When I try to launch it and have task manager open, it actually shows up in the list of processes, only to dissapear after a second or 5, never showing the iTunes screen or pictogram in the system bar. 
Could anyone help me please? Thanks alot!!

Info: I run Windows 7 64 bit, any other information needed, just ask! Cheers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 23:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Murica best country in the world, mmmkay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 18:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I would love a probe aswell, over a zergling tbh. Surprised probe has so few votes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 17:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found the Late Game Ward map pretty accurate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 14:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for responding! Yes, the same problem still occurs when I switch accounts. Do you have a suggestion for a subreddit that might be able to help me better? Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iTunes 11 doesn't open anymore, help please! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-13 21:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

So I recently upgraded to iTunes 11. Everything went great for a day or 2 but ever since then, iTunes just doensn't open anymore. I tried everything, re-installing, opening as admin, giving priority, deleted iTunes and all sub-components, cleaned registries and reinstalled. Same problem tough, just doesn't want to open..

When I try to launch it and have task manager open, it actually shows up in the list of processes, only to dissapear after a second or 5, never showing the iTunes screen or pictogram in the system bar. Could anyone help me please? Thanks alot!!

Info: I run Windows 7 64 bit, any other information needed, just ask! Cheers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-12 14:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am the 17%!

No seriously, it's pretty disturbing that 17% actually chose that option </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-11 12:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nevermind how fast Rengar got there, DAT FLASH!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-11 02:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smart leopard, wanting to keep the baby to stuff it untill worth eating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 22:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom used to say 'Oh, those dates on products don't mean a thing, if it looks and smells good, eat it' 
I have a pretty strong immune system now.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 00:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would love to see the final 4 players A-move the middle of the map simultaniously, would be epic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-09 20:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, if you happen to be without an ashtray, you can peel a piece of before smoking and tap your ashes in there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-09 00:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Signed up. What kind of stuff will we be trading? Things like Champions and Skins? Best of luck with this project! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-07 14:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was watching this and just knew it would end up on reddit.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-06 19:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tried this, deleted iTunes and all sub-components, cleaned registries and reinstalled. Same problem tough, just doesn't want to open :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iTunes 11 does not open anymore, help please? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-06 14:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

So I recently upgraded to iTunes 11. Everything went great for a day or 2 but ever since then, iTunes just doensn't open anymore. I tried everything, re-installing, opening as admin, giving priority.. Nothing worked.

When I try to launch it and have task manager open, it actually shows up in the list of processes, only to dissapear after a second or 5, never showing the iTunes screen or pictogram in the system bar. Could anyone help me please? Thanks alot!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Youtube sound not working? ( Sorry id repost) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-06 14:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-05 09:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually very true, well said </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just my toughts on the new Idra.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-05 00:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No need to upvote, just wanted to tell this..

Important: I'm not a native english speaker and I will try to make this nuanced as possible.

IHonestly, 've wasn't a huge fan of Idra, he was once one of the best zergs out there but then eventually just got passed by others. Nothing bad there, but he kept his 'BM' behaviour and 'I'm the best out there attitude', something wich I tought was a pretty dumb thing to do with no results to back that up. I tough that he would just keep on sinking, trying to survive on the name he once made for himself. 

Now, I must say tough, I was really impressed the last few times I've seen him play on stage, he seems to have really dedicated himself on reaching the top level again. Wich was partially what made me open his stream this evening when I was bored. There, I was pleasently surprised, I found a well-playing Idra, explaing his tactics to his viewers, interacting and not calling people bad every 5 seconds. I really enjoyed it and even felt bad for him and the other viewers when he had to stop streaming because someone tought it would be funny to do the Clan Invite glitch thing.

Just an honest story I wanted to get out there.

TLDR: Idra improved and cleaned up his act imo, best of luck for him in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iTunes doesn't open anymore since update to 11, help?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-04 23:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

So I recently upgraded to iTunes 11. Everything went great for a day or 2 but ever since then, iTunes just doensn't open anymore. I tried everything, re-installing, opening as admin, giving priority.. Nothing worked.

When I try to launch it and have task manager open, it actually shows up in the list of processes, only to dissapear after a second or 5, never showing the iTunes screen or pictogram in the system bar. Could anyone help me please? Thanks alot!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-04 22:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I speak both Dutch and French yes, how'd you know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-03 23:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, if I don't find another solution I might have to try this. Weird tough.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
