<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5015</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 17:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What software did you use to remove malware and the like? and then to keep it off the machine? I usually just go for malwarebytes/adwcleaner and an installation of nod32 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 16:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And extremely edgy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 20:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yIlaD-qa'! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 18:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why people are afraid to come to EvE as a new player. The community is absolutely horrendous, and because of it I don't blame them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 15:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seriously doubt these teens follow their culture or subculture, but you never know I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 04:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine it's like choking yourself, you'd pass out before you'd actually die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 03:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> people actually upvoting this... no wonder people in /r/realsocialengineering are calling this sub a shithole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 00:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're joking, you should have put a /s tag... just in case you're not: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Plate_smashing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 20:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When would you do this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 00:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scandi hotdogs are good. *Really* good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 11:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conan did a hilarious remote on them: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k-BkKCUBGwQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 19:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "She took the wireless adapter.. i've got another one." Best line. This isn't cringey, its actually pretty funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 14:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're either a really bad troll or really stupid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 14:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he did get paid, just 5 months late. and still no travel expenses either ($600) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 14:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> someones salty, just because he cant cast dosent mean his life is 'worthless' rofl. what an asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 23:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just switch this one, with this one... Take these two out- disable the prolinear reactor aaand i've got you control of the bridge cap'n. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TotalBiscuit's take on Ubisoft's response to the new Watch_Dogs graphics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 15:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 14:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be so fucking mad if they brought it back to the Abrams Universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 13:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how you take a hypothetical, turn it into the worst possible situation, and then apply that to 100% of cases. Impressive, really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 14:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone's a bit defensive. I don't think the person you replied too was being too serious mate... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 03:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's amazing how relatable this is. If you've ever made something, you'll see someone say it's shit, but know that you've just done something wrong, and that the concept is still strong. You'll know that next time you can do it again, but better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 14:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering a modder came out with those files not even one month later, I doubt it. They didn't trust us enough to make the decision for ourselves, now we have to not trust them anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 13:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They just didn't trust us. Now instead of us *possibly* being mad over them not finishing it, we have no choice but not to trust them anymore. It's a much higher price IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 13:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only this, but ubisoft didn't trust us to make the decision for ourselves. Okay, so the new graphics are a tad glitchy. Why not include them anyway and let people turn them on/off if they wanted to? I doubt the community would have reacted as badly to them saying 'were not finished but we're still giving you the option' as they are to them just straight up lying to us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 20:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gave them a call, probably expedited [this process.](http://i.imgur.com/lDBZX3t.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 20:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that a.. double positive? So they actually can't? Damnit man they've outsmarted us again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 20:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the world of customer service. "Now repeat after me Johnny, the customer is *always* right." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 20:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's plenty of people on Ebay with 98%+ positive feedback and they don't have to bully their customers. Pray tell  how they can do it and this person can't? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 18:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I called them and reported it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 17:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Making ISK in eve isn't about what makes you the most 'isk/hour', it's about finding the most isk/fun/hour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 17:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [obligatory picture](http://puu.sh/9xC73/376c5918f6.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 14:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 00:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent. I really liked the description in the last paragraph. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 23:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Amazing.](http://i.imgur.com/EZsNgly.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 22:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 22:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I noticed that too after posting it here. It dosen't seem like theres many up to date free recourses like this one. If anything the theory probably still holds, but the practical side of things probably dosen't (99% of the links are broken, but the software is still out there). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] NASA observes in real time the Curiosity rover being taken, by an unknown entity in a spacesuit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 21:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 13:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Travel here for the city, not for the convention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 13:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? If you use something like Airbnb you can get some pretty good accommodation for 45~ pounds a night, and if you pick the right place, a good host who is kind, and will answer any questions. 

If you eat out every day then, yes, like any other country it will be expensive, although granted it's still not 'cheap' if your making your own meals.

Not sure what you mean by a nightmare traffic system? If you mean in terms of road congestion then you're going to find that in any large city you go to, not just London.

With the mass transit you just need to use the replacement bus' services on weekends, otherwise AFAIK they're usually pretty good about keeping everything open in the week days. It's not like you won't be able to get somewhere just because they've blocked off a few tube stations.

The people are welcoming when you get to know them. The stranger culture, on the other hand, is different than most American states, you won't find strangers being quite as cuddly towards each other. For the most part however, 99% of strangers i've encountered are kind and helpful. Just like any other large city.

In terms of things 'to do', as well, there's pretty much an endless list of museums, places to visit, clubs to go to, beautiful architecture, etc etc etc.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 13:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obligatory 404 not found joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 11:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently using the ten keyless CM Storm Quickfire keyboard, am extremely happy with it. One thing I don't like though is how unless you have numock on, the arrow keys are always lit up. I'd like to have an option to just turn off all backlights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any chance of Koibu making a youtube series on DM'ing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 00:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure there's plenty of people that would watch this, and not just die hard fans of the series either. I for one am interested in being a DM and Koibu's style of DM'ing with the adaptation of 2e is really attractive to me. Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 23:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me when I say this, 90% of things said on this and the eve forums is speculation. Someone told someone something that CCP actually ghost patched two patches ago, and they still think is the truth. You're better off testing most things rather than asking them on these forums.

Citation: myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 22:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a link for you, just what i've been told. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 22:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, warm them... warm them till they burn! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 22:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Qapla'! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 21:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were testing it to see what the numbers were like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 21:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you jump through a gate and there's an EXCESSIVE ammount of cans/drones/ all around 12km~ off the gate then that's an exploit. They're actively trying to disable the cloaking mechanism for all people jumping through. Petition the GM's and they'll give you your ship back and warm the exploiters, and get rid of the items. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 06:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious, how long did it take you to get comfortable with malware analysis? Do you have a degree related to computer science? Cheers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 20:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tweeter them this link. There's no point of a boycott if they don't know it's happening, or why for that matter.

Here's a copy paste tweet for the lazy:

@PNY_Tech @kingstontech http://www.reddit.com/r/buildapc/comments/284k11/kingston_and_pny_have_been_caught_in_a_bait_and/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 07:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title and it's bias fits this subreddits circlejerk perfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 17:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really nice overview I found, if anyone has anything like this which isn't too long but provides a nice bit of information i'd be glad if you could post it here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malware Analysis: An introduction - SANS Institute </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 17:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 16:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wanted to point out your description of airstone, made me laugh because it reads like one of those infomercials (/r/hailcorporate?).

We used airstone for the patio.  It's great because it is 75% less weight than real stone, so you don't need to build any footers, yet it still looks and feels like real stone.  It's cheaper than real stone, you can only get it at Lowe's.  It's best to cut it with a hack saw, but you could also use a band saw if needed.  No need for any mortar or mess, you simply apply it with any outdoor construction adhesive (we used locktite) and you're good to go!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 10:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [mirror here](http://www.ikea.com/gb/en/images/products/grundtal-mirror__26202_PE093307_S4.JPG) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 10:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing we didn't ask for your opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 09:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three points:

1.This post reeks of insecurity. No one that's remotely successful in real life feels the need to defend themselves in a 1500 word essay to a bunch of internet strangers, unless of course they're, in some way, invested in that community. Why take the time?

I really have no interest in this game or community anymore

Seriously? See my above point.


 2.You still haven't apologized for when you did flame him. No 'sorry', no 'I guess I did something bad'. In fact, you completely avoid the matter of reconciliation and just say that the fact that you've stopped is enough. Seriously, WTF? Anyone with basic reasoning skills can see the absurdity of this.

3.The fact that you just deleted the comment you got called out on (http://i.imgur.com/rnYE344.png) means we can't trust your comment history, or your claims of not flaming him in 6 months.You even reply to that comment not with a humble or an apologetic tone, but with the words "Haha I forgot about that". Seriously? Is this how a person who works "full time in a STEM field" acts? Although TBH doing tech support is working in a STEM field too, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 20:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awesome, thank you for all your input. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 19:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the detailed answer, it's interesting hearing your perspective on it. On the thing about C/C++ i've made some pretty long programs in Java, will that come in useful? I assume people have made malware embedded in java programs before? Also, should I just randomly choose whether to go with C or C++ or perhaps go for C++ because thats closest to what I know? 

Another question, what do you mean by 'learn the PE'? Do you mean just getting an overview of it through somewhere like this website: http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/magazine/cc301805.aspx or is there a book that you could recommend? Cheers again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 03:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I should learn Assembly - Python - C - C++? Cheers for the info about the calling codes, will read up on that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 02:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers for the detailed reply. I'll definately look into that python book. What's your take on C/C++ in terms of priority to learn for analysis? I've heard that Java and C++ are quite similar so the leap wouldn't be that hard for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help with getting into Malware Analysis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 01:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already know a bit of java, from what i've heard it's useful to know C/C++ (both?), Assembly, and Python(?), which one should I learn first? 

For books, i've read on this subreddit that Malware Analyst's Cookbook and Practical Malware Analysis are the best? Any other books you'd recommend? I have a basic background in CS, nothing graduate level however. 

Would you recommend I read up on other, broader, fields before Malware Analysis, perhaps something like forensic analysis for windows?

Cheers.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 00:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are still plenty of bad extensions in the chrome webstore, many of which i've reported and have not been taken down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 19:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kill mails? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 03:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He just said it on Unfiltered. ChanmanV's vods will be up soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Richard Lewis' article about Sapinda taken down via threat of lawsuit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 02:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those wondering what happened with the Sapinda article -  http://www.reddit.com/r/leagueoflegends/comments/22pe3w/a_look_at_the_major_players_behind_the_sapinda/ Richard Lewis received a libel lawsuit for that article and thus decided to take it down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 00:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any tips for flying ECM? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your favorite book on SE? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 23:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title. I'm also interested in pentesting, both digital and physical so any recommendations there would be great (already saw this awesome post: http://www.reddit.com/r/realsocialengineering/comments/1z3qzn/looking_for_information_getting_started_in_the/)

Edit: forgot to search before, apologies for the repost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 20:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tutorial will not restart. If you want to go through them again, however, you could just make a new character for the sake of it.

Edit: To expand on the corp thing, someone like Brave Newbies or E-Uni is good for new players. E-Uni especially because one of their 'selling points' is holding classes for free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 17:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My god you perfectly captured the ambient sound. My sides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 17:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the most well put and logical sentence i've ever seen on reddit. are you a Vulcan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 17:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your electronic device shorts out do not turn it on. Turning it on will only make it short out again and thus further damage the electronics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 12:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish youtube would have something like twitch.tv where if you want to support a specific person you just unblock their domain, e.g. twitch.tv/taketv.*

I'd be more than willing to turn off adblock for the people that I want to support on youtube. Unfortunately Google seems to be the ones behind the times this time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 12:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That private chat about sandwiches sure looks Opsec, hhhehhehe. ontopic: that happens sometimes. its annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 11:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dear god my sides, someone give this man gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 11:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like in on this too, please. Any against the notion of polygamy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 05:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you get to hug a sloth? Were they soft and cuddly?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 02:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not meant to get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 21:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People downvoting you just because they don't get the reference, lol, how salty of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 17:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG /r/ladybonersgonecuddly now!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 16:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they were just ratting? im pretty new to this game so i wouldnt know that just by the kb, i was just genuinely interested in what the term carebear was used for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 16:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> uwotm8? my question was about the term carebear because i thought that was just for highsec gankers. ive seen plenty of other people too ask simply questions and get negative scores for some odd reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 15:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol. love how this subreddit downvotes legitimate questions, its pretty mindboggling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 13:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm confused, who in eve is a carebear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 16:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised I didn't notice it earlier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 00:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I know what im doing to make my isk tonight.](http://i.imgur.com/dzDsW.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 00:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is the only thing I could think of while reading your post.](http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-n9-5hkWRXps/U0Epu8vIIqI/AAAAAAAAQIg/RzUGmQ6SEoo/s320/fingerless-gloves-fedora.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 20:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Johan Liebert, anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 15:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should be possible, but only with every titan in EvE doing it within a 10 minute window. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else notice how much the ST:ENT writers love metaphors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 13:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm re watching the second half of ENT (can't stop loving that xindi story arc) and i've noticed that when one of the crew wakes up from being unconscious, they'll often say something like "It feels like a shuttlecraft just hit my head" or "it feels like I just ran into a brick wall". Anyone else notice this or am I just crazy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 02:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before you go around calling someone shit at something you better be less shit than they are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 00:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 23:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a very beautiful picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 23:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so basically like every other eve corp but just with fun coms? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 23:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are you tishu? plz no slave set pullerino. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 20:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 16:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially if you can coordinate your EWAR with your DPS alpha, it can be amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 16:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To get all the EWAR frigates to III and their EWAR skill counterparts to III required takes about 15 days. To IV takes about 42 days. This is not including required support skills like CPU Manag. IV.  This is also assuming you get base EWAR skills like Target Painting and Sensor Linking to IV to train Signal Suppression and Signature Focusing to III. Not exactly a few hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-26 13:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hate to break it to you but what the other people in this thread said was true. Apart from there being discreet similarities the games are really nothing alike. I guess if you ran a guild the managment skills would be comparable but even then it's pushing it.

If you're completely new to the game: do the tutorials, do the sisters of eve quest line. Look at this website: http://swiftandbitter.com/eve/wtd/ and find out what you want to do. Join a corp for it. Get better at it, and above all have fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-26 00:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You won't find any other syndicate corp of that size accepting people one month old, that's for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 21:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait, accurate? as in god actually does this shit? what an asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 21:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually get my cables within one week. Usually about 4 days later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 14:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought you were talking about your ui being all blurred out.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 02:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CHEERS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 23:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can i see your blackbird fit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 16:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assault frigates are good for solo pvp afaik </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 01:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You...you mean drop bears are real!??! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 21:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We even have our own water boarding center right in the depths of the MI5 building! Just insult the queen to g </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 16:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a biiig difference between trying to be a good troll and trying to get negative karma. One requires subtlety, and the people you're talking to not really sure if they're being trolled. The other requires stating one of the dozens of opinions that the hivemind will downvote, and it's a lot easier than the former. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 14:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They told me they had been watching me the entire time

are you sure they were the *real* police and not the panty police? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 08:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm laughing my ass off trying to imagine someone chuckling slyly while smuggling this fish into the bathroom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 00:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it 11 minutes long? Was it aimed to shock the viewer, possibly lowering the viewers enjoyment of the website because of it? Since you didn't counter with that i'll assume not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 00:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dosen't matter how true you think it is. It just has no place being that long or being placed on a website completely unrelated to the subject content, or being 11 minutes long, or having a shock advertisement when people just want to relax and watch video games.

Please don't try and hijack the thread to talk about your personal opinions on education. This isn't /r/education or /r/vegan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 15:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much, that was nothing but a legitimate question and yet you get downvoted for it. What a bad way to represent a community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 15:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol at the people downvoting you. I was actually wondering the same thing as your question, people are really salty and take this game way too seriously in this subreddit. You only downvote someone if they don't add anything to the conversation, not if you think they're a filthy casual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 14:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 14:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone that knows what they're talking about ELI5 the conclusions of this document? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 20:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 15:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just newbie friendly, stupid friendly!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 11:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Oh god, the onions.](http://i.imgur.com/5tRFgj1.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 10:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's decades of training behind a knife at work. Really impressive! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
