<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5173</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Audrey Hepburn's films have always been my favorite. She is such an elegant and kind woman. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 05:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will watch some foreign movies, but i 'm worrying about the understanding of the words without the subtitle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harry Potter has always been my brother's favorite movie. The spinoff film obviously will make him excited.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope they can create an excellent movie for us. Looking forward to this movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you guys are interested in horror films? I have to say that I won't watch horror films alone. I would ask my friends or my brother to watch them with me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some believe that this green color seems to be used to describe where their powers came from. However, I am still a little bit confused that this is the volcano so that the green color may be unreasonable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 10:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jackie Chan is one of my favorite Chinese actors. His action movies are really excited and excellent!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so cute and lovely. BTW, I think it looks more like a dinosaur than a dragon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The King's Speech was made on the basis of the true story happened to King George VI. here's the link of the movie. i was deeply impressed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 05:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 05:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, i think some animals may cry, too. but just not in front of human beings, or not as a baby but the adult. such as lions, apes, tigers and so on. Baby born with the human nature and since they were first brought to the world, they need to cry to announce he/she was alive and healthy. therefore, i think baby's crying is forgivable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 05:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won't mind talking about salary with my friends. I think by talking about our salary, we can know the welfare in different workplaces so that we may have the chance to choose a better job for ourselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think people's endless research will lead to the result as what happened in Rise of the Planet of the Apes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 04:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 03:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a girl, now I know all these movies. next time if I were asked to watched one of these movies, i think i would think twice to figure out whether i would agree or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 03:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what's the differences between 8mm, 70mm and other size?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 03:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two men kissing? Did you cut it down?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
