<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3482</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 19:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because you're one of 4,000,000 people to try it.  It's like the lottery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 19:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, we don't share a psychic connection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 19:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Minimum wage is less than half of what it should be."  That's very disputable and many would not agree.  Have you ever tried to hire someone with a good work ethic, someone who doesn't steal from you or try to game the system?  Well I have.  I've hired workers who are so lazy that I should pay them to stay home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 19:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should ask, "Why am I so unoriginal, what defect do I have?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 19:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe people pose this exact question, sometimes reworded, a dozen times a day every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 19:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forget the entertainment, we couldn't access our money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 19:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should message the mods directly for their response.  They don't always answer in the thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 07:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could send a condolence flower arrangement.  I've never heard of sending a gift before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 07:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Visit before moving.  Don't make the mistake of your life and regret it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 06:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a good question for /r/AskScience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 06:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regarding a potential purchase: When in doubt, be conservative and when you're sure, keep the receipt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 04:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they like it and they want to.  Nicotine is an addictive drug and this is what keeps them coming back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 18:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Governmental overreach restricting personal rights and violations of the Constitution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 09:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tiffany  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 09:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm watching in coastal NC. No problems yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 07:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps you haven't been on reddit long enough to know how unsecure these user names really are. I'd post the gawker article, but it's banned from reddit, so here's an example for you:

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Michael_Brutsch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 07:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would someone openly answer these things and bring possible retribution upon themselves? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 07:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bible says there were some dinosaurs that lived the same time as humans.  There are also images of stegosaurus carved in stone in ancient monuments at the Ta Prohm Temple near Angkor Wat in Cambodia dated during the 12th century. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 07:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Behemoth  Job 40, 41.  Also, leviathon, the fire breather with scales.  Great chapters on dinosaurs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 07:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd go straight to a homeless shelter because $1,000 won't get you anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 06:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked in the snack bar of a large department store.  I was 16. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 06:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a scary thought.  I guess I'd have to go back to tv, reading and mailing out my bills again.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 06:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Water heater.  I get hot water anytime I want it and I don't have to do a thing for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 06:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course not.  Give people time to get used to things, geez.  Why are you in such a hurry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 06:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try /r/DIY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 06:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have two stories.  My sister once darted out into the road and was hit by a car.  I watched my dad woosh! over to it, pick that car up by himself and pull that child out.  She ended up with only a broken arm and he had a bit of trouble with his shoulder for a few days.  The other incident with her and my dad: she'd taken her aquarium into the bathtub to wash it(?) while he and I were outside throwing the ball around.  All of a sudden my mom let out a blood-curdling scream and, whoosh!, he was inside that bathroom, whipped off his belt and applied it as a tourniquet around her slashed up arm because she'd dropped it and it broke.  That man could move so fast he was a blur sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 05:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Dominos pizza full of bad mushrooms.  Had to fly the next day and it was a bad, bad day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 05:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3.8, UNC-CH. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 05:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I can. http://metareddit.com/stalk?user=greatvalue2112 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 05:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Click on their name and then click the green friends button to the right of your screen under their user name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 05:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We only get to be here a short time, but, we still get the opportunity to be here.  It's like a roller coaster ride, when our time is up someone else gets on the ride.  We only get to have the ones we love in our lives for an indeterminant amount of time.  Be glad we got them at all because it could have been a far different experience.  The cycle of life is as exactly as it should be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 05:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard people call those guys every name in the book and expect them to just volunteer to load up groceries, furniture, etc. immediately after questioning their intelligence and saying all kinds of mean things to them.  Then they threaten them with a complaint if they aren't ever so happy to do it.  People are hateful to them with absolutely no reason to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 04:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see how hard they work day-in and day-out.  I'll never allow anyone around me to display a condescending attitude towards cart pushers again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 03:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burning crosses in the front yards of my friends' homes while riding the bus to school.  Those that had picture windows had them broken by bricks at least once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 03:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I don't need any more sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 03:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can message one of the mods and ask permission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 03:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 03:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spades.  It's how I earned the down payment for my first house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 03:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basic bookkeeping and child care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 03:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Jack Russell does this too.  I guess the floor is of superior quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 03:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From an old trivia room on IRC years ago.  Playing and chatting lead to meeting and we've been good friends for 15 years now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 03:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dog will whine to go to McDonald's for an ice cream cone.  He doesn't allow any to drip and it's funny to watch him lick the cone before chomping it.  He's a German Shepard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 03:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8 months isn't exactly new.  Just click on comments under the post title and comment away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 02:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people I come in contact with are just insufferable.  They're boring, only want to talk about themselves and will simply tell the same lame stories to the next person they come upon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 02:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never, ever go to bed mad.  Settle your differences first.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 02:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 01:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also [posted here](http://www.reddit.com/r/WTF/comments/1km60s/a_disgusting_letter_sent_by_a_mother_against/) earlier today by another user.  How many mothers does this kid have? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 23:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it was just a rainbow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 22:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2013 Dodge Avenger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 21:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corruption in the managing structure of those charities account for most of the dollars donated.  Few dollars actually see their way through to those that need it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 21:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, racist jokes' on you.  The aliens are black. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 19:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Five days while I was in the hospital and didn't feel hungry at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 19:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8 hard years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 19:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITT "mankind" means only the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 06:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not yet, it's not high enough this week.  Soon.  Very soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 06:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if I won the mega-millions and my after tax take home was $300 million? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 19:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more than confidence, it helps them create the image of their own self-worth as a female.  It's unfortunate that this is what they reduce themselves to, a body with all the nice, pretty parts, instead of what they have to offer as individual, creative, intelligent human beings capable of achieving far more than a common slut can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 19:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It took me a while.  I had to write them over and over before it sank in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 19:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't do it for sex, they do it to create lust in the viewer and to make themselves feel sexy and desirable.  It's about them, they desire admiration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 19:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weapons dealers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 19:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those abused animals ads and commercials.  But that was years ago, I'm immune now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 19:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give them time, they'll grow wiser as they age, just like we did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 19:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  An OP is someone who submits content, you know, posts something, text, pic or a link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 18:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think so.  Wait and see how far it goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 18:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ScienceDaily is just a press release recycling service, nothing more.  They also banned BusinessWeek, The Atlantic, Phys.org and GlobalPost.  Reddit claims these sites, among others, are guilty of artificially promoting their content to make it appear more popular. In other words, they were cheating.

http://venturebeat.com/2012/06/14/reddit-banned-domains/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 18:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that'll work great.  Now tell it to the other millions of users of this website. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 18:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shut up, listen and watch.  People often think there's something wrong simply by not contributing to a conversation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 18:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posts like this come all too often.   Do you understand that by posting a controversial opinion you're essentially asking people to volunteer for downvotes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 18:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That account has a very long and colorful history on reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 17:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apostolate

http://www.karmawhores.net/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 15:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop posting this and follow the sidebar rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 15:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to wonder if that's still true.  I would bet not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 07:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, sorry, I guess they weren't tanks, just looked like them from what I remembered.  But they were actually [these vehicles](http://www.google.com/imgres?um=1 client=firefox-a hs=yoa rls=org.mozilla:en-US:official hl=en biw=1787 bih=843 tbm=isch tbnid=LvByqMace6_gaM: imgrefurl=http://libn.com/2013/04/19/manhunt-in-boston-after-bombing-suspect-is-killed/ docid=SmsPaxCZ7xW7jM imgurl=http://libn.com/files/2013/04/Police-Converge-Mass_Edit1.jpg w=1296 h=865 ei=mA0PUvfRB4moyAHO94A4 zoom=1 ved=1t:3588,r:2,s:0,i:85 iact=rc page=1 tbnh=179 tbnw=275 start=0 ndsp=25 tx=154 ty=71). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 07:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they sent tanks into Boston looking for the bombers.  The drones are used in many areas.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 07:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you saying criminals in America have drones and armored tanks like they used during the Boston bombing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 07:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disband the NSA and recall all military grade equipment from local police forces, including drones and surveillance aircraft.  Decriminalize marijuana retroactively and make medical marijuana more easily available to those that need it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 06:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't even know it was the plumber. The man was hired to do a job and he did it. It could have been your landlord or maintenance man  peeking around at the place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 06:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you aren't missing anything stop being so paranoid.  He used your toilet, so what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 06:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The variety of info I can access.  From the mundane to the outrageous, I can find interesting things to keep my attention.  I learn in some, laugh at some and share bits and pieces of life with people I'll never meet.  I read the news here first, see the pulse of politics from all sides, read science, history and technology articles and never miss the latest videos, films and documentaries.  This site gives me something to think and talk about every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 06:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, not everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 06:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start by spell checking your question before posting it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 05:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think diversity is the spice of life.  I'm a grandmother from the south, used to all kinds of people, and I say the more the merrier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 05:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who says they're fine with it?  No one has even tasted it yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 05:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking of Straight Talk at $45 per month unlimited, but I don't think they support the S3.  You might want to try US Cellular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 05:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original poster = you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 05:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What phones do you want to keep?  Does Verizon have good coverage where you live?  Do you travel often? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 04:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These few words have become a major statement on human rights and  have been called "the most potent and consequential words in American history."  We're different, but equal in importance in our own right to pursue safety, happiness and our own well-being.   We are born equal. Society and personal agendas, not self-evident truth, changes and perverts that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 04:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course we are.  No one is born better than any other and we all got here the same way.  What cultures decide to do with that truth is another thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 04:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That all men are created equal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 03:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better have some clean pants ready for them.  Might want to warn the neighbors if they're close to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 03:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check this out:  http://www.reddit.com/r/pics/top/?sort=top t=year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 03:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 01:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Download some of these strange sounds onto an mp3 player, sit it behind a tree or something just before they stop talking and settle in to sleep.  Wait for it, wait for it.  Position yourself with a flashlight somewhere holding it under your chin, smiling maniacally and laughing when they come out.  Wear something you wouldn't usually wear, add a hat or wig.  Put the player on repeat and have your S.O. film it.

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q5XsVZ8OgTs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 01:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What should he do when neighbors call the cops to report someone murdering a screaming boy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 10:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Gates.  I've used more products produced by his company than I have those by Jobs.  Plus, he seems to be a much nicer person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 10:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need more info on this topic.  I suggest you visit /r/Egypt and /r/PoliticalDiscussion for a more thorough examination of pertinent issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 10:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it doesn't refer to black guys, it refers to old guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 09:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If what they're doing is going to ultimately cause harm to another in some way, they're deluding themselves if they call it good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 08:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in uniform, wearing a badge and people will still ask, "Do you work here?".   I really want to say, "No, I just dress like this and hang out here to confuse people." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 08:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 08:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't mention where you live, so I'd try posting this to the subreddit for your state or city, if it's large enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 08:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 06:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These articles should give you some insight:


[The Importance of Egypt to the US Economy](http://www.arabamericangiving.org/the-importance-of-egypt-to-the-us-economy.php)


[Strengthening the U.S.-Egyptian Relationship (A CFR Paper)](http://www.cfr.org/egypt/strengthening-us-egyptian-relationship-cfr-paper/p8666)

[Egypt's New Regime and the Future of the U.S.-Egyptian Strategic Relationship](http://www.strategicstudiesinstitute.army.mil/pubs/display.cfm?pubID=1148)

[US embassy cables: Egypt's strategic importance to the US](http://www.theguardian.com/world/us-embassy-cables-documents/199866) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 06:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coastal N.C. and I pay $59 month for the same as OP, 20 down/2 up.  I'm two weeks into the billing period and usage is at 290 GBs for the month, no cap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 06:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the last I heard of him:

 http://www.reddit.com/r/SubredditDrama/comments/1hl7bl/reddit_ultrapoweruser_uandrewsmith1986_is_no_more/cavgmep?context=3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 05:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he gets his own show, good for him.  I doubt I'd watch it regularly, but he's fine for filling in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 05:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be my best friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
