<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5088</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 21:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just going to go ahead and cancel this week - see you guys next week! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 21:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just going to go ahead and cancel this week - see you guys next week! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keeping it fancy this morning - all homemade! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 21:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 18:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fyi might cancel today since there's only 2 rsvps so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 18:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might cancel today since there's only 2 rsvps so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 19:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will... eventually... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 17:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! Doesn't have to be this week, but anyone else interested in a play?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 16:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, figured out what was wrong with your chair: http://imgur.com/994F87X

tl;dr: You're dumb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 15:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree - I was shocked how similar it was tbh. I figured they were already bringing David Tennant back and they've said the killer is going to be another person so I figured it would be pretty different from the original...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 05:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sigh... /u/spacenut37 we've got a troll. Please ban. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 05:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone have a copy of Descent?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10/5 Morrisville Board Games RSVP Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 05:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CANCELED - see you guys next week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 05:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been awhile since I've seen Broadchurch but I swear huge chunks of the dialogue were verbatim from the original (not to mention the scenes themselves). I found it highly distracting even though I loved all the American counterparts on Gracepoint.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 14:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, otherwise Chinese spelling would be Mei. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Week 35 Progress Thread (3500 Words) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 07:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for the sporadic updates - work's been crazy. 

As usual please use this thread for updates and posting your snippets. Don't worry if you fall behind or miss a week, just keep on pace with the current week. As always, any discussion or feedback is encouraged but not required! If you are just joining the community never fear, just start with the current week's number of words. Each new week will start on Tuesdays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 04:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of me wants Ward to feel bad at what he did to Fitz and part of me just wants him to continue down his path of evil and openly mock Fitz's current state. Long live evil!Ward.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 04:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Fitz knows deep down because he's still a very intelligent young man, but he hasn't come to terms with that reality because he's trying to lie to himself (think Shutter Island style). I think we'll get a really heartbreaking scene when he "lets go" of dream!Simmons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 04:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They keep showing Skye's creepy (and possibly alien) dad with blood on his hands. I MUST KNOW MORE.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 04:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want to know more about Coulson's episodes. Does he blackout during these? Does he just feel an unnaturally compelled to draw these symbols and lines he sees in his head? Will it become a serious impairment as his new job as the director of SHIELD? 

And more importantly - how does this tie into the 084 and the overall season plot?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 04:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "And that's just tip of the iceberg!" 

"... now let's get out of here before the iceberg runs of out of fuel."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 04:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great episode for developing Lance's character - I'm still not quite sure I believe Lucy Lawless's character is gone for good though. I feel like she might get resurrected somehow and crawl out of her grave they made a big point of showing this episode.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 04:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still cannot get over Nathan Petrelli's molestache and European footballer hair. Dear make up department, there is a way to do too much. You have succeeded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 04:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fitz and Mack did have some great bonding moments this episode though. Though I'm afraid of liking this guy... we know what happens when the audience starts to like someone in Whedon land.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 04:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Though it would be an interesting twist if Simmons actually did leave Fitz because he's slightly brain damaged now and she just wants to work with the best and brightest to advance science. 

More likely, she's trying to use Hydra's better resources and equipment to help fix Fitz.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 04:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's in charge of Skye's wardrobe this season? They are clearly obsessed with black shirts with cutouts/random strappy lines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 04:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor Fitz - you could literally feel his frustrations coming through in the is episode. Also, it's going to be a heartbreaking scene when he realizes/comes to terms with the fact that Simmons left him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 04:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the biggest OMG moment was the preview of the next episode. I really hope Simmons is just infiltrating Hydra because she needs the resources to fix Fitz. Though it would be a nice angle if she just gave up on Fitz because he's slow now and she just wants to work with the brightest and best in pursuit of science.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 21:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Miller's Crossing, The Godfather, and Hot Fuzz.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 20:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw you'll be missed Brad. And good luck again with all your future endeavors. 

I'll forever cherish your throne - so much squishier than my current computer chair. Now if only I could figure out how to make it tilt back like it's supposed to...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 05:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I'm interested in the black and white Anthro tunic. How long is it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 06:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And humans won!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 18:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great link - I wasn't in that uber cab so I can't comment. We took one 30 mins prior and it was $45. I'm just saying as a psa everyone should be warned. I had no idea they had policies like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: Warning About Uber - Read up on their Surge Pricing Policies Before Riding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 09:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My roommate just paid $190 for a ride from downtown Raleigh to Morrisville. A regular cab would have cost right around $40. Watch out - they didn't know the fare until they were getting off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 20:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww... I'll totally play as Cally and use my move to shoot you in the face.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Script Request] St Vincent (2014) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 17:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read an article on how Ted Melfi got Bill Murray to star in his movie. Trailer looks good - would be interested if anyone has the script that interested Bill Murray enough to reach out to this first time writer/director (for a feature film).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 15:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noo you said you were coming last week!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 05:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would anyone be interested in playing Munchkin Quest this Sunday...? :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 05:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asara? Or something fantasy-ish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 00:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Awesome Covers collection.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9/28 Morrisville Long Game Day RSVP/Planning Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 23:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Board gaming is moving to Morrisville starting this week. As usual, use this place to discuss what games and food you are bringing. 

Don't forget this week is long game day - so we'll be starting at 2 PM. 

If you're new - PM me for the address.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 04:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the best so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 04:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are two scenarios I would accept: 1. Ward is a broken man all season, then gets broken out by Hydra, reasserts his evilness 2. Ward plays their sympathies, finally convinces them he's had a change of heart and then betrays them all mwhahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 04:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Milk that sympathy and then betray them all Ward!! Evil!Ward forever! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 04:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know... it was so much worse than it was first presented. :'(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 04:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL - the joys of watching live.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 04:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is she really dead though??  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 04:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG and it got worse. SO MUCH WORSE.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 04:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is she really dead though? She did just grab some weird alien tech thing right before she "died".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 04:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jed proving himself to be a true Whedon :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 04:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG IT WAS WORSE THAN I INITIALLY THOUGHT. NOOOOooooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 04:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OH SHIT OH SHIT. THAT ENDING.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 04:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coulson is too cute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 04:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw Coulson trying to act tough. Too cute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 03:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Milk that sympathy and then betray them all Ward!! Evil!Ward forever!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 03:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor Fitz :( This is probably the most real fallout/consequence of all of the events that happened at the end of last season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 03:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no Fitz!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 04:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robin Taylor is doing an awesome job. Penguin was the highlight of the pilot for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 04:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like the kid who plays Bruce is not half bad though, judging from that last scene so I'll reserve judgement on the whether or not having Bruce in the main plotline will be good or bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 04:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think cinematography really sells the grittiness of Gotham well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 04:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ditto. I was not expecting to see him in pilot so I definitely had a ! moment when he showed up. 

Really all the casting is spot on. Ben McKenzie is doing a great Gordon and Robin Taylor is a great Penguin. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 04:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup completely agree. I wish they had paced the show a little better (especially with the villains) but this is just a problem that network pilots run into. You basically have to use the first episode to hook your viewers so you need to throw every single crazy plot twist/characters into it. All the character introductions were solid though a little rushed. We should have had a couple of episodes to establish Mooney   Penguin's relationship and also a couple to establish Gordon and Harvey's relationship - that way the last scene would have been more powerful. Like Penguin realizing he's on the brink of loosing everything from his attempt at betraying Mooney and Gordon realizing the true extent of his partner's corruption would have made for a way more powerful scene. 

On a side note, everyone is wonderfully cast and I look forward to this season. This was a solid pilot and solid way of introducing all the characters very quickly.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 15:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooo... is this going to be a new service? I like. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 22:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm running a little late - will be there around 5:30.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 22:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ops sorry for the confusion, I am bringing sour cream! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 18:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Won't be necessary. EDIT: I'm doing a mango salsa and a corn side and bring sour cream.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 02:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remind me if I forget about those stools. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 19:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be there with some spinach and artichoke dip as well as fish tacos!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9/21 Brier Creek Board Games RSVP and Planning Thread (a.k.a /u/Bio-ScienceGuy's Last Hurrah!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 19:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our last meeting at /u/Bio-ScienceGuy's place before he sails off to greener waters! ;__; 

Gaming will start at 5 PM. Please post your RSVPs and food details below. Bring something special - let's make this a send off party for our awesome (though sometimes snarky) host!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Week 34 Progress Thread (3400 Words) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 03:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As usual please use this thread for updates and posting your snippets. Don't worry if you fall behind or miss a week, just keep on pace with the current week. As always, any discussion or feedback is encouraged but not required! If you are just joining the community never fear, just start with the current week's number of words. Each new week will start on Tuesdays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 08:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brooklyn Nine Nine! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 23:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got back from the beach early - heading over now. Be there around 5:30.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Week 33 Progress Thread (3300 Words) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 02:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As usual please use this thread for updates and posting your snippets. Don't worry if you fall behind or miss a week, just keep on pace with the current week. As always, any discussion or feedback is encouraged but not required! If you are just joining the community never fear, just start with the current week's number of words. Each new week will start on Tuesdays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 20:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be there with a pie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WANT TO BUY] Levi's 535 Jean Leggings, Size: 1 Short </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 21:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 21:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL - nice try.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 15:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /cryy 

Now who am I going to trade mean jabs with at board game nights?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 01:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you pay $44M to stream one season of the Blacklist? Surely no show is worth that much... for $2M/episode you could easily produce 22 solid episodes of new content.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 20:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Companies NEED competition, otherwise they turn into monopolies. And we need constant the innovation and improvement, otherwise we pay up the ass for subpar service.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 04:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to say, it improved a lot towards the latter half of the season and I actually started to get invested. I do have to agree that the pilot was one of the worst I've seen in recent memory. SO many stereotypes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 22:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I'm interested in the BR red skirt and blue Gap shorts. Will you take $25 for the both of them including shipping (I live in NC)?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Week 32 Progress Thread (3200 Words) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 20:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back from my vacation and getting back on schedule! 

As usual please use this thread for updates and posting your snippets. Don't worry if you fall behind or miss a week, just keep on pace with the current week. As always, any discussion or feedback is encouraged but not required! If you are just joining the community never fear, just start with the current week's number of words. Each new week will start on Tuesdays.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 18:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh boooo! Where are you heading off to?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 17:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Godfather! I've been watching that movie at least once a year for the last 15 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 06:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm baaaaack! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 08:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I did not but I had just applied to two different credit cards that were giving me 50,000 AA miles and 40,000 UA miles if I spent 5k in the first 3 months so worked out perfectly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 06:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used cardpool when I was buying a set of new appliances for my house (washer, dryer, fridge, stove, dishwasher) which winded up being around $5k worth of gift cards. No problems whatsoever. Make sure you stack with 20% off coupons and other promos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 22:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very eloquently put. My feelings exactly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 20:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the hat tip!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 16:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Pushing Daisies for something romantic, whimsical, and just plain unique.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Week 31 Progress Thread (3100 Words) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 16:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As usual please use this thread for updates and posting your snippets. Don't worry if you fall behind or miss a week, just keep on pace with the current week. As always, any discussion or feedback is encouraged but not required! If you are just joining the community never fear, just start with the current week's number of words. Each new week will start on Tuesdays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going to Grand Canyon/Zion National Park/etc next week - wardrobe help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 16:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm taking a road trip with my SO and we're doing a bunch of (casual) hiking and will probably be walking around outdoors for most of the day. I know it's going to be insanely hot and I've never done much hiking before - what types of clothes should I be wearing? I've heard people say looser cotton/natural fabric items or even cotton sundresses. I was originally planning on just wearing tanks/tees with gym shorts (or something similar to that) - what do you guys think? Should I throw some loose cotton sundresses in there? (Or will I look like a fool traipsing around the parks in a dress?) 

Also, any recommendations on a reasonably fashionable hat to wear? 

Thanks in advance! 

EDIT: Thanks for all the great tips. And don't worry I will definitely plan on bringing enough water and sunscreen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 20:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going to be making dinner for my parents tonight so I'm out this week. And I will be in LA   Vegas the following two weekends so I'll see everyone in Sept most likely!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Week 30 Progress Thread (3000 Words) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 22:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3000! 

As usual please use this thread for updates and posting your snippets. Don't worry if you fall behind or miss a week, just keep on pace with the current week. As always, any discussion or feedback is encouraged but not required! If you are just joining the community never fear, just start with the current week's number of words. Each new week will start on Tuesdays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 17:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snap back to reality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 17:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was almost like a "snap back to reality"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 17:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His facial expression in that picture is just perfect. Chris Pratt goofy white guy face juxtaposed with rappers trying to look their most gangster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 16:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how Chris's rapping had to be slowed down to match the beat. The man absolutely owned this song.  

Also HUGE thanks OP for doing an amazing job... now if only we could all laughing from the radio hosts edited out haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 17:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might also want to check out Firefly (TV show) and it's sequels Serenity (movie) and the Serenity comics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 16:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy crap Chris Pratt as a undercover agent posing as a hardcore biker? 10/10 would be SO awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 08:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one of those great song in movie scenes that will always be with me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 08:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This must have been incredibly difficult to shoot for both the director/crew and the actors. Practically *everything* is green screen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 15:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP the flip cam.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 18:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be there. Bringing my friend Richard again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 21:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know you can turn that off under settings by setting notifications off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 21:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for offering to do this! I sent over a very short story!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 20:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's a good tool for for highlighting adverbs and passive voice. Thanks for sharing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 16:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm now 100% on board for an Uncharted movie with Chris Pratt as Nathan Drake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 23:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **"Unspoken"**

Two characters talk about an event without ever referring to the actual event itself, but the details and repercussions are made clear through their dialogue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 21:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just did the loudest snort-cough ever in the most quiet office from reading this comment. -_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Week 29 Progress Thread (2900 Words) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 20:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As usual please use this thread for updates and posting your snippets. Don't worry if you fall behind or miss a week, just keep on pace with the current week. As always, any discussion or feedback is encouraged but not required! If you are just joining the community never fear, just start with the current week's number of words. Each new week will start on Tuesdays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 17:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is beautiful - are you a native writer of either arabic or chinese scripts?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 06:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! I am absolutely committing line to memory. My favorite super villain comparing his role to my favorite action movie villain. My day was made.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 14:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to say this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 14:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Availability heuristic in the US. I'd say Bebop probably deserves the spot for legacy, but personally I'd vote for Baccano.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 14:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should really give it another shot. There's a reason why it's a plot point that both fans and writers pretend never happened. My personal recommendation is just to skip the entire second half of season 6 starting from when it happens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 08:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this just gets more and more ridiculous every year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 06:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comment needs to be higher.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 06:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an absolutely beautiful album. Great images of daily life and fashion in Tehran and Iran in general. (Women really rock those scarves!) I had no idea the city was this modern and pretty! Thanks so much for sharing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 03:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SO good. I've seen this movie like 3 more times this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 22:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet - usually happened right before all the pre-frosh and their parents start touring the campus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 21:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL - this just makes me think of all the times they were returfing the grass near the West Campus bus stop and then you were forced to walk along those stupid diagonals to get to the bus stop instead of being able to cut across the grass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 19:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a kid in my 7th grade class who was a little weird, but one day he showed up to class one morning and he had stitched thread into his cheek (at least 3 or 4 stitches). The needle was still hanging off the end of the thread and was just grinning like crazy when people saw it. 

The teacher called for security real quick.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 18:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be there!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 19:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check your spam folder. Mine was in there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
