<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9731</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 12:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need some scratching up on your Major League movies there Roger Dorn! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 12:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know Georges line, but the free and clear reminded me of the scene when Pedro Cerano says Free and Clear, but Charlie Sheen asks 'did he day Free and Queer?' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 06:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading your title, have you watched the movie Major League part 2? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 08:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, so have I.

I abandoned them when they were full blown iOS fanboys, but now they're less biased. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 08:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Josh went to the New yorker or something posh like that, didn't he?

He was a bit of a pretentious wanker at times, but he got the job done.

Jon Rettinger is probably one of favorites and I should visit technobuffalo more.

For video reviews, Jon and MKBHD are my top picks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 21:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The verge is now the old Engadget. 

Engadget has now become what the verge used to be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 11:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That I'm aware of, then again I'm sure parts of Asia are 240v too.

Holidaying in the states, the ex didn't shut the hell up about her hairdryer not working properly EVERYWHERE we went. 

She was hoping it worked differently when we went from San Diego to New York. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 05:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys 240v? I thought that part of the world was the 110-130v range too.

Well, looks like my hairdryer would work fine there.. If I had one, and if I had hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 11:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its Reddit. There is a subreddit for every weird bit of obscure shit in the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 07:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 240v ? Aus or NZ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 07:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to post this in /r/NSFWmomoftheyear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 05:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well hang on..

I did the ota manually to lollipop. 

So far I've had no dramas, the battery is better than it was on KitKat, the phone is still very snappy and quick, and it might be a placebo effect but the camera seems better.

The only issue I have is that the 4chan app Chanu no longer works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 01:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think its time for a r/bootgirl sub to be made specifically for her.

Trashy or not, I'd sub to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 22:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well... Maybe her crotch looks like a worn boot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 08:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as that's not my family or SO in the pic, I'm all good with this post.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 07:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooohhhh she's wearing boots.

Didn't see that till it was pointed out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 12:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine showed the 'error', then told me to download it again, crashed the second time and now no new update is available.

They can't even get the bugs in the bug fix sorted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 13:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing but a positive experience every time I've dealt with Vapeking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 08:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooohhh.. THAT Herman grid illusion... Oh yeah, I knew it was that I was looking for  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 08:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any episode that's Dale centric is a winner for me.

A firefighting we will go is awesome as well, not Dale centric, but plenty of his awesomeness  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 01:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate, what about battery? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 16:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate, pretty basic, compared to the nexus 5..

- battery life
- camera
- sound quality
- screen quality

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 10:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bingo.. Well 5.2 inch I believe.

The only down side is that it doesn't have dual front speakers. 

If the Aus play store sells out of the Nexus 6, then I can be 100% sure that they only released 15 phones on launch day.

No one can be stupid enough to fork out $800aud+ for a nexus.

I cringed at paying what I did for my Nexus 9, but at least thats a tablet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 07:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well either way, this just reaffirms that the Moto X will be my replacement for the Nexus 5 I have.

Fucking nexus 6 and its stupid size. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 07:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - The Sopranos
- Seinfeld
- King of the Hill


This is my top 3 which I've personally accomplished. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 16:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was one of the nicest built phones back in its day.

From memory I think HTC released it with windows on it too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 15:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're thinking of the HTC Dream / G1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 08:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had that design in Aus, it was called the HTC Legend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 08:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where does he find those shirts? And noticed the 360 on his wrist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 20:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 chan less /b/ro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 00:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being in Aus, that date made perfect sense to me.

It's only you imperial loving clowns that get confused :)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 20:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How's your tailbone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 10:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I'm seeing lately is that The Verge has hired all of the reporters Engadget once had and vice versa.

Engadget was just a tech site for Apple fanboys, not The Verge has taken over that role. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 11:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh, I'd still tap it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 09:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Metalife isnt a scam, I feel so refreshed and full of energy. I've lost 5 pounds and haven't even left the couch.

Idiots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 09:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh? Their Banana custard rivals all the crap I've paid a fortune for from the US </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 09:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bosco? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 09:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Nan Nan?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 09:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the exact same path I'm taking.. The nexus 5 was a done deal for me, but a monstrously big phone with a hefty price tag isn't something I'm willing to just buy Willy nilly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 05:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought one on release day by sheer fluke.

I was one of the 8 people that got the first run of the Nexus 4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 10:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Count me in the club. 

I don't mind their shitty built plastic phones, with horrible battery life and over saturated screens, its Touchwiz that pisses me off the most.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 11:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Nexus One, Nexus S, Galaxy Nexus, Nexus 4, Nexus 5, Nexus 7 and just ordered a Nexus 9.. 

This sub isn't condescending at all, everyone is really friendly.

Oh.. Wait...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 07:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This whole screenshot with the OP and 'creep' is worthy of r/cringepics 

'Welcome to r/creepypms, say cheese!'

The cringe.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 13:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mate, you're not alone, I thought the same thing.

Now they just have to make their phone's take decent photos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 01:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if it didn't, the lovely Nerds on XDA would surely conjure something up for us! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 01:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a N5 and a 2012 N7,

I pulled the trigger and pre-ordered a 32gb N9 the day it was open for pre-order.

I buy every Nexus, including the dreaded heap of shit Galaxy Nexus.

The Nexus 6 will be the exception, I don't mind the price as you're paying for what you're getting, but 6 inches is just too stupidly big.

Project Volta better sort out my Nexus 5 battery life, or I'll be updating to the 2014 Moto X instead.

Just when Google finally release the dream Nexus phone, with all the hardware and build quality we have been waiting for, they fuck it right up by making it the biggest phone on the market.

Where's my Nokia 8210, I'm going back to the days when my battery lasted 3 days and the phone fit in my pocket. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 01:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's awesome that Google is listening to their userbase and including functions that have been on custom roms such as CM for a long time now, but they should've had these functions included a long time ago.

Especially the flashlight functionality, that should've been included with stock Android from the moment they made a phone with a camera and an led flash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 22:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That whiney American accent made me internal rage throughout the whole video.

She sat there filming and barking orders instead of actually doing anything.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 02:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember to pass it back on to someone who is now in the same shoes you once were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 11:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well as per some of the below comments, I hope its not.

5.9inch is fucked.

The nexus 5 is the border for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 04:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Order it to an address in Ballina :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 06:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew exactly what the video was going to be before I even clicked it.

Still watched it in its entirety. 

One of the best clips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 04:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you're right  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 01:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to remember, cigarettes tasted ok when we smoked, but you never had 4 in a row, you could see when you ran out and were left with just the butt.

When vaping, we are inhaling all types of flavours that taste awesome (most of the time) and if you really wanted to, the only stop would be you running out of juice in the tank or battery.

You definitely had too much nic and that's the feeling you get.

If you're a chain vaper and are on it quite a fair bit, maybe drop the nic to 8mg .. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 01:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been saying this since Gingerbread.. 

I want to be able to finally to a backup of my phone and then restore it app for app, message for message, icon on home screen for icon on hone screen, when I login to my new phone.

It can't be that hard.

I don't care about my music, photos are already backed up to google..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 16:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot the 21. Do  a gonewild post, claim I'm shy and a virgin, but show everyone on the internet what I ate for breakfast 2 weeks ago, with a cat in the background and an anti religion poster on the wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 15:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I didn't watch that.

I automatically thought of my son and almost shed a tear feeling the pain the dad was in the video.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 14:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to cross post this to /r/justneckbeardthings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 14:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That episode had the best Dale moments in it.. Especially when Hank finally let Dale rip on Bill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 14:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They spelt what hwat wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 13:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For any absolute beginners, I always recommend an Evod kit.

They're cheap and come complete ready to go.. If Vaping isn't for you and you don't like it, you're not stuck with an expensive bunch of equipment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 13:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! As a kid when one of our family picnics went down the usual path of one of my drunken uncles getting into a fight with another picnic goer.. 

He threatened my uncle with "you want to take this outside??!!"

The response was an instant "We are outside you fucken idiot!" 

Needless to say, everyone laughed and situation was defused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 13:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From memory, I remember reading somewhere that its the bodies way of checking that the old fella still works and the plumbing is all ok as it does its system checks and mainframe restarts while you sleep.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 14:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm probably doing it wrong, but I'm not enjoying dripping at all.. I have a Stillaire on it at the moment and its not for me, the Kayfun lite and the Stingray are a perfect match. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 11:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny this, I'm having this same issue with mine and its a day old..

Gonna try and change the pin out as a first step..

It is probably the best mod I've owned so far, especially that it's smaller than the nemesis as well!

The nemesis is now in the draw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 15:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is your name actually Yatzi? I don't know any Jewish names but that sounds Jewish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 15:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spare some change for an old buccaneer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 15:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not too bad, I'm trying to grow hair in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 06:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I almost drowned as a kid when I was caught in a really strong rip..

This article is 100%, screaming for help for some reason was the last thing on my mind, I did everything the books tell you not to do such as panic and swim against the current.

It took a while of struggling before I realised what I was doing and started to swim away from the current and not against it.

Needless to say, it scared the shot out of me and reaffirmed why I hate the beach so much.

Now that I have a son, I'm even more cautious when he is next to water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 03:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nancy, Why is John Redcorn in our shower? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 23:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's copying this guy - Trent from Punchy: http://youtu.be/0RjC-vh06_c

I hope to good he doesn't get a following, that was painfully annoying to listen to and watch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 23:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MY NAN NAN??!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 14:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/wtf has basically turned into r/mildlyinteresting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 17:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SPEAK UP FAGGOT!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 17:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! Spacedicks is my go-to subreddit for when people ask me to show them what Reddit is.

Its the 2 girls 1 cup of Reddit.

The rest will remain Blue.

Ok I lie.. I just clicked on clop clop to see what it was.. Sad world we live in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 06:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are a gentleman  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 06:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You want to advertise the bottle don't you! :)

Let me make some up mate and I'll give you a yell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 06:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once you start with this stuff it's bloody life consuming!

The hardest thing I've found is a balance in making the juice strong enough for evod / clearomiser users but not too strong from Kayfun / RDA users!

Strawberries and cream is sickly sweet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 12:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I might need to register a new account with PENIS_Juice as the username :)

Thanks again mate and the work you did is absolutely brilliant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 12:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its the one that gets the most laughs!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 12:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are a gentleman and I would be more than happy to share my recipes!

At the moment I'm only really kind of happy with my banana custard and strawberries and cream. The grape is ok but nothing crash hot in my opinion.. But I'm a little finicky! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 09:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mate you have outdone yourself.

I mean honestly outdone all expectations I had.

Bottles will be mixed up this weekend and on their way, I have all your details via pm as well.

All I need is your mg preference or do you want to mix your own? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 09:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol not attached to fonts colours etc.. And all my bottles are the standard 30ml size.

The ONLY thing that can be changed is maybe dropping the penis and balls off Nut Butter.. I love the joke being subtle :)

The grape isn't quite ready yet, but my Banana custard is and so is my Strawberries and cream.

Your concoction sounds bliss!

I have a bit of a sweet tooth, so be warned.. All my mixes are 70vg 30pg at this stage :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 08:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn it, I haven't even sold a juice yet and I already have 3 employees on the books.

Fine, you're hired.

Plus you get a free bottle of Statutory Grape from PENIS Juice Down Under (Being from Aus, this only makes sense to add to the name)

No, honestly, PM me details, I'll pay the shipping etc and send you a bottle of Juice for you to try out and tell me what you think. 

Even though technically I can't sell Nic based juices in Aus, doesn't stop me selling to the US! , So let me know the mg.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 05:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sometimes spell Jerry with a G.. And an I !!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 04:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you people understand that I will now make this a reality.

426 upvotes, to me means 426 possible customers with a sense of humour.

Thanks to User u/GhotiOuttaDHMO - I will make 'Statutory Grape' a my first flavour and send out the samples as a free give-away, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 04:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are the WINNER!

Some of them made me actually LOL

You will be my PENIS Juice Chef. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 02:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can make that juice a joint venture with you, 

A part of the new and improved PENIS range of Juices..

My PENIS Juice will be spread around in mouths world-wide, being sucked on by many people of many cultures and races..

Then it will be second hand inhaled by non vapers.

My PENIS Juice knows no bounds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 02:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Veeeery good, but I'm really liking the other recommendation of 'Baby batter' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 02:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hehe, I have.. well, About 5 mins ago I asked him how he likes my Juice in the back of his throat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 01:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not available in my country... Damn it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 01:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure what Chicago flag stars look like, the only stars I know are on the Aus flag :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 01:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm... let me consult google on this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 01:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have now just labelled my Beehive Blend.

'Milky Man Honey' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 01:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, this is clever.

Very clever.

It will be my Cookies and Cream name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 23:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Mr Floorspud - thank you!

You're little comment has now become a reality.. Like that guy that watercolours everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 23:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sure is, one of the events girls photoshopped the bow-tie on him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 14:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That boy ain't right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 14:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooohhh that's a good name.

I've been trying to figure out funny names for the juice flavours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 14:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha ha yes!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 14:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that bottle was Strawberries and cream. 


Extra creamy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 14:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to show him the comments, the guy is basically Hank Hill, his squareness will make his cringe face even better  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
