<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5807</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 17:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for adding that! I can see how my title could be misconstrued. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top 10 Junk Science/Bullshit Stories of 2013 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 17:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Material can capture mechanical energy from walking, driving, or even the wind using the triboelectric effect. A square meter of the stuff can now produce as much as 300 watts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 00:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Life on Earth may have developed below rather than above ground. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 05:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The FDA Stifles the Advance of Modern Molecular Medicine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 04:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 02:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before clicking, I thought this was going to be one of those "that's terrible but kinda funny" posts but this is actually heart-wrenching. You have to feel for Vin Diesel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have recovered the oldest human DNA to date, beating the old record by 300,000 years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 19:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the first time, scientists have succeeded in transforming human stem cells into functional lung and airway cells. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 20:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 07:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's one fiiiiiiiiiiine piece of [forced perspective](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Forced_perspective) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-22 18:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a laugh, go to the video section and watch the spokesperson try to talk up the machine while on it -- you can barely understand him because his voice is shaking in and out.

I'd wager this might impart small boosts to bone density, but as far as increasing aerobic capacity or losing weight, the effects will most likely be negligible. 

Source: http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/whole-body-vibration/AN01598 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 20:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 Tips for Analyzing Claims of a Scientific Study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 23:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 18:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found a terrific study in PubMed:

**Lifetime exercise and disk degeneration: an MRI study of monozygotic twins.**

Study: "...the effects of power sports were investigated in 12 discordant [twin] pairs (2,300 vs 200 h of weightlifting). The age range of the twins was from 35 to 69 yr.

Finding: Increased power sport participation was associated with slightly greater disk degeneration in the lower thoracic spine, but not in the lumbar spine.

Link: http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/9346167 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drinking or eating caffeine even six hours before bedtime could reduce sleep by more than one hour. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 00:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's a large volcano forming under Antarctic Ice, and it's going to erupt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 21:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 21:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This press release is terribly written.

Something to remember: Not all fat is created equal. Visceral fat, which coats internal organs in the abdominal cavity, is far more dangerous than subcutaneous fat, which is stored just underneath the skin. It doesn't look like the study made any effort to differentiate the two.

Addition: Yowzers. Nobody seems to like this comment. Here's information to back up what I'm saying. From the Harvard Medical School:

"Abdominal, or visceral, fat is of particular concern because its a key player in a variety of health problems  much more so than subcutaneous fat, the kind you can grasp with your hand. Visceral fat, on the other hand, lies out of reach, deep within the abdominal cavity, where it pads the spaces between our abdominal organs."

Link: http://www.health.harvard.edu/fhg/updates/Abdominal-fat-and-what-to-do-about-it.shtml
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 million acres of land set aside for conservation - more than Yellowstone, Everglades and Yosemite National Parks combined - have vanished and been planted with corn to make Ethanol. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 17:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 01:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do I assign flair to this? I don't see a bright yellow box under the submission... (Browser = Firefox)

Update: Looks like somebody else did. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As little as 20 minutes of moderate exercise three times per week during pregnancy enhances the newborn child's brain development </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 01:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Freakish' asteroid discovered that resembles rotating lawn sprinkler. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 18:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 22:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend lost about twenty hair ties to my roommate's orange tabby.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Male nursery spiders initiate mating by presenting the female with a "gift"  an insect prey wrapped in silk. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 20:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 17:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR

http://www.realclearscience.com/journal_club/2013/10/16/why_do_we_elect_attractive_politicians_106724.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 16:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. We've always known that muscles atrophy after disuse -- muscle is physiologically expensive for the body to maintain. What's incredible is how fast the body does away with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 16:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Precisely. I don't think people have to worry about wasting away from just days off at the gym. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever had to get a cast? A new study shows you lose a fair amount of muscle after just five days! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 06:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's an interesting new study:

"Substantial skeletal muscle loss occurs during only 5 days of disuse."
http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24168489

What did the researchers do?

"Twenty-four healthy, young (231 y) males were subjected to either 5 (n=12) or 14 (n=12) days of one-legged knee immobilization using a full leg cast."

What did they find?

"Quadriceps muscle CSA declined from baseline by 3.50.5 (P0.0001) and 8.42.8% (P0.0001), leg lean mass was reduced by 1.40.7 (P=0.07) and 3.10.7% (P0.01), and strength decreased by 9.02.3 (P0.0001) and 22.92.6% (P0.0001) following 5 and 14 days of immobilization, respectively."

The takeaway: It's amazing how fast muscles atrophy after only five days of total disuse! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New compound battles type 2 diabetes and promotes weight loss. It does this in smaller doses compared to current drugs and with minimal side effects. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 19:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eye-tracking study shows that everyone ogles women's bodies. "Both sexes fixed their gaze more on women's chests and waists and less on faces" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 00:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brain training improves memory, but it does not boost intelligence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 06:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 05:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 58% approval is nothing to scoff at, though. Polls never reached anywhere near that in the 60s, as far as I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Support for Marijuana Legalization at Its Highest Yet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 02:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interactively exercising with music can make your muscles work more efficiently and reduce strain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-16 23:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These government-made public health and safety posters from the 1930s are terrific. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-16 20:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 20:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RealClearScience actually interviewed the author of the paper. (Link: http://www.realclearscience.com/blog/2013/10/40-years-of-government-nutrition-data-may-be-flawed.html)

Here's what he said about the Coca-Cola funding: "Archer explained that it's an unrestricted research grant. In other words, the soft drink maker contractually has no input or say in what he researches or publishes."

I actually think that Coca-Cola wouldn't like the findings of the paper, because it's actually saying that people eat MORE calories than they think. Hmm now I wonder where those calories come from... soda maybe?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Love actually tastes sweet. Psychologists have found that thoughts of love cause people to rate the taste of plain water as sweeter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 16:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 16:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For all those people eating paleo diets thinking to themselves that calories in vs. calories out doesn't matter, this study reported that obese people UNDERESTIMATED their intake by about 800 calories a day. So the largest individuals in society are actually eating a lot more. Thus -- if true -- the results of this study seem to further reinforce the USDA's general stance on obesity, that we just need to eat less and exercise more.

Study is here, btw: http://www.plosone.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0076632 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 08:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glitch Gaming, an organization at the University of Minnesota, did this at the local BWWs on campus for the LCS Championship. The joint was actually at capacity, with 90% of the people there to watch the LCS. It was a blast!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 18:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to Tom Clancy's Hunt for Red October, Sean Connery played a Lithuanian submarine captain -- Marko Ramius -- resulting in the best accent mash up of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A nearby alien planet six times the size of the Earth is covered with a water-rich atmosphere that includes a strange "plasma form" of water. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 17:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A massive review of the scientific literature has found that genetically modified crops pose no significant hazards to consumers or the environment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 17:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have discovered the first physical evidence of structural brain differences that distinguish early risers from people who like to stay up late. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 08:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stereotyping isn't always morally wrong. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 06:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
