<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5236</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 17:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm proud of you too, bro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 02:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Detroit ATC here, this is actually quite common. I'd say it happens at least once or twice a month from sept to may. Has no one ever seen the pictures? I know some guy submitted a bunch last winter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 16:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I admitted to stealing government supplies, lying, cheating, and taking drugs to the special agent and psychologist interviewing me. 

I got my clearance no problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 03:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean he could have never even fought any of these guys, I mean it is an autobiography, but I like to believe he was the Shaft of his generation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 00:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From his narrative, Frederick Douglass went around chesting up to slave owners, learning to read and write through perseverance and deceit, and then became a free man who worked to tear down the institutions of slavery.

Why hasnt an action movie of this been made yet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Frederick Douglass once fought a slave master and his hand for two hours in a barn. Douglass beat the slave master so badly that the slave master never whipped Douglass again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 22:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 05:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on Africa, get your shit together... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 05:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck it, might as well skip the abuse phase and go right to the snitching </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 03:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RHODE ISLAND! RHODE ISLAND! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 03:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone must have called him the Dane Cook of his generation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 03:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pure Envy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 08:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always have pipe cleaners, duct tape, super glue, and silicon on hand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some items that you always keep around your house that always come in handy for repairs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 08:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 07:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean sorry I dont know all the big words behind it, but I dont hear you coming up with anything Mr. Sarcastic Smartguy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 07:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pou-Pou-Pou-nanny! Can't get it out your head now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 07:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a theory on this...

Our cells, know how to survive this environment. Come in contact with closely related cells from 5,000 years ago (that dont know how to survive these elements). And Bam, Science. Bam. You die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
