<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8344</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As head mod, can I physically prevent the other mods from banning people? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 04:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you can give and turn off certain things your moderators are allowed to do. Here are the categories of choices I have:

* access

* config

* flair

* mail

* posts

* wiki

Will turning off one of these prevent them from banning people? And whichever one it is, will it prevent fro doing other things as well? I only want to them to not be able to ban. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GESUNDHEIT! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 04:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Thank You] Everyone here. You may not realize it, but you bring more than just smiles. Today my mom walked! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 03:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 92 year old mom became very ill a few months ago. She did not eat for a month and didn't even recognize me much of the time. My family and I had pretty much figured it was only a matter of time. 

Figuring it was her last Christmas, I asked you all to card bomb her:




* http://www.reddit.com/r/RandomActsofCards/comments/2p172o/request_may_i_ask_a_huge_favor_from_everyone/

You did not disappoint. Slowly I saw improvement in her as I brought new cards in every time I visited. She loved them. She showed them off to others. Soon she began reading them herself. I saw the mom I once had, slowly regaining strength, eating, carrying on a conversation and she finally stopped calling me Pete (my name is Wayne).

But the incredible thing I saw today is she walked about six feet. It may not sound like much, but for me it is a miraculous. 

I know I asked you all just to make one last Christmas special for a very special lady. But you may have actually given her another Christmas as well.  You have provided her a will to live and to reason to fight. I wish I could send you all a personal thank you but there were just too many cards. But know together you did something I had given up on. 

Thank you all and may you actually get the opportunity to send more cards next Christmas. :D

train_subject8344

P.S. Whoever sent the dancing polar bear card and the snowman with the shaking butt card, you really have provided more laughter and happiness than you could have ever expected. She still shows them to me when I visit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank You to Everyone Here. You may not realize it, but you bring more than just smiles. Today my mom walked! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 03:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 92 year old mom became very ill a few months ago. She did not eat for a month and didn't even recognize me much of the time. My family and I had pretty much figured it was only a matter of time. 

iguring it was her last Christmas, I asked you all to card bomb her. You did not disappoint. 

Slowly I saw improvement in her as I brought new cards in every time I visited. She loved them. She showed them off to others. Soon she began reading them herself. I saw the mom I once had, slowly regaining strength, eating, carrying on a conversation and she finally stopped calling me Pete (my name is Wayne).

But the incredible thing I saw today is she walked about six feet. It may not sound like much, but for me it is a miraculous. 

I know I asked you all just to make one last Christmas special for a very special lady. But you may have actually given her another Christmas as well.  You have provided her a will to live and to reason to fight. I wish I could send you all a personal thank you but there were just too many cards. But know together you did something I had given up on. 

Thank you all and may you actually get the opportunity to send more cards next Christmas. :D

train_subject8344

P.S. Whoever sent the dancing polar bear card and the snowman with the shaking butt card, you really have provided more laughter and happiness than you would have ever expected. She still shows them to me when I visit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beverly Hillbilly Elly May Clampett - Dead at 81 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 07:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seeking a bot that attaches a "NEW USER" flair to the OP in our subreddit. A flair that expires after a given amount of time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 05:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run /r/Assistance    and you guys have helped us sooooo much. Yes_it_is_weird has really done some great work for us. I know he is busy so I didn't want to bug him again.

People request help in our subreddit and we want our subscribers to be aware of when a request is being made by a new user so they can use extra caution.

So we are looking for a bot the reads the age of the OP's account and gives it a special flair if it is a newer account. We would of course want that flair to disappear after a certain amount of time. 

Is this a possibility and is there anyone that might help us implement this?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't forget to post those pictures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 20:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still looking for more pics - We just love them here. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From all of us at r/assistance, here's wishing you and yours a prosperous New Year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 05:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It been a great year thanks to the many awesome people here. Thank you for all your kindness and letting us be a part of your community. :D

http://i.imgur.com/CKBXMMd.png


*"rabbit, rabbit, rabbit!"* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is /r/Assistance, if you have no assistance to offer, please keep your judgments to yourself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 07:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is our number rule. Please abide by it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank you everyone for the cards to my very sick mother </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 07:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom was barely conscious when I asked for cards to be sent to her. You guys sent over 250 cards to her and she responded in an awesome way. She can carry on a conversation and she is eating again. There is actually hope now. She is still very weak but she is now talking and even reading your cards. Words can not express my gratitude.

Thank soooooooooooooooooooooo much everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Thank You] to everyone here for a wonderful card bomb to my very sick mother </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 06:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom was barely conscious when I asked for cards to be sent to her. You guys sent over 250 cards to her and she responded in an awesome way. She can carry on a conversation and she is eating again. There is actually hope now. She is still very weak but she is now talking and even reading your cards. Words can not express my gratitude.

Thank soooooooooooooooooooooo much everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Say What? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 03:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks you everyone for a wonderful season - It warms my heart to see the good in this world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 20:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This year we helped over 700 families and had a good time doing it. This is what Christmas is all about. Thank you to everyone that made it possible. Each and everyone one of you should be very proud.

We will make a video and it release early next year. And we will be back again next year and it will be bigger and better ever.

All my wishes for a happy and awesome new year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone help /u/rumpypumper make her pics public please? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 04:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her pics are showing up as private and she doesn't know how to change them. Can someone please help her?


http://www.reddit.com/r/SantasLittleHelpers/comments/2qendg/welcome_to_the_santaslittlehelpers_after_party/cn5hhgk?context=3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Choose the theme song to this year's video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 04:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every year we make a video that highlight all the great things we have done here. But we need a them song for the new video we are about to make. Please give us yours choice for the it. It should be four to six minutes long and make you want to hug someone. :D


---------


Here is last year's for an example:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vUyt_JwBDeQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And the winner of the Emerson 32" TV is..., </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 04:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/Amesann           - You have won a 32" Emerson Color TV in our Giver's Appreciation Raffle. Please send us your shipping information so we can get this to you right away. 

**Congratulations!!!**

I sure wish we could send all of you a TV but this is the best we could do. Bless you all for the happiness you have brought to this wonderful wonderful community. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drawing for the TV to be held at 10:00 EST - 7:00 PST - That's in 30 minutes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 03:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are giving away the Emerson 32" color TV in 30 minutes from when this is posted. Good luck everyone. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh my did the gang ever surprise me. Thank You Fowgzilla, Sue Olsen, Dudicles, Automateallthethings! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 02:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got home to a plethora of awesome gifts. I'm not used to this glorious treatment. I got  tons of tools and a tool belt, a monocular, a wallet, a harmonica, Nagelene water bottle w/ belt, and extra Nagelen bottle, a music stand, a therma-rest pad, a thermarest pillow, a Siuperman hat, a Bear Gryls survival knive, guitar strings, a **Lego camper set** and a three wolves howling at the moon Zippo lighter.

My god people..., this is the most I have ever gotten for Christamas, moreless from all my reddit friends. This is massive! This is fantastic, 

**I LOVE YOU ALL!!!**

What an awesome surprise. I knew they were sending a few things but turns out they bought out the whole frickin store!


**Thank you, Thank you, Thank you!!!!!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome to the SantasLittleHelpers after party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 02:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please post your pics, tell your stories, convey your thanks and hang around because we are giving away a 32" TV tonight. 

Merry Christmas Everyone!!!!


------------------


Edit: **/u/Amesann won the TV** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Come join the post-Christmas party tonight   post you pics, tell you stories and we are giving away a 32" Color TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 19:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After all the festivities at your house, come join us here and post pics of the happy event. Let's hear your stories of Christmas fun, humor and miracles. And we are giving away an Emerson 32" Color TV as well.

Come join us as we celebrate one awesome season here at SantasLittleHelpers. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sorry, My Bad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 06:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When what to my wondering eyes should appear..., </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 06:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fa la la la la </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 05:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The hard part </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 03:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please Post your pics! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 03:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the best part for us. We so want to see your family experiencing the wonderful joy of Christmas and the gifts this awesome community provided.

**PLEASE SHARE YOUR PICTURES!!!**

Join us here tomorrow after the festivities are over and share your, pics stories and find out who wins the 32" color TV in the giver's appreciation raffle.

**Still time to enter:**

http://www.reddit.com/r/SantasLittleHelpers/comments/2o4dp7/announcing_santaslittlehelpers_giver_appreciation/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He's on his way </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 02:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And the regifting begins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 23:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was awarded Employee of the Year at work today with the best and worst award ever! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 22:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  **This is to notify you, that you have won employee of  the year. Not because you were that great, but because every other employee wasn't worth a shit.**

**Congratulations.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are We There Yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 22:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Christmas portrait </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 22:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One More Day! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 09:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did anyone water the tree? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 03:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grandma dealing with getting run over by a reindeer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 02:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9 Uses For That Sad Fruitcake You're Never Going To Eat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 01:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please congratulate rhubey - Today's Moderator of the day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 14:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Please congratulate r/hubey** - Todays Moderator of the day. Hubey has been away this last week or so, on a long grueling road trip; and not a fun one. But she is racing back trying to get home before Christmas.  She helped out tremendously in the early going and deserves some accolades for her fine work.

And  in case you are out there listening to us  hubey, we selected a special holiday song, just for you:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I4s5MMLN_NY
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not Exactly Reality TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 06:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Christmas Wardrobe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 06:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One more for my fellow Trekies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 14:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please congratulate SueOlsen - Today's Moderator of the Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 13:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have saved the best for last. Please congratulate the beloved SUEOLSEN  Todays Moderator of the day. Sue is my rock and has a heart of gold. She is the main reason I have not killed anyone this year. I would be so lost without her.

So please give her all the love you can. It still wont be as much as she deserves but try anyway. 

**WE LOVE YOU SUE!!!**

http://www.blastr.com/sites/blastr/files/wonder-woman-comic-should-wonder-woman-keep-her-classic-costume-in-the-upcoming-movie.jpeg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some fun gifts you can send to someone that you only know their email address </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 03:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's for a great person that doesn't need anything material. But something to show you care a whole bunch. It would be more symbolic than material. All I have is an email address. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remember every gift you get someone give you a raffle ticket the Emerson 32" TV - Drawing to be held Christmas Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 03:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christmas Cancelled! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 00:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Group therapy at the North Pole </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 22:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monopoly: $10 - Buzz Lightyear Action Figure: $22 - The face on the pictures we receive here on Christmas Day: PRICELESS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 21:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scarred for Life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 19:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All your love for Dudicles - today's Moderator of the Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 16:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Dudicles** is a special one indeed and has been one of the most versatile and best additions to our staff. I just love this guy. He has not only made my job much easier but has made SantasLittleHelpers a much better place. All with an attitude that makes puppy dogs sing. Christmas around here will never be the same without him.

Please put your hands together and send your love to  the **DUDMAN!**
Today's Moderator of the Day: 

* http://i.imgur.com/qDH3iUL.png


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now come on people, I said don't be a dick! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 04:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CutieJudy's computer keeps freezing up so I'm making this request on her behalf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 03:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 



Her computer keeps freezing up and she is getting really frustrated so I'm making the post for her.

Good luck Judy!

* http://www.amazon.com/gp/registry/wishlist/3HIO3XLBKH5TM/ref=cm_sw_su_w </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone posted at thanksgiving about places that have prepared meals you can pick up. Is there something similar for Christmas dinners? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 02:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  

Someone told of a real bargain at Thanksgiving but I just can't seem to find that post. It's for some needy families so it doesn't have to be fancy. Just good.



Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our apologies for forgetting one of the most needy group of people out there </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 01:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The real meaning of Christams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 00:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please join us Christmas Day after all your festivities are over for SantasLittleHelpers holiday Bash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 22:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it's all over come and join us as we celebrate the happiest place on Reddit. This year we have brought Christmas to hundreds and hundreds of people around the world and had fun doing it. Proving that helping people is not only doable, but is actually fun. 

Share your pictures with us, tell your stories of your crazy uncles, tell your best jokes, maybe a contest or two, picking a new song for our 2014 video, and don't forget we are giving away a 32" Color TV to one lucky giver. 

See you there. :D

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Real Meaning of Christmas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 18:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congratulation to Baes - Today's Moderator of the Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 18:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations to Baes  Todays Moderator of the Day!

Baes is our good friend from way back and I am proud to call him a friend. Everyone here loves him. Even the trolls cant find anything bad to say about him. He does awesome great work here and does so with extremely limited eye site.  The guy is an inspiration!

* [Here he is at our annual softball game:](http://img4.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20130617072440/docmcstuffins/images/6/6c/Awesome_Guy.png)



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christmas just got creepy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 06:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So who won the Legos contest? - Everyone! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 06:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **We just couldn't pick one winner so we did an Oprah on you.**

* http://hotmeme.net/media/i/b/d/oHk-everyone-gets-a-prize-you-get-a-prize-and-you-get-a-prize.jpg

**Everyone who entered gets a Lego set. Congratulations to you all:**


* /u/MomNeedsSantasHelp 

* /u/HappyPanda_3210

* /u/angie6921

* /u/the_right_place

* /u/sarancape 

*  /u/AMommaof3

* /u/LapppToppp

* /u/twinjen


* /u/Ketoponic

* /u/user/royalalez

* /u/ravyrn

* /u/CandyAnn

* /u/Acole2407

* /u/blue_eyed_girl

-----------------

**The Legos are being supplied by an anonymous Secret Santa. Please let him and her know just how  awesome  they are. :D** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worst Christmas Gift Ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 06:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When it comes to memes, reindeer got a raw deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 04:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last chance to enter your child for one of these awesome Lego sets - Picking winners soon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 04:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **This contest is closed** Winners will be announced shortly


----------------------



We have several sets of Legos to give away. If your child has received little or no help, sign up for a chance to win one of these great Lego sets:

---------------

[Lego set 60053](http://lh5.ggpht.com/-0XEM0GmRIGg/UqEWTDgDKGI/AAAAAAAA1Go/xlEd8hsbXyo/s1024/60053_alt2.png)

[Lego set 60054](http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-kARnVuGpg8k/Up5EL24lr7I/AAAAAAAAC0E/k1ta-ctrkeg/s1600/131203c-lego-city-light-repair-truck.jpg)

[Lego set 60000](http://cache.lego.com/e/dynamic/is/image/LEGO/60000?$main$)

[Lego set 60041](http://www.mycraze.com.au/wp-content/uploads/60041_003.jpg)

[Lego set 70400](http://img1.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20130702125529/lego/images/3/31/70400.jpg)

[Lego set 60011](http://cache.lego.com/e/dynamic/is/image/LEGO/60011?$main$)

-----------------------

Tell us what you have received so far.

**And thank you to our Mystery Santa who donated them. :D**


And moderators are not eligible:

* http://www.louiseoneillauthor.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/crying-baby.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congratulations to Anikando! Today's Moderator of the Day - This is one busy woman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 01:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am reposting this because all the comments disappeared on the first one. So please comment again:

---------------------------





Anikando came in and has practically taken over /r/assistance which allows the rest of us to handle things here. This woman does the work of six people and kicks some serious butt.

Thank you Anikando. Today's Moderator of the Day:

[Anikando at the office](http://previews.123rf.com/images/jayfish/jayfish1204/jayfish120400218/13189471-woman-with-six-arms-multitasking-her-work-and-daily-life.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congratulations to Anikando! Today's Moderator of the Day - This is one busy woman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 00:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anikando came in and has practically taken over /r/assistance which allows the rest of us to handle things here. This woman does the work of six people and kicks some serious butt.

Thank you Anikando. Today's Moderator of the Day:

[Anikando at the office](http://previews.123rf.com/images/jayfish/jayfish1204/jayfish120400218/13189471-woman-with-six-arms-multitasking-her-work-and-daily-life.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legos for kids that have received none or very little help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 00:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Winners have been picked. This contest is closed. Winners will be announced shortly.**



We have several sets of Legos to give away. If your child has received little or no help, sign up for a chance to win one of these great Lego sets:

---------------

[Lego set 60053](http://lh5.ggpht.com/-0XEM0GmRIGg/UqEWTDgDKGI/AAAAAAAA1Go/xlEd8hsbXyo/s1024/60053_alt2.png)

[Lego set 60054](http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-kARnVuGpg8k/Up5EL24lr7I/AAAAAAAAC0E/k1ta-ctrkeg/s1600/131203c-lego-city-light-repair-truck.jpg)

[Lego set 60000](http://cache.lego.com/e/dynamic/is/image/LEGO/60000?$main$)

[Lego set 60041](http://www.mycraze.com.au/wp-content/uploads/60041_003.jpg)

[Lego set 70400](http://img1.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20130702125529/lego/images/3/31/70400.jpg)

[Lego set 60011](http://cache.lego.com/e/dynamic/is/image/LEGO/60011?$main$)

-----------------------

Please only enter if your child hasn't got very much yet. Leave these for the kids who have gotten very little. Tell us what you received so far.

**And thank you to our Mystery Santa who donated them. :D**


And moderators are not eligible:

* http://www.louiseoneillauthor.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/crying-baby.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BREAKING NEWS: SANTA HAS BEEN RESCUED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 19:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congratulations to /u/bnyeeyore. Todays Moderator of the Day! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 14:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Congratulations to /u/bnyeeyore. Todays Moderator of the Day! She has been hard at work here despite having to contend with finals.  But even so has managed to contribute to the community and make my job easier. 

She finally is done and sent me this picture at a celebration party:



https://floatingrealities.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/done-with-finals-time-to-party.jpg

**Thank you Bnyeeyore!!!**

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BREAKING NEWS UPDATE: Santa still missing search area expanded </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 01:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R_cczIWvBq4

Read more about the story here:

* http://www.reddit.com/r/SantasLittleHelpers/comments/2pi8za/more_breaking_news_seal_team_six_has_been/



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MORE BREAKING NEWS: Seal Team Six has been dispatched - Obama: "We Don't Negotiate With Martins!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 22:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you haven't heard the news:

http://www.reddit.com/tb/2phyj8


Latest updates tell us Seal Team Six has now been dispatched.

President Obama was quoted saying: *"We don't negotiate with Martians."*


------------------

**Update. 6:35 PM EST:**

Satellite captures this image:

http://images.onset.freedom.com/ocregister/kpj43o-19santalg.jpg

---------------

**Update 7:07 PM EST:**

The search area had been expanded


The call for volunteers has been sent out for the search:

* https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R_cczIWvBq4

---------

**Update: 8:44 PM EST:**

A concerned Obama addresses the nation:


http://b-i.forbesimg.com/harrybinswanger/files/2014/01/Obama2.jpg

 *"We will not stop until we get our Santa back. This is attack on our nation. We stand together as one and will go to the ends of the Solar System until justice is served."*


-----------------

**Update 1:00 PM EST

**SANTA HAS BEEN RESCUED IN A SUCCESSFUL SEAL TEAM SIX OPERATION!**

Only one injury reported from the hostages. **Vixen lost her antlers during the rescue attempt.** She is expected to make a full recovery.

Martians now lie at the bottom of the ocean (don't tell the kids about this part)


http://www.defense.gov/dodcmsshare/newsphoto/2012-12/hires_121201-F-EL833-044.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DELETING REQUESTS IS A BANNABLE OFFENSE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 21:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deleting requests is a bannable offense. 

Sorry to sound harsh. We have just had a rash of this tactic being used lately. We try to be nice and give out warnings. We do not like to be dicks. But there are a few who are abusing that.

If there is a special reason you want it removed, contact the mods and they will do it for you. Then there is no suspicion or no problem. 

Sorry to sound like a hothead. We just don't want any of your generosity to be taken advantage of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BREAKING NEWS - We will keep you updated as more information comes in </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 20:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Faster than a speeding UPS truck. Able to leap tall buildings with a single bound. It's a bird, it's plane..., No It's Fwogzilla: Today's Moderator of the Day! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 20:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a real special moderator of the day. /u/Fwogzilla has done such awesome work and has helped so may. This guy is a hero among heroes. 

Please give all the love you can mustard to today's Moderator Of The Day:

***FWOGZILLA***

http://www.freakingnews.com/pictures/20500/Superman-Kermit--20747.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Coburn Blocks Bill On Veterans' Suicide Prevention </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 05:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am really trying to help this guy but am just really stumped - Maybe you can offer some advice or help that I couldn't Thank you </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 04:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm facing all sorts of adversity right now. Whether it is health, being able to afford to live, being able to work, and just being able to live for another day. It is all happening at once. Without a family to run to and without any remote friends that can lend a hand in the way I need, I am facing extreme calamity. Possibly death.


Everything that I'm going through is because of a mystery illness that I was faced with a couple years ago. It's gone to far to the extent where I really need help, especially since a recent accident that happened a couple months ago. I can't walk. If I must, I have to wear leg braces. I can't walk because of my arthritic and ligament problems, which was caused by the illness that spread throughout my entire body to cause all of these things. It doesn't help that I was training and working out a lot during my time in the Marine Corps. It's caused me constant bleeding throughout these past couple of years. Lately, and for the first time this year I have lost feeling in both of my feet and legs. It's starting to spread upwards on my leg. I've fainted numerous of times just from being too sick. I've found myself passed out in the bathroom floor or in the hallway. I've fainted in the hands of professions in the hospital, as well. I've had to deal with tons of research done to me. Seen tons of medical professionals. None have been able to really help me or conclude what possibly happened to me. I haven't gave up despite all of my problems.


I'm ultimately needing 20K for treatments. I'm living in an apartment without any bed (I've been sleeping on the floor) and my tent has been due ($1,445 for November and December). I'm about to get an eviction notice. My apartment complex wants to kill me. It is winter time. I'm on my last $30. To say that I just need $20K for treatments wouldn't be enough. My treatments can take 1 and half to 2 months total. This is from a doctor that I know can make me better. I'm really ashamed and feel like I'm asking for too much already. But, I already exhausted all the possible resources I can and whatever anyone can give me as advice. I can immediately start working after this and finish my schooling. 

* www.gofundme.com/gilvx4


I'm the review of what I ultimately ask, please consider my statements hereforth.

Does someone chose to get sick? Or is it someone else's fault to get sick? I have been blamed for both. I feel at fault and at my wits end. I feel like I have asked from the VA (Veterans Affairs), to the government, to my friends (and "friends") and to my connections to no avail. I am at your full mercy to pick me up. To give me a chance, again. Not to run and to sloth at this given opportunity, but given a chance to make a difference. A difference that I know I can do and promise. To give back.

If you need any proof, questions, or concerns, please let me know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Winners of the Teddy bear and Dinosaurs - Oh My God! - They had babies! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 02:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I woke up this morning and found that the Teddy Bear and Dinosaur had babies. Six of them:

http://i.imgur.com/ssyFMUd.jpg


I am so sorry to the folks that didn't win. I wanted to get one for you all. I really did. But here are the eight lucky winners:

* The Blonde Bear: /u/LittleBit8 


* Green Dinosaur: /u/Kookiem 

* Green Dinosaur: /u/LadyHallow
 



* Blue Dinosaur: /u/Denserusse

* Blue Dinosaur: /u/AllisonChadwick 

* Blue Dinosaur: /u/Patty_Death_Cakes  

* Blue Dinosaur: /u/midgisms  

* Blue Dinosaur: /u/robbin1175 


Please PM me your shipping information as soon as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The dark side of the North Pole </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 05:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ISIS Reportedly Releases Guide On How To Treat Sex Slaves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 04:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think she heard the lyrics wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 01:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Karl Rove Defends Rectal Feeding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 01:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congratulations to Kimberly71 - Today's SLH Moderator of the day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 19:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please congratulate Kimberly and send her get well wishes. She has been ill recently so we haven't got to see her much. Please send your love and get well wishes so that Santa will bring her good health and a merry Christmas.

http://www.fitnessfusions.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/we-miss-you.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Oh Darling..., Won't you please..., Stand By Me [WW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 06:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time is growing short and we have lots of needy families that need Santas. It is so easy to give here. Just click their Amazon wish list, choose an item(s) and the gift is on the way. Most requests are for inexpensive items. But ones that will bring a smile to some that would normally not get one.

* **This is what we did last year:**

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vUyt_JwBDeQ

------------------



**Just go to:**

* /r/SantasLittleHelpers  and click on any of the blue shaded posts to see their individual stories and requests. Each gift you give, enters you into out givers appreciation raffle where the grand prize is an **Emerson 32 Color TV:**

* http://www.reddit.com/r/SantasLittleHelpers/comments/2o4dp7/announcing_santaslittlehelpers_giver_appreciation/

And while you are there, enter on of our many daily contest where great prizes are given away every day. Just click **contests and events** on the sidebar.


Please get in the spirit and help with a small or large gift of any kind. Show the word what reddit is really all about.

Thank you and Merry Christmas

Backpackwayne :D.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Random Acts of Kindness at its best: r/SantasLittleHelpers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 06:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request   Offer] Oh Darling. Won't you please, Stand By Me [WW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 06:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know that cute huggable bear I just gave away to uscgirl? Well he has a brother and a grandpa who also need a home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 04:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So in our latest contest, you have a chance to win one of these cute boogers. 

Here is the entire family posing for a picture. Jeremy on the left has already found a home. But the other two are still available. 


* http://i.imgur.com/I9xHYWJ.jpg

All you have to do to enter is to say I want to enter and who it is for.

And promise you will let them watch the Simpsons:

* http://i.imgur.com/ZvUk8Ac.jpg

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some one had written about providing some t -shirt screening and I lost your username. If you are still out there, give me ring please. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 03:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You had PMed me and offered to do some T-shirt screening. I have searched and searched but can not find your name. Please contact me if you see this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time is growing short and we need Santas! It is so easy to give and you get a chance to win a new TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 00:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time is growing short and we have lots of needy families that need Santas. It is so easy to give here. Just click their Amazon wish list, choose an item(s) and the gift is on the way. Most requests are for inexpensive items. But ones that will bring a smile to some that would normally not get one.

** *This is what we did last year:**

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vUyt_JwBDeQ

------------------



**Just go to:**

* /r/SantasLittleHelpers  and click on any of the blue shaded posts to see their individual stories and requests. Each gift you give, enters you into out givers appreciation raffle where the grand prize is an **Emerson 32 Color TV:**

* http://www.reddit.com/r/SantasLittleHelpers/comments/2o4dp7/announcing_santaslittlehelpers_giver_appreciation/

And while you are there, enter on of our many daily contest where great prizes are given away every day. Just click **contests and events** on the sidebar.


Please get in the spirit and help with a small or large gift of any kind. Show the word what reddit is really all about.

Thank you and Merry Christmas

Backpackwayne :D. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congratulations uscgirl - You have won the Big huggable stuffed toy contest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 22:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You heard me right. Ethan is going to love this guy.

* http://i.imgur.com/yTVAGvb.jpg[1]

But those of you who didn't win, do not fret. There are more of them coming. Look for the new contest this week.

Congrats to you and Ethan. May he treasure it as much as I do. :D

Please send a pic if you can. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congratulations to bnyeeyore - Today moderator of the day She's a little bashful but has a heart of gold </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 18:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our moderator of the day is /u/bnyeeyore. A little bashful but this one has big, big heart. Thank you bnyeeyore for all your hard work. Here is her photo for her company ID:
 


http://www.famouscutouts.com/images/detailed/0/684-Bashful.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Reddit Administrators celebrating Christmas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 06:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know it is again reddit rules to post someone's personal information. Does the same rule apply for your own information? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 05:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you allowed to post your own information, such as an email address or even a home address? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Try your best to choose only "PRIME" items on your Amazon wish list. We want to spend money on you..., not shipping </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 02:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When making your Amazon wishlists, be aware that items marked **PRIME,** give many of our users free two day shipping. And since time is growing short, that is becoming more and more important.

And we want our donations to go to our community. Not To UPS, USPS or FedEx. 

* http://fm.cnbc.com/applications/cnbc.com/resources/img/editorial/2014/09/23/102026283-Toilet.530x298.jpg?v=1411495615 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please congratulate of Mod of the Day! CutieJudy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 01:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats to CutieJudy for who despite working long hours, getting paid less than she is worth, stills finds time to help the good people of this community.

Someone out there in Jersey, please get this woman a real job. She deserves better!

I tried hard to get a picture of her without luck. So I finally had to pay a guy on the street $100 to get me one. Here it is:

* http://thebillfold.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/Screen-Shot-2014-04-25-at-11.44.35-AM-640x305.jpg

**We love you Judy!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please give a big thank to yes_it_is_weird - Today's Moderator of the Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 02:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/yes_it_is_weird is our behind the scenes guy who you may never even hear a peep from. But when we have technical problems arounf here, he is the one that comes to our rescue both here and in /r/Assistance.


I have searched high and low and finally found a picture of him:

* https://macblog.mcmaster.ca/fryeblog/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2009/09/diff.jpg

Congrats and thanks to one of the greates mods you never see.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] May I ask a huge favor from everyone - Please send a card to my 92 year old mom. This will be her last Christmas [California] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 02:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Backpackwayne's mom has really gone down hill in the last couple months. I have had to face reality and accept that I will lose my mother soon.




The last couple months I've watched my mom, who is the epitome of kindness, waste away to what look to be her final days. She didn't eat anything for the last month.



But this last week I bought a new TV for her hospital room just to give her some kind of stimulus. I never dreamed it would spark her will to live like it did. She has started to eat again and can once again carry on a limited conversation.

Well I thought if something like a TV could do that much good, Just think what would happen if we flooded her with hundreds of cards from arounf the world. Even if it didn't have that effect, it would be wonderful that in her final days she knew  that the world was still thinking of her.

**Please, everyone send her a card.**

She likes cards with cute babies and kids and loves the funny stuff too. She is no prude. So feel free to send risque stuff too. Just make her smile.

If there was ever something you could do for me, this would it. I want my mom's final days to as happy as I can make them.

Please PM for the address.

Thank you everyone 

And spread the word elsewhere if you can. I want to shower her with all the cards and love I can.


-------------------

Thank you everyone. Over 250 cards and it has really brightened up my mom. She is actually carrying on a conversation. She just loves it. Words can not express my appreciation. Bless you everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] [WW] May I ask a huge favor from everyone - Please send a card to my 92 year old mom. This will be her last Christmas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 02:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Backpackwayne's mom has really gone down hill in the last couple months. I have had to face reality and accept that I will lose my mother soon.




The last couple months I've watched my mom, who is the epitome of kindness, waste away to what look to be her final days. She didn't eat anything for the last month.



But this last week I bought a new TV for her hospital room just to give her some kind of stimulus. I never dreamed it would spark her will to live like it did. She has started to eat again and can once again carry on a limited conversation.

Well I thought if something like a TV could do that much good, Just think what would happen if we flooded her with hundreds of cards from arounf the world. Even if it didn't have that effect, it would be wonderful that in her final days she knew  that the world was still thinking of her.

**Please, everyone send her a card.**

She likes cards with cute babies and kids and loves the funny stuff too. She is no prude. So feel free to send risque stuff too. Just make her smile.

If there was ever something you could do for me, this would it. I want my mom's final days to as happy as I can make them.

Please PM for the address.

Thank you everyone 

And spread the word elsewhere if you can. I want to shower her with all the cards and love I can.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> May I ask a huge favor from everyone - Please send a card to my 92 year old mom. This will be her last Christmas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 01:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Backpackwayne asking a huge favor from everyone - Please send a card to my 92 year old mom. This will be her last Christmas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 01:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Backpackwayne's mom has really gone down hill in the last couple months. I have had to face reality and accept that I will lose my mother soon.




The last couple months I've watched my mom, who is the epitome of kindness, waste away to what looks to be her final days. She didn't eat anything for the last month.



But this last week I bought a new TV for her hospital room just to give her some kind of stimulus. I never dreamed it would spark her will to live like it did. She has started to eat again and can once again carry on a limited conversation.

Well I thought if something like a TV could do that much good, Just think what would happen if we flooded her with hundreds of cards from arounf the world. Even if it didn't have that effect, it would be wonderful that in her final days she knew  that the world was still thinking of her.

**Please, everyone send her a card.**

She likes cards with cute babies and kids and loves the funny stuff too. She is no prude. So feel free to send risque stuff too. Just make her smile.

If there was ever something you could do for me, this would it. I want my mom's final days to as happy as I can make them.

Please PM for the address.

Thank you everyone 

*train_subject8344*

----------------------------



And please spread the word elsewhere if you can. I want to shower her with all the cards and love I can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> May I ask a huge favor from everyone - Please send a card to my 92 year old mom. This will be her last Christmas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 01:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Backpackwayne's mom has really gone down hill in the last couple months. I have had to face reality and accept that I will lose my mother soon.




The last couple months I've watched my mom, who is the epitome of kindness, waste away to what look to be her final days. She didn't eat anything for the last month.



But this last week I bought a new TV for her hospital room just to give her some kind of stimulus. I never dreamed it would spark her will to live like it did. She has started to eat again and can once again carry on a limited conversation.

Well I thought if something like a TV could do that much good, Just think what would happen if we flooded her with hundreds of cards from arounf the world. Even if it didn't have that effect, it would be wonderful that in her final days she knew  that the world was still thinking of her.

**Please, everyone send her a card.**

She likes cards with cute babies and kids and loves the funny stuff too. She is no prude. So feel free to send risque stuff too. Just make her smile.

If there was ever something you could do for me, this would it. I want my mom's final days to as happy as I can make them.

Please PM for the address.

Thank you everyone 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scandal at the North Pole </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 05:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I missed you all and really want to be here, but..., </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 05:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Win this cute hugable bear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 03:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have a  child in your home that would fall in love with this hugable bear, enter this latest contest. 

http://i.imgur.com/yTVAGvb.jpg


You must:

* Be registered with /r/SantasLittleHelpers 

* Have a child in your home that has not received many many gifts so far

* Agree to send pictures of the child opening it on Christmas Day



**Drawing will be help this Saturday Evening.**

**Edit:** Drawing will be **HELD** this Saturday. I am the one that apparently needs help.

http://rogovoyreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/Wiley-Coyote-Help.jpg

**Good Luck!**

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh Christmas Tree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 14:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> //SantasLittleHelper needs more givers - We are giving away a TV - Will nay of you let me post in your subreddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 06:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/SantasLittleHelpers grants Christmas wishes to redditors around the world. We are a little short on givers right now. To attract them I bought an **Emerson 32"  TV** to give away in a raffle. Every gift someone gives, they get a ticket for the raffle.

----------------


We really need to spread the word about this.

**I'm asking if any of you would allow me to make a post in your subreddit.**

Here is the post:

http://www.reddit.com/r/SantasLittleHelpers/comments/2o4dp7/announcing_santaslittlehelpers_giver_appreciation/

Thank you so much,

train_subject8344 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fruitcake Therapy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 05:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit! Answer me this! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 03:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twas the night before Christmas, and all through the house </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 03:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Denial Bunny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 05:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pegoeg182 is at the hospital with her darling daughter Bailey and really needs a laugh - Let's grant her wish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 02:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have been following the story, Pegoeg182 daughter Bailey has been in and out of the hospital with pneumonia. She has been there all day today with her and told me she could use a laugh.

Well let's all see what we can do. Post the funniest stuff you got.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fido's bad day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 01:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yes Santa does exist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 01:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Decisions, decisions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 01:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please congratulate u/AutomateAllTheThings - SantasLittleHelperModeratorof theDay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 00:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **/u/Automateallthethings**  is SantasLittleHelpers **Moderator of the Day!**


Please join me in thanking him for all his incredibly awesome work. He designed and developed this entire page. He is the reason we not only are festive, but look it as well.

Here is the a picture we took of him at our last company picnic

http://thumbs.dreamstime.com/z/waving-robot-22623701.jpg


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Okay Joseph, Cameron, William, Jake, Joshua, Jamie, Lewis, Benjamin, Ethan, and Luke. We know it was you now. We've got proof! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 05:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/SantasLittleHelpers is giving away an 32" Emerson Color TV to one of our givers - Come on over and join the fun and excitement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 05:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many of you know our sister sub only open during the Christmas season:

/r/SantasLittleHelpers 


We bring Christmas to children of **ALL** ages. We have daily contests for everyone, we share recipes, tell jokes and share stories. And most important, we bring Christmas to hundreds of families that would normally not have one. 

And now we are having our biggest contest yet, open only to the givers of the subreddit in our first annual Givers Appreciation Sweepstakes.

* **[Here is how you can win a 32" color TV and help a deserving family at the same time]
(http://www.reddit.com/r/SantasLittleHelpers/comments/2o4dp7/announcing_santaslittlehelpers_giver_appreciation/)**

Please come over and give a small gift to any of these families. 

**We are short on Santas this year. We really need your help.**

***PLEASE SPREAD THE WORD!!!***
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grandma always gets a little lonely at Christmas time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 22:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please congratulate thelittlestelf - Today's Moderator of the Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 21:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Announcing SantasLittleHelpers Giver Appreciation Sweepstakes - Grand Prize is a 32" LED Emerson Color TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 05:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The folks here that give make the success of this subreddit possible, so we have designed a sweepstakes exclusively for them. For every gift given, you are automatically entered in the sweepstakes. You must report the gift here:

* https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1NAmMSMtNtmc8S1e6MYF3CjNTHYWPFnCAg9XZXL4zCGM/viewform

**GRAND PRIZE IS:**

**[32" Emerson LED Flat Screen Color TV](http://www.amazon.com/Emerson-720p-60Hz-HDTV-LF320EM4/dp/B00FFJ33N2)**

We hope to be adding additional prizes as well. 

* If you have  reported a gift you have given, you are already entered. Every time you give, you get an additional raffle ticket. 

We just feel that you too should share in the fun for all you do. After all, it is your kindness and generous nature, that makes this sub what it is.

* For those of you new to our wonderful community, just go to any of the **blue shaded posts** and you will find people that need your help this Christmas. Pick an item off their wish list and help make someone's Christmas what it was meant to be. Or make an offer of a gift. Then report the gift to the link above each time and you will be eligible to win.


And please spread the word. We have lots of people who need help this Christmas. A simple toy  toy can make the difference. :D

**Thank You all and best wishes for great holiday season. :D** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Dealt Major Setback in Closing Guantanamo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 07:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To all the nice people who have been saying all the nice things to me, I just have to say: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 06:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joesph was pissed! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 07:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Santa isn't stupid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 03:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cross Posting Request to Another Subreddit is Not Allowed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 15:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Making a request here that leads to another subredit is not allowed.

Mainly what we are saying is you can not make a **request** post here and have it lead over RandomActsOfChristmas. Your can make separate posts in both subreddits. Thanks for your cooperation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Santa has been working out - And he gave me a message to pass on to everyone at SantasLittleHelpers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 03:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Santa has PTSD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 01:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christmas Gifts For Weird People </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 06:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rick Perry Ramps Up For 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 06:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh Niiiiigggght..., Oh Hoooo-oollly Niiiiiiiight..., Oooooo Night Diviiine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 06:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Caroling with Yoda sucks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 06:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To all of you out there who are helping out this year, I just wanted to say: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 04:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Check out all the cool contest going on here at SantasLittleHelpers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 02:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have lots of contests going on here at SantasLittleHelpers and will be adding more ever day. There is a button on the sidebar that lists them so you be sure to enter them all. 

Good Luck. :D




https://www.reddit.com/r/SantasLittleHelpers/search?q=flair%3Aevents sort=relevance restrict_sr=on t=all#res-hide-options </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Check out all the cool contests going on here at SantasLittleHelpers. More to come every day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 01:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9 year old future mod of r/SantasLittleHelpers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 06:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are sorrry. We just got a little excited - Happy Thanksgiving everyone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 04:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please welcome with open arms our new staff members for this year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 22:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With all the excitement going on, I have forgotten to welcome  new members to our staff. You have already seen some of them in action and can't help to falling in love with these awesome people.

Please welcome with open arms:




* **AutomateAllTheThings**

* **fwogzilla**



* **Dudicles**

* **Anikando**

* **bnyeeyore**


We am thrilled and extremely fortunate to have them all aboard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you do when you get stuck in the snow? - You get out and push! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 21:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You Fat Bastard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 06:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Didn't really think that one through, did you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 04:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who out there did I buy a Fruit Bouquet cutter set for? It came to me by mistake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 02:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought this Fruit Bouquet Cutter set for someone here and it was delivered to my house by mistake. I can't seem to find out who it was supposed to go to. 

Please tell me if this was on your wishlist so I can get it to you.


http://www.amazon.com/MSC-Flower-Power-Cutter-28444/dp/B00CPNUY7Y/ref=sr_1_22?ie=UTF8 qid=1416966275 sr=8-22 keywords=fruit+bouquet


----------------------------

**Edit:** My Mistake!!! CutieJudy had sent them to me as a present. It all makes sense now because she knows what a fruit I am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Christmas Box For A Family (X-Post to RandomKindness) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 01:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You Can't Have Everything </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 06:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New SantasLittleHelpers rule </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 04:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ever wondered what was on Santa's Amazon Wish list? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 05:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rule #1 to have a good Christmas: Don't Be A Grumpy Cat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 04:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please be sure to report all gifts here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 01:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We ask you  to report all gifts given with an approximate value and to who it was given. This helps us make sure no one is being taken advantage of and identifies the folks not getting help.

You can report them anonymously if you like. And you don't have to be all that specific. Mainly who it was given to and an approximate value.

Report the gifts here:

https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1NAmMSMtNtmc8S1e6MYF3CjNTHYWPFnCAg9XZXL4zCGM/viewform

The link is also on the sidebar.

Thank you so much for making this community what it is. We could not do it without you. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do we do here? I am so glad you asked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 01:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The real reason for giving </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 23:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is what Christmas is all about </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 22:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/SantasLittleHelpers is open for the Christmas season and we are having a balst!

Come request a gift if you are in need, grant a wish if you can, enter our daily contests, share your recipes, make a humorous or inspirational post or just spread Christmas joy in any way you can.

This is what Christmas is all about. Lets show the world reddit cares and reddit is  what Christmas is all about.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowmen: Expectations vs. Reality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 05:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everybody Poops - Even Santa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 00:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christmas in the ghetto </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 05:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The story of the two wise men - The third guy, not so much </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 05:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SantasLittleHelpers Tabernacle Choir </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 08:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't be a Pessimist - It's Christmas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 07:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Weather Outside Is Frightful </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 03:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I feel when I click on a post and see someone spreading Christmas Spirit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 01:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Before I go to bed for the night, I just had to say one thing: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 07:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We love you ~~Jew~~ Too! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 03:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Forget The Reason For The Season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 03:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 33 days until Christmas and I'm already pooped </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 07:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are giving a bike away over in r/SantasLittlehelpers right now - Come join the fun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 05:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **/r/SantasLittleHelpers is now open for the Christmas season!**

Come request a gift if you are in need, grant a wish if you can, enter our daily contests, share your recipes, make a humorous or inspirational post or just spread Christmas joy in any way you can.

This is what Christmas is all about. Lets show the world reddit cares and reddit is  what Christmas is all about.


We are giving a bike away right now!


http://www.reddit.com/r/SantasLittleHelpers/comments/2mmru4/win_a_bike_for_a_kid/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit and Christmas at its best! - r/SantaLittleHelpers is now open and we are giving away a bike right now! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 05:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
/r/SantasLittleHelpers is now open for the Christmas season!

Come request a gift if you are in need, grant a wish if you can, enter our daily contests, share your recipes, make a humorous or inspirational post or just spread Christmas joy in any way you can.

This is what Christmas is all about. Lets show the world reddit cares and reddit is  what Christmas is all about.


----------------

And we have tons of contests and we are giving a bike away tomorrow night. Please come join us and spread the Christmas spirit around the world.

http://www.reddit.com/r/SantasLittleHelpers/comments/2mmru4/win_a_bike_for_a_kid/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some great news for a change - r/SantasLittleHelpers is now open - And we are giving a bike away tomorrow night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 05:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/SantasLittleHelpers is now open for the Christmas season!

Come request a gift if you are in need, grant a wish if you can, enter our daily contests, share your recipes, make a humorous or inspirational post or just spread Christmas joy in any way you can.

This is what Christmas is all about. Lets show the world reddit cares and reddit is also what Christmas is all about.


We have new contests every day. We are giving a bike away right now:

http://www.reddit.com/r/SantasLittleHelpers/comments/2mmru4/win_a_bike_for_a_kid/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I feel about Christmas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 04:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SantasLittleHelpers is open for the season. Plenty of feel good to go around. Come join us for the fun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 04:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/SantasLittleHelpers LittleHelpers is now open for the Christmas season!

Come request a gift if you are in need, grant a wish if you can, enter our daily contests, share your recipes, make a humorous or inspirational post or just spread Christmas joy in any way you can.

This is what Christmas is all about. Lets show the world reddit cares and reddit is also what Christmas is all about.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Miss All the Daily Contests! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 04:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just click the **Contests   Events** on our sidebar and see all the great chances there are to win some awesome gifts and Christmas amenities.

We will have new giveaways every day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/SantasLitlleHelpers is open for the season. Come help or be helped and spread the Christmas spirit. Make sure Santa visits your baby. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 04:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/SantasLittleHelpers is now open for the Christmas season!

Come request a gift if you are in need, grant a wish if you can, enter our daily contests, share your recipes, get a personal letter from Santa, make a humorous or inspirational post or just spread Christmas joy in any way you can.

This is what Christmas is all about. Lets show the world reddit cares and reddit is also what Christmas is all about.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Offer] r/SantasLittleHelpers is now open for the season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 22:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/SanatsLittleHelpers is now open for the Christmas season!

Come request a gift if you are in need, grant a wish if you can, enter our daily contests, share your recipes, make a humorous or inspirational post or just spread Christmas joy in any way you can.

This is what Christmas is all about. Lets show the world reddit cares and reddit is also what Christmas is all about.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OFFER] r/SantasLittleHelpers is open for the season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 22:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/SantasLittleHelpers  is now open for the Christmas season!

Come request a gift if you are in need, grant a wish if you can, enter our daily contests, share your recipes, make a humorous or inspirational post or just spread Christmas joy in any way you can.

This is what Christmas is all about. Lets show the world reddit cares and reddit is also what Christmas is all about.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please report all gifts here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 20:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please report all your gifts here:

https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1NAmMSMtNtmc8S1e6MYF3CjNTHYWPFnCAg9XZXL4zCGM/viewform

It will help us keep things on the up and and up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are sending gifts out every day but need help with shipping costs - Any help would be much appreciated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 00:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mods have been collecting prizes left and right to give to you happy folks out there. But the shipping costs are killing us.

We will sending stuff out almost every day until Christmas so if anyone could see it in their heart to chip in, it would be great. Even $5 would help. Let's make this Christmas awesome for as many people as we can.

Thank you all. :D


http://www.gofundme.com/ha5oo0


-----------------------

**Edit: Thanks to our good friends Fwogzilla   n33nj4, it looks like we got it covered.**

Thank you men!

https://loltruestory.files.wordpress.com/2012/06/blue-lt-that-s-me-right-now-so-happy.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [DON'T DO THIS] Please do not type your flair in brackets when you make your post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 21:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do not type your flair in brackets when making your post.

This is the proper way to add flair:

http://www.reddit.com/r/SantasLittleHelpers/comments/2ljlm3/how_to_add_flair_to_your_post/

Thank you. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reagan, Bush Also Acted Without Congress To Shield Immigrants From Deportation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 01:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to create an Amazon account, wishlist   add a shipping address to your wishlist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 08:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We highly recommend you make a wishlist that helps our givers know what you want and allows them to send it directly to you. Here are some tutorial to help you do that:


---------


You must first create an account.


* **How To Create an Amazon Account:**




   https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B37BFyksMPvcQmM2ZE5CUHpsZEU/view

----------------

Then you make your wishlist.


* **How To Create An Amazon Wishlist**

  https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B37BFyksMPvcZ2xlOXlLMkVYWG8/view

----------------------

And make sure you add your shipping address to the wishlist.

* **How To Add An Shipping Address To Your Wishlist:**

   https://docs.google.com/file/d/0B37BFyksMPvcNUpNeW9VT0N2TGc/edit
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/SantasLittleHelpers is now open for the 2014 Christmas Season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 07:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/SantasLittleHelpers is now open for the Christmas season. Over the next six weeks we will be providing Christmas for so many who would not normally get it. We are open to all ages and have events, contests and games planned throughout the holiday season. Be sure to tune in every day as new contests are planned daily.

Come help make someone's Christmas or come and request your own. Please only request gifts if you or your loved ones are truly in need. Everyone can request cards and letters ans share their Christmas secrets, stories, recipes or just make us laugh.

So welcome one, welcome all.

It's time to get this part started! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hats off to the great work by automateallthethings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 07:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Automateallthethings is the one who created our great new look. And what an awesome job he has done.

Thank You! Thank You! Thank You! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WE ARE OPEN FOR THE SEASON - WELCOME ALL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 06:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome everyone to the 2014 SantasLittleHelpers Christmas season. Over the next six weeks we will be providing Christmas for so many who would not normally get it. We are open to all ages and have events, contests and games planned throughout the holiday season. Be sure to tune in every day as new contests are planned daily. 

Come help make someone's Christmas or come and request your own.   Please only request gifts if you or your loved ones are truly in need. Everyone can request cards and letters ans share their Christmas secrets, stories, recipes or just make us laugh.

So welcome one, welcome all.

***It's time to get this part started!*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for someone to do a resume revamp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 02:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am trying to help someone get a job. And their resume did not look good to me. I am looking for someone to redo it to look much more professional. I will pay a reasonable amount.


--------------------------



**Thank you to /u/mhtyhr. This request has been fulfilled and done very nice. Thank you so much.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP Senators Call On Attorney General Nominee Loretta Lynch To Weigh In On Immigration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 00:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/SantasLittleHelpers will be open for the season on November 15th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 20:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a great season planned with contest and events all the way up to Christmas. We hope to provide and share a joyous Christmas for all.

See Ya there!  :D

http://www.reddit.com/r/SANTASLITTLEHELPERS

-------------------------

**Just take a look at what you did last year:**

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vUyt_JwBDeQ


See ya next Saturday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looks like we found the cure for Ebola - Just have an election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 07:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't amazing that now that the election is over that someone Ebola is no  longer even an issue. It's like we have already forgot it even happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIPS FOR OUR GIVERS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 05:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **TIPS FOR OUR GIVERS**

We thank you for your generosity and want your experience here to be joyful Here are a few tips to make sure that happens:

-------------------------


	Check the OPs overview page to see their history. 

	Feel free to PM the OP and ask for proof of their situation. Please be polite and do not question them in a accusatory manner.

	The mods can assist you and answer your questions though we can not make the decision for you. If you suspect any monkey business, please report it to us, rather than attacking the OP

	Please report your gifts to help us make sure no one is taking advantage. You can remain anonymous if you choose. 

**- Report gifts HERE:**   (https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1NAmMSMtNtmc8S1e6MYF3CjNTHYWPFnCAg9XZXL4zCGM/viewform)



-----------------------------------


And please join us for our contests. There should be one going on every day and we would love to give back to the great folks here who are providing Christmas to so many. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to add flair to your post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 04:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We ask that you add flair to your post to make it easy for others to see what kind of post you have made. It's very simple to do.

Under your post you will see the word **"flair."**


**http://i.imgur.com/cHCLT90.jpg**


Just click that and a menu will drop down. Pick one of the available ones or type one in yourself. Then press **SAVE** 

That's all there is to it. The mods will happily assist you if you have any trouble with it.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
