<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9503</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 04:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Self-Compassion](http://www.amazon.com/Self-Compassion-Beating-Yourself-Insecurity-Behind/dp/0061733512/ref=sr_1_1?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1337308524 sr=1-1 tag=acleint-20) by Kristin Neff shows how much better self-compassion is than self-esteem.  Not sure how you'd teach it to a 4-year-old but you and your wife could apply it to yourselves.  It's a good read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Europe on a Cross of Gold? | There is growing evidence that the medicine on which European countries have agreed - austerity - is killing the patient. There is now talk of adjusting the dosage, but talk has not yet given way to action. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 03:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Too Much Familiarity Bad For Creativity? | If you want a creative solution to a problem, youd better find someone who knows a little about the situation but not too much. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-17 23:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists Build Electricity Producing Viruses | Scientists were able to produce about a quarter of the voltage of a triple-A battery. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-17 23:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nick Hanauer is a venture capitalist who was the first non-family investor in Amazon.com. He's screaming to anyone who will listen that he, and other wealthy innovators like him, doesn't create jobs. The middle class does - and its decline threatens everyone in America, from the innovators on down. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-17 19:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Student Debt Bomb | This particular bubble doesnt burst on Wall St. It oozes over a generation. In a sense its a pre-approved government bailout. The government protects the college, but each debtor is paying so much throughout their lives that its impossible to live a regular life.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-17 19:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are JPMorgan's Losses A Canary in a Coal Mine? | Simon Johnson, once chief economist of the IMF and now a professor at MITs Sloan School of Management: "...all of this suggests that we are absolutely on the path towards another financial crisis of the same order of magnitude as the last one." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-17 18:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Preying on Poverty: How Government and Corporations Use the Poor as Piggy Banks | ...effective interest rate as high as 600%, which is perfectly legal in many states...charging defendants the price of occupying a jail cell...wage theft..in a third of the states, being in debt can land you in jail. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-17 18:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-16 19:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article:

If we think of the tax code as a set of incentives, rather than simply a mechanism to redistribute income, there are creative and effective ways to moderate the extremes of wealth, boost the pay of ordinary workers, make American companies more stable and efficient, and reduce the long-term federal budget deficit.

An astonishing contributor to inequality, then, is corporate bosses taking a larger share of the companys revenue for themselves.

Because current CEO pay numbers are so far out of the ordinary, its hard to argue that they are a natural outcome of the market.

Its difficult to estimate what combination of approaches will prevail, but whatever happens, it will be bring broad benefits to society as a whole, far outweighing the impact on the federal budget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big Idea: To Fight Inequality, Link Worker Pay to Corporate Taxes | We can and should actively use the corporate tax code to create a real incentive to pay CEOs less, and workers more, by linking the head honchos compensation to both employee salaries and tax rates. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-16 19:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-16 03:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote for terrific typo: *morose* for *more so* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cycle of Fear | Cartoonist and Essayist Tim Kreider on the soothing effect of dangerous situations.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-15 02:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chteau Sucker | Rare-wine collectors are savvy, competitive guys with a taste for impossible finds. The biggest hoax in history took place right under their noses. | If Kurniawan's rise demonstrated anything, it was how easily the urge to know more can be overpowered by the temptation to know less. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-15 00:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No Country for Rich Men | From Manhattan to Monaco, the world's wealthiest people are disconnecting into a class of stateless transients. "The more money you have, the more rootless you become because everything is possible." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-14 23:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-14 22:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhm, those are not facts those are assertions and the editorial the OP adds doesn't even match the article. 

The so-called editorial line, *Privatization simply hasn't worked for health care, mortgage banking, higher education, or prison management,* is taken verbatim froom the article.  You don't consider that a *match*?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Wisdom of Slime | The slime mold network matched, at least partly, the network of human-made transport systems, though the closeness of fit varied from country to country. The United States highway system, for instance, is less slime-mold-like than that of Canada. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-14 20:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Krugman: Why We Regulate | The key point is not that the bet went bad; it is that institutions playing a key role in the financial system have no business making such bets. Weve just seen an object demonstration of why Wall Street does, in fact, need to be regulated. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-14 17:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Empathy | Others shouldnt have to convince us of their humanity to arouse ours. If empathy can be likened to light, a diffuse glow extending everywhere is far better than a powerful but narrow beam focused on a select few, while leaving the rest of the world in darkness. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-14 17:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five Facts That Put America to Shame | Privatization simply hasn't worked for health care, mortgage banking, higher education, or prison management. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-14 17:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Coming Meltdown in College Education   Why The Economy Wont Get Better Any Time Soon | We freak out about the Trillions of dollars in debt our country faces. What about the TRILLION DOLLARs plus in debt college kids are facing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-14 03:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Geneticists Link Genes To Diseases | It is astounding to think that just 20,000 of these protein coding genes is enough to take a single cell, which we all once were and inspire this program of elaborate complex development into a human being. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-14 00:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nature or Nurture? The Surprising Way Genetics Could Reshape the Debate. | With the cost of genotyping falling at a rate faster than Moore's Law, genetics could be used to answer questions that have nothing to do with genetics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-14 00:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Future of Architecture = No New Buildings | Should architects abandon the search for new built form in order to address the environmental crisis? Perhaps not, but looking at this presumably extreme alternative would be refreshing, useful, and maybe even revolutionary.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-14 00:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Lose 23 Lbs in 28 Days (Hint: it requires radical system-hacking) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-13 23:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taking the Christianity out of Sex | Cross-cultural data collected from pre-industrial societies suggests that culture - including religion - has played an important role in ingraining many truths about human sexuality into our collective psyche. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-13 07:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-12 08:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you tell your husband that the boob comments aren't welcome, what does he say?  You have told him, haven't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Easy Useless Economics | Authoritative-sounding figures insist that our problems are structural, that they cant be fixed quickly. We must focus on the long run, such people say, believing that they are being responsible. But the reality is that theyre being deeply irresponsible. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-11 17:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Buy the Spin: How Cutting the Pentagon's Budget Could Boost the Economy | To advance beyond the wreckage caused by the Great Recession to build a stable, secure and environmentally sustainable society, we need to break the grip of the military-industrial complex on the $700B military budget.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-11 17:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders and Friends Plan to Cut Fossil Fuel Subsidies | "The biggest 5 oil companies made 135 billion in profit last year. Why in the world are we giving them at least 10 billion in subsidies while we are closing public schools?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-10 19:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome to the Knowledge Factory | Just as American manufacturing turned belly-up in the face of the out-sourcing of labor in the globalized market in the 1990s, higher ed is now poised to do exactly the same thing with the professoriate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-09 21:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Kids Start Doing Root Cause Analysis | My son is in the phase of life where theres only a single question on his lips - Why?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-09 21:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Building resilient cities and towns with fiscal conservatism | A compelling case that suburban sprawl is basically a Ponzi scheme, in which municipalities expand infrastructure hoping to attract new taxpayers that can pay off the mounting costs associated with the last expansion, over and over. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-09 03:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Global Corporations Undermining Democracy Worldwide | Bilateral investment treaties allow companies to sue governments but not vice versa. Ecuador was forced to pay fines of 78 million dollars after Chevron claimed that efforts to protect the Amazon from pollution have negatively affected business. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-07 17:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Major Groups Beg Congress to Rewrite NCLB | We cannot for a second appreciate the unfathomable lack of leadership you have already shown on this issue and realize, sadly, that you cant even get simple legislation passed much less such a complex piece of legislation like ESEA. [NOT] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-07 17:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is Good Teaching? A Reflection | "Good teaching comes down to six essential practices. I call them Inducement, Conveyance, Meta-Learning, Empowerment, Modeling, and Application. All six of these activities must be present for Good Teaching (and Good Learning) to occur." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-07 17:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Women Are a Foreign Policy Issue | The most pressing global problems simply won't be solved without the participation of women. Seriously, guys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-26 18:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Do They Hate Us? | The real war on women is in the Middle East. | They don't hate us because of our freedoms. We have no freedoms because they hate us. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-26 18:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Splitting the Difference Between Myth and Reality Is Not Good Economics | Every economist and policy analyst worth his or her salt warned against adopting austerity measures in the midst of a jobs crisis.  They also noted that deregulation had been a root cause of the 2008 collapse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-26 16:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dirty Medicine | How medical supply behemoths stick it to the little guy, making Americas health care system more dangerous and expensive. [2010] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-26 01:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earth to Ben Bernanke | Faced with an economy still in desperate need of help, the Fed is unwilling to provide that help. And that, unfortunately, makes the Fed part of a broader problem. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-25 04:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Violence puts wear and tear on kids' DNA | Children who have experienced violence might really be older than their years. The DNA of 10-year-olds who experienced violence in their young lives has been found to show wear and tear normally associated with aging, a Duke University study has found. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-24 17:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Insurers Alter Cost Formula, and Patients Pay More | Despite a landmark settlement that was expected to increase coverage for out-of-network care, the nations largest health insurers have been switching to a new payment method that in most cases significantly increases the cost to the patient. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-24 17:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Lesson for Obama of Europe's Failed Austerity | "Such an economic strategy - forcing banks to help distressed homeowners, stopping oil speculation, boosting spending until unemployment drops to 5%, and fighting to ensure economic gains are widely shared - is critical to jobs and growth." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-24 17:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Companies Need to Embrace Whistleblowers | "Any organization which has a whistleblower ought to start from the supposition that they are right and there is an issue to address until proved to the contrary." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-24 01:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Follow Our Weird Politics | Social scientists are flipping the old base-superstructure relation on its head and acknowledging that politicians are not rational decision-makers, and that politics drives economics, not the other way around. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-23 22:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thresholds of Pain: Assessing the Human Costs of Health Care Reform | These people all endure daily physical and psychological pain because they are unable to access the treatment their physicians have prescribed. Their misery will end if the ACA takes full effect as scheduled in January, 2014. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-23 18:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Defaulting to Conservatism | Energy-saving shortcuts may have us defaulting to more conservative ideology when we dont have the resources to think through a situation.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-23 07:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Down With Everything | We cant be great as long as we remain a vetocracy rather than a democracy. Our deformed political system - with a Congress thats become a forum for legalized bribery - is now truly holding us back. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-22 18:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Distance Learning and Academic Labor: Promise   Peril | Welcome to the knowledge sweatshop of the future. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-22 18:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-22 08:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...for all *intents and* purposes, but that's a *moot* point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I Should Pay Higher Taxes | It doesn't do me any good to be personally wealthier if my country or the world as a whole is becoming more unequal, more unstable, more gripped by poverty, more resentful, more insecure. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-21 23:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany to Greece: Cut Safety Nets for Citizens But Keep Buying Our Weapons |  "Greece owes 1bn for submarines that proved to be faulty and which it doesn't even need.  That's three times the amount Athens was asked to make in additional pension cuts to secure its latest EU aid package." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-20 17:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Romney-Rosen Firestorm Is Reminder: We Need to Redefine Gender Justice | The question is which women have the privilege of choice. That gender gap in personal autonomy and freedom may be more detrimental to feminist struggles than economic or employment disparities. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-19 17:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When We Grow Up, We Will Fall in Love with Earth | As the global systems in which we live change in utterly unpredictable ways, we have no choice but to expand our thinking to embrace the unfathomable . . . We must fall in love with the Earth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-19 17:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Day Yahoo Decided I Liked Reading About Child Murder | Violence against children has dropped over the past four decades, yet the perception that times are more dangerous has made American parents more over-protective than ever before. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-18 21:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spain Is Doomed: Why Austerity Is Destroying Europe | ... but the beatings will continue until bond yields improve! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-18 20:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First, Do A Little Less Harm | As Mark Jenkins knows, wilderness first aid can hurt. (Just ask his patients.) So he finally did what everyone should do: he took a class from real experts. [repost from TrueReddit] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-18 18:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Tyranny of Freedom | The phrases that were looking for, I think, are economic equality and social justice. We not only have to reclaim equality and justice, we have to expand their definitions beyond the legal and juridical.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-18 08:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atul Gawande: The Score | How childbirth went industrial. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-18 04:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First, Do A Little Less Harm | As Mark Jenkins knows, wilderness first aid can hurt. (Just ask his patients.) So he finally did what everyone should do: he took a class from real experts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-18 03:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Read This Book, Obama! | David Frum on what Obama could learn from Robert Caro's new biography. | Johnson didnt do it by inspiring or exhorting. He did it by mobilizing political power, on a scale and with a ruthlessness that arguably surpassed all other presidents, before or since. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-18 00:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Unequal Pay Is Even More Unequal For Some Women | Women make less by industry. Black and Latina women are still struggling much more than their white counterparts. Women with higher education face a larger pay gap. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-18 00:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Boss Man Cometh: Through State Tax Breaks, Employers Pilfer Workers Earnings | Some companies can simply pocket the money that would otherwise be remitted to the state in the form of workers income tax. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-17 18:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No Tax Dollars for Deadbeats | Who, after all, are the real drags on society? People who dont pay income tax because theyre barely scratching out a living? Or corporations that make billions in profits and then come to us with their hands out?  GE's tax rate was negative 45.3 percent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-17 18:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why it's OK to leave a tech job at 5 p.m. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-17 01:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-17 01:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been to Cuenca yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Conversation: Barney Frank | If you care deeply about a cause, and you are engaged in an activity on behalf of that cause that makes you feel good and warm and enthusiastic, youre probably not helping, because youre out there with your friends and political work is much tougher and harder.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-17 00:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Europes Economic Suicide | Rather than admit that theyve been wrong, European leaders seem determined to drive their economy - and their society - off a cliff. And the whole world will pay the price. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-16 23:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-16 22:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the swaddling, shushing and the others?  Is there something wrong with every one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Five S's' can keep babies calm during shots | swaddling tightly in a blanket, being laid sideways or on the stomach while awake, shushing, swinging back and forth, and being allowed to suck on something </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-16 20:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PDI is a policy-agnostic political party that does not have, nor will ever have, a political ideology. It has a single and radical proposal: PDI elected representatives will vote in congress according to what the people have previously voted through the internet using Agora. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-15 07:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Civics Class Should Be Sexy | What you weren't ever taught as a kid: There is a secret curriculum that explains how stuff actually gets done in America. In a democracy, that knowledge should be democratized. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-14 23:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How To Train Your Robot | When kids have fun, they get very smart and creative about programming. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-14 18:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Federal Reserve Turns Left | The Fed keeps explaining why more aggressive action is needed, and is gently nudging the politicians who decide fiscal policy to step up. But its message is ignored by Congress and the president and viciously attacked by right-wing Republicans who say, Butt out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-14 18:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corporate Socialism: How Employers Skim Workers' Tax Dollars | Companies can keep some or all of the state income taxes withheldfrom their workers' paychecks in 16 states. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-13 20:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Participatory Budgeting Lets Citizens Experiment with Economic Democracy | What seems like an unprecedented step forward for notoriously mismanaged and politically stagnant U.S. cities is pretty routine in other parts of the world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-13 19:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fossil-Fuel Subsidies Are the Real Job Killers | Instead of bankrolling an industry that is laying off workers and threatening our economic future, why not take the billions in subsidies going to oil companies and invest instead in a sector that both creates jobs and protects the planet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-13 19:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Dying Empire Invades Oaksterdam, Our Privacy   Our Speech | Mired in imperial war and corporate privilege, the US Supreme Court and Obama Administration have escalated their attacks on our basic rights. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-12 20:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You Can't Say That: Why the Best Solutions Are So Often 'Off The Table' | The conversation must be expanded. If we can't stop the wealthiest 1% from limiting what the rest of us understand to be realistic, our political dialogue will remain terminally irrelevant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-12 20:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Left Behind | What We Lost in Iraq and Washington, 2009-2012 | The space between what we were doing (the eye-watering waste and mismanagement), and what we were saying (the endless claims of success and progress), was filled with numb soldiers and devastated Iraqis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-12 08:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-09 01:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry and thanks.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-09 01:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, I wish the OP could be edited.  Thanks for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Single Payer Doctor Carol Paris Packs It Up | The insanity here is that we have a system of financing health care in this country that is all about profit for corporate America and not about the health care of the people. You cant be about profit and be about a social service. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-08 20:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dan Ariely interview on Haaretz | In his Duke University residence, the Ramat Hasharon-raised Prof. Dan Ariely pauses to talk about behavioral economics, the serious accident he suffered as a teenager and what its like to know what were all thinking. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-07 22:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nasa scientist: climate change is a moral issue on a par with slavery | "Our parents didn't know that they were causing a problem for future generations but we can only pretend we don't know because the science is now crystal clear." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-07 21:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-29 02:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The entire title and headline is taken from the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-29 02:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I post something I've seen on Common Dreams I try to link to the original article, as is recommended. I hadn't seen the post by wang-banger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-29 02:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The entire headline is taken from the article.  Let's see your pick of something to put after the article title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-26 00:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We like it too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-25 21:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cross post away... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-19 06:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would it be if thousands of protesters swarmed a city but not in clustered groups?  Just in twos or threes but all over a really wide area -- all peaceably carrying signs without obstructing vehicle or pedestrian traffic.  Make it so everyone in that city would continually see the protest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-18 05:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just heard a podcast about Michael Gazzaniga.  I'm planning to read [Who's in Charge?: Free Will and the Science of the Brain](http://www.amazon.com/Whos-Charge-Free-Science-Brain/dp/0061906107/).  Maybe you'd like it too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-10 06:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **...there are a ton...** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-09 06:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There's no lack of clarity in *for you and I* but it still bugs me. I agree on singular *they* and sentence-ending prepositions.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-09 01:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get annoyed at constructions such as *for my wife and I* or *just between you and I*. Does that make me dumb?
Actually my annoyance is more with the school teachers who always corrected *Johnny and me* to *Johnny and I* without providing any context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-29 19:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article:
It has been my experience that many anti-authoritarians labeled with psychiatric diagnoses usually dont reject all authorities, simply those theyve assessed to be illegitimate ones, which just happens to be a great deal of societys authorities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-27 00:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some 'victims abroad' would probably disagree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-21 00:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems it's you who is jumping the gun when you think he says anonymous comments are inherently wrong.  

What I saw was that they don't carry any weight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-15 03:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pick an area of the world about which you have some curiosity and go there.  Stay in hostels and guest houses.  If you get too bored there, go somewhere else in that country or to a nearby country.  Just stay out of your home country for several months, ideally 6 or more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-14 21:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a mystery to me that this subreddit has managed to stay relatively sane and respectful.  :)  xoxoxy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-14 00:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like an African elephant.  Can it be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-28 18:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about intelligence that is *grown* -- that arises from interacting with the environment?  Would that be considered artificial, or would it be 'true' intelligence comiing from an artificial entity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-27 21:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Nikon D5000 has a flip screen but it may be out of your reach.  If you can, borrow a camera with a flip screen and try it out.  

For me a flip screen has become a must-have.  But then I like the candid camera aspect and being able to shoot macros of ground level stuff without lying on my belly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-26 00:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better not to keep your camera in the 45L pack.  How about a waist pack?

And look into a flip-twist (articulated) LCD screen.  They are great for raising the camera over your head to see over crowds, for flowers and stuff close to the ground if you're into that, and especially for candid photos where people don't know you're photographing them -- people pay more attention to where you're looking than where the lens is pointing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-24 04:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why wouldn't you read the article before responding? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-23 18:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that kind of down.  Indifferent to hip-hop, bling seems like empty posturing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 23:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 74 and I know of many of us geezers who support OWS and are down on SOPA/PIPA, Citizens United and the rest of the corporatist agenda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-21 05:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deliberate government decisions to adopt austerity programs have tended to be followed by hard times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-17 06:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We cannot help but be a society of strangers, yet underneath this, we cannot be a society at all unless we recognize our mutual obligations to one another. It is possible that our rude ancestors had it right all along: that obligations are more important than debts, and that amnesties are the key to economic and social order. Surely this question faces us now with a force that cannot be ignored. We are truly in each others debt, but it is a debt that extends beyond the mere payment of the sum of money.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-14 03:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're in a state that's safe for Obama, like I am, you can feel okay about voting third party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-16 20:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your thoughts on Cuenca? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-30 05:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a direct quote from the article but I admit the lack of context makes it confusing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-05 06:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loving the article first, that one blurb comes waaaaay after. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-27 22:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remeber seeing something that persuaded me [range voting](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Range_voting) was better than IRV.  There are so many [voting system criteria](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IRV_voting#Voting_system_criteria) that no single system satisfies them all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-10 20:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting to see the varied reactions.  They *all* seem ungrammatical to me when judging by SAE but I don't really stumble over any of them. 

I grew up in and have lived in several regions and countries so maybe getting used to 'funny' ways of talking is easier for me.  The differences are fascinating though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-10 05:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [YES]  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-06 07:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, after reading the links I understand the concern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-06 05:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently subscribed to GMP but I'm not otherwise 'affiliated.' The article was interesting to me.

What's the touchy history? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-04 08:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's directly from the Krugman article.  Before that it's of unknown origin though [widely used](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_beatings_will_continue_until_morale_improves). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-04 03:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess I do a pretty piss poor job of the clan/tribe/pack thing. When traveling in New Zealand and Australia I'd get into a rant and have local people reassuring me that they understood all Americans didn't support Bush. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-27 19:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure.  That line was taken directly from the article.  This says it better but is too long for a headline:

 Malone and Woolley didnt find that women per se were the key to a good C factor. Its just that social sensitivity, which was overwhelmingly the leading ingredient in high C factor, was overly correlated to women. In fact, when they controlled for the number of women in a group, it was shown that it was the emotional sensitivity scores which won out. So adding a woman to a team no more guarantees higher success rates than adding an Aaron to your dance party will make it a success.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-19 05:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, that looks like what she needs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-18 23:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend needs to be able to describe and tag her photos and then put them on a CD.  The CD would be for archival purposes and also to gives a copy to someone who didn't have an internet connection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-12 17:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article:

 As we work on specific policy issues, lets organize with an eye toward building not coalitions but communities. In hard times, coalitions evaporate, but communities have a shot at surviving.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-10 05:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen it.  It's $26.25 from [2mminutes.com](http://www.2mminutes.com/products/pc/viewPrd.asp?idProduct=22). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-07 17:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He says:

Democrats continuously voted for Bush policies because they were either indifferent to their enactment or actively supported them, and were owned and controlled by the same factions as the GOP. 

What a strangle hold!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-07 04:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the way evolution does it, I believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-05 20:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the only way to prevent that is to do a search before submitting, I'm not sure that's always practical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-17 22:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do any agents search sites like reddit looking for possibile violations they can pursue?  How would they go about pursuing it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-15 19:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-15 08:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interactive Brokers, because trades in my IRA account are only $1, with a $20/month minimum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-07 23:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which part of the article led you to believe he was advocating that someone else should decide what you listen to or watch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-07 20:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, just thought it was interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-05 23:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should be required reading for engineers, architects, city planners, building inspectors, and pretty much everyone over the age of 12.  And it would make a terrific movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-04 00:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  That's what we'll do then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-01 18:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is cooperation among animals, though.  So worse than animals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-01 00:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all.  Just that there was some controversy in the link you posted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-31 21:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You say that like it's the end of the matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-31 18:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Googling "joy of atheism" gets over 5000 hits.  Some of those have got to be inspiring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-17 18:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After 3 trades, I'm better off than at $7 a trade.  I don't have to make 20 trades, just pay at least $20. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-17 01:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much do you guys pay per trade with Schwab, BofA, Ameritrade?  On Interactive Brokers I pay $1 per trade with a $20/month minimum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-15 07:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does your condition affect the way you think?  The way you program? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-13 23:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You agree with the article and headline, then: 

Torture is not simply illegal, immoral and ineffective. It is also counter-productive.

The meaning of that is that torture is illegal, immoral, ineffective and counter-productive.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-04 21:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In what ways do you expect genetics to contribute to social goals?  Is there a possibility that genetics can help with early identification of sociopaths?  Or even just greedy bullies?  It seems they have inordinate power over the rest of us who make up 99+% of the planet's population. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-04 07:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Native English.  Fluent Swahili with a somewhat limited vocabulary.  Some very rusty French and German.  Formerly a little Japanese, mostly forgotten.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-02 00:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was passed by the Senate Health Committee and goes next to the Senate Appropriations Committee.  Different but still very good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-26 22:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there's something implied but not stated, it's more like **(supposed)** than **(about)**.  I don't sense this as a kind of future tense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-26 01:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easy enough to buy [Market Vectors Chinese Renminbi](http://finance.yahoo.com/q?s=CNY) but my small holding is only up a smidgen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-26 00:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your brush is too broad.  **alewis14151** is 67, I'm 73 and we are not the old people you're talking about.  I didn't even vote for Obama. Since I'm not in a swing state I didn't have to choose between a woman and a black man -- I voted for a black woman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
