<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1529</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 01:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm gay." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 01:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Eh, I got work in the morning. Catch ya later!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 00:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 07:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ron Paul suggests using DDT to stop the spread of Ebola (like malaria), and is quite wrong about that being an effective treatment. From the article:

"'As far as I can make out he's wrong about everything,' Fordham University's Dr. Alexander van Tulleken told Foreign Policy. No licensed or approved treatment for Ebola exists. Yes, the experimental ZMapp drug seems to have effectively treated two American aid workers transported from Liberia to Atlanta, and more such untested drugs are in development. But those patients have also benefited from expert care, van Tulleken notes, so the jury's still out. 'The only treatments for Ebola really are supportive care' such as ventilation to support lung failure, dialysis for kidney failure or fluid replacement via IV.

As for Paul's claims about DDT and organic phosphates, neither is an actual treatment nor control mechanism for Ebola. While some in the public health community view DDT as a legitimate solution for slowing malaria, there's no science that says it would cure or control Ebola.
'What Ron Paul has done is confuse Ebola with malaria,' van Tulleken says. **'If you hose DDT around, you get rid of the mosquitoes, and maybe get rid of malaria. But Ebola is transmitted by bodily fluid. He's really fucked it up.'** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ebola Expert on Ron Paul: 'He Really Fucked Up' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 07:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 06:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/botsrights </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drug-fueled, EDM-obsessed millennials are saving the music business </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 21:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Associated Press journalist, translator killed by explosion in Gaza </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 00:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Associated Press journalist, translator killed by explosion in Gaza </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 00:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Militarization of the Police: Its dangerous and wrong to treat Ferguson, Missouri, as a war zone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 22:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Militarization of the Police: Its dangerous and wrong to treat Ferguson, Missouri, as a war zone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 22:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 20:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't voting mandatory in Australia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 08:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God this is gonna be a question on ELI5 in like 6 months, the way things are going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 22:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [link to study](http://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nclimate2335.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The much-debated Keystone XL pipeline could produce four times more global warming pollution than the State Department calculated earlier this year, a new study concludes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 22:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The night before his husband's funeral, Kendall Capers was told the service was cancelled. The pastor of New Hope Missionary Baptist Church in Tampa learned the pair was gay and the congregation was livid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 20:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The night before his husband's funeral, Kendall Capers was told the service was cancelled. The pastor of New Hope Missionary Baptist Church in Tampa learned the pair was gay and the congregation was livid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 20:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 10:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, indubitably! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An "unprecedented" spill from a mine tailings pond in Canadas pristine British Columbia has prompted a local state of emergency and water ban while environmentalists worry the contamination could have far-reaching environmental impacts as salmon return to spawn. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 00:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Europes low inflation is sending it into a lost decade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 00:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Europes low inflation is sending it into a lost decade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 00:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> European Spacecraft Pulls Alongside Comet After 10 Years and Four Billion Miles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 20:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the Summer Music Festival Bubble is About to Burst </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 20:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 00:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He really could've just given a straightforward "I was happy to see so many great law enforcement folks there last week, whether they were on duty or not." It was a little too bullshitty of an answer. Gotta really tread that line carefully between "bullshit" and "steaming bullshit." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An American Jewish blogger who called the genocide of the Palestinian people a "responsible" and "permissible" goal has continued to defend his position on social media despite widespread criticism. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 20:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Managers are nearly twice as likely as service workers to get paid time off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 20:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An internal investigation by the Central Intelligence Agency has found that its officers improperly penetrated a computer network used by the Senate Intelligence Committee in preparing its report on the C.I.A.'s detention and interrogation program. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 19:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A sharply divided House approved a Republican plan Wednesday to launch a campaign-season lawsuit against President Barack Obama, accusing him of exceeding the bounds of his constitutional authority. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 07:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The middle class is 20 percent poorer than it was in 1984 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 23:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The middle class is 20 percent poorer than it was in 1984 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 23:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Renting drives U.S. homeownership to 19-year low </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 22:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A federal appeals court panel ruled Tuesday that a Mississippi law that would close the state's only abortion clinic is unconstitutional. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 22:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Insurgents fighting in Syria to oust President Bashar al-Assad detonated bomb-packed tunnels under buildings in the contested northern city of Aleppo on Tuesday, killing at least 13 pro-government troops, opposition activists said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 22:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A top Canadian government research organisation has been struck by Chinese hackers, the government has said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 22:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a startling charge delivered at an anti-Initiative 594 meeting last week at Silverdale, the National Rifle Associations chief state lobbyist likened Washingtons campaign to close the gun show loophole to Nazi Germany. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 00:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The new land of opportunity for immigrants is Germany </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 03:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The new land of opportunity for immigrants is Germany </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 03:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> States that allow officers to pull over a driver for texting while driving saw fewer deaths than those that use secondary enforcement of texting bans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 03:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five members of a family, including three children, were found shot dead at their southern Maine home on Sunday, with a gun located near one of the bodies and no outside involvement suspected, a police spokesman said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 03:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ebola kills senior doctor in Liberia: First Liberian physician dies in an outbreak that has killed more than 650 people in West Africa since February </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 03:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A tanker carrying crude oil from Iraqi Kurdistan was anchored near the Port of Galveston, Texas, on Sunday, a delivery that has infuriated Baghdad, which has threatened to sue anyone who buys the black gold. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 03:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Only stones remain': Gaza lies in ruins | Palestinians in Gaza have been shocked by the scale of Israeli destruction, as long-term truce efforts continue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 03:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S.: Satellite Images Show Russian Rockets Hitting Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 20:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Many Lawyers Does It Take to Fight a War? | When the dust finally settles in Gaza, the battle will head to the courtroom. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 20:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Kneecap the Thug in the Kremlin | It's time to treat Vladimir Putin like the crime boss he is: Go after his money. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 20:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hamas rejected Israel's four-hour extension of a humanitarian cease-fire Saturday as the Palestinian death toll in the conflict rose to more than 1,000. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 21:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Typical Household, Now Worth a Third Less: The inflation-adjusted net worth for the typical household was $87,992 in 2003. Ten years later, it was only $56,335, or a 36 percent decline, according to a study financed by the Russell Sage Foundation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 20:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United States shut down its embassy in Libya on Saturday and evacuated its diplomats to neighboring Tunisia under U.S. military escort amid a significant deterioration in security in Tripoli as fighting intensified between rival militias, the State Department said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 20:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraines army advanced on a last main separatist stronghold as the U.S. said Vladimir Putin is poised to give the rebels heavy weapons and European Union leaders considered their toughest sanctions yet on Russia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 20:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraines army advanced on a last main separatist stronghold as the U.S. said Vladimir Putin is poised to give the rebels heavy weapons and European Union leaders considered their toughest sanctions yet on Russia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 20:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barrel Bomb Attacks Devastate Iraqi Families </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 20:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Liberian man who died in quarantine in Lagos was suffering from the deadly virus Ebola, Nigerian officials said Friday, confirming that the worst-ever outbreak of the virus has reached Africa's most populous country. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 21:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most conservative way to fight poverty is to send everyone a government check </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 21:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
