<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3651</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 23:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's gone down 0.1 pH. It's now 7.9 to 8.2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 22:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is one right answer. It is this one. ^

*pronounced Ehn-Cel-Lay-Dee-Ans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 21:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can't know with just Cassini. When Cassini was sent out the idea that Enceladus of all places would look even marginally interesting (life-wise) was laughable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enceladus, Saturn's 6th largest moon, has a warm ocean with hydrothermal vents. This is the first ever discovered outside of Earth, and makes for the most habitable off-world environment ever found. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 19:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police lineups cause false accusations up to 60% of the time. But now scientists are exploring "nose-witness testimony" in a new study that suggests victims may be able to identify their attackers based on body odor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 13:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 19:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like it would look like some sort of cross between Lucy and Homo habilis... so sorta ape plus caveman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 21:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough.

And when you tally how much money every Star Trek movie grossed collectively since 1979 (without correcting for inflation, we admit), its only slightly more than that one Transformers movie made at the box office.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 17:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point...the mirror test has some flaws. 

But note, rhesus monkeys have never passed the mirror test before. The study is interesting because these monkeys, which do not intrinsically understand mirrors, could *learn* to use them. That's promising, especially when you think of neurologic conditions that cause humans to fail the mirror test. If mirror recognition can be taught, perhaps therapy can help these people in the future.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 20:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...says the biologist :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 20:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those Alberta servers are clearly not made to handle Redditors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 15:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It turns out that cowbirds gauge their risk of death-by-truck based on distance, not speed.

So yeah, basically.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 18:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robert Seyfarth, a psychology professor at the University of Pennsylvania and pioneer in the fields of animal behavior and learning, wrote in an e-mail. This is the first time that a professional linguist has tackled the data on call combinations in wild monkeys.

So at least from a research standpoint, it means that we may want to start examining animal calls through the lens of linguistics. That's a sort of revolutionary idea, since we tend to think of animals noises as "calls", rather than a language or a dialect with logic-based rules. It's an interesting new avenue for research.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists translate monkey sounds into English, and develop linguistic rules for different primate dialects. Their research is published in the journal Linguistics and Philosophy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 17:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 20:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always think it's ironic that Greens cite scientific consensus for climate change, but ignore the equally compelling evidence that GMOs are safe. 

If you're on the side of science, stick with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 20:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WELL...the DoE lightbulb thing and the EXIM ban were honestly a bit draconian. It's one thing to charge companies extra for choosing the less environmentally friendly option, or to add taxes or incentives. But these were outright bans on investing in incandescent lightbulbs and coal-fired power plants. And the DoT light rail thing just shuts down current projects (the same senators who pushed for that rider are also working on new light rail projects as we speak).

The only thing that I see on your list that looks purely spiteful and "villain level" is the UN Climate Fund. Why the hell can't we let the poor guy fulfill his pledge to save the world?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 19:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even small farmers are notoriously bad for the environment. They all need to make money, especially the small ones, and so they often let their cash crops mess up normal crop cycles.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 19:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, the good news is that these sorts of things can be easily reversed next year. They won't be...but they could be. Every year when it comes time to figure out appropriations, it's another opportunity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 19:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It made the farmers pretty happy. It's strange, you usually think of farmers as being lovers of the land and pro-Earth etc...and then you take a look at the politics of it all, and notice that farmers are usually the ones pushing hardest against climate and land protection. Strange times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 18:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pres. Obama is not allowed to fulfill his pledge to give $3 billion to the United Nations Green Climate Fund, designed to spur other countries to respond to global warming.

...that can't be a good thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
