<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1317</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 22:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For $80k you might as well get a Tesla instead for a few bucks more. But maybe that's what he's getting at with letting this generation of ELR retire so they can have something better to go after Tesla with in the future. He's been involved with that E-tron R8 at Audi. I'm all for something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cadillac CEO Personally Comments On Blog Post Calling Him Out For Killing The ELR And Calling Chevy Volt Owners Idiots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 16:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 02:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your copy paste cop defense argument is weak. This was a murder. And he lied in the police report to CYA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 09:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next outrage: Cop shoots a 12 year old kid in the back. Why is it always shoot to kill? Why is running or holding a gun or resisting arrest now an instant death sentence? Even Rodney King wouldn't have a chance these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 09:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rutledge Wood is just great. So are Freiburger   Finnegan. Hey Derek. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 09:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm okay with Top Gear USA. It's not gonna be the same so I'm glad they abandoned the British format after S1. Who needs 10 minutes every episode with some asshole celebrity driving a cheap car around the same track? Rutledge Wood is the breakout star of TGA. Tanner can really drive. Adam I'm still not sold on. Adam Carolla might be good in that spot but you'll eventually have to fire him for being a dick like Clarkson.

But TGA is better than no Top Gear or all these dumb shows about flipping cars for cash, screwing people over and being a douchebag. We have our quota there. Also TGA doesn't shit all over American cars at every turn. Roadkill is fun but most of those cars are complete garbage not worth putting a dime into. I guess that's part of its charm though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even Twitter's 'Who To Follow' Suggestions Won't Let Poor Monica Lewinsky Be... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 03:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 07:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However I'm pretty sure Top Gear will carry on...after all, how many different Dr. Who's has the BBC put on the air? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 06:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Sure he's funny and makes good television but he's a big ugly bigoted asshole baby. You can't drop the N word on camera, incite a near riot in a foreign country, and beat up your producer in the span of a few months and expect to remain employed by a state run television network. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I see the Internet crying over Jeremy Clarkson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 05:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
