<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8210</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former trooper accuses Utah Highway Patrol of needlessly and publicly humiliating him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 12:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daddy, daddy, what are you doing? Mom hears daughters last words before dad kills girl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 12:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 12:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relative text:

Asimina triloba, the pawpaw, paw paw, paw-paw, or common pawpaw, is a species of Asimina (the pawpaw genus) in the same plant family (the Annonaceae) as the custard-apple, cherimoya, sweetsop, ylang-ylang and soursop. The pawpaw is native to the Eastern, Southern, and Midwestern United States and adjacent southernmost Ontario, Canada, from New York west to southeastern Nebraska, and south to northern Florida and eastern Texas. The pawpaw is a patch-forming (clonal) understory tree found in well-drained, deep, fertile bottom-land and hilly upland habitat, with large, simple leaves and large fruits. **The paw paw is the largest edible fruit indigenous to the United States.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The paw paw is the largest edible fruit indigenous to the United States. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 12:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 20:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came upon this situation 

You did huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 20:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Common sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 20:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pigs taste amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for sarasotacarpetandcle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 20:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 20:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not as important as you think you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 20:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I have to have that faith first.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 19:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Somali </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 19:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buy the t-shirt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 18:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems to me you like to tell people what they should do, how they should do it, and how they should act.  You sound like a selfish and narcissistic individual.  Two traits commonly found in rapists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When all else fails, insults abound in TIL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 18:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 18:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you can't answer what I was called out about?

You can't point out where I joked about their being raped?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 17:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting that you are so pissed 

[Uh, I am?](http://i.giphy.com/MZqKytwjOkPHG.gif)  

about being called out.

[Being called out about what?](http://i.giphy.com/MZqKytwjOkPHG.gif)

Kinda sad too, that even knowing people who have been victimised, that you think it is appropriate and okay to joke about it.

Can you please point out to me where I joked about their being raped?  Go ahead, [I'll wait](http://i.giphy.com/iiMoePGtKauU8.gif).

My suggestion is, if you are overly sensitive and PC, to stay away from /r/askreddit.  You're obviously too thin skinned.  

Or, in your words, "*You knob. Why so serious?*"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 17:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

**In 1991, she voiced the baby, Julie, in Look Who's Talking Too. She was nominated for a Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Supporting Actress.** She appeared three times on Saturday Night Live from 1991 to 1994, co-hosting with then-husband Tom Arnold in 1992. In 1994, she released a second book, My Lives. That same year, Barr became the first female comedian to host the MTV Video Music Awards on her own. She remained the only to have done so until comedian Chelsea Handler hosted in 2010. In 1997, she made guest appearances on 3rd Rock from the Sun and The Nanny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Roseanne Barr was nominated for a Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Supporting Actress in 1991. She voiced the baby, Julie, in Look Who's Talking Too. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 17:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dallas SWAT standoff with barricaded, armed man ends safely </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man leads police on 80-mile chase from Fort Worth to Dallas and back | </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL /u/deadfreds didn't read Rule III. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

The first lawn mower was invented by Edwin Budding in 1830 in Thrupp, just outside Stroud, in Gloucestershire, England. Budding's mower was designed primarily to cut the grass on sports grounds and extensive gardens, as a superior alternative to the scythe, and was granted a British patent on August 31, 1830.

Budding's first machine was 19 inches (480 mm) wide with a frame made of wrought iron. The mower was pushed from behind. Cast iron gear wheels transmitted power from the rear roller to the cutting cylinder, allowing the rear roller to drive the knives on the cutting cylinder; the ratio was 16:1. Another roller placed between the cutting cylinder and the main or land roller could be raised or lowered to alter the height of cut. The grass clippings were hurled forward into a tray-like box. It was soon realized, however, that an extra handle was needed in front to help pull the machine along.Overall, these machines were remarkably similar to modern mowers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The first lawn mower was invented by Edwin Budding in 1830 in England. Budding's mower was designed primarily to cut grass on sports grounds and extensive gardens, as an alternative to the scythe, and was granted a British patent on August 31, 1830. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man killed in lawnmower rollover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man killed in lawnmower rollover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You cum a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ferguson, MO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, they don't go anywhere.  Being that you'll be able to run up to it pretty quick, what the hell then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  

This is one of those things in society that I don't understand why people think it's weird/sad/etc.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Stick it in crazy." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL /u/redroguetech can't comprehend simple rules.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thinking rape is a serious, devastating crime **or being you**?

[HA!](http://i.giphy.com/LVIbmaUwpRJ1C.gif)

Doesn't change that it's rape

Unless my SO is tired and gave me permission ahead of time.

it isn't what you want to hear

I actually could care less either way.  Only thing I **want** to hear right now is someone telling me I won Powerball last night. 

Shame on you for perpetuating rape

Yes.  Because my reddit comment perpetuates rape culture. [OK](http://i.giphy.com/3xz2BY6H3nhkb0wabe.gif)  

I hope that nobody needs to depend on you as a support in healing from the experience.

Actually, I've had two people confide in me their experience in being raped so that they may talk about it and help themselves feel even just a little bit better.  [Shame on you](http://i.giphy.com/MT42FIRFdmKxa.gif) for wanting to take away a support outlet.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 14:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about every single post for every single day that is related to something.

Now you're just being ridiculous and reaching for an argument because you can't get your way.  Then again, coming from someone who has posted on a few occasion in TIL, where you put spin in the title of your post, I'm not surprised.

New posts were and are being added without being automatically deleted. Ergo, the rule is not being enforced in general.

AND now you're just going in circles.  Again, because you want to have a point but you don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 11:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shut up and go be a white knight somewhere else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 00:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if I [ask](http://i.giphy.com/GQ5F7StyjSwRG.gif) nicely? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 23:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will just ask CT_Kid's wife where I need to pinch **you**.... 

I'm [confused](http://i.giphy.com/CvgezXSuQTMTC.gif). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 23:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And?

And what?  You're talking about posts going back **years** yet the rule pertaining to police brutality wasn't in place at that time.  Not a difficult concept to understand why those ones were not removed.

So far, every post added after the rule has not been removed

Yet you weren't even aware of the rule in the first place so how do you know when it was added?  Additionally, it's highly improbable that the mods are going to catch every single post put up on here so I'm not surprised *every* post added hasn't been removed.  With that said, you also have no idea how many have been removed because you can't see them anyway and have no idea what has actually been posted and taken down in totality.

despite all of them being "related" to something in the news in the last 8 years

The rule doesn't talk about *something in the news* in the last 8 years.  It mentions many different aspects within the rule itself that requires only an elementary school level of comprehension.

 if the mods want to delete everything in TIL

I'm pretty sure they want to delete everything in TIL **that doesn't abide by the posted rules.**

In the meantime, the rule is meaningless.

Why is it meaningless?  Because you can't grasp the simplicity of it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 22:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The intent is from the time the rule is created.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 22:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> going back YEARS without being flagged 

Well genius maybe that's because that aspect of the rule was just recently added. Tough concept I know.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 20:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FIFY

FIFY

And see my other comment I just left.  I'll get some regardless.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 20:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slip it in slowly while she sleeps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 19:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are my boss... 

FIFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 18:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only thing I can think of is to say they did it.  Other than that, I'm stumped for a legitimate reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 17:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, [OK](http://i.giphy.com/hhy5zwTKXRXxe.gif). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 17:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Standing in line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 17:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/Fighting_Ferret </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 14:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have however many helium balloons that would be needed to carry me up as high as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 14:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their selfies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 13:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

The Quadruple Bypass Burger with 9,982 calories (41,760 kJ) has been identified as one of the "world's best junk foods". It consists of four half-pound beef patties, twenty strips of bacon, eight slices of American cheese, a whole tomato and half an onion served in a bun coated with lard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The Heart Attack Grills Quadruple Bypass Burger has 9,982 calories and has been identified as one of the "world's best junk foods". It consists of 4 half-pound beef patties, 20 strips of bacon, 8 slices of American cheese, a whole tomato and half an onion served in a bun coated with lard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 13:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Connecticut serial killer already jailed for 2003 murder of still-missing woman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 13:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mother's Day ends in arrest for 28-year-old woman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 13:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police: 3 men met women online, robbed them at gunpoint </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 13:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Explosion rips through bus on Mass. Pike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 13:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disturbance call ends with Denver cop buying dinner for family </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 03:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 20:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reddit people is not sleep bark dog neighbor outside because. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 20:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have an affair with the wife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 20:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Bankers' Friends](http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/45/G.W._Bush_delivers_State_of_the_Union_Address.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 20:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/Fighting_Ferret </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 20:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grilled at her place.  BBQ pork and chicken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 20:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one who says "the" instead of "da." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 20:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kickstart My Heart by Motley Crue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 16:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

The first Peet's Coffee   Tea store opened in 1966 in Berkeley, California by Dutch native Alfred Peet. He chose to focus on roasting batches with fresher, higher quality seeds than was the norm at the time. He was a trainer and supplier to the founders of Starbucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Peet's Coffee   Tea founder, Alfred Peet, was a trainer and supplier to the founders of Starbucks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 16:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 15:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

Women have used tampons during menstruation for thousands of years. In her book Everything You Must Know About Tampons (1981), Nancy Friedman writes, "[T]here is evidence of tampon use throughout history in a multitude of cultures. The oldest printed medical document, Papyrus Ebers, refers to the use of soft papyrus tampons by Egyptian women in the fifteenth century B.C. Roman women used wool tampons. Women in ancient Japan fashioned tampons out of paper, held them in place with a bandage, and changed them 10 to 12 times a day. Traditional Hawaiian women used the furry part of a native fern called hapu'u; and grasses, mosses and other plants are still used by women in parts of Asia." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Women in ancient Japan fashioned tampons out of paper, held them in place with a bandage, and changed them 10 to 12 times a day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 15:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 15:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

The stereotype of Jews eating Chinese food on Christmas does have an origin. In 1935, the New York Times reported that a restaurant owner named Eng Shee Chuck had brought chow mein to a Jewish childrens home in Newark on Christmas Day. This article is considered to be one of the earliest publications of the stereotype that relates Jews to Chinese food on Christmas.

The relationship that Jews have to Chinese food certainly goes deeper than this stereotype. Eating Chinese [food] has become a meaningful symbol of American Judaism For in eating Chinese, the Jews found a modern means of expressing their traditional cultural values. The savoring of Chinese food is now a ritualized celebration of immigration, education, family, community, and continuity. Chinese food is considered a staple in the Jewish culture, and the further option of kosher Chinese food is also becoming more and more available in the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL In 1935, the New York Times reported that a restaurant owner named Eng Shee Chuck had brought chow mein to a Jewish childrens home in Newark on Christmas Day. This article is considered to be one of the earliest publications of the stereotype that relates Jews to Chinese food on Christmas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 15:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 22:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hurt Locker. Movie overall sucked but the scene in the grocery store/cereal aisle is spot on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 22:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other: vagina </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 22:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liquor store </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 22:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuq.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 22:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pay bills </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 21:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do these assholes get off thinking they are immune to things that the people they "represent" are not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man admits stealing car, fleeing with owner clinging to roof </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 21:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man admits making child porn with 2 kidnapped Amish girls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 21:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mom taped to chair, hit with shotgun; daughter takes cash   car </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 21:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bark with a bang: Dog eats 23 rifle bullets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 21:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 21:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relative text:

In Berlin in 1931, Dora R, born as Rudolph R, became the first known transgender woman to undergo the vaginoplasty surgical approach.

This was followed by Lili Elbe in Berlin during 1930-1931. She started with the removal of the male sex organs, the operation supervised by Dr. Magnus Hirschfeld. Lili went on to have four more subsequent operations that included an unsuccessful uterine transplant, the rejection of which resulted in death. An earlier known recipient of this was Magnus Hirschfeld's housekeeper, but their identity is unclear at this time.

The Iranian government's response to homosexuality is to endorse, and fully pay for, sex reassignment surgery. The leader of Iran's Islamic Revolution, Ayatollah Ruhollah Khomeini, issued a fatwa declaring sex reassignment surgery permissible for "diagnosed transsexuals." Eshaghian's documentary, Be Like Others, chronicles a number of stories of Iranian gay men who feel transitioning is the only way to avoid further persecution, jail and/or execution. The head of Iran's main transsexual organization, Maryam Khatoon Molkarawho convinced Khomeini to issue the fatwa on transsexualityconfirmed that some people who undergo operations are gay rather than transsexual.

**Thailand is the country that performs the most sex reassignment surgeries, followed by Iran.**

On 12 June 2003, European Court of Human Rights ruled in favor of Van Kck, a German transsexual woman whose insurance company denied her reimbursement for sex reassignment surgery as well as hormone replacement therapy. The legal arguments related to the Article 6 of the European Convention on Human Rights as well as the Article 8. This affair is referred to as Van Kck vs Germany. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Thailand is the country that performs the most sex reassignment surgeries, followed by Iran. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 21:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 15:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

Sundae (Korean pronunciation: [sund], also commonly spelled soondae) is a Korean dish made generally by boiling or steaming cow or pig's intestines that are stuffed with various ingredients. It is a kind of blood sausage and believed to have been eaten for a long time. The recipes related to sundae can be found in Joseon cookbooks published in 19th century such as "Gyuhap chongseo" and "Siuijeonseo". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL "Sundae" is a Korean dish made generally by boiling or steaming cow or pig's intestines that are stuffed with various ingredients. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 15:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 15:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

While being filmed by documentary maker Louis Theroux, they picketed a local appliance store because it sold Swedish vacuum cleaners, which the church viewed as being supportive of gay people because of Swedish prosecution of ke Green, a pastor critical of homosexuality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The Westboro Baptist Church picketed an appliance store as it sold Swedish vacuum cleaners. The church viewed it as being supportive of gay people due to Swedish prosecution of ke Green, a pastor critical of homosexuality. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 15:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 15:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP submitted this TIL with an extra "?TIL" at the end of the URL because the wiki article has been posted before in /r/todayilearned .

And? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 15:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> translated the word into **Enlgish**

Awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man shot by Wake Forest police dies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 15:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 14:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty pathetic that things like this even need to be voted on.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Brown Finds Unknown Female Intruder Naked In His Bed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 13:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former judicial marshal facing prostitution, human trafficking charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 13:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 20:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get it drunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 19:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fleshlight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 19:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What do you do while waiting for AOL to connect?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 19:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When people trip and fall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 19:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steak, corn on the cob, fries, garlic bread, and apple pie for dessert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 19:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll keep that tucked away for now............ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 17:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh crap, are you bringing the strap on again?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 17:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If reposts were actually banned, this subreddit would be dead within a month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 17:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Does this mean no sex for awhile?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 17:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the middle of a marathon orgy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 17:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd rather hear someone squeal like a pig while getting anally raped? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 16:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you gotta watch out for those people in NE Georgia.  I hear they like to listen to people squeal like a pig occasionally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 16:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That kid is going to get his in jail.  I'm sure he'll be thrown up against a wall as well and have a train run on him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 16:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> was ahead of the times

Then they got stuck somewhere along the way....... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 14:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

The Three Sisters are three rocky islands in the Potomac River in Washington, D.C., west of the Key Bridge. A notable landmark in colonial times, the islets are less well known as the Three Sisters Islands and Three Sisters Island.

Various legends are associated with the Three Sisters. One of the earliest myths involves three Algonquian sisters who crossed the river in an attempt to win the release of their brothers, who had been kidnapped by another tribe. They drowned while crossing the river, and were turned into the rocky islets. A less commonly cited legend says three daughters of the local Native American chief were marooned on the islands by their father after rejecting the husbands he picked out for them. The legend holds that the sisters cursed the spot, saying that if they could not cross the Potomac there, no one could. A strange moaning or bell-like sound is said to come from the Potomac River when the curse is about to claim another life.

The first European to see the Three Sisters was Captain John Smith, who sailed up the Potomac River and saw them in 1607. The islets were a landmark in colonial times, and appeared on Pierre L'Enfant's first map of the area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The Three Sisters are islands in the Potomac River in D.C. Legend says three daughters were left on the islands by their father after rejecting the husbands he chose. Legend says the spot is cursed and a strange moaning sound comes from the river when the curse is about to claim another life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 14:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suspended priest due to be sentenced on meth guilty plea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 14:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New free mobile app encourages video recording of police officers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 14:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Phoenix dad jailed after throwing son against wall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 14:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 13:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

General Order No. 11 was the title of an order issued by Major-General Ulysses S. Grant on December 17, 1862, during the American Civil War. It ordered the expulsion of all Jews in his military district, comprising areas of Tennessee, Mississippi, and Kentucky. The order was issued as part of a Union campaign against a black market in Southern cotton, which Grant thought was being run "mostly by Jews and other unprincipled traders." In the war-zone, the United States licensed traders through the United States Army, which created a market for unlicensed ones. Union military commanders in the South were responsible for administering the trade licenses and trying to control the black market in Southern cotton, as well as for conducting the war. Grant issued the order in an effort to reduce corruption.

Following protests from Jewish community leaders and an outcry by members of Congress and the press, at President Abraham Lincoln's insistence, the General Order was revoked weeks later on January 17, 1863. During his campaign for the presidency in 1868, Grant repudiated the order, saying that it had been drafted by a subordinate and that he had signed it without reading it during warfare.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL General Order No. 11 (1862) was an order issued by Ulysses S. Grant ordering the expulsion of Jews in his district, comprising areas of TN, MS, and KY as part of a campaign against a black market in Southern cotton, which he thought was being run "mostly by Jews and other unprincipled traders." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 13:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 13:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:
Sickles's career was replete with personal scandals. He was censured by the New York State Assembly for escorting a known prostitute, Fanny White, into its chambers. He also reportedly took her to England, leaving his pregnant wife at home, and presented White to Queen Victoria, using as her alias the surname of a New York political opponent. In 1859, in Lafayette Square, across the street from the White House, Sickles shot and killed the district attorney of the District of Columbia, Philip Barton Key II, son of Francis Scott Key, who Sickles had discovered was having an affair with his young wife.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL In 1859, across the street from the White House, congressman Daniel Sickles shot and killed the district attorney of the District of Columbia, Philip Barton Key IIson of Francis Scott Keywho Sickles had discovered was having an affair with his young wife. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 13:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 13:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:
Slavery in Georgia is known to have been practiced by the original or earliest-known inhabitants of the future colony and state of Georgia, for centuries prior to European colonization.  However, the penal colony of the Province of Georgia, under James Oglethorpe, was the only one of the thirteen British colonies to have banned slavery (1735) before legalizing it. It was legalized by royal decree in 1751, in part due to George Whitefield's support for the institution of slavery.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The penal colony of the Province of Georgia was the only one of the thirteen British colonies to have banned slavery1735before legalizing it. It was legalized by royal decree in 1751, in part due to George Whitefield's support for the institution of slavery. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 13:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 03:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but figured with all the negative crap we see in the news all the time, I'd post something on the more positive side.  Good pic in the article of the grandmother and granddaughter on the beach to go with it too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 03:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm far from any kind of expert on this stuff so I have no idea.  With that said, I'm guessing if anything it's bought the child some time as well as happiness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas grandmother donates kidney to save her toddler granddaughter's life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 01:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas grandmother donates kidney to save her toddler granddaughter's life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 01:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 23:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Self absorbed people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 23:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was a kid I'd pull the legs off of salamanders.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 18:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The positive pregnancy test of your mistress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 18:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check the news for the latest riot outbreak.  Should be able to get some freebies there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 18:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Give a fuck, I will not." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 18:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "OP's mom" is up near the top if it's not **at** the top.

No idea how it started though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 18:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't matter to them, don't let them matter to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 18:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes, sometimes, once in awhile, and one or two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 18:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marriage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 18:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly what they do when I tell them something and they want to act interested when they really aren't.

Either ignore them altogether and stare blankly or change the subject completely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 17:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rita Bennet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 17:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone who is open minded and not selfish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 17:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ignore them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 17:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crunchy.  Who doesn't like some nuts in their mouth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 17:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe it was Pitfall on one of the Atari systems within the few years prior to the first Nintendo system coming out.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 16:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No reason whatsoever that phone calls for prisoners are a necessity anyway.  Regular snail mail will work out just fine and most are allowed visitation as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 16:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I downvoted you

[OK](http://i.giphy.com/hLUiXoGKNIVb2.gif)

Are you implying also that if Bernie Sanders was even more left-wing, that he'd actually stand a snowball's chance in the Democrat primaries?

I'm not implying anything.  I'm stating that Jeb Bush, who apparently trails most of the Republican field in Iowa, is not at the level of blowhard crazy that some of the others are at.  If you can't discuss the topic/article at hand, best to stay out of the thread.

Or are you saying that the left-wing base is educated and enlightened while the conservative base is "blowhard crazy"

I'm saying what I said at the outset.  *He's not at the level of blowhard crazy that some of the others are at.*  I'm discussing Jeb Bush and the other candidates in the Republican field.  What exactly are you talking about?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 15:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course he does.  He's not at the level of blowhard crazy that some of the others are at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 15:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to hear from Ted how he would have prevented it if he was the current acting president.  As far as I know, nobody can predict the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 56-year run over for real Shawshank escapee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 14:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two fans file class-action lawsuit against Manny Pacquiao over undisclosed injury </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 22:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP gets offended when called out on rules violation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 16:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 13:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:
In the 1950s, researchers from Quaker Oats Company, MIT and Harvard University carried out experiments at the Walter E. Fernald State School to determine how the minerals from cereals were metabolized. Parents of mentally challenged children were asked for permission to let their children be members of a Science Club and participate in research. Being a member of the Science Club gave the children special privileges. The parents were told that the children would be fed with a diet high in nutrients. However, they were not told (and the consent form contained no information indicating) that the food their children were fed contained radioactive calcium and iron. The information obtained from the experiments was to be used as part of an advertising campaign. The company was later sued because of the experiments. The lawsuit was settled on 31 December 1997.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL In the 1950s, researchers from Quaker Oats, MIT, and Harvard carried out experiments to determine how minerals from cereals were metabolized. Mentally challenged children participated in the research. They and their parents were not told the food contained radioactive calcium and iron. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 13:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 13:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:
Methuselah is a 4,846-year-old Great Basin bristlecone pine (Pinus longaeva) tree growing high in the White Mountains of Inyo County in eastern California. For many years it was the world's oldest known living non-clonal organism, until superseded by the discovery in 2013 of another bristlecone pine in the same area with an age of 5,064 years (germination in 3051 BC).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Methuselah is a 4,846-year-old Great Basin bristlecone pine tree growing in eastern California.For years it was the world's oldest known living non-clonal organism, until superseded by the discovery in 2013 of another bristlecone pine in the same area with an age of 5,064 years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 13:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 13:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

The Tower at PNC Plaza is a skyscraper currently completing construction in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. It will be the new corporate headquarters of the PNC Financial Services Group. It will have approximately 800,000 square feet (74,000 m2) and stand 33 stories (545 feet) tall. Nearby buildings totaling 37,000 square feet (3,400 m2), were purchased by PNC and deconstructed to make space for the Tower at PNC Plaza.The project was estimated to cost $400 million when announced in 2011 (or $419 million today). Construction started in spring of 2012 and is planned to be completed in September 2015. The tower will be the greenest Skyrise ever built and will exceed the current criteria for a LEED Platinum certified building. The Tower will feature numerous sustainable attributes such as an operable double skin facade, an onsite blue water reuse system, locally sourced building materials, fixtures and furniture made from recycled materials, and numerous other green strategies to substantially reduce the environmental impact of the building. Some of these features will enable the Tower's heating and cooling systems to operate in a "net-zero-energy state" up to 30% of the year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The new PNC bank headquarters in Pittsburgh will be the greenest sky rise ever built and exceed current criteria for a LEED Platinum certified building. Some of the features will enable the tower's heating and cooling systems to operate in a "net-zero-energy state" up to 30% of the year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 13:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No Sign of $10 Million Bail From Floyd Mayweather for Suge Knight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 11:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lottery Winner Who Was Given $75 Instead of $75,000 Was Undercover Inspector </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 11:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Men Arrested in Alleged Road Rage Attack With Ax in Palm Desert </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 11:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 13:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

How come all the Jedi have first and second names except Yoda? We have Obi-Wan Kenobi, Anakin Skywalker, Mace Windu and Qui-Gon Jinn, among others, but Yoda's just Yoda. In fact, his full name  never revealed in the films  is Minch Yoda. Lucas deliberately decided to leave him with just one name to enhance the air of mystery and power around him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Yoda's full name  never revealed in the films  is "Minch Yoda." George Lucas deliberately decided to leave him with just one name to enhance the air of mystery and power around him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 13:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 13:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

After attempting to develop his own version of the proposed show called House of Mystery, Joseph Barbera, who handled the development and sale of Hanna-Barbera shows while William Hanna handled production, passed the task along to story writers Joe Ruby   Ken Spears and artist/character designer Iwao Takamoto. Their original treatment, based in part on The Archie Show, was titled Mysteries Five, and featured five teenagers: Geoff, Mike, Kelly, Linda, Linda's brother "W.W." and their dog, Too Much, who were all members of the band "Mysteries Five," including the dog who played bongos. When "The Mysteries Five" were not performing at gigs, they were out solving spooky mysteries involving ghosts, zombies, and other supernatural creatures. Ruby and Spears were unable to decide whether Too Much would be a large cowardly dog or a small feisty dog. When the former was chosen, Ruby and Spears wrote Too Much as a Great Dane, but revised the dog character to a large sheepdog (similar to the Archies' sheepdog, Hot Dog) just before their presentation to Silverman, as Ruby feared the character would be too similar to the comic strip character Marmaduke. Silverman rejected their initial pitch, and after consulting with Barbera on next steps, got Barbera's permission to go ahead with Too Much being a Great Dane instead of a sheepdog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Scooby-Doo, initially named Too Much, was originally written to be a Great Dane but then changed to a sheepdog due to worries that hed be too similar to Marmaduke. The initial character pitch was rejected and he was reverted back to a Great Dane. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 13:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carly Fiorina jumps into GOP 2016 presidential field </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 12:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corpus Christi police chief dies in motorcycle accident </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 12:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shirtless Man Gets Stuck Upside Down on Basketball Hoop, Prompting Rescue at Seattle Park </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 12:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shirtless Man Gets Stuck Upside Down on Basketball Hoop, Prompting Rescue at Seattle Park </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 12:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gone for Three Years, Missing Dog Reunited With SoCal Family After Being Found in Virginia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 12:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teen Mom Tosses Baby Off Pennsylvania Bridge, Then Jumps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 12:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for luxurylashloungega </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 10:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enfield, CT man caught masturbating in car parked at Suffield market </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 03:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inmate assault on officer leaves prison in lockdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 03:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for /u/BigGFly/ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 02:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 02:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you even talking about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 01:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However the article does not state rape is **the** leading cause.  The article states it is **a** leading cause among a group of three identified events.  We don't know which of the three actually has more recorded/reported events. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 01:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your source doesn't even have the word "African" anywhere in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 01:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rule V

"While **rape, sexual assault, and sexual harassment** are strongly associated with a wide range of mental health conditions for both men and women veterans, **they are the leading causes of post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD) among women**" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 21:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I was trying to figure out how best to word it to fit the 300 word character limit.  I live about a 15 minute drive from Mt. Vernon and have been there a couple of times, just never recall hearing about the "crypt" in the capitol until this morning when I was reading the site.  Pretty surreal when you go there and having his remains right there in front of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 18:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which are both equally dumb.

I want to hear what they themselves have a vision of doing and how they plan on getting it done.  What the other guy did is done and over with.

Party is insignificant to me.  The only difference, in my mind, between the two is who is stuffing money into their pockets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 18:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 16:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, I'm fully aware of that.  I didn't agree with it then and I don't agree with it now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 16:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he forgets that Democrats had their fair share of complaining about the incumbent Republican president in 2008.

I did?  You can read my mind?  

In actuality, no, I didn't forget and I'm fully aware.  However, that was in 2008 so what's the point of discussing that in a 2015 subject?  Do I agree with this tactic?  Not at all.  Not from either side.  Using the defense of "they did it so we can do it" sounds like an excuse children use when they get caught doing something wrong.  

But hey, thanks for assuming you know what I think.  I could care less if someone is "Republican" or "Democrat."  It's amazing that as soon as I question something one *side* is doing, I'm immediately put into the category of the other.  Try thinking outside the box a little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 15:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

George Washington's will directed the building of the present vault in the following words: "The family Vault at Mount Vernon requiring repairs, and being improperly situated besides, I desire that a new one of Brick, and upon a larger Scale, may be built at the foot of what is commonly called the Vineyard Inclosure. . . In which my remains, with those of my deceased relatives (now in the old Vault) and such others of my family as may chuse to be entombed there, may be deposited."

Immediately after Washington's death, Congress resolved that a marble monument should be erected to his memory in the new Capitol in the city of Washington, and that his family should be requested to permit his body to be deposited beneath it. Martha Washington's consent was solicited and obtained. A crypt was provided under the dome of the Capitol, but the project was never completed. In 1831, the surviving executors of Washington's estate removed the bodies of George and Martha Washington and those of other members of the family from the old vault to a similar structure within the present enclosure at Mount Vernon.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL After George Washington died, Congress resolved that a monument be built in the Capitol in Washington D.C. A crypt was provided under the dome but was never completed. In 1831, the executors of Washington's estate moved Georges body from the old vault to a similar structure at Mount Vernon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 15:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 14:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where in your source does it say that?  This is a clear violation of rule one.  This is what I found in your source...........which I was able to get to after having to verify my age and search through a table of contents.

This is what I found:

*How is the alcohol content in beer measured?*

*Alcohol content in beer is typically measured in one of two ways: by volume (which is most common) or by weight. Using Coors as an example: A 12-ounce serving contains 5.0 percent alcohol by volume which means that of all the liquid in the container, 5.0 percent of the liquid is alcohol. The same 12-oz. serving of Coors Light is about 4.0 percent alcohol by weight, which means that of the total weight of the liquid in the container, 4.0 percent of the weight is contributed by the alcohol.*

*Sounds simple, but if we're talking about the exact same serving of beer, why the difference between volume and weight measurements? That's because a given volume of alcohol weighs less than the same volume of water. (An ethyl alcohol molecule, or C2H5OH, is larger than a molecule of water, or H2O, and takes up more space.) So whatever the serving size, the alcohol weight percentage will always be smaller than the volume percentage. This basic fact should help dispel any myth about 3.2 beers or so-called "near-beers" allegedly containing much less alcohol compared to regular beers. The "3.2" in 3.2 beers represents the percentage of alcohol by weight, which means that there's about 4 percent alcohol by volume in the beer. Anyone who believes that he or she cannot become intoxicated consuming 3.2 beer is just plain wrong. If you know of anyone who's a believer in the 3.2 beer "myth," do him or her a favor and share the facts.*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul blames absent fathers for Baltimore protests just days after his sons arrest for DUI </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 13:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> West Baltimore photographer lands cover of Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 12:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
