<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9117</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 13:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that puddle is actually a portal to another dimension </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 13:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for being able to save for gold. I gave you some well done OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 13:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your name made me laugh... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 18:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what this person said. (I'm a fireman) also mostly we change them when approaching intersections, people get used to hearing the sirens so we change them to warn people when we are about to drive through intersections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 18:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm always that guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 18:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no this subreddit is /r/dadjokes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 13:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so today my bank account was hacked... I lost everything but the money in my home loan. I get the money back but it takes up to 45 days for the bank to do all the paperwork. so that leads me to my question. has anything like this happened to you? how did it all go?

Edit: had to edit it because I wrote this in the text box instead of the comments box </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 13:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait... he pooped on your front step? did you poop on his? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 12:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow that's pretty crazy, glad it all worked out for you in the end  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> have you ever been hacked? what was the outcome? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 12:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 21:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not going to lie it took me a couple of goes to find the mistake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 19:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> someone that obviously needs the money to buy better robbing gear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 15:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we don't have time for leap years. pretty much every animal wants to kill us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pokemon is a game where you find and catch pets then make them fight other peoples pets for money </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 21:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the title says. But if you look at it that way pokemon is a pretty dark and twisted game. You also fight young children's pets and take all their money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 12:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just started playing and i love the dialog! excellent game so far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 19:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://ssl.redditgifts.com/marketplace/product/nicolas-cage-christmas-card---merry-nic/
https://ssl.redditgifts.com/marketplace/product/happy-holidays-bitch-breaking-bad-jesse/
https://ssl.redditgifts.com/marketplace/product/funny-love-you-card---mac-and-cheese/
I would give the Nicholas cage one to my brother as he loves him (actual man to man love) the breaking bad one to my sister, she loves the show and also is a bitch... and finally the mac and cheese one to my SO, she makes amazing mac and cheese </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 19:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pretty sure if your being buried alive they wont let you take your shirt off to cover your face, most probably have hands tied </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 20:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn now every time I blink I see a dickbutt... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 21:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if one twin is born on February 28 and the other February 29 one twin could turn 100 while the other only turns 25... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 15:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you need to charge you phone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wonder what terrible things some peoples pets have seen... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 12:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So like the title says. I wonder what some bad things some peoples pets have seen (Might end up NSFW) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My puppy using his toy as a pillow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 05:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 10:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe a similar one. But no he is mine and legit picked him up today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 09:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy crap, yeah that's pretty crazy in itself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 09:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is Zeus, he's my 14 week old Siberian husky. Today is the day I finally got to pic him up. So I thought I would show him to the world. Enjoy :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi Reddit meet Zeus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 09:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 12:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok so everyone knows. I know you have to spread the branches out. My SO called out to me, saying that it looks nothing like the picture.(she didn't know) Should have said that before but have been busy trying to fix it after her Christmas tree failure. Sorry reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looks just like the picture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 11:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 09:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flintstones chewable morphine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
