<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1033</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 10:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  /r/19kidsandmounting, more like.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 09:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just trying to view it from all the angles.

So did Josh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 09:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully he was able to actually learn something from it.

Freelance gynecology?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 09:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they thought they could pray the play away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 09:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a tragedy how Christian Fundamentalist extremists have managed to sully the phrase "Christian" in barely more than a generation.

"Christian" used to be a noble and honorable appellation, and in its traditional definition remains so.

However, given all of the scandals, scams, hucksterism, fraud, and extremist right-wing political activism we've seen among Evangelical Protestants in the last 30 or so years, "Christian" has picked up very negative connotations such as to imply ignorance, smug self-delusion, and false righteousness.

It should never have been this way, but there was too much money and power to be had. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 09:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most foolish and self-destructive move the American Catholic Church ever made was to ally with frothing Fundamentalist Evangelicals on "Culture War" issues.

It's cost the Church so much in the credibility department (especially among Catholics) that I wonder if the damage can ever be undone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 06:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Doctors are not really allowed to unionize

What's the AMA, then?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 17:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not go for a swim in it, petro-apologist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 17:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can anyone take the Paul family seriously? They've been canoodling with far right-wing extremists for decades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 15:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MONEYBOMB! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 00:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another Hero Patriot from "the Party of Personal Responsibility!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 00:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another fine representative of "the Party of Personal Responsibility!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bush blames Iraq unrest on Obama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 00:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 03:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dinesh D'Souza and various other right-wing cranks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 03:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worked himself into a froth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That means it's working. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 17:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could it be . . . LIBERTY!^TM ??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 17:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "right-to-rise society"

I wouldn't be surprised if this becomes a new Republican catch phrase. I see Rove's hand here.

Remember how Rove sold GWB as a "reformer with results" and a "compassionate conservative"?

"Right-to-rise" is both alliterative and has a slight tinge of dog-whistle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 16:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully this will hasten the decline of social conservatism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 05:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I was interested in Rand, but my inbox got filled with requests for money.

Ever notice how Ron and Rand Paul ***constantly beg*** for that "worthless fiat currency" they so deride?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 04:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm more of a Democrat than anything

Yep. Because Democrats always run around snarking about "SJWs" and whining about "feminists."

Everyone believes you.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 04:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The LIBERTY!^TM Brigades are here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 04:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want a similar deal, I'm sure Ron would still be willing to take your "worthless fiat currency" in exchange for it, just like he's done for all his true believers for decades.

You act in your own "informed, rational self-interest," right? Give Paul a call! I'm sure he'll be willing to work with you. He might even throw in a racist newsletter for your troubles!





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 03:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ron Paul has been "consistent" in courting, then scamming money from White Nationalists and Neo-Confederates for decades (if that's what you mean by "consistent.")

See [The Ron Paul Survival Kit.](http://farm8.staticflickr.com/7018/6560359999_b98a55fc71.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 03:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a Bush family tradition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 03:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's OK. Those Iraqis died for FREEDOM!^TM

We liberated their souls right the fuck out of their bodies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 03:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget the Carlyle Group! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 03:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The GOP doesn't have a way of shutting that whole thing down.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 03:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeb and GWB: two more Republican Chickenhawks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 03:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm glad my brother GWB sent them all to die for his lies." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditor describes her abortion at 27 weeks, and why the House's proposed 20-week abortion ban feels like a slap in the face. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 12:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oath Keepers Founder: John McCain "Should Be Hung By The Neck Until Dead" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 02:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oath Keepers Founder: John McCain 'Should Be Hung By The Neck Until Dead' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 22:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Florida governor used mother's death to execute Medicaid ruse: Rick Scott claimed her 2013 death led to change of heart on supporting Medicaid expansion  then he privatized the program and is looking to further gut it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 23:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tornadoes reported in Oklahoma, Kansas, Nebraska </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 07:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $100,000 for a website domain name? Rand Paul pays up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 23:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio Governor Kasich to Run for President </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 23:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Bridgegate' dogs Christie as indictments, guilty pleas unveiled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 21:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indulging the Lunatics on the Right: "Gov. Greg Abbott ordered the Texas Guard to monitor federal military exercises in Texas after some citizens have lit up the Internet saying the maneuvers are actually the prelude to martial law." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 17:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul: 'Lack of fathers' responsible for 'thuggery and thievery' in Baltimore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 20:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the NRA Think Rand Paul Is Too Extreme? Why is the NRA snubbing pro-gun candidate Rand Paul? The answer lies in his historic affiliation with gun groups with even more extreme views than the NRA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 18:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron Pauls AR-15 giveaway shows hes not going anywhere, despite Rands presidential bid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 15:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberty University: The rise of a really big conservative college </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 23:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Pauls Internet Army: Welcome to the front lines of the battle for your Facebook news feed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 15:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul's son cited for DUI in Lexington </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 01:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/politics Mods pull Mother Jones article,"LISTEN: Alleged Kansas Gunman Frazier Glenn Miller Discusses the Tea Party, Obama, and Ron Paul" as "Not US Politics" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 21:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/230x3l/listen_alleged_kansas_gunman_frazier_glenn_miller/

This story was just pulled by the Mods from the /r/politics "New" queue as "Not US Politics." Decide for yourself if their characterization is accurate: the users of /r/politics aren't able to.

Here's the full text of the article:

In a 2010 radio interview, Frazier Glenn Miller, the man suspected of killing three people Sunday at a Jewish community center and a Jewish retirement center in Kansas, said he was interested in the tea party, voiced support for then-Iranian President Mahmoud Ahmadinejad, and spoke approvingly of Ron Paul, the Texas Republican congressman and presidential candidate. In late April 2010, Miller, a former Ku Klux Klan Grand Dragon, was a guest on The David Pakman Show, a nationally syndicated left-of-center radio and television program. At the time, Miller was running for US Senate as an independent in his home state of Missouri with the slogan "It's the Jews, Stupid," and Pakman pressed Miller on his extreme views.

During the interview, Miller was unabashed about his anti-Semitic positions. When asked whether he thought the United States would be better off if Hitler had succeeded, Miller responded, "Absolutely, the whole world wouldHitler would have created a paradise on Earth, particularly for white people. But he would have been fair to other people as well." He added, "Germans are blamed collectively because of the alleged so-called Holocaust."

Not surprisingly, Miller denigrated most American politicians, but cited one positively: "If I had my way [all US senators] would be in jail right now for treason, if not hung from a sturdy oak treeRon Paul is the only independent politician, representative in Washington." He also spoke highly of another conservative: "Patrick Buchanan, he's a great man, he's a great historian, he's one of the very few journalists who has the courage to speak out against Jewish domination in the country." Miller called Howard Stern "a Jew liar." When asked whether he supported the tea party, Miller replied, "The school's still out on them. They're a new movement. I'm watching them closely. I suspect, however, they'll be infiltrated by the Jews and therefore led into defeat."

During the interview, Pakman asked Miller whom he would "elect, deport, and waterboard"given the choices of President Barack Obama, Vice President Joe Biden, and former Fed chair Alan Greenspan. Miller answered, "I like Obama more than the other two, by far." He chose to elect Obama, deport Greenspan, and waterboard Biden. Miller said, "I have a great deal of admiration [for] Louis Farrakhan," and he called Ahmadinejad "a great man" because he "has guts and he tells the truth about the Jews."

"I'm a convicted felon and I'm proud of it," Miller boasted, noting that he "was convicted of declaring war on the federal government and possession of illegal weapons." He added that Jews "were responsible for my conviction that prompted me to go underground and declare warMorris Dees mainly, he's a Jew that runs the Southern Poverty Law Center." (The SPLC monitors hate groups.)

In November 2013, Pakman had an exchange of emails with Miller in which Miller noted that he was "close friends" with Craig Cobb, a white supremacist who had attempted to form an all-white town in Leith, North Dakota. According to Miller, the two had worked together "on several White Nationalist projects, including the Aryan Alternative newspaper." Referring to the recent news that a DNA test indicated that Cobb had African ancestry, Miller told Pakman, "I can't believe a man as intelligent as you, actually believes Craig Cobb is an octoroon. Surely, you know it's just another jewsmedia fraud." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dog Whistle Alert! Sen. Rand Paul this morning on 'This Week': "We have 3% of the vote in Detroit." Ron Paul in 1992: "Opinion polls consistently show that only about 5% of blacks have sensible political opinions." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 23:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Video and transcript at link.

http://abcnews.go.com/ThisWeek/video/week-sen-rand-paul-23309342 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron Paul is in a masturbating frenzy over this news. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 21:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Neo-Mods at /r/politics will do *anything* to prevent this story from getting out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 05:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rogue /r/politics mods are trying like hell to kill this story. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 05:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Censorship Mods have, only moments ago, deleted the first r/politics Meta thread in many weeks. To learn why, follow the link and sort comments by "New." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 02:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did the Censorship Mods get a brush-back? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 00:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm noticed that some of  the news sources the Censorship Mods arbitrarily banned (oops, *sorry,* "filtered") have been getting through.

Did the Admins have to have a little talk with that petulant crew of self-appointed authoritarian censors over at r/politics?

What say you, our dear Censorship Mods? Did those "Community Outreach" purges of yours finally catch up with you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On the Censorship Campaign of the Neo-Mods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 23:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comment was deleted on at least one other subreddit. Hopefully this redacted version will pass muster. Please give it you consideration, and add your thoughts in the comments.
______________________


In response to another redditor's query: **"What are some trends on reddit that should die?"**

Censorship.

In some reedits, censorship of legitimate news sources, users, and user comments based on the whim of rogue, self-appointed Moderators is now the norm, not the rare exception.

Yes, /u/[REDACTED] , /u/[REDACTED] , /u/[REDACTED]r , /u/[REDACTED] , and /u/[REDACTED](among others,) you Censorship Mods over at /r/[REDACTED] ban users and sources at individual whim. This has been well documented and will only become a larger issue until the Admins of reddit deal with the censorship dictates you Neo-Mods have forced upon the largest political message board on the Internet.

You deem sources "unacceptable" and they are pulled before they even hit the /r/[REDACTED]/new newsfeed.

As a redditor, I don't need some vigilante Mods deciding what is and what is not acceptable to their whim and censoring content "for our own Good." There are tens of millions of redditors, and we don't need authoritarian control over the means of our communication. We can decide for ourselves, thank you very much.

Salon is banned on /r/[REDACTED]. Wonkette is also banned. For a brief time, until reddit outrage grew too large to ignore and the Censorship Mods were forced to backtrack, Mother Jones was banned. (Mother Jones is the media outfit that broke the "Mitt Romney 47%" story, the biggest political story of 2012.) But the Censorship Mods were forced to back down when it blew up in their faces; they were made to undo their unjustified and partisan ban of Mother Jones. Other of their arbitrary bans remain in place to this day.

What sources are you not able to see, fellow reddit users, because the /r/[REDACTED] Neo-Mods have decided that they know better than you do what is and what is not news and/or politics? (Hint: more than you think.)

Reddit exists because of the free flow of information. When self-appointed guardians of what is valid and what is not seize control to impose their spiteful will by force upon an unwilling community, they are violating the very premise of reddit. This is why Admin intervention is needed: this Censorship train needs to be stopped in its tracks before it becomes a trend among other would-be authoritarian Mods.

The "Digg Patriots" destroyed digg; we cannot stand by as "Reddit Patriots" force the same fate on Reddit.

Don't let the Censorship Mods win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A relevant self x-post from "Ask Reddit." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 03:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Statists want to do Tyranny on my Milk. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 10:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone's favorite IAMA dweller comes out of his shell. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 07:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google to fix map image showing slain boy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 10:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/politics mods label Slate story on their antics "Not US Politics," pull it from /r/politics front page. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 22:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me and a few cohorts managed to win control of reddit's /r/politics, but the sub's 3.1 million members hate Liberty. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 11:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron Paul aide wrote Iowa senator $25K check days before defection from Bachmann, records show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 10:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This doesn't seem very 'MURICAN to me at all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 08:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do so many PaulBearers refuse to recognize the Ron Paul Newsletters for what they are: the crown jewel among Ron Paul's disqualifying events for any serious consideration in American politics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 01:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit user "FourthReichsFuhrer" wishes the Good Doctor "Happy Birthday!," tell us Ron's place in American history. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-21 01:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spontaneous Anti-Paul sentiment clear in "creepyPMs" thread "Japanophile, martial-artist, redpiller, men's rights activist, and fedora enthusiast would love to get to know you!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 02:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Rodeo Clown Is Becoming a Right-Wing Hero </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 18:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama rodeo clown not one of Missouri's "finer moments," W.H. says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 11:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Political pundit Jack Germond dead at age 85 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 23:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOPs pathetic faux-populism on Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 05:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What qualifies as "satire" in American politics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 05:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Claire McCaskill, (D-MO): State Fair Stunt "shameful, unacceptable" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 04:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Political Correctness Runs Amok As Decent People Not Amused By Rodeo Clowns Hysterical Blackface Routine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 18:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP Rep.: House could probably get the votes to impeach Obama  CNN Political Ticker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 06:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Condemnation of Obama-Masked Rodeo Clown Incident Grows; MO Reps, Dems Alike Denounce State Fair Incident </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 05:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "We're Gonna Smoke Obama, Man!"  the Scene at the Missouri State Fair Rodeo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 01:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "We're Gonna Smoke Obama, Man!"  The scene at the Missouri State Fair Rodeo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 01:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Right-Wing Mods in /r/politics repeatedly kill the "Obama Rodeo Clown" story from the MO State Fair, repeatedly and deliberately mislabeling it as "Not US Politics." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 01:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American Politics: Obama Rodeo Act Shameful and Out of Line </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 00:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missouri State Fair Gives Lifetime Ban To Rodeo Clown Who Mocked Obama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 00:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missouri State Fair Rodeo Clown Dons Obama Mask; Announcer Asks Crowd if they'd like to see "Obama run down by a bull." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 08:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leaked Audio: Cuccinelli Affirms Support For E.W. Jackson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 01:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul's terrible, horrible, no good, very bad week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 22:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron Pauls 2012 campaign allegedly bought Iowa endorsement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 09:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The guy who owns the land my Liberty trailer sits on just showed up and raped my bride. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 08:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said something about "primate nocturnal" or something and declared it was his natural right to devirginize my new wife.

I know he's right, because he is richer and better and smarter than me. But does anyone know what he's talking about?

This is a disappointing start to our marriage. I can't make ice in the Liberty trailer, so the Liberty champagne I had specially chilled for our honeymoon night went warm while we used the ice to keep her swelling and bruising down.

She just arrived here from abroad last week. I hope this incident doesn't skew her perspective on LibertyWorld, where the natural rights of Propertarians reign supreme, and they harvest our Flowers of Freedom at will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul, John Harwood spar over ex-aide, "Southern Avenger" Jack Hunter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 01:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When did you first realize that Ron Paul was a scam artist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 03:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please share your stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The Charitable-Industrial Complex," by Peter Buffet (son of investor Warren Buffet) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 03:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Probable Koch AstroTurfer selling plan to "privatize" Detroit, and thus "make it a Top 10 Global City." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-26 00:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zimmerman Speaks! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 06:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do so many poor American whites vote in complete opposition to their own interests? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 05:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And why do they seem so happy to do so, even as they continue to lose ground every year? Is the American Right's "flag-and-eagle-porn" really that effective?

Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question: in what ways have the Paul family helped/hurt the Libertarian cause? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 00:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron's raison d'tre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 22:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polio Eradication Suffers A Setback As Somali Outbreak Worsens : LIBERTY!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 02:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Important Question for Ron Paul Supporters, Past and Recent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 03:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When did you first realize that Ron Paul was not in fact "a Champion of the Constitution" but nothing more than a Neo-Confederate grifter who exploits the paranoid fears of White Supremacists?

Did you fall for the "Hey, he's 'Grandpa Peace 'n Pot!'" rebranding that started online in the mid-2000s to cover up Ron Paul's past and his decades-long associations with the *Turner Diaries* crowd?

How long did it take you to get out of the Cult of Paul? Are people you know still in?

Please share your personal stories.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gov. Rick Perry Signs Texas Anti-Abortion Bill Into Law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 20:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aide to Rep. Michele Bachmann arrested, charged with theft </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 03:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michele Bachmann explains 'the way we spank the president' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 22:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you like to meet the only politician in America able to convince people that paying $1,675 for $375 worth of coins is a good deal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 02:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's right  it's [Ron Paul!](http://farm8.staticflickr.com/7018/6560359999_b98a55fc71.jpg)

(The "official World War II U.S. Army Ammo-Holder" containing the coins is free with purchase, lest anyone accuse Ron Paul of trying to rip them off.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little Known Fact: Ron Paul worked for the Koch Brothers (PDF) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 21:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 7/9 Luckovich cartoon: Regulation, Texas style </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 18:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Libertarian Hero Adam Kokesh Arrested for Gun, Drug Violations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 16:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wisconsin governor signs abortion law, faces court challenge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-06 16:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker Quietly Signs Bill Requiring Ultrasounds For Wisconsin Abortions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 22:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Wendy Davis: We Will Not Concede On Texas Abortion Bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 02:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Family Research Council Responds To Marriage Rulings With Choice Language </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-28 17:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Family Research Council Launches On Our Knees For America Campaign, Sparks Hilarity with Graphic Design </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-28 16:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dick Armeys Split From FreedomWorks Detailed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 23:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perry Calls Wendy Davis' Filibuster The 'Hijacking Of The Democratic Process' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 17:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Following Voting Rights Act Ruling, Perry Signs New Texas Congressional Map Into Law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 16:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top 10 Rage Quotes From Scalias DOMA Dissent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 05:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Santorum named CEO of Christian film studio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 09:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge bars audio experts from George Zimmerman trial who say screams were not Zimmerman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-22 16:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gold tumbles to 2-year low in Fed bloodbath </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 19:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Right-Wing Extremist "Minutemen" co-founder arrested on suspicion of child molestation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 16:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minuteman Founder Arrested On Suspicion Of Child Molestation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 06:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gov. Scott Ultrasound Walker will never be president </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 11:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wisconsin GOTP Senate passes "rape via ultrasound" bill, shuts down all dissent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 23:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did George Zimmerman say? You be the judge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 05:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trial of George "Fuckin' Coons" Zimmerman Begins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 03:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4-year-old boy accidentally kills father in Arizona </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 10:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone going to Adam Kokesh's July 4th state capital gun parties? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 12:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why or why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christians of Reddit: how do you feel about the (mis)appropriation of your faith by extremists of the American Right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 00:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Background checks remain popular in Deep Southern states </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 00:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minnesota Rep. Michele Bachmann says she will not run for re-election in 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 10:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Court rejects ban on funding Planned Parenthood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 06:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seven men charged in "Liberty Reserve" global money-laundering operation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 03:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Liberty Reserve": your one-stop shop for laundering money from drug running, arms sales, and child pornography. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 03:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I thought after the glorious Libertarian revolution I would get a banker like George Bailey. Instead, it turns out my account with "Liberty Reserve" funds drug/gun running, along with CP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 23:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Liberty Reserve": a money-laundering operation for international tax thieves specializing in running drugs, guns, and CP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 22:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A relevant crosspost from our friends at /r/wheredidthesodago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 02:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ralph Nader loses appeal over 2004 presidential election ballots in Maine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 02:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does the future hold for the Republican Party? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 02:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know what the future holds for the Republican Party.

The Republicans, desperate to win at all costs, deliberately targeted both the malignantly ignorant, the dangerously paranoid, and all combinations thereof. This segment remains prized for both their malleability and their susceptibility to flag-and-eagle porn. Single issue voters, who will often vote in direct opposition to their own interests for the sake of litmus test issues, are really all the Republicans have left.

Beginning with President Nixon continuing right up until today, the Republican apparatus has catered ever more to these loons to secure victory. As a result, the paranoid and proudly ignorant now make up the largest segment of the Republican coalition, and traditional Eisenhower/Rockefeller Republicans are not only excoriated as "RINOs," they're viewed as prize game.

The Party now finds itself in trouble: it can no longer win national elections due to this self-cultivated demographic albatross, yet they now have no chance of winning without those voters. It's not merely a matter of their individual votes: these are the activists who man Republican phone banks, donate money, walk the precincts, and hand out lawn signs.

There really is no place for a sensible American conservative to seek shelter these days. The Libertarians are even more tied to the extremist American Right and its bizarre "black helicopter" conspiracy fantasies than the Republicans are, so there is really no refuge for a sane Republican moderate.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul: Obama is working with anti-American globalists plot[ting] against our Constitution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-12 06:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heritage: We Have Nothing To Do With Racial Immigration Study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 20:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Domestic Terror Attack Thwarted in Minnesota; suspect's first name is "Buford." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 00:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man shoots self while cleaning gun in Colorado </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-05 22:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police release video of fatal shootout with Ohio terrorist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-05 05:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harvard historian Niall Ferguson apologizes for tying Keynes economic views to his homosexuality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-05 04:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How, exactly, did the Party of Lincoln become the Party of Yosemite Sam? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-03 03:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FDA makes access easier to morning-after pill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-01 03:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron Pauls Extreme Ties Re-emerge At New Institute </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 13:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Nugent (neither dead nor in jail): Michigan ads should show dead animals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 08:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Thinks Up Totally Sick Burn: Jon Stewart Is A Jew </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 23:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iowa GOP Still Butthurt About How Much Their Supreme Court Loves The Gays </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 23:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
