<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8459</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 09:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whilst it is a good thought, I find that it's just such a waste of water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 18:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can also find it easier to play with a friend and have them if they video, choose somebody who you'll talk with and will help you lighten up and not feel too nervous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 16:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that happened in rank.. no no, but the reason Apollo can support is the protections he gains from his mez (in case you were wondering). Also, you need to try two junglers, just get somebody who can play safely on ADC and maybe have them play Neith. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 12:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whilst it is a good idea in thought, in theory it would fail as somebody could always just leave an obvious loss just so that the team doesn't suffer as big a TP loss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 12:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to be rude or anything, but I could not understand what that meant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 10:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well good guy Greg, have you seen... support Apollo?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 09:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heyo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 17:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best/main way to join a professional team is to play league and get to somewhere such as masters and get people to notice you. Good luck on your quest to make it big. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 18:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Each god has a Gold ~ God Rank 1, Legendary ~ God Rank 5 and recently added in the Cabrakan update Diamond ~ God Rank 10 skins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 18:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another piece of advice is actives, while beads can be really good, on a support it would be wiser to get something that helps your team, e.g. heavenly agility, shell or creeping curse. And would be nice to get a reply for feedback but can't since it is only for ranked, but looking at your stats you didn't seem to have done bad. If you have any questions feel free to PM me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 14:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before the Cabrakan update in which it fixed itself, I couldn't hear any gods taunts, jokes or laughs. Can you hear any of them for other gods? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 10:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, I'm getting sick of players who just want a snowball game, who cares if you're down eg 10 kills, if you work together and try you could actually bring it back instead of surrendering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 15:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That seems about right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 05:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play a fair amount of conquest and these all seem normal picks to me but I can still run Neith solo, Ra mid/solo, (Can't jungle). What servers do you play on, NA or EU? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 05:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep in mind, this way also helps encourage the support when to ward, generally you should make sure the area is clear before putting down a sentry to clear another in case this happens^^ but as somebody who mains support, it does get annoying being unable to rotate to a fight because that ability was used for a ward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 19:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I get a Geb shield on at the last second saving them with the smallest amount of health and they escape (although it generally inspires people to run back in *sigh*) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 17:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> P S with Garterbelt is an awesome series... if only they made season 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 11:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hoping for a Neith skin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
