<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8022</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 22:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 21:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are, then so am I... I can't even remember the last time I cried, and even then it might have been out of frustration. In my adult life I don't think I've ever really cried hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a German study found women cry on average between 30 and 64 times a year, and men cry on average between 6 and 17 times per year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 20:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 03:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People that buy the "high end" expensive RAM for game usage are really better off throwing their money elsewhere. For most applications such as gaming, memory is never the bottleneck.

The only place it really counts, and even there not too noticeably, is with enterprise/businesses/researchers/enthusiasts that are running in-memory DBs.  

Personally I would recommend always going with 1600Mhz or less for DDR3. Anything more is a waste of money for most consumers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 03:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet they are still nearly 2.5x what they were almost 2 years ago. Prices never recovered after the factory fire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 22:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a bind. The situation in Eastern Europe/Ukraine is escalating and we don't want it to escalate, and the way to deescalate the situation is to escalate our actions against Russia.

... I'll be in my bunker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 21:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have chronic pain due to an autoimmune disorder. I wish I knew what mistake I made =( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 17:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most Muslim countries are already death camps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 01:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Volunteer somewhere. For me, the only time I really make friends is when I'm working with someone towards a common goal (usually manual labor). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 01:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jupiter be like 'deez my hos'  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 17:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the award for the most boring job in the world goes tooooooo.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breakthrough in stem cell treatment for Parkinson's: Researchers generate dopamine cells from embryonic stem cells and successfully implant them into rats, resulting in long-term cell production and survival. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 12:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 12:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This could really turn your world upside down! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 11:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's cool, but I don't have motivation to buy one. I already have Cortana with my phone, and I can take it anywhere, and it doesn't take up any extra space.

The Amazon Echo doesn't look like a BAD device, but I would be very amazed if they sold enough of these to justify the research   development costs. Not too pleased as a stockholder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 12:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had my investments split between two brokers and it allowed me to see which one performed better with my assets. After seeing a clear winner I transferred all my funds into that brokerage account tax-free.

That would be the only benefit I could see, it would allow you to 'shop around' a bit, even if it's only two options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 12:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an excellent documentary show. Lots of information, lots of visuals, and no over dramatizations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 05:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would an Nvidia Tesla card have been a better performance/price buy in comparison to 4 GPUs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 05:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only check mine in the following scenarios:

* I get an email from my bank about suspicious activity
* When I get a bonus
* When there is a significant event that greatly shifts the stock market or my stocks for better or worse
* When I'm checking in against goals (such as another home) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 03:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also worth noting that the WHO statistics for Ebola are for cases confirmed through testing. It is estimated that the number of cases are vastly under-reported, the actual numbers are believed to be at least 3x as high. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 02:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are likely thinking of Smallpox. Polio is actually seeing a resurgence in the Middle East due to conflicts and the difficulty of vaccination campaigns in such stressed and distrusting areas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 10:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a note, if you are actively running your VM VHDs off the NAS and plan to do any data intensive operations, you are going to have a bad time. I'd suggest perhaps storing the virtual hard disks to the NAS for backup purposes or swapping, but when you spin up the VMs themselves use local storage. That will GREATLY simplify your NAS needs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 08:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Look at me! I'm FABULOUUUUUUUUS" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 08:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I see is a guy getting cancer.

Source: I used WebMD once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 12:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not 'good' with math and I think I'm a fine programmer. Been with a very well known software company for 8 years now and still climbing, so I'm not sure it can even be said that math helps... the vast majority of programmers will never need to do any complex mathematical operations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 09:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ramen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 01:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The type of tree they grow at the Boardman tree farm is called Pacific Albus, a trademarked name that loosely means Pacific whitewood. Its a hybrid of four to five different poplars, cross strained for better yield, faster growth, less use of irrigation water, straighter growth, and things like that." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that preventable medical errors are estimated to kill 210,000+ hospital patients every year in the US. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 14:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 03:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because it hasn't been observed/detected in active use, does not mean it does not serve a potential purpose correct? That's like monitoring some computers on the same day and saying 70% of the binaries of Microsoft Windows are non-functional and unnecessary (just because they weren't observed to be used during that time period). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 02:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm. I have a friend who works at a large company that will be announcing/releasing an automated hair styling/cutting machine for men and women. It's going to be marketed to franchises. The results are impressive and according to female feedback, look better than styling/cuts done by humans.

When and if they take off, thousands, and possibly hundreds of thousands of hairstylists will no longer be able to compete. I'm sad they will no longer have jobs, but I am extremely happy that automation/technology has no longer made such labor necessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 08:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're supposed to dress up in a costume. It's not a costume if you wear it everyday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 08:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well now I know what my getaway vehicle may be for my next bank robbery... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 05:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No particular order:

* A stop to ISIS gaining ground in Iraq/Syria
* A reduction or end to Ebola cases in Africa
* A better agreement/truce for the Ukrainian/Russian fiasco so tensions can calm on all sides.
* A US economy expanding more than predicted
* More space tourism from private companies
* A reduction in RAM prices (computer memory costs have been increasing since 2013)
* More states voting for legalizing marijuana
* The collapse of the North Korean government
* Continued protests in Hong Kong until they are allowed to choose their own candidates (unlikely, but I hope it happens)
* The discovery of the missing airliner MH370
* The Elios car go into production gain good reviews
* More stem cell/regenerative medicine trials with absolutely amazing results
* Announcement of new metropolitan fiber networks with ~1Gbps speeds


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 11:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My god, that brings back the memories. The most disturbing thing I ever saw was [this goatse](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dQw4w9WgXcQ). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 11:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching LiveLeak videos at 7? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 11:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How I imagine this went down:

**Daughter**: "Dad I want to be a princess for Halloween!"

**Dad**: "No you're going to be a Xenomorph!"

**Daughter**: "But Daaaaaaad"

**Dad**: "NO!" _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 05:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't attempting to "buy a girlfriend". She was already romantically interested in me prior to that, though I was not interested in a serious relationship and she understood that and said she was fine with it. She said she just wanted to have a fun and carefree relationship after getting burned in previous relationships. But because of the way she abruptly broke off contact I think she was just out to use me. I would not consider her a bad person in the slightest, I'm just using her as an example of why it would be hard to get anyone to just 'gift' money, even if there is already some attachment.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 04:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck with that unless you're an attractive young lady. Even then you'll have a hard time. I once paid off the college loans for a girl I had recently met because she was working towards good things (health field) and her loans were really holding her back. Then about a week later she stopped talking to me. Then she got a fitness trainer boyfriend, and that was it.

So... Yeah, good luck. Older billionaire dudes are probably a lot wiser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 03:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOW did they do it?!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 23:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's cool until it falls off on the freeway and you're in a mesmerized state after following the vehicle for miles and miles. Imagine how terrifying that would be... It'd feel like time suddenly stopped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 23:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the important part of the fear is the chance of injury and death in relation to the amount of exposure to the item. Nearly everyone rides in a car or bus everyday, and almost everyone has a good outcome percentage wise. However if everyone were to step on a snake, or have a bee/wasp land on them, the percentage of bad outcomes would no doubt be very high (even if just a dry bite or a sting).

Just because something doesn't kill many people, doesn't mean it's not a worthy candidate for fear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 23:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the little bits I just read it seems as though the severity is typically reduced over time. That's got to be a good feeling in a less than ideal situation. As time goes on, does your seem to be improving? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is it determined when solid pills (painkillers, antibiotics, etc) should 'expire'? And is the pill expected to undergo chemical changes soon after expiration? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 02:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When someone is killed by poisoning, how are investigators able to determine what poison was used? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 03:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 02:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't really need a pump if it's just goldfish and frogs. Just think of how many goldfish bowls are out there without pumps! I think adding a pump will just give you more headaches.

I've had a backyard pond for 10+ years with no pump, and it had large goldfish for most of those years until the racoons came and decided to go fishing. It also had frogs and salamanders, and algae was never much of a problem (it also never really got full sunlight). In the winter it would freeze over with almost a foot of ice, and the fish would still be there the next spring when it thawed. You'll be fine without a pump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 04:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not touching your eyes is equally important if not more important than your nose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 04:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a regular surgeons mask seems a bit unreasonable for Ebola, but gloves aren't anything bad but overly cautious perhaps. The biggest thing to remember is to not touch your face, and to take off the gloves without making contact with any part of the glove that could have made contact with surfaces. Throw them away each time of course.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 02:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole finite resource part doesn't make much sense to me, but temperature increases associated with wind farms is well known. Thankfully based on what is currently known, we also know that the effects are minor, and are of course reversible.

An example of a paper regarding research into this subject: http://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/v2/n7/full/nclimate1505.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 02:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cue the armchair Redditor architects and building engineers who will tell you about how it's going to rot and fall to the ground within the next couple of days. But that'll be the least of your worries, because they will also diagnose you with some fatal disease related to some imperfection found on your skin in one of the pics after glancing across it with their doctor eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 02:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     if (profile.Gender == Gender.Female    GetAttractiveness(profile) = Attractiveness.High) {
       MatchHelper.AddMatch(me, profile);
    } else {
       MatchHelper.AssignRandomMatch(profile);
    } </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 05:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? You haven't really lived until you've been on fire! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 02:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another thing to note is that due to competition and also the nature of pleasing investors, it is highly unlikely for a company to cut hours unless it is because they lack the budget to pay for the number of hours they'd like employees to work. 

It comes down to how no business wants to be the first to reduce hours without cutting pay. Unless you are an absolute market leader, making such an action will only allow competition to get ahead, while the business costs remain the same for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 06:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you think people get battle hardened? They have to start somewhere... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Netherlands says no laws are being broken as some biker gangs head to Syria to help fight ISIS... Are there any laws in the US that would block a private citizen such as myself from providing funding and weapons to those fighting ISIS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 03:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 08:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I firmly believe the reason it has not been enacted in the US or other 1st world nations yet is because it has a high potential to cause an economic collapse. Not because goods in those countries would be disrupted, but rather because it sends a huge negative signal to markets that things will be getting worse. By keeping travel open it falsely conveys the sense that everything is under control.

If the US government were to announce such a travel ban, I would begin selling and taking profits on more of my investments in stocks. The economy looks to already be teetering on a precarious edge that few officials are willing to admit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 02:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I could ever live in a building so tall. I'd be paranoid of fires all the time. I'd probably learn how to base jump just to give myself the unrealistic feeling of safety.

I can't imagine how terrifying it would be to be so far up, sitting in that bathtub, hearing the fire alarm go off, and then seeing smoke calmly drifting up past the window. I'd sure hope the toilet was nearby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 14:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'll tell you hwat. That boy aint right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 11:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's it like being the son of the Michelin Man? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 14:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most 3D printers work with plastic, and those that work with metal are really unable to extrude the materials needed for handling the thermal aspects of a laptop. It really comes down to designing something that is capable of dissipating heat in such a small form factor. I don't think consumer 3D printers are near that point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 12:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really no. There is a lot of custom hardware in name-brand laptops, and you would be unable to shrink/slim down a laptop chassis to comparable common consumer models without going through extensive design and research.

A giant bulky one that probably doesn't have much visual appeal or comfortable 'laptop' functionality is doable though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 12:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More than 1 in 50 people died in WWII. That's pretty eye opening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 06:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The navy version has the ability to take off and land vertically, it's part of, if not the biggest reason that the project is so ridiculously over budget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 02:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like further spiraling in Ukraine's downward spiral. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 14:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They typically do with disinfectants. Decontamination stations are critical.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 12:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is pretty damn scary considering that the patient the health worker treated was the first person to come down with Ebola symptoms while in the US. They were extremely well prepared for that patient, they were extremely careful, and they put vast resources into keeping it from spreading. Yet it still spreads.

I'm fearful of what will happen when enough cases start popping up that such resources cannot be dedicated to single cases. I hope to god they find a significant/fixable flaw with their previous treatment and containment procedure... Because if they don't, it's very bad news for what the future might hold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 11:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reach over to your glove compartment and start screaming "Allahu Akbar!!!!!!" at the top of your lungs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 11:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would advise against this unless you have liquid bandages and someone to help you. The risk of something going wrong far outweighs the benefits in my opinion. For example if you use super glue and accidentally make contact with something before the glue dries entirely, you risk ripping open the cut to the point where it could become a serious issue.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 03:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok cool. Can you tell us when you'll next be in a public place and where it will be so people can come take pictures of you for Reddit?  

Just because something is not illegal does not make it right or less douchey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 03:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even though it's not really an image for ridicule... taking a picture of a stranger because of his appearance and then posting it online for millions of people to see  is a total doucher move unless he gave it his blessing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 00:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't understand the issue here. Some of the companies he invested on failed, and obscure companies can be found in a lot (if not most) of investment portfolios. What's the unethical part?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 00:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems a lot better if the girl planned it. Versus: "I like that girl but she doesn't seem to notice me. I'm gonna go knock that bitch down." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 11:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks like me when I can't remember whether I turned off the stove. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 10:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd much rather the response be overboard than not enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 08:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deactivating my Facebook account was one of the wisest life decisions I've made recently. Since then I feel much less depressed (seeing people posting their fun life highlights while I slayed away at my career does that) and it also resulted in me hanging out with my friends a lot more in real life, and just generally being more sociable.

I highly recommend it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 07:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is certainly scary. Though I think it's partially because it brings thoughts of huge pandemics such as those caused by the Spanish Flu, the plague, etc etc.

Even the regular flu which is often brought up as a huge worldwide killer, isn't *that bad* in terms of some of the other pandemics the world has been facing. For example, AIDs is estimated to **kill 4000+ people per day** and the HIV pandemic is still spreading, yet I think the overall 'panic' is absent from the media. 

The world is a scary place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 04:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Play it. _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 04:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lighter full of chlorine. When he goes to light a cigarette he will press the valve release and the striker, but it won't light. Instead he'll get a wiff of **extremely toxic** chlorine gas. 

Fuck you pickpocketer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 00:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no greater punishment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 12:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $4.99 for shipping and handling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 11:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubtful. Both tins and documents from the early 1900s are not uncommon. I would be surprised if you could get $3 for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 01:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can only hope. But at this point it is the only *known infection* to take place outside Africa. It's not impossible that there are other infections which have occurred in countries outside Africa without the infrastructure/support to detect/isolate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Ebola begins to rapidly spread in your country and people within your region start falling sick, how will you change your day to day behavior? Will you continue to go to work? Move away from the city, etc.? Or will you continue to live your life as you do today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 00:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 00:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty cool, but someone should put a seizure warning on this post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 13:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I rebelled in school and didn't do the work, mostly because I didn't like being told what to do when I didn't see a huge benefit in it. When I went home after school I'd tinker around with software and programming if there was nothing super fun going on.

I dropped out of school when I was 16. Got hired at 21 for a 6 figure job doing software development. I've been there 8 years now and it's been very good to me. The only thing I regret about not taking school seriously and dropping out, is that I missed out on a lot of social experiences like college shenanigans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 13:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your cat may be the spawn of a vampire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 13:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Multiple casualty counts in the wikipedia articles:

* http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/War_in_Afghanistan_(2001%E2%80%93present)
* http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mexican_Drug_War
   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 10:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think a lot of people realize just how bad the situation in Mexico is... To put it in perspective, the number of deaths from the Mexican Drug War since 2006 is estimated to be 4-5x higher than the deaths (including civilians) occurring in the **ENTIRE** Afghanistan War since the US invasion in 2001.

It truly is a bloodbath down there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ISIS Militants Enter Key Border City Of Kobani </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 01:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
