<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4100</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 09:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He looks a lot like [Barsad from The Dark Knight Rises](http://i.imgur.com/Opapm.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fireworks - Drake feat. Alicia Keys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-02 07:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-27 23:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That wasn't him being offended. That was him thinking over the joke you just said. Hence the 'hmm.'

I don't think all religious people are as easily offended as you think they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 19:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another person replied to you talking about how Lasers basically sounds like the studio made the album for him. It's because they did. Lupe Fiasco was in a legal battle with Atlantic for about a year or so before they would even let him release Lasers because of their disagreements over what should be on it. Lupe himself has not only admitted, but spoken out on his dislike for Lasers. 

I went to a concert of his about a year before Lasers came out, and it was a concert actually promoting the then-expected album. The T-shirts for the tour had something called 'The Lasers Manifesto' written on the back. Look it up if you have the time, because it really is a nice message to see on the back of the shirt other than just the tour dates.

Basically, Lupe hated his own album, and promised his fans that the next one will be what both he and the fans wanted. 

And with that, I ask you to listen to his newest album: Food and Liquor II. It'll definitely change your mind on whether he's still an amazing lyricist or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It took me months of hunting at half-price bookstores, but I finally found all three of them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-24 00:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 12:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Folsom Prison Blues.

*I hear the train a-comin...* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samsung's advertising. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 05:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please don't upvote this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-14 08:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dave Grohl was wearing a cross necklace while performing at the DNC. Reddit, when did you lose all respect you had for someone you once admired? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 07:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 14:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the fuck do you remember your username. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-26 08:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HEY PAUL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-12 21:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Your punishment must be more severe.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-08 20:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fox News Tonight:

**OBAMA ENDORSING TAX-EVADING THIEVES AT LAST NIGHT'S FUNDRAISER?** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's have a toast to our fellow terrorists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-06 04:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's time we have a toast.

Let's have a toast for the real terrorists out there: a toast to the conservative talk radio hosts that fill the minds of idiots up with ideologies that every brown skinned turban-wearing citizen in our country is out to destroy our beautiful country. Thank you, again, for setting more people out there to act like dogs on their unjustified hatred for people who don't look, dress, or live the same way they do. They couldn't have done it without your help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-04 11:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll post mine. [J. Robert Oppenheimer's commentary, after having witnessed the destruction his atomic bomb can cause, is short and powerful.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n8H7Jibx-c0) I can't imagine what he felt at that moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most haunting video you have ever seen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-04 11:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not asking for a video based simply on gore or shock value. I'm also not necessarily asking for something that can find itself onto an episode of Ghost Hunters. I want you guys to post a video that truly hit you to the core; something that made you realize how destructive and scarred people can make the world, or themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-28 06:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP here. This was posted on Facebook by one of my friends in Jordan. Even he thought this was ridiculous for what he usually sees. I'm a Pakistani-American myself so I tend to see some crazy drivers over there as well. 

But this.. uh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-28 02:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must be a really cheerful guy in person.

Oh, and the person that shot this picture took it in Jordan. Your shallow comments shouldn't even offend anyone because you obviously have no clue what you're talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw this on Facebook: A kid sitting in the trunk of a car being driven on the freeway. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 23:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 23:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure you're not just listening to the preview? The song's over 8 minutes in length.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 23:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure you're not just listening to the preview? You do realize the song is over 8 minutes in length, right..? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 12:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh hey! Something else I had no earthly clue existed until a Redditor brought attention to it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-17 22:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I get impatient about something and someone says something along the lines of "Don't worry, just wait.", I instinctively cut them off with "I DID MY WAITING. TWELVE YEARS OF IT.


IN **AZKABAN**." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-11 13:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's 5:44 AM, and I'm laughing more than I should have been when I got to Schumacher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 07:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Well, fuck you too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think r/music may be pleasantly surprised by this leak from Linkin Park's next album. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-17 03:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-22 22:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to be rest assured with how much difference there can be between the quality of a movie and it's poster, take a look at these two:

http://i.imgur.com/ScjXg.jpg

http://i.imgur.com/Nga0a.jpg

Now let's all chill out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-13 01:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanna feel Joseph Gordon Levitt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-01 07:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Gottem.](http://collider.com/wp-content/uploads/The-DARK-KNIGHT-RISES-Set-Photos-Lazerus-Pit-1.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-01 05:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we'll hunt him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-01 05:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT DID EVERYONE SAY? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-14 10:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, um.. TL;DR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-14 03:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't Twitteritis. Please don't post your daily activitoses here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-20 20:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> www.kanyezone.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-19 20:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys, let's focus on the game here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-08 19:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a bit late, but I'm the guy that originally wrote this picture. The original post is in my username history. Yeah, it's Plano, Texas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-04 21:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like DanielOnFilm said in this thread. Pixar's characters have identity. It's not sound editing, or anything being extra done by the voice cast. The characters are simply written brilliantly. 

I'm the other way around because of it. I can't watch any other Tom Hanks movie without thinking about Woody in the middle of Omaha Beach or trying to capture Leonardo DiCaprio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-03 06:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Dat mean he luv her moar den 4eva) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-25 00:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JUST STAY OFF THE SET YOU FUCKING PRICK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-17 07:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, that was my intention. Somewhat of a remake of that storyline. I've given it more of a Middle-Eastern/South Asian influence to replace the Irish influence given in the Scorcese movie.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-17 07:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Working on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys, I'm working on a film heavily inspired by The Departed for a school project. I need a bit of your help in letting me know what you think of the posters I've worked on for it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-17 05:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-08 10:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Into the West - Howard Shore and Annie Lennox. I'm pretty sure it's the only song to ever have made me cry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-06 22:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of all the changes that have happened in the time between the release of *Blink-182* and *Neighborhoods*, what was/still is one of the hardest things to deal with personally and professionally for you as a band member and as a friend?


And thank you for giving me the soundtrack to my youth and more than I can say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-29 03:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-15 17:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inna lillahi wa inna ilayhi raji'oon. I hope her family pulls through this with as much ease as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-12 19:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT? MR FREEZE WASN'T EVER IN A BATMAN MOVIE.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-11 12:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're the exact kind of person I intend to make sure my kids never grow up to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 17:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotham. Come nightfall, Bale's city is mine. And anyone who's in it plays by my rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 12:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, and obligatory Salam handshake from another Muslim college kid. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 11:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just choked on a Samoa from seeing Christian bale in a hijab. Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 09:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 06:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao Jeremy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-07 16:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still seems more enjoyable than the Crystal Skull.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-07 16:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See post taking off for Karmastan.

Think of something clever to board flight.

Think nothing
Bear pun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-13 12:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 19 now. I've been playing the piano for 11 years. The first couple years or so, I always told people how much I love playing the Plano. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-13 12:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know who you're talking about too. I FEEL SO EMPOWERED. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
