<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3431</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 06:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't even know you get an engineering ring! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What were the pros and cons of Greek Direct Democracy (In context of Ancient/Classical Greece)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 04:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far, i've been reading to no avail. What i've found is that some limitations included:
- Women, Slaves, Foreigners were excluded
- Men, regardless of education, were allowed to vote so some uneducated people could be making important political decisions
- Unpopular but necessary decisions would not be likely passed (can't find examples though)

Pros:
- Allowed a representation of what the people want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 18:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About writing music, i've composed a few musical pieces, mostly for the piano like double and triple fugues and etudes though i've sketched out an incomplete symphony (only the first movement)

I don't think i'll ever be a band leader, not really interested in leading, I just want to play music aha

And about the type of prog, i'm still relatively new to prog so i'm open to everything right now :)

Thank you for such a detailed reply! I'm going to watch those links now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey, need some advice! How do I transition into Prog Rock? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 16:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all! For the last 15 years i've been playing as a classical pianist and did dabble a bit into jazz and was wondering what advice you could give me if I wanted to move into prog rock? 

For a sense of ability, my repertoire included Chopin's op.25 (Full), Debussy Preludes Book II (Including no.12) and the Shotakovich Concertos.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 16:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two worlds one sun... If only the warring nations of this world realized that we all share a single sun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 03:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds cool! Thanks :)

One more question, how long after you submitted your materials did you get invited for an interview? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 02:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 02:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much money do you make monthly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If gravity makes things go down how come air and clouds and birds don't go down? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 16:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 15:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you soo much for introducing me to Palmgren! I have never heard of him or felt this way about music for a very very long time. :')

edit: Just sightread it after printing the score from IMSLP and played it on my piano with my windows open close to midnight and I am soo happy right now, thank you soo much Catt! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If we know all the elements that make humans, why can't we create another man simply by mixing all those elements? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 15:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 13:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never said any of my pieces were easy :p, yeah that prelude was a monster! I included it in my fellowship recital a few months back. Loved the quote of La Marseillaise towards the coda xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 13:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listening to it right now and I am in awe! Can't believe i've never heard of this gorgeous gem before (esp. the third one!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, i'm looking for some piano pieces that are relatively unknown but are beautiful and not too difficult (limited time)! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 12:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! Just to give a sense of my ability, here's some pieces from my repertoire:
Chopin Etudes op.25 (Full)
Schubert D.960 Sonata
Beethoven op.110,109 Sonatas
Debussy Preludes Book I and II
Shostakovich Concertos I and II
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My College's motto is "God as Guide, the Word as Light". Are there any biblical references? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 12:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what are some critiques of the Invisible Hand? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 02:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 02:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly 666 comments, how meta- ops I spoiled it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For people living in residential colleges, how was the interview process like? Any advice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 15:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 14:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I can just buy a plane ticket right now with no preparation whatsoever and fly straight into South Korea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I want to go to South Korea for a holiday for less than 20 days, how can I apply for a VISA and what documentations do I need? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 14:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 16:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's freezing down here in Melbourne! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 16:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A high school friend of mine did a research essay on Nobili's Rings and Liesegang Rings which I thought was subtly beautiful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Without high school chemistry, can I still major in chemical engineering? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 11:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the Chemistry equivalent of Feynman and Sagan? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 11:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, how in the world do I write a stunning, one page, personal statement? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 06:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
