<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1598</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 17:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't speak for TFA, but it's UK-version Teach First, found that its teachers on average remained in teaching slightly longer than those who had taken a traditional route to teaching (there is a very high rate of teachers quitting on conventional training as well). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The state of the nation: Animal Research in the UK in 2012 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 15:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Animal Research in 2012 - The facts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 14:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTF?! Peta advocate beating up animal researchers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 11:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 16:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More from the government: https://www.gov.uk/government/uploads/system/uploads/attachment_data/file/212610/spanimals12.pdf  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Number of animal experiments in UK rose to over 4 million in 2012. Let's look a little closer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 15:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 15:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do think that you can't hide a brutality behind a religious veil. If it's unnecessarily brutal, it should be banned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poland bans Kosher slaughter of animals. Ethical or Intolerant? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 15:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 14:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> London, I have to go to Hull in a couple of months for work ... yayz.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You've heard of blind dogs, now there are dementia dogs! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 14:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A southerner's guide to Hull (with pictures) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 13:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gene Therapy gives children back their future </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 21:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 11:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazeballs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 11:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original article: http://www.buzzfeed.com/donnad/russian-scientists-build-monument-to-honor-lab-rats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yoda - the product of a scientist and a lab mouse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 11:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Combining a lab mouse and a human creates the spitting image of Yoda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 11:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 22:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem to be overlooking the simple fact that DINOSAURS ARE WEARING HATS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DINOSAURS!!! Click link and type: up up down down left right left right b a (then keep pressing a) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 21:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are lower barriers to publishing increasing the number of retractions (PLOS ONE) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 11:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 18:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it would have to be consistent with equivalent film ratings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Modern violent video games don't promote poor social behaviour (PLOS ONE) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 17:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australian researchers close in on malaria vaccine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 12:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You can boil them, freeze them, leave them in space, starve them for decades and even poison them but they survive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-28 12:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The research that halved deaths from coronary heart disease </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-26 17:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Taiwanese Filibuster (violence and all) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 18:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-19 11:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> true - I just wish PETA didn't influence so many young minds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 15:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't surprise me given all their lettuce ladies stunts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PETAs makes a poor defence for promoting violence against researchers in new video game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 14:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 11:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The depressing game is here: http://features.peta.org/cage-fight-mma-game/

The article is about why PETA have a very poor understanding of the average research lab </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 11:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the whole article: http://speakingofresearch.com/2013/06/13/petas-mixed-martial-assault-on-scientists/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What PETA thinks an animal research lab looks like (Scientists may have an image problem) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 11:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Liquid tungsten is so hot, if you dropped it into a lava flow, the lava would freeze the tungsten. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 11:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-15 14:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Age of Empires </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PETA's Mixed Martial Assault on medical science should be condemned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-13 15:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 16:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, not sure - possibly promotes grafitti </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 12:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to ask students to take notes on 4 pages of a textbook in 10 minutes.
After 10 minutes they must close the text book and use their notes to answer some questions.
Then I would give some notes I took which are "model notes" so they can see how to write briefly but clearly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 12:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NQT is still regarded as a training year where certain things are expected of you, so the term is used enough to need the acronym </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 12:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Total number of lego bricks divided by total population </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: The average person on earth owns 75 lego bricks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 11:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-06 14:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 17:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Activists have been breaking into anial labs and stealing animals. Politicians seem reluctant to step in, instead moving science policy away from animal research. Researchers had a rally to try and explain to the public the importance of such research. 

Pro-Test Italia ran the rally on a shoestring rally, and from what I've spoken to them, received no money from any pharmaceutical or university </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hundreds of scientists hold rally to defend biomedical research in Italy despite harassment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 15:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 15:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one?
http://www.swaebr.org/images/23YearsPoster_lg.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 15:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good story! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 15:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nature also did a brief summary of the rally (and I got name dropped, yay!)
http://www.nature.com/news/italian-scientists-fight-back-on-animal-testing-1.13116 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 15:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't Lord Prof Winston suggest labelling all medicine (in the UK) with "has been tested on animals". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 15:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some context here: http://speakingofresearch.com/2013/06/03/pro-test-italia-stands-up-to-animal-rights-activists/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who do you want controlling Italian science policy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 14:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 14:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orginal Study : doi:10.1038/nm.3181 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hundreds of scientists hold rally to defend biomedical research in Italy despite harassment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 13:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists in Italy in rally against extremism and for biomedical research on Saturday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 14:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the collective noun for tigers is an "ambush" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 16:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 23:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's derived from Crowley's paper stating only 0.004% of research has clinical use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 12:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So parents who are more skeptical of modern medicine are also more skeptical of all proper medicine? No surprise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 11:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. Here's an online version of Crick and Watson: http://www.nature.com/nature/dna50/watsoncrick.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 15:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a similar paper that's more recent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 14:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prof Lovell Badge has done other great debunkings of these sort of statistical myths:
http://speakingofresearch.com/2013/01/23/nine-out-of-ten-statistics-are-taken-out-of-context/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prof Lovell-Badge destroys the myth that only 0.004% of animal testing is relevant to humans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 14:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-16 12:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original Paper: http://www.cell.com/abstract/S0092-8674%2813%2900571-0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRC are running a poll on the biggest development in medicine in the last decade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 17:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 17:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So people like Andrew Wakefield should be able to make up stats to put in the discussion about the benefits of vaccination? Those falsehoods killed people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cross-species liver transplant succeeds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 11:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese researchers unveil sheep with new type of artificial heart [with video] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 11:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-14 16:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's another myth that's done its rounds - so definitely right to be skeptical </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: Armadillos are used to understand and treat leprosy in humans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-14 12:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: Alligators go through 2-3000 teeth in their lifetime </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-14 11:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-11 12:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a ridiculous video. It takes footage from what looks to be 30-40 years ago. The video says clinical investigation is "the ONLY valid kind" - how exactly are you going to discover the patterns of disease, or which treatment works without clear large number of very similar patients and control groups (so as to have scientific rigour).

"Any disease which is provoked is unlike any disease which arrives spontaneously". WHAT?! We have treated many diseases successfully by creating models - that is the principle of biological science.

There are so many factual errors throughout that video </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-11 12:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their claim personalised medicine will replace animal experiments
Their claim that animal research is non-predictive
Their claim that human and veterinary medicine are unconnected

All pseudoscientific nonsense, and the post deals with most of those points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-11 12:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mouse study is interesting. It does show significant failings of mouse models for three conditions. It's a good peer reviewed paper. 
Note the paper doesn't suggest to stop using animals, it says we need to improve the models. Read this specific reply to the paper in question:
http://speakingofresearch.com/2013/02/15/why-mice-may-succeed-in-research-when-a-single-mouse-falls-short/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-11 12:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> teklord - you should visit a lab. They are not like the 70s videos you watch online. They are not tortured, research is always done under anaesthetic unless there is a VERY clear reason why this shouldn't be the case (usually because the procedure itself is milder than the anaesthetic injection, such as a blood draw or a breeding experiment).

And what is a failed experiment? If something doesn't work, you learn something, modify your actions, and try again.

In terms of enslaving humans you should read this: http://speakingofresearch.com/2011/12/06/the-gorgons-visit-earth/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confidence is rising among scientists defending animal research [Nature] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 16:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 22:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article you sight shows limitations of some animal models - it also suggests these models are improved not binned. See this article: http://speakingofresearch.com/2013/02/15/why-mice-may-succeed-in-research-when-a-single-mouse-falls-short/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 22:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The computer models generally come from the animals. When computer models improve it is because of animal research - so they are unlikely to replace animal models but rather to complement it.

No model is perfect (I am not a perfect biological model for you), but we use a variety of techniques in tandem (including in vitro, computer models, DNA chips, human skin cells, (etc) AND animal models) to get the best results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 22:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also note that Vioxx passed human clinical trials to show it was safe. Yes it passed animal trials (which were much smaller than the subsequent human trials which is why they were less likely to show the side effect which affected around 1 in 400 patients), but it also passed human trials. It is the exception to the rule where a dangerous drug makes it through all tests (incidentally these would have included in vitro and computer models). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 22:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What on earth makes you think most are killed instantly. A mouse might be hit by a stone knocked by a thresher, or might get just its leg hit by the blade. It crawls underground and waits to die - no anaesthetic (mandatory unless special reasons not to in most western labs), no food, no water, no safety </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 16:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The original papers dealing with aspirin and birth defects rabbits involved huge overdoses of aspirin to rabbits (1). The same is likely to be the same with humans (humans can certainly overdose on aspirin), with some anecdotal evidence (2), but large scale studies would not be ethical.

1) Suwa T, Urano H, Kohno Y, Suzuki A, Amano T. Comparative studies on the gastrointestinal lesions caused by several nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory agents in ratsAgents Actions. 1987 Jun;21(1-2):167-72. PubMed 349831
2) Corby DG. Aspirin in pregnancy: maternal and fetal effects. Pediatrics. 1978 Nov;62(5 Pt 2 Suppl):930-7. PubMed 364401 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new drug to treat type II diabetes: Thank theGila monster? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-02 20:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teaching a dog to stay still in an MRI machine for The Dog Project [Video] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-01 12:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five masked men ambush prison van in Salford (UK) [BBC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 11:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five masked men ambush prison van in Salford [BBC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 11:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bangladeshi garment workers crushed to death </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 18:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 15:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't the only incident in Italy - they've broken into breeding facilities and harassed pharmaceuticals as well
http://speakingofresearch.com/2013/04/24/european-storm-clouds-gather-over-italy/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 14:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> develop a leaping penguin logo then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 14:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blame the bodyshop - they keep saying "we don't test on animals" so people assume everyone else does </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-23 16:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two related articles:
http://www.nature.com/news/animal-rights-activists-wreak-havoc-in-milan-laboratory-1.12847
http://www.understandinganimalresearch.org.uk/news/2013/04/animal-rights-extremists-wreck-milan-laboratory/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pro-Test Italia movement in Milan stands up against animal rights extremists who broke into a lab </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-23 15:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 17:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article isn't an argument for animal research - it was never intentioned as such - this is why it doesn't have any arguments for research in it. It's about the relationship between animal-use movements.

In regards to your argument:
- No billions of animals are not bought yearly. It is likely to number about 100 million (that's the estimate from animal rights groups). 
- I can't talk for research in lesser developed countries, but in the US and EU research can only take place when the researcher can show there was no other method that would work and that the benefit outweighs the cost - so not "pointless experimentation". 
- Our genetic differences are far overwhelmed by our genetic similarities. This can be even closer when you look at genetically modified mice which have humanised genes. You should also note that humans are not genetically identical (far from it) yet you would not argue that human tests work. 
- Human skin cultures are a brilliant development and are widely used - but cannot tell you about how organs react, or how drugs move through the body, or their mechanisms of action - they are limited and are used alongside animal experiments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 14:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full link: http://speakingofresearch.com/2012/12/17/brain-machine-interface-success-allows-paralysed-woman-to-feed-herself-for-first-time-in-a-decade/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those who agree with animal research should not be concerned with condemning other forms of animal use </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 14:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2010 Nobel Prize winner, Sir Robert Edwards, dies - He was behind pioneering research into IVF </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 19:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perhaps the cutest picture ever of a baby covered in puppies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 17:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 11:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a skewed title here. All they say is that 9% use animals from the same litter. They point out this would be better. So 91% could have potential flaws, that doesn't mean 91% of studies are flawed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 21:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know more about the research on horses? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 18:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liviyas story - How research on horses saved a girl's life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 15:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 16:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference being that continuing to use the product of knowledge from the holocaust doesn't perpetuate such research. Continuing to use the benefits of animal research does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Difference Does Animal Research Make - Morrissey vs Medicine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-28 16:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-28 11:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More from the BBC http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-21958361 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-28 11:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently the method they used to improve the vaccine might be relevant to the polio vaccine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New foot-and-mouth vaccine - Could this wipe it out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-28 10:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
