<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5015</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 23:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you ordered the pizza from a website like JustEat you can probably have the restaurant banned from whatever website that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 07:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't you need really good skills to play in a wormhole? Usually I see people saying you need T3's for them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 05:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the good ol' drake bait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 05:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sent! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 05:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops, wrong thread, ignore the pm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 04:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got linked here from /r/IAmA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 02:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll be asking yourself that question a lot with the majority of content on this site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 02:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can just imagine it now -

"The sounds from the flogging is leaking into the recording booths, any ideas?"

"Why not just flog them *to* the movement of every single limb? At least then we don't have to buy some more goddamn absorption panels." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 02:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool,cheers for the answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 02:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/inbread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 02:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What specific dish do you think is best to try if i've never been? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 01:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never been to taco bell, what do you recommend I try if i ever visit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 11:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? I love how every genuine question in the subreddit is taken as an attack on their intellect, and people wonder why people stay away from the game's community. I really don't know how suspect mechanics work, not trying to argue with anyone... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 11:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can the reps be neutral if you're repping someone that's suspect? Dosen't that make you suspect? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 10:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  posting something automatically implies you created it

Sounds like the antithesis of reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 05:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His character is 10 days old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 05:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should just take his plex and tell him you lost it on a risky investment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 05:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell him to use that ISK to buy a 100mil sp character, at least then he can't complain about not having t2 mods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 14:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes sense, thanks for the reply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 14:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, I don't mind it being said in non serious matches of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LoL casters, please don't use the word 'tryhard'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 14:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heard this said on an official stream, what does this word even mean at that level of play? You're not going to see some of these professional players not actually trying to play, or just taking the games as if they were playing normal solo q, playing with their eyes half closed not giving a shit.

Not only that but it's insulting to the player to say that just because someone under performed it means they weren't trying hard enough.

Sorry if this is a bit harsh, but that word is mostly used by people who call people better than them tryhards and people worse than them noobs. It's a really stupid word, and has no place at that level of play.

Thoughts?

Edit: People downvoting, please try to post in the comments instead of just mindlessly disagreeing without an actual argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 18:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does 'tps' stand for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 18:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My god, this and all the juicy celeb photos, things that TMZ will pay thousands for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 09:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AFAIK They just nuked the whole facebook page, including the 'apology'. So buttery! Anyone got screenshots? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 08:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The UK has, in fact, been called out for being a 'nanny' state. We lock people up for offensive words/libel.

http://www.legislation.gov.uk/ukpga/1986/64?view=plain

See part III, section 18. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 16:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity, what languages did you use to write the game in for Steam/Chrome webstore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 10:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What. The. Fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 07:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that now, the way he turns his head when laughing seems so unnatural. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 06:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey OP, please don't forgot to give us updates! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 00:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to clarify, does answering questions about a link you posted count? E.g., you post a guide on x champion, does posting 9 replies to comments/questions in that same post count? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 02:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that quote, 2edgy4me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 01:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is coming from? Ask any pro that's played on both and you'll see the difference. Or even jump on the korea ladder and you'll probably be one league behind your NA  standing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 00:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget the difference between Plat V KR and Plat V NA is huge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 09:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better check your tiger privilege, son. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 05:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Albeit off topic, that community is so fucking scary - they take that shit way too seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 07:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huge respect, but I can't help but laugh how awkward the reporter must be having to switch from person to person because they all start crying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 07:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if it is fake, sometimes ignorance is better - why not just let people enjoy the video and think its real and take happiness away from that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 00:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pictures are pretty shit, can't actually see what they look like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 00:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best: One of the richest places in the world, in terms of culture, architecture, etc.

Worst: High cost of living. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 00:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprised no ones said reddit yet. It's perfect! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 00:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Launder it, split 25/75 with my co-conspirators then live an above average life in a country with above average living standards but a below average cost of living. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 00:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My reddit username. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 21:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/scorpion-takes-a-ride-on-the-tube-9317336.html I'm more looking for the species </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [London, UK] Found inside a tube car! Article inside. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 21:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 07:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only one character faster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 00:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. This subreddit takes itself way too fucking seriously, turning into something like /r/shitredditsays where the circlejerk quickly becomes the reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 01:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boots has a wonderful Boots brand allergy medication: http://boots.scene7.com/is/image/Boots/10052606?wid=280 hei=343 op_sharpen=1 I think they also have a drowsy one so make sure you read the label.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 23:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excuse me if I don't take the person who obviously has it out for LS and seems to have some weird obsession with how he looks. Seriously, quoting that guy is akin to just linking to Wikipedia as a source. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 21:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's of a diamond play level (he even got scouted by Korean LoL team for top, but they closed the position before he could tryout) , apparently if you ask MonteCristo he'll attest to that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 21:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he has a crush on LS OuO! (TBH who dosen't?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 21:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd probably be better off posting this on his facebook page, I remember him saying he checks that and answers questions off there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 21:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd probably be better off posting this on his facebook page, I remember him saying he checks that and answers questions off there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 21:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes because cheating in SC really affects if he's going to scam you out of $45 and lose potentially dozens of future customers. All of my wat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 21:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems a bit of a low blow just to try and discredit him over things he did then; and it really shouldn't have any impact on how you view his purely informative guides, it's not like he's trying to put across that he's the most perfect player and person in the universe. We've all made mistakes, as i'm sure you have. We try to learn from them and move on. How would you like it if in every post you made on reddit some guy was bringing up your past begrudgingly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 08:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did he say? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 06:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4AS6bc_IbjU 

Reminds me of Twitch chat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 06:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -0/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 06:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just your reminder that Bubba's "worst idea ever" got him into LCS: http://www.reddit.com/r/leagueoflegends/comments/1fr1nj/guy_quits_job_to_become_best_support_ever_support/cad3m5l </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 06:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel the need to tell you that you were wrong. Bubba is now in the LCS.

http://www.reddit.com/r/leagueoflegends/comments/1fr1nj/guy_quits_job_to_become_best_support_ever_support/cadb5i1  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 04:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You say that, but the multiplayer in Blacklist is honestly it's best feature, an well worth going through uplay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 01:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's probably because it's a lot easier to disagree with an idea than to hand over your cash. Also the experiment probably would have been better if they put up a sign "DONT HELP THE POOR" instead, rather than just trying to piss people off with inflammatory comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 21:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the [laugh](http://i.imgur.com/nJTgg7p.gif). God help your shiny ships if you're being serious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 09:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only way to restore the true natural order of the narwhaling bacons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 09:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cat will do stupid shit like this if I don't play with her. Moral of the story - play with your cats people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 08:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like an onion title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 08:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, no, with the heat in there at some times of day it's pretty impossible to stay awake if you're sitting down. Also I hope you reported it those times you saw it happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 08:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That SSID/MAC idea is genius, too bad there isn't WiFi in all stations. Although what you could do is set it up so the users taps when he's at one of his stops, the app scans for nearby networks and works of those instead. Not sure if you'd be able to find any in some of the deeper underground stations, however. Maybe you could record the time between each stops after the first time setup, then if no SSID's are available, give or take 5 seconds of when they should be it wakes you up, sort of as a backup for a dodgy phone or network. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 08:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're absolutely right. Who does UKIP think it is, making fun of WW2 like that? Bloody bastards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 08:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is against my Bushido code of honor. I didn't buy the $1200 samurai sword-trilby combo pack for nothing m8. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 07:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mayhaps good sir, did I ruffle some feathers with one of the preceding statements? Perhaps you are a feminist like me? Pray tell my fellow redpiller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 07:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an atheist who dabbles in the hard sciences, I believe it my duty to do so. Only by challenging the established so called 'facts' of the monolithic, science detesting, oligarchical patriarchy will we reach enlightenment... [*trilby tip*](http://i.imgur.com/Ir905bR.gif).

Edit: This comment really took a nose dive, did I offend you guys by implying that trilbys are better than fedoras? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 04:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you haven't heard - Comic Sans is so 2000 and late, crayon brush is all the new rage in bad graphic design. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 23:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't go to a comedy show, hear a story about a restaurant then decide on that story if you think it's worth going to that restaurant, do you? Of course not. The comedian is there to make you laugh, and that often entails misrepresenting whatever he's talking about in one way or another. People that don't see that, then complain about how he's misrepresenting whatever game just aren't looking at it right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 23:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, it's shit if you look at it like a review. Too bad his videos aren't meant to be reviews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 01:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lucky bugger who got that probably lost it moving it through null. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 02:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He checks his reddit inbox AFAIK so you can just message him there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 03:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, you say that but you don't actually say how/what program to use. Much helpful, many kind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 23:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/respectporn ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 23:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, fuck men with earrings. Who are they to say how they get to dress? Plebs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 23:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So brave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 00:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait so all the API's not from BRAVE are BRAVES spies ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 18:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all seriousness a Bar-at-law sounds like a bar in a courtroom you could get a Mojito from in between rulings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Firewall propaganda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 23:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/qV4lYfv,wLmKDdA,BegnmIF#0

Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My present, to you, /r/RPG. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 23:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey,

I asked a few hours ago about how I would go about modding one of my Eclipse Phase campaigns. I got a ton of really awesome answers. 

I made these wallpapers primarily for me and the people I play, but since you guys are really cool I thought it only fair to share them here.

Please feel more than free to use/share them : 

http://imgur.com/qV4lYfv,wLmKDdA,BegnmIF#0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I run a scenario with less than the 'required' palyers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 10:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey,

I'm looking to run an Eclipse Phase scenario with some of my mates (two) and the only problem is the majority of the scenarios come with a 'required' amount of four players. I however see people/books saying that it is possible to run a scenario with less players, but no where have I read how I would alter the scenario for less players.

Let's say there's four enemys they have to face, do I just halve that down to two enemys? Or would I halve some of their stats instead?  Of course it isn't always as simple as this, so i'd be interested and appreciate any help people could give.

The scenario i'm interested in is Glory, if that helps.

Cheers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It only took him 2000 years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 02:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dogecoin wallpapers for my fellow shibes! [1920x1080] (xpost /r/dogecoin) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 22:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dogecoin wallpapers for my fellow shibes! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 22:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explain these terms? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 20:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard people use subcap, cap, supercap, carrier, dreadnaught and titan. I'm just really confused as to what the usage of the 'cap' ones are. Afaik the 'cap' ones are used independent of of the other ones? What ships do they apply to?  Cheers

Edit: thanks to everybody that helped, upvotes to all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Required support skills for a new character? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 06:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,
Does anyone have a link to a list of support skills that you should prioritize on making a new character? I've seen plenty of lists but they usually just list all of them instead of which are most important. 

Also if anyone knows what support skills are good to train if you don't know what EWAR race you'll be flying but want to generally go ewar? 

Cheers for any help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The only way to make sense out of change..." - Alan Watts [1280x960][OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-08 11:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you guys know what bad games TotalBiscuit has reviewed ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 04:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts on this ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 17:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The goal of zen is to trick the ego, i.e. to trick it into making the illusion go deeper and deeper, until eventually you are able to look back at the game you've played and realise the futility. Only then you can live half as the ego, and half as the God head, as a true genuine fake. Playing the game of life, just as you always did, in the same way as you always will.

Maybe Enso represent the full circle that the ego takes on its journey to be extinguished ?

I think people take the rituals too seriously, but maybe that's the point.

Just some thoughts, take them as you will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cookie Phone vs Police (SA Wardega) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 17:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please add an option to make the minimap smaller. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 18:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find myself walking into the enemies because I missclick the minimap way too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [beg] Will make fairly simply wallpapers for Dogecoin. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 10:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's some examples of what i've done in the past : 
http://i.imgur.com/iYTTEzt.png

http://imgur.com/NPK0GPd,1FmEyFX,GwDVcRh#2 

There all fairly simply in terms of actual design so i'd prefer it if you just gave me a quote and an image for me to superimpose them, or just something to do with text.

If I do end up making something for you I don't really mind how much doge you give me, just not a stupid amount.

Will check back later on today and get on any requests!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "You don't look out there for God..." - Alan Watts [1920x1080] [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 02:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's some desktop backgrounds for you Alan Watts lovers, made by me. Please feel more than free to share them! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 00:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Complete Waste Of A GoPro </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 11:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just dinged 90 for the first time, can someone answer a few questions for me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-12 05:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all, here's my character sheet : http://eu.battle.net/wow/en/character/twilights-hammer/Enigmi/advanced and i'm looking for some help on where to go next. I'd like to continue tanking, so can I do heroics now or do I have to get better gear before I start them? Where would I get this gear ? Also, I have about 314 Ghost Iron Ore and I was wondering If i should keep them and prospect them when my jewelcrafting gets high enough or turn them into bars and AH them or get a blacksmith to make me gear with then? Any ideas? Thank you for any help!. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to blend in. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 04:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does the 'world' need more of, tanks or healers ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 03:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently dungeoning as a retri pala, but i'd like to switch to something for faster queues, are there more healers or tanks in the world? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone got any idea what this plate ? I was told it was a Kings plate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 01:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/KDpSB9F,yLhLUuy,I30AyQC,Warz9vY,ccbkNL3,Y1ZbwcA,3qJjmns,2OtDie3,nDLzVFm#0

The first inscription (red) reads : 

CH PILL VUYT   CU

PARIS

EXP 1900 GRAND PRIX

The only thing I can read on the blue inscription is 
 
[?]EKUN

The gold pattern on the front of the plate is ingrained. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hot sexy ginger rubs cream on nipple </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 08:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This guy gives gamers a bad name. It's a real shame. [x-post /r/gaming] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 07:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DSPGaming hates people who are negative! [x-post /r/cringe] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 07:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to defuse a nuclear bomb with Microsoft Excel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 06:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is this guy not one of the biggest youtubers yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-19 02:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HD-558 vs HD-598 ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 07:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jacque Rancir sees art as a democratic modality and a principle means of generating what? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 03:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jacque Rancir sees art as a democratic modality and a principle means of generating what in the blandly consensual times in which we live?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do so many people put TNG as their favorite ST series ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 04:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm genuinely curious, it would be my #2 or 3. It certainly has it's moments, and Picard is played almost to perfection, but dosen't it seem a bit dull compared to something like DS9 or ENT S4 ? It seems to have all the good elements of what a Star Trek series should be, but the only element that stands out to me as being the hallmark of TNG is it's affinity for a philosophical undertone, which all of the Star Trek series have. Could it be that's the one that most people on the internet grew up with ? Thoughts ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /b/ro is in a bit of a bind </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 03:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I stop a stale game ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 15:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heya, iv'e been playing for two days now and iv'e been trying to get into the mage control class. Now I always try and wait for the opponent to make their move, so that I can get the card advantage and what not; but most of the time they also wait for my move and so it becomes almost a stale mate. This stays until I play a card and they end up assassinating it or whatever, and they always end up getting more cards on the board. Anyone have any tips that would help someone like me ? Just basic stuff; iv'e watched kripp/ls's videos so far.

Also, can anyone lead me to any resources for building a strong mage control deck ? I don't have any Legendaries yet but iv'e unlocked all the mage basic cards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: hitbox.tv is essentially own3d.tv. The current CEO of Hitbox.tv was the CFO of Own3d.tv (x-post /r/starcraft) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 04:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://whois.domaintools.com/hitbox.tv [1]

http://own3d.tv.ipaddress.com/ [2]

He also has Oleg in his G+ Circle : 
https://plus.google.com/105814245529036999531/posts [3]

In case you've never heard of own3d : 

http://www.reddit.com/r/starcraft/comments/16rxev/own3dtv_a_beginners_guide_to_being_an_asshole/

EDIT: Please proceed to  this thread : http://www.reddit.com/r/DotA2/comments/1qv28i/psa_hitboxtv_is_essentially_own3dtv_the_current/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's the full documentary of Muslim's in Luton. "..this is not a true representation.." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 00:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a reminder. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 04:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone help me find this website? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 23:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found a really good website that helped me organize my thoughts, it was basically a note taking website that acted like a folder system:

You could add a list of bullet points, then click on one of the bullets and it would take you to almost another folder, where you can put more bullet points.

Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not surprised this was on /r/funny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 17:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone help me find this tidbit ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 08:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I remember (i think it was on day9) where he asks one of his relatives why they smoke, and the relative then gives them a really polite and informed response. Anyone remember what episode this was from ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone help me find music like this ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-19 03:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I couldn't think where else to put this so apologies if it's in the wrong place -http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage v=uBxkphYQyEU#t=301 in this video theres a soundtrack going on in the background. Anyone have any idea what sub genre this fits into or where I can find artists like the one that made it ?

Cheers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the most emotional moments in DS9 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 21:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
