<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9154</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swedish Penis   Vagina Cartoon (For ages 3-10) w/ Subtitles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 20:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 406k Counting Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 09:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to /u/Qaz for the assist. Never seen a snipe for an assist before. Good counting with you /u/Bausse, I was rooting for you to get an assist or win the GET. Servers went busy around 996 it was chaos we had so many people trying to count all at once, like 5-6 people lol. 

Continued from [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/counting/comments/3a0jf0/405k_counting_thread/cs9bumc?context=3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Penguin Rage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 06:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 405k Counting Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 09:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologies to /u/KingCaspianX   /u/Mooraell for the snipe. I know Mooraell wanted that one and honestly you deserved it. 

I will never snipe again. You guys had some amazing counts in there. 

Continued from [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/counting/comments/39sgv7/404k_counting_thread/cs85f1b?context=3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I now get more likes on my facebook status updates by following how people on reddit get karma upvotes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 01:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boop at the end </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 00:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When people call me OP I automatically imagine I'm an OG and get my swag on. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 13:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by not finding the corpse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 10:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I FUCKED UP REDDIT. I FUCKING FUCKED UP. THIS IS WHAT I GET. 

FUCK FUCK FUCK FUCK. 

A spider came down on his web from my ceiling and ONTO MY FUCKING LAP PILLOW. He landed on the pillow and began crawling across it, I was frozen in place unable to fucking move by this unsettling and surprising move. 

Out of a rush of panic and delirium i used MY FUCKING HANDS to squish him into the pillow. But the pillow isn't a hard surface, there isn't enough surface friction there, I don't know if I killed him because I CANT FIND HIS GUTS OR CORPSE. 

And to make matters worse I think he is a spiderling babe, so THERES PROBABLY MILLIONS OF THEM PLOTTING REVENGE. 

I'm so fucked reddit. I gotta burn my apartment down. MY CAT IS NO FUCKING HELP. FAT CAT ASSHOLE. 

I'm gonna try and find him, but my carpet is brown and my shorts/ and recliner are both black. FUCK. I'll try and update as the situation progresses into the early morning. Not sleeping tonight. 

**UPDATE: Well reddit, I can't find anything. I can't find the spider's remains or his guts or his live body. Save yourself reddit. I'm a goner. I think maybe I will buy a hotel tonight. I'll bring my cat, as lazy and fat as he is, I don't want him to be killed. This is the end, I'm sure of it.**

Update: Still not found. Hard to sleep. Got a hotel with my cat the next two nights and set a bug bomb off in the apartment...

**TL;DR  can't find the spider i did or did not kill, may have to leave all my possessions and move...tonight**   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mother duck asks for help to save her children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 10:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a dinosaur's least favorite reindeer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 07:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Horizons Flyby of Pluto with (new) pictures in bottom right of video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 05:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Immaculate Conception of Little Dizzle (2009) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 01:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was a great forgotten film I feel like. It wasn't the best of movies, but it had some good acting, a solid story, and enough weirdness to say the time was well spent watching this creation. 

So here's the discussion: What other forgotten films do you think are good? (or films no well known by the general movie buff) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jack with Robin Williams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 00:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still the strangest movie I've ever seen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This library for cat lovers, lets you 'Check-Out' cats for a day or give them a forever home in Las Cruces, New Mexico </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 15:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sir Christopher Lee dies at 93 - latest reaction and tributes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 13:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crystal Pepsi is coming back!!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 06:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simulation of Milky Way Galaxy Colliding with Andromeda Galaxy with billion year time lapse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 08:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jimmy Fallon makes music out of French Open Tennis grunting on The Tonight Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 08:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 394k Counting Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to /u/KingCaspianX for counting down the last 200 with me! 


[Here](http://www.reddit.com/r/counting/comments/38zjo4/393k_counting_thread/cs16qdh) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Florida man apparently tries to sell live shark in front of grocery store. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Event Horizon Telescope could take the very first picture of a black hole </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 10:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My cat taking a nap after a long day of being petted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 09:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet the Arabian Sand Cat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 08:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio State Marching Band Tribute to Video Games: Pacman, Tetris, Super Mario, Halo, Zelda (With Epona walking),   Pokemon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 07:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walt Disney Animation Studios Short Films Collection - Trailer Blu-Ray August 11 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 13:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Wilcox County High School in Georgia held segregated proms, one for black students, one for white students up until 2013 where students organized an integrated prom. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 01:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All my video files stopped working </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 01:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were working not 20 minutes ago. When a video ended I went to start another one and VLC crashed immediately. I went to try the last video file that worked but it crashed too. I tried using my other video players but they all crash immediately.  HDC, VLC, Realplayer, itunes, they all crash when i start to play a video file- audio files they play fine. 

I do not know why it started doing that so suddenly. It happened yesterday too, but I ran a malwarebytes scan and got rid of some malware and then it started working again. However, I ran malware again and it found nothing today. So I am confused. 

I have windows 7, 64bit, 8GB Ram 

All my graphics card drivers are up to date. I tried uninstalling and reinstalling the video players. Any suggestions?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ultima Online, Theme Music...love this music </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 23:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I get to the secret garden? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 22:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bothans- Return of the Jedi Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 19:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone think that this lady probably had a bothan husband? The way she conveys the information is so sad and filled with such sorrow. 

I'm willing to bet one of the dead bothans was her lover. 

[Bothans](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CQeabed9N9M) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mysterious sea creature green slime seen in Taiwan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 13:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brittney Griner files papers seeking to annul marriage to Glory Johnson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 02:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dancing to Hall   Oates on a cop car...in the county I live in Lee County...you guessed it Florida. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 21:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VLC Player crashes automatically when opening video file </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 20:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have Windows 7, 64 bit

8GB RAM

I have had VLC for a long time, it's fully updated and the newest version. I began using it a few hours ago to watch a television show .avi file and another was a .mkv file. It worked fine as it has always worked fine.
Then I decided to listen to some music. So I listened to an audio file on the VLC player. When I was finished I went back to the video file and VLC crashed. It kept crashing upon trying to open a video file. It still plays music files .mp3 but not mp4, .avi. or .mkv files. It just crashes immediately.
I tried uninstalling and reinstalling which did not work, as well as resetting all the preferences. Troubleshooted some stuff on youtube/google but couldn't find anything that was like this issue.

In addition, I tried installing older versions to no avail. I also ran a virus scan, but nothing changed.

EDIT: Fixed it. I ran Malwarebytes and it removed some malware and now VLC runs again. Weird. Keeping this thread up in case someone encounters same issues. I had originally run Avast Virus Scanner and it found nothing so I figured it was okay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VLC player crashes upon opening </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 19:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have Windows 7, 64 bit 

8GB RAM

I have had VLC for a long time, it's fully updated and the newest version. I began using it a few hours ago to watch a television show .avi file and another was a .mkv file. It worked fine as it has always worked fine. 

Then I decided to listen to some music. So I listened to an audio file on the VLC player. When I was finished I went back to the video file and VLC crashed. It kept crashing upon trying to open a video file. It still plays music files .mp3 but not mp4, .avi. or .mkv files. It just crashes immediately. 

I tried uninstalling and reinstalling which did not work, as well as resetting all the preferences. Troubleshooted some stuff on youtube/google but couldn't find anything that was like this issue. 

In addition, I tried installing older versions to no avail. I also ran a virus scan, but nothing changed. 


EDIT: I ran Malwarebytes and it removed some malware and then I tried VLC again and it worked. Weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 390k Counting Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 18:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last thread was great! Wonderful counting by everyone, especially the last 300. 

Continued from [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/counting/comments/38ndut/389k_counting_thread/crwkl5s?context=3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FLIKE- Flying Tricycle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 13:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flying Tricycle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 11:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL there is a subreddit that counts. Literally, all they do is count 1,2,3,4... each replying to the next. They are currently around 389,000 /r/counting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 10:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Counting Subreddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 09:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> if some celestial bodies were closer to us, here's what it might look like </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 06:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hubble Deep Field Diagram (How far it can see) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 11:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yoda is a coward. He ran away at the end of the Emperor fight (when he slipped) and then stayed in a swamp for twenty years not helping the rebellion until Luke training. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 04:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SS   SK - The Foot Song [Hip-Hop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found my two year old music video today: The Foot Song 2013 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How did the guy on America's Got Talent swallow sugar and then water after that and regurgitate the sugar still dry with no water? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 17:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super grunting tennis match </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 16:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just started watching Tennis this week. I guess some tennis players scream really loud? This is from Wimbledon couple years ago Sharapova vs De Brito </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 16:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aragorn's Sword - Narsil (Lord of the Rings) - MAN AT ARMS: REFORGED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 06:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aragorn's Sword - Narsil (Lord of the Rings) - REFORGED for real </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 06:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dog Dies After Being Left in Petco Dryer, Owner Says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 17:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When a pregnant woman swims she is a human submarine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 13:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biting your nails is auto-cannibalism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 13:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man says his daughter's future career as a veterinarian has been hindered by learning about evolution in school. His lawsuit against the school board also claims evolution is a religion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 12:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Chris Farley was originally cast as Shrek and completed about 80-90% of the role before his death. The role was re-cast after his death to Mike Myers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 10:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seeking assistance to get a mural painted on work building, liven up the surrounding community a bit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 02:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am seeking assistance to obtain a mural painted on work building to help liven up the surrounding community a bit. It also goes to support a local artist in Columbus, Ohio. It also helps the artist attend art school. 

[Here is the page](http://www.gofundme.com/vz6t53u) Any amount is helpful and if you are unable to donate a share on facebook or twitter is equally as valuable. Thank you so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend's cousin made this cake. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 02:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend went to a bridal shower and this was the cake made by someone there. All edible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 02:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Songhoy Blues - Nick [Rock/Blues] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 09:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This girl I'm talking to sent me this photo of her dog. "Aw for once she doesn't look like a grump" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 06:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kung Fury: A Review (Spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 03:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   'I've got your permit right here!' And thus began the best movie ever filmed. Kung Fury, a short film, about a cop who becomes Kung Fury, master Kung-Fu martial artist, via lightning/cobra strike. 
He protects the city of Miami from crime with his super awesome one liners and impenetrable forces. This adventure he must hack time with the help of his friend Hackerman to rid the world of Hitler, who wants the pwoer of Kung Fury for himself. 
         
Written   directed by David Sandberg, it was originally a trailer turned into short film. Made with the help of an amazing kickstarting campaign what David Sandberg has accomplished here is nothing short of brilliance in animation   filmmaking. After my first viewing, I thought it would be better if it could be a feature length film. Then I realized, I could just watch the film three times in a row and it would fulfill that need. 

 This film has everything you could ever want from an over the top, cheesy one liner 80's flick. 

1. Laser-Raptors

2. Hitler, the villain

3. Triceracop- Half mancop/Half Triceratop

4. David Hasselhoff singing 80s style music 

5. Cheesy one-liners 

6. Arcade machines with lasers trying to kill people 

7. Thor 

8. Barbarianna   Katana, Viking Age warrior women with machine guns

9. The Nintendo Power Glove hacking time with 80s computers 'breaking' time. 

10. T-Rex Vs Golden Metal Eagle monster fight with small t-rex arms vs small eagle legs. 

11. Anime sequence with cobras as spirit animals.

12.  Amazing action sequence where Kung Fury takes on Hitler's minions. This scene is perhaps one of the greater achievements of the film. It reminded me of playing Mega Man   Sonic where the POV moves horizontally. Simply genius. 

13. Cheesy product placement. 

**14. And finally paying homage to Laser Unicorns with the beginning arcade game being laser unicorns and a laser unicorn seen in the anime sequence when Fury goes to 'heaven'.**



 Every so often a film comes along, once in a lifetime, where it makes you rethink your entire life. This is that film. The greatest film ever made.  I salute this film. And now will go watch it again. 

**Also, watch the film in 144P or the lowest setting on youtube if you can. It's better than HD. HD is good, but to get the full effect, go for the lowest setting in quality.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: South Korea Women's Soccer Player   U.S. Woman both go for ball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 01:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This guy took his Dying Dog, Poh, on Bucket List Adventure Across the Nation: 35 Cities, 12,000 Miles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 11:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: When I orgasm, I somehow become stronger and can lift more weight than when I am not orgasming Why is this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 07:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Shawshank Redemption - 8 Bit Cinema </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 03:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robots Can Now Perform Brain SurgeryOn Fruit Flies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 09:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL from this girl I know, that her hospital has a mannequin that simulates birth. She talks, groans, and pushes the baby out. They do drills practicing an emergency childbirth and hemorrhage after delivery. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 09:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A robotic butt exists, and his name is Patrick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 08:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A robotic butt exists, and his name is Patrick to help students who want to be doctors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 08:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Krayzie Bone, Snoop Dogg, Kurupt,   Layzie Bone - The War Iz On [Hip-Hop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 04:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eminem's Rap God done in ASL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 04:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Say hello to the dementor wasp. It turns cockroaches into zombies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 00:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> But ...but.... socks belong in mouth :( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 05:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: Sad dog wearing a baby sock so he doesn't chew on his paw. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 04:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Teddy Roosevelt helped make the forward pass legal in American Football. In a meeting of more than 60 schools in late 1905. This meeting was the first step toward the establishment of what would become the NCAA and was followed by several sessions to work out "the new rules." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 03:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> sloth squeak! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 02:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jonny Quest Movie: Robert Rodriguez to Direct Live-Action Film </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 01:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TNG Edit 38 - "Riker" Episode 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 01:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What in my stomach determines whether gas will come out of my mouth as a burp or out my butt as a flatulence? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 01:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sounds of a spider communicating to potential mates that it wants sex (the audio samples are in the middle of the page) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 13:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone please take this image and somehow fit a Lumberjack man or Lumberjack men into it? The football and LFFL have to stay. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 13:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Camel Style </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 10:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need some help with overheating GPU when trying to play Dark Age of Camelot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 07:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an HP All in one. It is old I got it in 2011. I have used it to play two games in the past: Ultima Online and Dark Age of Camelot. It's always worked fine playing UO, never any overheating problems. I've never had any problems with Dark Age of Camelot until today. I went to re-download the game and play after haven't played for about a year...

When I go to patch the game, which takes some time to patch 3 GBs... my GPU gets up to around 80 degrees and the computer shuts off so I have to wait for it to cool down. I have a fan pointed at my computer to help, but it doesn't help so much. I don't have my computer connected to a TV or anything. 

What could have changed in the past year that my computer would start overheating playing a game I've played for years on this machine? What can I do to ensure it won't overheat without having to buy anything at this juncture? 

My drivers are all up to date. I have ATI Radeon HD 5570 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Towel Day Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy Fans!!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 05:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uthgard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 01:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know if they have an ETA on when they are coming back up? It's a free server.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the origin of some gay people talking with lisp/accent? Why did it start? (serious) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 11:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Speed Dating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 07:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your greatest shame? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 03:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What is the Nash Equilibrium in game theory? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 02:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Darkman the film by Sam Raimi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 01:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favorite films growing up. It's not a particularly good film, but it is pretty awesome. It's such a different superhero type movie. 
[Anyone remember this movie?](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0099365/?ref_=nm_flmg_act_1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were going to have an adventure with a character from a book, who would it be and what adventure would you go on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 01:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Roots - Long Time [Hip-Hop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 00:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guestbird </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 22:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is a penguin's favorite relative? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 23:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His Aunt Arctica. 






*source: The Oatmeal*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Back   Forth. Forever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 20:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unbreakable- Bruce Willis   Samuel L Jackson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 19:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I watched this movie again today. I figured it would be different than the last I watched it which was when I was 15/16. I liked it a lot then and I loved it even more now. 

  I understand the director has made really terrible films since this starting with The Village; however, Unbreakable is quite amazing. I enjoyed the acting from Samuel L Jackson. I think, besides a few other roles it may have been his best acting job. I liked the cinematography and the music. It gave each character a theme much like superhero films. For Bruce Willis, his character had cool colors always around him, greens   blues. While the supposed supervillain was immersed in purple. I liked that contrast. 

I think what I enjoyed most in the movie was this idea of understanding our place in this world. 

I liked watching it in contrast with the influx of all the comic book movies that are popular right now. This is so different from them, even more different than Nolan's Batman films. His Batman's films attempted a sense of more realism I think, but this film captures it ...differently, much more dramatic less action. 

What are some movies similar to this? I can't think of any. It's unique.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Original Empire Strikes Back Trailer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The man who wrote the real Argo script in 1979, with assistance from sci-fi visionaries Ray Bradbury, Paolo Solari, and artist Jack Kirby, was using the script to help fund a science-fiction theme park named, appropriately enough, Science Fiction Land </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 02:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Batkid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 01:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Letterman Highlights featuring Foo Fighters performing "Everlong" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 18:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Letterman Highlights featuring Foo Fighters performing "Everlong" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 18:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1,2, buckle my shoe....What's next in this rhyme? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 02:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I waved a magic wand over your head and it made everything right in your life, what would your life look like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 02:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We all need a little encouragement from time to time.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 23:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were stuck on an island with a unlimited food and water, what hobbit from the middle earth saga would you pick to be stranded with? It can only be one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 22:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Nye and The Planetary Society Successfully Launch LightSail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 20:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the dumbest lie you've believed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 20:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slapping a bag of carrots with a cactus leaf 15 times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 20:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sounds heavier than I remember </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 20:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jamie Foxx's John Legend impersonation is uncomfortably good </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 19:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: When I get hit in the testicles why do I immediately have to go to the restroom? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25 Years Ago Hubble Released Its First Photo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 15:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio State Ghana Study Abroad 2008 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 22:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Wilhelm Scream Compilation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 21:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charges dropped against vet who saved dog from hot car </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 16:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite custom license plate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 13:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kitty Loves Ice Cream except when..... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 11:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio State Ghana Study Abroad 2008 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 10:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What you lookin at? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 06:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flexible EO Smart Connecting Car 2 can drive sideways and shrink </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 09:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about Star Trek: Into Darkness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 08:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why couldn't they beam Spock/Khan back to the Enterprise while they are fighting? Chekov says it is become he can't get a lock because they are moving. But..in Star Trek (2009), he beams Kirk and Sulu back on board when they are falling without a parachute. So they were moving a lot faster/worse then, why can't he simply do the same this time when all they are doing is fighting?

Also...wasn't Kirk dead too long for them to save him. I mean, he was dead for what 30 minutes? That's...I don't understand this. So..Khan's blood can effectively raise the dead? Why don't they just harvest his blood? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Besides Star Trek 2 The Wrath of Khan, what is the best Star Trek movie (original cast) to watch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 08:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen 1, 2 and 3. I enjoyed 1 actually because it was more in space n shit. I liked Wrath of Khan a lot and the search for spock was interesting to say the least but wasn't really as good as 2, but it was better than 1. 

I read the synopsis for 4..and ..humpback whales? It just seems kind of strange. So out of 4, 5, and 6 which one is seen as next best from 2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What misspelling bothers you the most? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 04:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened to Anthony Kim? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 16:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard some stuff about insurance money 10 million dollars not to play golf ever again. But that was over a year ago. He was a solid golfer, I loved watching him play.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Panda cat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 16:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Alpha Uterus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 09:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cobwebs in Australia after spiders 'rain' from the sky. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 08:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Derp. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 07:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: If so many people dislike Standardized Testing, why are they still used for to monitor student achievement? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 05:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Order of Middle Earth Books </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 09:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What order should I read middle earth books in? 

I have read The Hobbit   Lord of the Rings. 

Here's what other books I have. 

Children of Hurin, Lost Tales Part 1, Lost Tales Part 2, The Silmarillion,   The Lays of Belariand  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> B.B King - Live in Stockholm 1974 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 08:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black Angel (1980 short film that played before Empire Strikes Back...is found and restored!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 03:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oklahoma man who killed stepfather with 'atomic wedgie' pleads guilty to manslaughter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 07:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AMA Request] Adrianne Lewis, Girl with Longest Tongue in the World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **My 5 Questions:**

1. What was it like growing up with a super long tongue?
2. Did people ever pick on you for it?
3. How has the mini-fame/viral youtube stuff gone?
4. What can you do that others with smaller tongues cannot?
5. What are your career goals?

**Public Contact Information:** 

[Twitter](https://twitter.com/LongTongueLewis/with_replies)

[Time Article with her youtube page](http://time.com/3856806/adrianne-lewis-long-tongue-guinness-world-record-viral/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
