<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5937</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 06:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A recent study showed that it is natural for nostrils to have differing air intake volumes under normal conditions. The findings suggest this aids in identification of scents, as the reactions occur differently at a higher volume and an lower volume.

Edit: [Nature.com Article](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v402/n6757/full/402035a0.html)

"The flow of air is greater into one nostril than into the other because there is a slight turbinate swelling in one. The nostril that takes in more air switches from the left to the right one and back again every few hours, but the effect of this switching on the sense of smell has been unclear. Here we show that this difference in airflow between the nostrils causes each nostril to be optimally sensitized to different odorants, so that each nostril conveys a slightly different olfactory image to the brain." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 05:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many new universities being created - - online.

Massive Open Online Courses (MOOCs) will continue to change the nature of education over the next decade.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 05:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or toss them off the Empire State Building  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 05:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At work when your work quality is questioned.

Frequently it's better to propose a solution then to say "sorry". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 05:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMHO the only threat to Hillary is ... Hillary.

If she can overcome her "baggage" and manage to not implode, I think the nomination is hers to lose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 05:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Late to dinner of course! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 05:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tropic of Cancer by Henry Miller. I was amazed that this was his first novel. It that has been described as "notorious for its candid sexuality" and as responsible for the "free speech that we now take for granted in literature". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 05:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **AS I LAY DYING** by William Faulkner. He said he wrote it from midnight to 4:00 AM over the course of six weeks (while working full time) and that he did not change a word of it. In addition, the book is narrated by 15 different characters over 59 chapters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 05:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [What has Biden done in the last 6 years?](http://i.imgur.com/HqwZl1v.png)

He has very little to run on, and won't be taken seriously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 05:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20 miles on my mountain bike </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 04:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Polite aliens: "Any last requests?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 04:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> f... five hundred year old virgins? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 04:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put it in a trust for your descendants.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 04:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Car engines that you could work on yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 04:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 10 years = a healthy politician

In 500 years = land (not too close to sea level though)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 04:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The TPP secretive process and corporate leadership role makes me very nervous. 

Elizabeth Warren (Massachusetts Senator) generally reserves her more acid critiques for Republicans and Wall Street, but in recent weeks shes been **leading a vocal coalition of leftist groups and lawmakers who oppose the presidents free-trade pact** with 12 Asian countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 03:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  As you lift higher, you lift less

Which is why, when carrying it up stairs, the heavy end is the downstairs end.

Edit: Why the downvotes - this follows the principles listed above. As one end is lifted, the weight increasingly shifts to the lower end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 00:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 2007 Atheist/Agnostic was 4%. So I could see in the 1980/90s it could have been around 2%.

It also might be that, with increasing acceptance in US society, more people are comfortable stating that they are Atheist/Agnostic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 20:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the survey, the unaffiliated category which is 22.8% of Americans, consists of:

3.1% Atheist

4.0% Agnostic

8.9% Religion unimportant

**6.8% Unaffiliated but religion is important**

This last group, while they are included in the unaffiliated group affirm that **religion is either very important or somewhat important in their lives** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pew Research Study  Only 16% in US are non-religious: Atheist/Agnostic 7%, Religion unimportant 9% (Unaffiliated but Religious 6.8%, Affiliated 76.5%) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 19:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 23:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 US Dollar = 6.21 Chinese Yuan

So $5.53 for the meal, $3.51 for the sandwich </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 01:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just the opposite. "Texas seceded from the United States in 1861, and joined the Confederate States of America during the American Civil War. It replaced the pro-Union governor, Sam Houston, in the process. During the war, slavery in Texas was little affected, and prices for slaves remained high until the last few months of the war. The number of slaves in the state increased dramatically as the Union Army occupied parts of Arkansas and Louisiana. Slaveholders in those areas often moved their slaves to Texas to avoid having them emancipated. By 1865 there were an estimated 250,000 slaves in Texas." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 02:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hunter Prince Castle   Dracula Hotel in the very heart of Transylvania in Turda. They also serve "Dracula's favorite bloody steak Tartare" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 03:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Interesting admissions in light of the title

"Though Increased Focus May ~~Suggest~~ ***Prove*** Otherwise"

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 03:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of pure heliocentric velocity, the current champions are two probes called Helios I and II that were launched in 1974 and 1976. They entered orbits that took them closer to the Sun than the planet Mercury.

The nearer you orbit to a huge mass like the Sun the faster you have to move, and the Helios sisters moved very fast indeed. Both hit orbital velocities in excess of **70 km/s**  or about 150,000 miles per hour.

the speed of light = **299,792 km/s** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 02:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it carrion? Bet they can't wait to close this case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 02:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [FLOYD MAYWEATHER'S NET WORTH: $280 MILLION](http://www.celebritynetworth.com/richest-athletes/richest-boxers/floyd-mayweather-net-worth/)

ANNUAL SALARY $50 MILLION

Upcoming payday: $100 Million.

Hard to see him penniless anytime soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 02:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello - Sheriff's Office? Yes, I'd like to report some missing items I want to claim . . . 

"A number of bales of marijuana were found in the area but they've not been linked to the shooting scene." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 02:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haters gonna hate, and hitters gonna hit - - or in Floyd's case, both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Floyd Mayweather has a disturbing history of domestic violence  will be paid over $100 million to fight a man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 09:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 06:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The video is so much better.

The guys filming are laughing, just 10 seconds after a ~~$75,000~~ $500,000 piece of equipment is cut loose and almost crushes one of their coworkers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 06:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ate his child's eyes right out of his face, **raw**

um . . . do you have recipes?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 04:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL:

[2010 World Cup: Argentina Fans Barred From South Africa](http://bleacherreport.com/articles/402572-2010-world-cup-argentina-fans-barred-from-south-africa)

[Turkey bans men; 41,000 women attend soccer match - ESPN](http://espn.go.com/sports/soccer/news/_/id/6997301/turkey-bans-men-41000-women-attend-soccer-match)

Anti-hooligan measures often include: 

banning opposing fans from matches and/or ordering specific matches to be played behind closed doors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 06:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but they WILL hold your cash and not let you give that to a friend?

the cash is evidence in cases of pimping, selling drugs, etc. So yes, cash is held, but the $10k gold necklace is released.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 18:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps this is it:

The Prince of Adventurers (1927) - - "Casanova" (original title) - - [Link](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0017736/?ref_=fn_al_tt_8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 18:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could he now be in trouble if any break in tuition or financial aid was based on this admitted lie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 17:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prosecutor: Judge, the defendant shot down a drone with a gun

Defendant: I am innocent - it wasn't a "real weapon".

Prosecutor: He fired a gun. It took out the drone. And he was wearing a ski mask. Here's the video streamed from the drone.

Judge: Guilty on all counts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 17:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You better be wearing a ski mask while doing this since you are being recorded. And if you are in a mob wearing a ski mask, I bet you're the one being targeted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 17:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't have to fly very high to be out of rock throwing range.

And with cameras on board people firing weapons (including slingshots) will be subject to criminal charges - especially if the images are live transmissions. 

At $10k - $15k a piece they sound pretty effective.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State has posted online what it says are the names, U.S. addresses and photos of 100 American military service members, and called upon its "brothers residing in America" to kill them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 22:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 22:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> " Islamic State has posted online what it says are the names, U.S. addresses and photos of 100 American military service members, and called upon its "brothers residing in America" to kill them. " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State calls on backers to kill 100 U.S. military personnel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 22:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 21:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> St. Louis County Prosecutor Robert McCulloch said Jeffrey Williams told authorities he was firing at someone with whom he was in a dispute, not at the police officers. 

The north St. Louis County resident was on probation in St. Louis County for receiving stolen property, McCulloch said. "I think there was a warrant out for him on that because he had neglected to report for the last seven months to his probation officer," he said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suspect charged of shooting Ferguson cops, says wasn't aiming at officers - Alleged culprit had been taking part in protest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 20:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 04:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is Bill Burrs unique take on this story]( https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TBFydFEbhmg#t=55m40s) [jumps to 55min 31sec] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a man jumped 500 feet from a tour helicopter to commit suicide because he was unable to get surgery for a chronic health condition he suffered with for the past 15 years at age 61 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 04:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 19:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Doxing" is a neologism that has evolved over its brief history. It comes from a spelling alteration of the abbreviation "docs" (for "documents") and refers to "compiling and releasing a dossier of personal information on someone". Essentially, doxing is revealing and releasing records of an individual, which were previously private, to the public. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 09:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I taught junior high kids would rip shirts, pants, etc. regularly - and often it could be quite embarrassing for them. I let my students know I had a large supply of safety pins so if they ever needed an emergency repair they should feel free to stop buy.

To this day I keep safety pins in my briefcase and my work desk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 07:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Knock knock ..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 07:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched the speech and I had this same reaction:

"Not since the time of Leonid Brezhnev's presentations before the Communist Party of the Soviet Union has one witnessed such a Pavlovian response to pointless politicized speech as occurred on the floor of the United States Congress, with American politicians being ushered to their feet with every carefully crafted sound bite uttered by the Israeli Prime Minister -- American politicians whose loyalty to the State of Israel would, by their actions, seem to trump their loyalty to the system of checks and balances that are the bedrock of American democracy." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 06:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially when it gets eaten by the momma fox waiting below.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 04:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, at least the US is doing a much better job negotiation relations in Syria . . . (not) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 04:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I found one](http://cdn1.bigcommerce.com/server4200/026b2/products/503/images/1842/INNOCENT__22531.1405408136.1280.1280.jpg?c=2) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 05:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kenebrew is represented by civil rights attorney Hank Sherrod, who last year represented Robert Bryant of Kelso, Tennessee.

Sherrod argued that Madison County deputies in the summer of 2012 conspired to stalk, beat and falsely arrest Bryant. Bryant sued Sheriff Dorning and eight deputies, including Countess, in federal court last year.

The county settled with Bryant for $625,000 last year and the FBI then announced it was investigating the deputies.

This lawsuit invokes the Bryant case and related newspaper articles to argue that Dorning and the Madison County Sheriff's Department have a record of ignoring or even covering up police misconduct.

"Deputies under [Sheriff] Dorning's command have learned that their justifications for using force and other unlawful actions will never be questioned," reads the Kenebrew suit, "and that they can act with impunity." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 01:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best part of having an iphone on AT T is - it means never having to say goodbye . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 17:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if you jump inside a moving train "you will retain your movement around the earth" just slightly offset by your movement within that train.

PS - you will likewise retain your movement around the Sun, around the Milky Way, and through the universe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 16:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I see no chance for Russia now to move from Putin's brutal dictatorship into something that will be even (as) mild as we had 10 years ago," he said, predicting it could take a violent mass uprising if change was to come.

I believe, as Russia's economy continues to plummet, Putin will become even more desperate, belligerent and aggressive. 

The prior parallels are there - - Putin is heading down a dangerous path. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 16:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boehner made a dick move by giving Netanyahu such a bully pulpit without consulting the White House, and right before Israeli elections. 

Netanyahu made a dick move by negotiating the speech with Boehner without at least giving Obama a heads up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 16:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I expected a TL;DR post - - but I read it all.

Very touching - - enjoy every moment you can with your dad (and of course work through those that are not so enjoyable).

Your post reminded me so much of my dad's last years. I miss him, but I miss him with a warm heart and with a big smile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 16:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed - Competition is good. I'm out of a 2 year contract soon and I anticipate better options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 16:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mother Fucker - - **Mother Fucker** - - MOTHER FUCKER - - **MOTHER FUCKER** !!!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 02:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Followed by](http://fc05.deviantart.net/fs12/i/2006/300/f/d/ALLIGATOR_by_Astral_Haze.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 22:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And debate continues about the black hole shifting light towards white and gold vs blue and black. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 22:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ranking articles based on facts - - just like Reddit does! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 01:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was representing a client in a poorer town and was negotiating with a prosecutor who was also the municipal prosecutor in a wealthier town, Voss says. He actually told me that if we were in the wealthier town he could cut my client a deal. But he couldnt do it in the poorer town, because there was more pressure on him to generate revenue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 01:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Some residents say police pull them over for vague infractions like braking too often or following too closely in order to fish for more infractions like not wearing a seatbelt or failing to have the car inspected. Here too the poor get hit especially hard. Older, shabbier cars get stopped more often because police suspect theyre more likely to be driven by people who cant afford insurance or registration fees." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The 90 St. Louis towns profit from poverty. Each has their own police force, mayor, town council, and 81 have their own municipal court. Some towns get 40%+ of their revenue from petty fines for traffic offenses, fare-hopping, loud music, uncut grass, trespassing, wearing saggy pants, etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 01:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 11:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just sent Josh an email asking if he's interested. I included a link to this thread, so we'll see if he responds. Cheers, JLP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 11:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would use that app.  Let me know when it's available.

Link it to Facebook logins or something similar to "discourage" double voting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 04:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michael Kulich is the founder and chairman of the adult entertainment company Monarchy Distribution.  He was suspended in high school for selling Playboy magazines out of the trunk of his car.  This might be part of his ongoing publicity campaign.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 02:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Headline: ***35 Dead in Number Land Tornado !*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 03:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. A length of rope will do nicely, and has many more uses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 04:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It ain't bigot hate

If your rhymes translate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 09:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SPOILER ALERT !!!

The cuts actually alternate between hard cuts and dissolves as explained in [this article, and as seen in the video that shows all 10 cuts.](http://nofilmschool.com/2013/10/understanding-hidden-editing-in-hitchcocks-rope) [3 min]

There are spoilers in the video - do not watch if you have not seen Rope already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Banks want to open cellphones to robocalls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 06:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 05:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Birdman (2014, Alejandro Gonzlez Irritu) made me think of Hitchcocks Rope. While superb editing is used to make Birdman look like a continuous take, Hitchcock did Rope in only 10 takes, one of which was 10 min long. I havent seen Rope since I was a kid  - - but now I want to see it again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Rope (1948 Jimmy Stewart, IMDb 8.1 RT 97%) is an 80 min Hitchcock film shot in only 10 takes, with every other cut masked so it looks like only 5 takes (projectionists changed reels every 20 min) It takes place in real time, is Hitchcocks first Technicolor film, and was banned for homosexuality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 04:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 00:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tonsils - they had been considered totally useless and were removed if they got infected. Today we know tonsils fight bacteria as part of our immune system. However, it is thought that they have lost their primary role and are thus vestigial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 22:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  can't walk or move for quite some time

And thus, cannot even actively feed themselves. The mother must coax them to suckle  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 22:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The human ear has many vestigial traits. For example, there's a  group of muscles attached to our ears that, for most monkeys, are used to move the ears like satellite dishes trying to pick up a signal. For us they just sit there  not moving anything  suggesting that they've lost their biological function. Except for some of you that can "wiggle" your ears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Human Vestigiality (traits that lost function via evolution) includes: appendix, tailbone, wisdom teeth, a devolved third eyelid, extra nipples (and male nipples), noncoding DNA, palmar grasp reflex (how baby primates cling to their mother), hiccups, goose bumps, and several reproductive traits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 22:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 04:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus does have first hand knowledge on the topic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Necrophilia (sex with a corpse): Is still not illegal in some states, Was not illegal in California until 2004, Can result in a life sentence in Nevada, Has a maximum sentence of up to 1 year in prison and a $3,000 fine in Minnesota </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 03:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Florida Extended The Stand Your Ground Law To Cover Warning Shots (previously only actual deadly force was covered so shooting someone was OK, but a warning shot resulted in jail time) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 03:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill to bring back firing squad in Utah clears 1st hurdle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 01:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California Reviews Oil-Industry Injections Into Aquifers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 01:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 05:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His views may be the will of the electorate, but very soon they won't be the the will of the nation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 06:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are correct. [Here's the donation form](http://thumbs.dreamstime.com/z/american-internal-revenue-service-tax-form-1040-13180159.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 01:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Different source and not verbatim, but a similar post (which I had not seen). I stand corrected.

My inspiration was actually a post I saw today: [Excerpt From A Children's Bible](http://www.reddit.com/r/atheism/comments/2v3gx0/excerpt_from_a_childrens_bible/) - [with this picture](https://i.imgur.com/WA3sIxv.jpg) 

That post reminded me of these disturbing fairy tales.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 00:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK - - I looked up the moral. I kid you not ... this is what I found ... 

The last line of the fairy tale  its moral  is as follows: "**Lucky people, so tis said, Are blessed by Fortune whilst in bed.**" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 00:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link please, thanks. A Reddit search on "Sleeping Beauty" for past 7 days shows no such post (lots of pics of sleeping "beauties" in various states of dress though)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 23:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL the nurse that owns the cat is just very possessive and insanely jealous of her cat giving affection to others </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 21:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are 10 of these disturbing fairy tales in the article.

**Sleeping Beauty** - In one of the very earliest versions of this classic story, published in 1634 by Giambattista Basile as Sun, Moon, and Talia, the princess does not prick her finger on a spindle, but rather gets a sliver of flax stuck under her fingernail. She falls down, apparently dead, but her father cannot face the idea of losing her, so he lays her body on a bed in one of his estates. Later, a king out hunting in the woods finds her, and since he cant wake her up, rapes her while shes unconscious, then heads home to his own country. Some time after that, still unconscious, she gives birth to two children, and one of them accidentally sucks the splinter out of her finger, so she wakes up. The king who raped her is already married, but he burns his wife alive so he and Talia can be together. Dont worry, the wife tries to kill and eat the babies first, so its all morally sound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Sleeping Beauty (in 1634) gets a sliver, falls apparently dead, is hidden by her father, found unconscious and raped by a king out hunting, gives birth to two children who wake her up, so the king burns his wife alive to be with her (after the wife tried to kill and eat the babies) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 21:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 20:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  a 32oz beer bottle in the shower that im ready to knock em out with

[Here's Johnny!](http://stream1.gifsoup.com/view1/1224040/heres-johnny-o.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 20:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Motocross](http://www.dirtbikefix.com/images/zoom.jpg) - They would look like quidditch players from Hogwarts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 20:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe we can do a Kickstarter project to make sure they have enough bombs and bullets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 13:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This ain't no party, this ain't no disco,

this ain't no fooling around

No time for dancing, or lovey dovey,

I ain't got time for that now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 13:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bananas - diced and stirred into the batter.

And serve with cookies-and-cream ice cream. Yum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 13:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can't eat 'em . . . teat 'em </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 12:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't remember my first beer . . . or my last beer . . . am I doing it right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 12:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Tsunamis  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 12:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Recycling in the US** - credit to post by NeverEverCatchMeNow 

* https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/2v2ihw/what_is_something_that_europe_does_better_than/
* https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/2v2qgv/what_is_something_europe_does_generally_better/
* https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/2v1osy/what_is_something_europe_generally_does_better/
* https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/2v2sns/what_is_something_europe_generally_does_better/
* https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/2v2x5e/what_is_something_europe_generally_does_better/
* https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/2v306y/what_is_something_europe_does_better_than_north/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 12:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vintage [Ayatollah toilet paper](http://i.ebayimg.com/00/s/MTQzOVgxMzE4/z/a38AAMXQlgtStdHa/$_35.JPG) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 19:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  according to the CDC 86 cases of measles were reported in the year 2000. ... The whole measles thing by itself is a joke and not a real threat to America.

[From January 1 to January 30, 2015, 102 people from 14 states were reported to have measles](http://www.cdc.gov/measles/cases-outbreaks.html)
"The United States experienced a record number of measles cases **during 2014, with 644 cases from 27 states reported to CDC**'s National Center for Immunization and Respiratory Diseases (NCIRD). This is the greatest number of cases since measles elimination was documented in the U.S. in 2000."

* The majority of the people who got measles were unvaccinated.
* Measles is still common in many parts of the world including countries in Europe, Asia, the Pacific, and Africa.
* Travelers with measles continue to bring the disease into the U.S.
* Measles can spread when it reaches a community in the U.S. where groups of people are unvaccinated.

[Chart: US Measles Cases by Year](http://www.cdc.gov/measles/images/measles-cases-616px.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 06:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you look at the [World Map of the measles outbreaks in 2013](http://www.measlesrubellainitiative.org/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/mmr_outbreaks_cropped-640x360.png)?

It's not about skin color - it's about geography.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 06:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No - the contagion vectors come from outside the Americas.

The spread is due to pools of non-immunized children that are exposed and quickly transmit it to others.

If the children were immunized, the virus brought in from Europe or Africa would not spread.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 06:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's some of the misinformation being spread: 

**Rep. Mo Brooks (R-Ala.)** said individuals who come to the U.S. illegally may be responsible for the recent measles outbreak, contending they dont undergo the stringent health screening others do when they enter the country. I dont think there is any health care professional who has examined the facts who could honestly say that Americans have not died because the disease is brought into America by illegal aliens who are not properly health care screened as lawful immigrants are.

**Rush Limbaugh** - The children coming across the southern U.S. border "were never examined after they got here and quarantined if they had a disease. They were just sent out across the country. Many of them had measles ... We now have an outbreak of it all because of our immigration policy."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: Measles was eliminated in the Americas (North South   Central) in 2000. The virus is imported from residents returning from abroad or from visitors. About half the measles cases in the US originate in Europe. Not from illegal immigrants. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 05:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 04:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Curry, Yes - if the execution is within a few hours of the meal, then **bring it on hot and spicy**.

A) Execution goes as scheduled - so **no "curry bum" to worry about**

B) Stay of execution - **the happiest I've ever been to have red hot curry shits** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 03:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most deadly animal in the world is the mosquito. It might seem impossible that something so minuscule can kill so many people, but mosquito bites result in the deaths of more than 1 million people every year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 01:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  vaccines may actually PREVENT Autism

and death from rubella, measles, polio, flu, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
