<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3267</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a doctor, a trader, and the billionaire Steven A. Cohen got entangled in a vast financial scandal, from The New Yorker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 07:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A.I.G. Bailout, Revisionists Version </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 07:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that, by law, Medicare must cover every cancer drug the FDA approves. A 2003 law, moreover, mandates payment at whatever price the manufacturers charge, plus a 6% cushion, prohibiting any negotiation between Medicare and the drug companies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 03:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Merrill Lynch bankster, Patrick Coppeard, pleads guilty to defrauding 5M from 60 familes in his church </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 00:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Merrill Lynch bankster, Patrick Coppeard, pleads guilty to defrauding 5M from 60 familes in his church </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 00:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There will be a price to pay for banker-bashing, says Ken Fisher. (Is that a threat?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 23:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JP Morgan [76 million customer] data breach: how long can banks live in denial over cyber threats? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 23:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former executives at the Austrian central banks banknote-printing unit were found guilty by a Vienna court of paying bribes to get contracts from the Azeri and Syrian national banks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 19:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 86 senior executives of 2 recently nationalized Spanish banks step down after spending 15.5M euros with off-the-books credit cards given them by their banks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 19:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 86 senior executives of recently nationalized Spanish banks, Caja Madrid and Bankia, step down after spending 15.5M euros with off-the-books credit cards given them by their banks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 19:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CEO of Citi's Mexico unit, Banamex, quits after $400M in bogus loans made to Mexican oil services company, Oceanographia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 19:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First high-frequency trader indicted under new rule </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 07:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JPMorgan to face U.S. class action suit in $10 billion mortgage-backed securities case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 06:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JPMorgan to face U.S. class action suit in $10 billion mortgage-backed securities case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 06:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $729 million still missing from the embezzled Kabul Bank funds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 17:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone recommend some contemporary southern fiction as good as Larry Brown's? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 06:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read everything of his, one book and then another. My favorites were "Father and Son", "Fay", and "Joe".  Wasn't into "Dirty Work" and "On Fire" so much. Have tried to find other authors similar, but didn't care for Barry Hannah or Harry Crews or (most of) William Gay. I found Tom Franklin excellent. My preference is for it to be a little dark and moody with some suspense/tension, but real. Any hint of pretense or self-aware author who is trying too hard, isn't good. Any thoughts on Ron Rash or Frank Bill?  Novels, not short stories. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Afghan president re-opens inquiry into 2010 Kabul Bank theft of $1,000,000,000 - brothers of former president (Karzai) and vice president were spared for "returning the money" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 16:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taoists vs. Existentialists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 09:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do existentialists see things as they are and despair, while taoists see things as they are and laugh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone recommend any contemporary southern fiction writers as good as Larry Brown? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 06:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eric Holder didn't send a single banker to jail for the mortgage crisis. Is that justice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 01:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet the prison banksters who profit from the inmates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 21:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter Thiel: Competition Is for Losers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 17:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goldman Sachs Admits Paying Bribes To Gaddafi Regime </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 17:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China Watchdog Finds $10 Billion in Fake Currency Trade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 17:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who were the real fraudsters in the mortgage crash? A Sacramento jury says the bankers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 17:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mohamed El-Erian quits PIMCO after daughter writes list of 22 milestones he missed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 17:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Didnt Eric Holder Go After the Bankers? - The New Yorker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 17:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Court upholds death sentence for senior bankster in Vietnam - involved in $95M fraud, bribery, swindling property.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 23:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Court upholds death sentence for senior banker in Vietnam - involved in $95M scam, bribery, swindling property </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 23:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could New Desert Plan Spell The End Of California Wind Energy Development? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 20:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside the New York Fed: Secret Recordings and a Culture Clash (The BANKSTERS own the Fed and the regulators) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 19:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glendale cop arrested in prostitution sting is set to get $10,579 a month in paid leave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 19:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glendale, CA, cop arrested in prostitution sting is set to get $10,579 a month in paid leave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 19:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Secret Recordings of Carmen Segarra - former regulator at the NY Fed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 19:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Lewis on the secret Goldman Sachs tapes: "The Fed failed to regulate the banks because it did not encourage its employees to ask questions, to speak their minds or to point out problems." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 19:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barrett Brown writes a column for D Magazine from jail. He happens to be an excellent writer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 06:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analysis Of Volunteer's Metadata Stream Reveals His Life In Detail, Allows Passwords To Be Guessed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 05:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analysis Of Volunteer's Metadata Stream Reveals His Life In Detail, Allows Passwords To Be Guessed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 05:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Untangling the Bizarre CIA Links to the Ground Zero Mosque </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 19:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Untangling the Bizarre CIA Links to the Ground Zero Mosque </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 19:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How banks systematically steal from us (one of the many ways). This is how I realized it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 06:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How banks systematically steal from you (one of the many ways). This is my experience. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 06:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to Wells Fargo to deposit a paycheck.  They told me it wouldn't register in my account until the next business day.  As I recall, it was about noon.  After depositing the check, I called my employer, who also happened to be my dad.  I asked him if he could look at his account and see if the money I had just deposited had been withdrawn from his account.  (He banked with a different bank than Wells Fargo.)  In fact, the money had been withdrawn from his account.  This means that the money wasn't in his account and it wasn't in my account.  *Where was it?*  That's right: In Wells Fargo's account....until the next business day.  

Every day for every paycheck/deposit after a certain time, they don't register it in the depositor's account until the next business day.  This means that they use the money themselves, lend against it, etc.  They have and use this significant rolling cushion of money that isn't theirs, that inflates their reserves by a given, though slightly varying, amount every day.  They position themselves as the middleman who takes his time transferring what isn't his; takes his time and *actually uses* what isn't his.  THIS IS THEFT.  This is systematic thievery practiced every day on many, many people.

When I got my next paycheck a couple weeks later, I went to Wells Fargo and recounted the above to a few tellers behind the counter.  I asked them if I could have cash for my paycheck instead of depositing it.  They said sure, and gave it to me.  I then asked them if I could deposit the cash.  They refused it and told me I'd have to go to another branch to do that, and wouldn't say why.  It was probably because I had gotten wise to their scam and had told them about it.  Since when does a bank refuse a *cash* deposit?

Further, one of the reasons they gave for not allowing me access to the deposit until the next day was for "my protection".  They had to take the check to another city about 250 miles away - presumably with one of those stagecoaches - to verify its authenticity and validity.  However, when I asked for cash, they had to give it to me, and "my protection" was no longer important.


TL;DR  I discovered that banks steal from us by often not making our deposits available to us until the next business day.  However, they do immediately withdraw them from the account that pays them.  For that partial day, banks use that money themselves, as neither the payer or payee has it in his account for that time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leading Anti-Marijuana Academics Are Paid By Painkiller Drug Companies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 18:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moral Dilemma: Should a Libertarian Who Does Not Need Food Stamps, but Qualifies for Them, Take Them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 03:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syndicate Bank bribery scandal grows in India </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 16:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deutsche Bank Fined $7.8 Million Over Faulty Reports on Swaps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 08:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barclays Agrees to Lend Detroit $275 Million to Exit Bankruptcy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 08:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A World Without Fractional Reserve Banks And Central Planning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 08:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Florida Activists Help Depose Florida's Worst Foreclosure Judge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 08:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Wall Street Journal Claims that only the Left is Willing to Prosecute Banksters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 01:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lurings: Powerfully and mysteriously attractive or fascinating pieces of jewelry fabricated only by the appropriation and modification of artificial fishing bait and worn on the lobe of the ear. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 00:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/Banksters - Real news about banksters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 23:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jacksonville bankster, Christopher David Boston, was sentenced to five years in prison for embezzling at least $10.5 million from his job at Fifth Third Bank over a four-year period. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 22:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Max Keiser talks to Matt Taibbi about the injustice that follows the wealth divide and how Ferguson, Missouri, plays into that (video, starts at 12:00) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 19:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael A. Lucarelli, the director of market intelligence at Lippert/Heilshorn and Associates, was arrested and charged with 13 counts of insider trading for buying and selling stocks based on information in news releases his company had prepared </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 16:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IMF Head, Christine Lagarde, Formally Charged In Fraud Probe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 16:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Rothschild banker replaces rebel minister in French cabinet shake-up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 16:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Royal Bank of Scotland has been fined 14.5m by the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) for "serious failings" in its mortgage sales business </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 16:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nearly 15% of California Senate Democrats Arrested or Found Guilty of Criminal Activity this Year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 00:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nearly 15% of California Senate Democrats Arrested or Found Guilty of Criminal Activity this Year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 00:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> B of A settlement invites future fraud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 18:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goldman and Morgan Stanley in DoJ mortgage talks over allegations they mis-sold mortgage-backed securities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 18:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Six directors disqualified over East Lancashire 'land bank' scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 17:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in 2012, the ALS Association had a total revenue of $64,661,521. Of that, $6,616,367 (10.2%) went to research; $9,137,186 (14.1%) went to fundraising; $40,164,177 (62.1%) went to "other program activities" - according to page 15 of their annual report. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 17:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gov. Christie Shifted Pension Cash to Wall Street, Costing New Jersey Taxpayers $3.8 Billion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 03:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jim Grant: "Economy Is Multi-Trillion-Dollar Abstraction" (Video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 20:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Janet Yellen - The Hand on the Lever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 06:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jim Grant: The Fed is "constitutionally behind the curve" and "a big problem is inevitable" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 06:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Los Angeles sues big banks for predatory mortgages but unlikely to win </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 06:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hedge funds: the mysterious power pulling strings on Wall Street </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 06:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goldman Sachs to pay $3.15 billion to resolve claims that it misled U.S. mortgage giants Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac about risky mortgage securities it sold them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 21:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goldman Sachs has agreed to pay $3.15 billion to resolve claims that it misled U.S. mortgage giants Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac about risky mortgage securities it sold them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 18:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> L.A. unions, allies issue fake parking tickets to protest bank deals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 01:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Despite a 1994 law by Congress requiring "data about the use of excessive force by law enforcement officers" to be acquired by the Attorney General, virtually no data has been compiled. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 19:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Co-op Bank admits: Scandals have lost us customers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 16:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bank of America Papers Show Conflict and Trickery in Mortgages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 08:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High Bull$#!+ to Cash Ratio in $17 Billion Bank of America Deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 08:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that US military suicides surpassed combat deaths in 2012 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 01:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IS DETROITS FINANCIAL CRISIS CAUSED BY BANK FRAUD AND COURT COVER-UPS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 22:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holder on B of A settlement: These financial institutions knowingly and fraudulently marketed and sold these loans as sound investments." Therefore no one gets prosecuted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 20:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mish Shedlock rebuts John Tamny on fractional reserve banking and how it is regarded by those of the Austrian school </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 08:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas Car Lender Is Accused of Distortion in Subprime Inquiry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 08:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buffetts Berkshire Hathaway fined $896,000 by Federal Trade Commission </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 07:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Countrywides Angelo Mozilo Said to Face U.S. Civil Suit Over Loans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 22:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Standard Chartered Bank Is Fined Another $300M - for failing to keep the terms of a previous $667M settlement and not remediating anti-money-laundering compliance problems (x-post from /r/banksters) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 17:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Standard Chartered Bank Is Fined Another $300M - for failing to keep the terms of a previous $667M settlement and not remediating anti-money-laundering compliance problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 17:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sound and Fury in Bank Settlements, Still Signifying Nothing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 17:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mortgage Servicer Ocwen Subpoenaed by S.E.C. Over Its Business Ties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 17:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goldman Sachs Said to Raise Junior Staff Salaries 20%; Morgan Stanley is raising salaries for junior bankers worldwide by about 25 percent (x-post from /r/banksters) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 17:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goldman Sachs Said to Raise Junior Staff Salaries 20%; Morgan Stanley is raising salaries for junior bankers worldwide by about 25 percent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 17:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Detention of Haitong Securities Executive 'Is Linked to Bond Scandal' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 16:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Man Who Blew The Whistle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 17:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Robson, former Rabobank trader, becomes first Briton to admit part in worldwide conspiracy to fix LIBOR benchmark interest rate (x-post from /r/banksters) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 16:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Robson, former Rabobank trader, becomes first Briton to admit part in worldwide conspiracy to fix LIBOR benchmark interest rate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 16:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PricewaterhouseCoopers fined $25M, banned 2 years, for altering bank money laundering report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 16:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York Regulator Announces $25M Settlement With Bank Consultant PricewaterhouseCoopers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 22:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Regulators Punting on "Too Big to Fail" Problem of Repo, Looking to Install Yet Another Bailout Vehicle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 22:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commonwealth Bank boss, Ian Narev, nets 20 per cent pay rise despite financial planning scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 16:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Credit Suisse linked to Banco Espirito Santo scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 16:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Closing Of The Austrian School's Economic Mind - by John Tamny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 08:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JPMorgan Chases $13 Billion Shadow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 20:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jamie Dimons $13 Billion Secret - The inside story of JPMorgan Chases landmark mortgage settlement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 20:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the net worth of the average American family dropped 39% from 2007-'10, putting it on par with where it was in 1992. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 20:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Georgia Teens Develop App to Document Police Abuse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 08:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A bank officer and her husband are held in Malaysia for 'stealing over $30,000 from the accounts of Flight MH370 victims' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 21:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Macquarie Group to compensate potentially thousands of customers caught up in financial advice scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 18:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Discover Interview: Roger Penrose Says Physics Is Wrong, From String Theory to Quantum Mechanics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 06:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Price of Keeping Bankers out of Jail: $110 Billion In Settlements And Still Rising (x-post from /r/banksters) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 05:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Price To Keep Bankers Out Of Jail: $110 Billion In Settlements And Rising </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 05:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Los Angeles To Vote On Killing Major Wall Street Deal As City Drowns In Financial Fees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 04:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aamir H. Khan, former executive of a Bahraini bank, plead guilty to a $1.3 million income tax fraud in federal court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 22:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Former Utah Attorneys General Arrested in Bank of America Scandal - for conspiring with the bank to derail major foreclosure lawsuit (x-post from /r/banksters) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 20:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lighter sentences sought for swindlers, embezzlers, insider traders and other white-collar criminals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 18:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Former Utah Attorney Generals Arrested in Bank of America Scandal - conspired with bank to derail major foreclosure lawsuit (x-post from /r/banksters) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 18:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Former Utah Attorney Generals Arrested in Bank of America Scandal - conspired with bank to derail major foreclosure lawsuit (x-post from /r/banksters) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 18:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Former Utah Attorney Generals Arrested in Bank of America Scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 18:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tonight in Ferguson (video gets crazy 9 minutes in) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 06:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More scare-mongering lunacy from the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau via Michael Hiltzik in silly op-ed: "Bitcoins are the wild west" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 21:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JPMorgan, Goldman Sachs reincarnate debt bets in new era </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 21:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edward Snowden: The Untold Story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 17:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Celebrating Greenspan's Legacy of Failure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 04:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Banks' second-quarter profits land close to record levels at $40 billion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 01:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keiser Report: Rid the Bankster Parasite! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 23:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> B of A Fake-Bomb Banker Charged With Insurance Fraud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 22:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neel Kashkari, former TARP chief, Goldman bankster, now running for CA Governor, spends a week homeless in Fresno as a silly campaign ploy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 20:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Financial Crisis in Portugal: The oligarch, the scandal and the bank bailout </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 16:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Petrobras-Linked Money Laundering Probe Spreads to Banks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 16:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New suit targets Shurtleff, Swallow and Bank of America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 16:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ASIC probes Commonwealth Bank over financial planner forgery (Austrailia) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 16:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> India aims to add 10,000 MW per year to lift wind energy sector </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 16:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Credit Bubbles Final Frontier  Meet Goldmans Fixed Income Global Structured Covered Obligation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 05:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese police are investigating the death from unnatural causes of the deputy commissioner of customs at Qingdao port which is under investigation for alleged commodity financing fraud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 02:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Banks Fear Missing Collateral in China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 02:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hackers Unveil Their Plan To Change Email Forever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 08:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Subprime Economy is BackBut It Never Really Left </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 03:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bank Fees: With 'Protection' Like This, Who Needs Enemies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 21:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Millionaire Blackrock executive, Jonathan Burrows, dodged 43,000 in train fares commuting to London </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 21:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New bonus rules may make bankers happier campers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 21:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US refuses to recognize UN court jurisdiction on Argentinas debt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 21:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confusion still surrounds banks' overdraft policies (as intended) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 21:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Big Is Bank of America's $16 Billion Bank Fraud Settlement, Really? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 21:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LAPD detective gets jail, must resign for fondling massage workers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 01:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shameless HSBC shuts Syrian refugees bank accounts in Britain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 22:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New charges filed against Alfred J.R. Villalobos, ex-CalPERS official, in corruption case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 20:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fed Study Finds 2 million in "Forced Retirement", 48% Cannot Afford an Unexpected $400 Expense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 07:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Argentina sues U.S. in International Court of Justice over debt dispute </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 02:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Greek Central Banker Questioned on Bank Sale to Fraudster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 01:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bank of America's Penalty Misses the Point </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 01:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Albania Central Bank Employees Steal $7 Million In Cash (x-post from /r/banksters) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 17:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Albania Central Bank Employees Steal $7 Million In Cash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 17:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Energy-Storing Wind Turbine Would Provide Power 24/7 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 06:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Too-big-to-fail banks' living wills are inadequate, regulators say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 05:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> America's 10 most hated banks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 05:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> B of A agrees to pay $17-billion penalty over mortgage meltdown (x-post from /r/banksters) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 05:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> B of A agrees to pay $17-billion penalty over mortgage meltdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 05:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Documents prove LAPD Chief Beck lied </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 01:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Documents prove LAPD Chief Beck lied </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 01:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fugitive Banker's Life on the Run Included Drug Trafficking, Fake IDs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 22:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yeah, Right (Banksters) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 21:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confusing Capitalism with [the fraud of] Fractional Reserve Banking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 20:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ross Ulbricht (Silk Road): FBI Didn't Have Search Warrant, Violated Fourth Amendment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 03:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UNSEALED: The US Sought Permission To Change The Historical Record Of A Public Court Proceeding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 03:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Congress Edited on Wikipedia Today: Snowden, Manning, Cato, More </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 02:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Congress Edited on Wikipedia Today: Snowden, Manning, Cato, More </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 02:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
