<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1529</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In an intensely awkward congressional hearing Thursday, freshman Rep. Curt Clawson misidentified two senior U.S government officials as representatives of the Indian government. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 21:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In an intensely awkward congressional hearing Thursday, freshman Rep. Curt Clawson misidentified two senior U.S government officials as representatives of the Indian government. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 21:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pentagon: Russia Could Move Heavier Weapons Into Ukraine 'Imminently' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 21:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Considering Refugee Status for Hondurans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 21:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 19:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually in Washington state at least you can fight another person consensually as long as each party agrees that it's consensual, except when there is reasonable suspicion of it being a domestic dispute.

At least, that's how I've had that RCW explained to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. says it has "new evidence" that Russian forces have been firing artillery across the border to attack Ukrainian military positions, and that Moscow is planning to ship powerful rocket artillery to the rebels it backs in the country's east. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 21:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Europe's top human rights court ruled Thursday that Poland broke the law by allowing the CIA to secretly imprison two terror suspects on Polish soil from 2002-2003 and facilitating the conditions under which they were subject to torture. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 21:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraqi lawmakers elected a veteran Kurdish politician as the nation's new president Thursday, just hours after an attack on a prison convoy killed dozens of people, brutally underscoring the challenges faced by the country's leaders as they struggle to form a new government. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 21:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine's prime minister has announced his resignation in protest of the disbanding of the ruling coalition in parliament following the withdrawal of several pro-European parties. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 21:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine's prime minister has announced his resignation in protest of the disbanding of the ruling coalition in parliament following the withdrawal of several pro-European parties. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 21:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Intelligence security initiatives have chilling effect on federal whistleblowers, critics say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 23:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For Israelis on Edge of Battle, Rockets Put On a Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 07:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Court allows Ariz. execution despite concerns over drug secrecy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 07:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In handling rape, high schools are worse than colleges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 02:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Chuck Schumer is calling for partisan primaries to be abolished, saying the current system engenders unhealthy political polarization. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 02:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Dakotas Oil Bonanza Is Unsustainable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 00:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the American dream dead? A groundbreaking new study from Johns Hopkins University shows that for big segments of the population it is </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 23:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 700 Syrians killed in two days of conflict </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 23:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The PowerPoint rant that got a colonel fired </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 04:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 19:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG you're the best.

I'm ashamed I didn't recognize that, though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 09:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait wait am I correctly seeing a tattoo combining the yin-yang/rebel alliance/galactic empire symbols?

That's the second-best thing in this photo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 06:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worst part is that it's a repost? Or that TIL never *actually* learns? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cro - Traum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 06:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cro -- Traum [Rap] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 02:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 00:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god bad memories from that movie. The one for Lust was awful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 00:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's all calm down, old sport. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 00:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd believe it. Americans are pretty famous for bandwagoning, y'know. (WWI, anyone?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 07:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah no apology, it's confusing regardless of any language barrier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 07:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, no to repealing it or no to keeping it?

Double negatives really suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 01:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NO MERCY. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-06 04:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "So edgy Dianne Feinstein's trying to ban it."

Ugh, can we just agree to leave gun-nut politics in /r/progun? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 05:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick! Save yourself and put an /s at the end!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 05:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Spartacus! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 08:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that was unexpected. Maybe he/she's in remission or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 08:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People aren't stupid, we just need a little tort reform. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 18:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basketball? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 09:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> top two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 02:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the minds of most Americans, yes, unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 02:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *sighhh*...thanks Belgium, you guys did good today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 02:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea no kidding. Americans dig an absolute crushing victory, not a tie at the last minute. If anything this will decrease interest in the next match. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 01:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IT WAS YOUUUUUUU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 01:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOD FUCKING DAMN IT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 01:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god Oh my god 4 minutes ok we can do this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 01:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> stop stop stop don't speak too soon damn it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia's Quiet War Against European Fracking: Environmentalists trying to block shale gas exploration across Europe are unknowingly helping Putin maintain his energy leverage over the continent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 20:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 04:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember they need to get approved by congress. That shit ain't easy, Supreme Court justices are always gonna be moderate unless one party controls the government, which is unlikely given the redistricting. And even if the democrats somehow gain control of both houses miraculously, when do they really ever have their ducks in a row to confirm a real progressive justice? The coalition is too broad for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 04:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many times do I have to do that? For gods sake, I've already deleted my account once to start fresh and customize my subs. The small, nice subreddits I find keep getting bigger and already I'm seeing some of them decrease in quality.

I wish I could just *enjoy* it. I don't mind a little work finding new subreddits, but it seems to be an endless cycle. Too much work.

*good example of this:* ELI5, ELIAMA, which both used to be pristine, awesome places. Now they're used as soapboxes for neckbeards and armchair revolutionaries, as well as racists (recall the recent "ELI5 Why gypsies suck" thread). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 08:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.

Zinn's one (slightly crackpot) side to a multifaceted story. The senate was an unelected body meant to provide (in theory, mind you) a bulwark against an overreaching federal government and semi-autonomous regional governments. 

Of course the framers were concerned about tyranny of the majority, as they should be, but the senate was not designed *only* to be a check on majority rule, and I disagree with his idea that "the framers" acted as one body that was exclusively interested in protecting their interests, and that that's the primary role they saw for the government. The framers were not a unanimous bloc, they had a lot of ideas for the roles of government, and they all disagreed about many of them. You can't make such blanket statements, things are more nuanced than that.

I can't stand people running around waving *People's History of the United States* and spouting these things as if they're the only way to look at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 07:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/polandball! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 08:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh. I get it. That's really bad, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 08:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/ladybonersgonecuddly for not just double, but *triple* the karma


^^and ^^compliments, ^^cutie ^^;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm still rooting for Germany tomorrow, but Portugal's got them beat for "Hottest Team Captain." (Cristiano Ronaldo) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 06:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 20:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAE reddit funnier than 9gag? We're so much FUCKING FUNNIER AND DON'T YOU DARE DISAGREE WITH ME.

[L]edit: thanks for the gold :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
