<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1458</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do I do about my younger brother? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-01 11:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if this is the place for this, but about a month or so ago, my brother's girlfriend broke up with him. Ever since, he's taken it incredibly hard. He's utterly inconsolable and it seems no one can really get through to him. 

I've tried chatting with him about it, having had my share of lady troubles in the past, but it's no good. He had once confided in me while they were still together that he saw them as being quite serious. I played it off as him being a high-schooler and thus given to such fancies, but it's obvious that he cared deeply for her. 

I don't want him to continue being so depressed, Reddit, as he's exceptionally bright, his terrific grades have begun to falter somewhat, and he's got a full ride scholarship that I fear he may be jeopardizing. 

Help me get my brother through this, guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where are all the Makarovs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-29 02:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few months ago, it was not uncommon to be able to find Makarovs at J G, Cheaper Than Dirt and others for sale at a fair price but now I can't seem to find them. What happened, gunnit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gentlemen, I submit this: a most tactful "Four-hundreds and four error notification" screen from the gentlemen at Cheyenne Tactical and Sons' Internet Page.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-27 23:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paging Runny Bear... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-27 03:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corn. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-24 03:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh those wacky, wacky Czechoslovakians! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-19 01:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone ID this Chechnyan firearm? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-15 09:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shit, who let Rob Liefeld design military gear? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-15 07:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The day /x/ became /b/ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-15 07:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunday Drive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-15 06:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear Gunnit; what is, in your opinion, the most ridiculous gun law? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-14 20:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, it has to be 922r. What practical purpose could it serve to limit the amount of foreign parts you have on an arbitrarily defined "assault weapon?" I think the rationale is to prevent the importation of military style weapons, but there are a plethora of US made parts that render this purpose moot. It's absolutely retarded. 

Does anyone else agree or can you come up with a worse law? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4chan on Chatroulette </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-14 11:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I get one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-12 23:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know it's a repost, but I can't stress gas protection to protesters enough. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-09 00:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does /r/Skeptic feel about the Dalai Lama? (Fixed link) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-07 19:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Songs of the Years of Fire (  )" A 1971 animated compilation of songs from the Russian Revolution.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-05 17:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Communism in the Southern United States </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-04 18:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even have much idea as to where to start with this, but I suppose I can just ask my questions here and hope for answers.

1. Are there any other Communists in this general region?

     a. Are there any Communist organizations in Georgia?
   
     b. Are there any [/r/Communism](/r/Communism) readers in the state? 


2. What is the best way to spread Communist ideas in such a traditionally anti-Communist region?

3. What is the best way for one in such a politically isolated area to contribute to the cause of the Proletariat? 

4. Finally, is there any suggested reading for someone in this dicey political climate? 

Thank you for your time and consideration, comrades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The West Sea Barrage: A three part documentary on the construction of the West Sea Barrage in highly accented, semi-broken English!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-04 07:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who else followed this thread? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-03 11:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Footsteps - The North Korean Propaganda song of the change in leadership. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-02 07:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The laziest 'We the People' response yet! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-01 02:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Thanks] to Fapocalypse_Now! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-29 04:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An e-gift card to Papa Johns can go a long way and I now have food for the rest of the month thanks to my generous benefactor. 

Thanks to a current deal, [I got three medium pizzas and a 2-liter of Dr Pepper.](http://i.imgur.com/UyoVO.jpg) I fully intend to pay this forward once I get my pay on the 1st of next month. So from the bottom of my heart, thanks Fapocalypse_Now.


Doo doo butter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We've all been here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-29 01:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet the team. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-27 09:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys, what's going on over here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-27 08:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fucking roller coasters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-27 07:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Probably a repost. I don't care. Fuck you.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-27 07:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There isn't enough creepy music here. I present to you, The Music of Erich Zann; after the story by HP Lovecraft. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-27 04:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone didn't think this through. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-24 06:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Infestation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-23 07:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys, what are the second and fourth amendments?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-21 20:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favorite easter egg in Outlaw Star </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-16 13:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> X-Post from /r/atheism, what on Earth is this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-14 16:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wow, someone is FUCKED. (sfw) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-14 12:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newfags can't triforce. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-12 00:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's no secret that The Venture Brothers has borrowed elements from Doctor Strangelove, but does Rusty Venture remind anyone else of this guy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 21:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A most exquisite chemical ignition projectile weapon courtesy of the lads and lasses at "/r/guns" and presented for your consideration, ladies and gentlemen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 11:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Believe it or not, I've bought from these people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 08:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snacks, niggaz. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-04 23:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I got a pretty awesome email today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-02 19:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know, at this point this shouldn't even surprise me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-31 19:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A question for /r/progressive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-31 02:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I consider myself a liberal and I have for quite some time. The Left's advocacy for egalitarian treatment for all, social services and better living conditions while advancing human rights is just common sense, to me, and the Left seems to be the only end of the spectrum concerning itself with these noble goals.

However, I have noticed that the one right that progressives by and large tend to ignore is firearm rights. So, my question, being a left winger who is also a firearms enthusiast, is this: why are so many progressives anti-gun? Aren't firearms the last line of defense people have against their government? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Herro there~ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-28 17:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I cried </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-27 15:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My fiancee gave me wood. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-25 17:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit has its share of creepy people. (As if we weren't enough proof.)  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-24 22:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On the way to school... in North Korea. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-24 18:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This isn't normal, but on religion it is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-23 05:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone's favorite faux-Communist dictatorship has a subreddit, courtesy of the Korean Friendship Association. Wut? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-22 13:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [for hire] Molecular and Cellular Biologist from UC Berkeley </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-21 09:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for a job for my fiancee. We're willing to move absolutely anywhere and could really use the job. She has a four year degree from UC Berkeley in Molecular and Cellular Biology and can happily furnish details on demand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well, this is about the worst thing I've seen today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-20 02:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I went to check on my free Steam gift... Oh... Thanks anyway, Valve. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-20 00:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just seven more nights... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-17 13:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fiancee coming to visit... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-15 00:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, /r/Atlantans! I'm engaged but in a long distance relationship and next month, my lovely fiancee is coming to Atlanta. I myself try to get to Atlanta every chance I get, but I am not in town often enough to know any of the good restaurants to which I could treat her and I don't know which ones would be accessible for my wheelchair. Further, we are somewhat strapped for cash as college is very expensive and most of our spare funds are spent on airfare whenever we can get it.

Therefore, I would like /r/Atlanta's advice. What would be an accessible and reasonably priced, yet delicious and memorable dining experience to which I could treat my beloved? 

BONUS: You might remember us if you went to the Dragoncon meetup. We were [these](http://i.imgur.com/YynFY.jpg) people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Under what context does this make sense? (NSFW, I guess) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-13 11:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a costume for my fiancee and I. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-12 07:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in a wheelchair and there don't appear to be many couples' cosplays involving wheelchairs. Does anyone have any suggestions?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PS Vita to only allow one PSN account per unit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-06 03:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that a fighter pilot in WWII flew himself home after being shot down... by stealing a Nazi fighter plane. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-02 11:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most beautiful thing in the world. (x-post from /r/atheism) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-01 17:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL there's a blind cave beetle named after Adolf Hitler. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-29 20:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was looking for DBZ Abridged quotes but that works too, Google. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-27 15:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The furious outburts in this guy's I Wanna Be the Guy playthroughs are just classic. (NSFW language) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-17 19:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It begins. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-17 06:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walt Disney's... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-16 18:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a thought. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-15 20:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found this friendly fellow lurking around in r/scifi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-14 03:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just finished watching 'Journey's End' with my fiancee. This song will always stick with me for some reason. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-09 14:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So this kind of just blew me away. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-04 10:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [creative] The People's Great and Prosperous Highway! (Leningrad-Silva Nova.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-03 20:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, I'm asking for volunteers. I have successfully mapped from the end of the blue line to my village Leningrad and would like volunteers to help me make it a bona-fide road. Any takers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I fixed my Internet connection just now... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-02 06:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the process of ghetto rigging it, I totally felt like the Doctor; especially once it pinged back on. I think I may be watching too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My fiancee is amused by 'Confucius Says.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-01 10:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's time for /r/revolution to make a comeback.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-28 06:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the recent transgressions against the peaceful protests, the brutality of the corporate police and the unwillingness of OWS moderators to allow discussion of anything but the most bleeding hearted pacifism, I think a new platform is needed to discuss - purely hypothetically and without any limitation - how we should proceed if the peaceful protesters continue to be ground into the dirt by police. 

Sure, it's just Atlanta and Oakland now, but what next? Do you really think Bloomberg will let the protesters stay on Wall Street for long? I do not advocate violence, but surely we've enough freedom left in this country to spread the word that we don't have to be docile little bitches for our corporate lords, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to resist tear gas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-28 06:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If peaceful protest just isn't doing it for you and you can't remain committed to pacifism at 'any cost' then this is probably a more welcoming place to discuss the alternative. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-28 06:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well, I'm done with the Internet today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-27 03:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else enjoy watching shitty B-Movies online with their SO? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-25 04:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My fiancee and I just watched [The Fantastic Four](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=omKd_bUQlXo) - the 1994 unreleased film - and it was the most hilarious thing we've seen in quite some time. Do you guys have any truly awful films, and does anyone else like to do this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 1994, Roger Corman produced an abysmal Fantastic Four film in order to maintain the rights to the franchise and buried it, never to release it. In 2011, I share that film with you. Enjoy the worst comic book movie ever! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-25 04:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone ever played Universe Sandbox? Here's what I thought about it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-25 01:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So this just happened. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-24 22:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wept. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-21 22:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think we have a contender... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-18 08:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pedobear ain't got shit on UC's Oski the Bear. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-12 07:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whenever I see 12.7mm ammo in stock... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-09 08:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aggrazel solves the alien abduction phenomenon.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-08 06:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/Atlanta x-post: Soviet Army uniform: $125. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-08 06:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A bit random, but would anyone know anybody who would like to buy a Soviet Army uniform?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-08 06:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even know if this is the right place to ask this, but I was wondering if anybody in the area would like to buy my old Soviet Army uniform. 

It's in perfectly good shape, but I've got bills to pay and I bought it at a point where, well... I didn't have bills to pay. It's of 1980s vintage and hasn't been worn since the Communications Bureau in Ukraine divested itself of it.

Pics below

[Front](http://i.imgur.com/QUr12.jpg)

[Sleeve](http://i.imgur.com/Zcumv.jpg)

[Liner info](http://i.imgur.com/ouXFT.jpg)

It includes the jacket and pants. The jacket is sized 51 centimeters at the chest and the pants have no sizing information, but should fit anyone who can fit into the jacket. I am selling it for $125, but the price is negotiable. Let me know if you're interested!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That Mitchell and Webb Look: Battlestar Galactica </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-04 17:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favorite song from the soundtrack? This is mine... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-04 03:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> x-posted from /r/gaming, nervous_testpilot talked to me and answered some questions!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-01 13:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interview: Frozen Synapse developer nervous_testpilot. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-01 01:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wrote an article about Survivor Zero... and got to talk with the developer team. Oh, and there's never before seen concept art, too.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-28 21:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My fiance took this at Dragoncon. You guys will enjoy this, I'm sure. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-26 14:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris-Chan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-24 04:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made a petition to repeal the NFA and make civilian ownership of automatic weapons easier. What do you guys think?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-23 06:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A nearly impossible question... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-22 14:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I'm disabled: a through the knee amputation that requires me to use a wheelchair. Here's the kicker, though: I love urban exploration and have always wanted to give it a try. However, abandoned buildings tend not to have working elevators and since they're generally very old, they almost always lack ramps where they're needed. So my question is this: can anyone think of a way to go urban exploring while in a wheelchair? 

Miscellaneous, helpful information: I am fairly mobile outside of my chair, though it's restricted to crawling and that's not wise in crumbling ruins, and my chair is manual so I don't have to charge it or anything. 

I know this is an unusual question and I'm honestly not expecting a miracle here, but if anyone has any information at all, I'd consider it a boon. Thanks for reading! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Imagination </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-22 12:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The nights are the worst. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-20 10:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've not really posted here much, but my fiance has; so bear with me if you don't mind. 

As you are all, I'm sure, acutely aware; the night is the absolute worst time of day to be missing your lover. It isn't so bad during the day, because I can text or call her and she texts and calls me. At night, though, as I try to sleep, I feel her absence very keenly - as though a part of me were missing. After noticing we were both on Google+, I texted her and we chatted for a while on Skype and she missed me as horribly as I missed her. This is a common course of events.

I want to know, /r/LongDistance, if you have any tips to alleviate our longing for each other. Is there anything we can do or - perhaps - send each other to make our beds feel less empty at night?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Honey on Bike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-20 04:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minecraft.net: continued login issues. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-15 00:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if this is related to Minecraft.net or a problem on my machine, but this morning, the launcher wouldn't let me login. I shrugged it off and waited a few hours until noon. I tried again and the same thing happened. It is now 18:29 and I have tried for a third time, to no avail. I've already updated Java so I don't see what else the issue could be. Any tips?

**EDIT: PROBLEM RESOLVED** Downloading the new launcher has fixed everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one who thinks that Neil Hamburger (left) looks like an up and coming Splicer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-13 11:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I must say, Google is pretty damn smart. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-12 08:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is awful and in poor taste. That being said, what the fuck is this and why does it exist?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-11 14:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is your left... [x-post from /r/offbeat] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-10 12:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is it so hard to find a good quality version of this song? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-08 06:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone help me find pictures of my fiance and I? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-07 05:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We were the obnoxious making out couple at the meetup. I was dressed as Adama and in a wheelchair while she was the sexy lady in my lap. 

Our camera was awful and we only got a few pictures, but I kinda wish we had more pics of the convention, so if anyone wants to help me find pictures of ourselves, I would appreciate it. She didn't cosplay, but I did on Friday and Saturday as an East German soldier and Commander Adama respectively. If you can help, I'll thank you forever! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flair idea: cosplayers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-07 05:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just an idea I had thought of for this subreddit. Feel free to shoot it down, but I'm in Con Drop mode so hear me out. 

What if we had flair for this subreddit and it was what we want to cosplay next year? Reactions: go!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't know if anyone posted this to here yet, but here's the Great Reddit Meetup of Dragon*con 2011!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-06 23:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunday? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-04 02:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone want another meetup tomorrow? My fiance and I had fun.

EDIT: FUCK IT, I MADE ONE.

6PM SUNDAY
Marriott, 10th floor lounge. Be there or you hate reddit and might end up getting robbed by Andy Warhol's ghost.

Trufax. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that peanut oil can be used as fuel in diesel engines. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-30 09:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't even want to know what was going on when this was made.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-26 01:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a fevered dream I saw the harbinger of the endtimes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-18 05:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I can't get back to sleep. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In response to recent revelations of infiltration by Stormfront, I present evidence that even horrible bigots can occasionally get along with other races. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-16 06:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's talk about Kuchisake-onna. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-13 22:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How about the Great Hill Cemetery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-13 06:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thursday? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-09 01:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting into town on Thursday and I was wondering if anyone else had anything planned for Thursday evening. A lot of my friends won't get in til Friday, so I was thinking it might be a good idea to see what my fellow Reddit congoers are doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disabled Access in Foreign Countries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-07 01:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have noticed, when looking at pictures of countries outside of North America and Western Europe that there seems to be no care given to public access for disabled people. I am very curious as to why this is the case, as at some point in the future I would love to travel. 

I know this is a very broad and general question, but it seems like if the United States - as backwards as we are in accommodating those outside the mainstream - can make laws mandating access for handicapped persons, other countries might do the same. I would love to hear what anyone might have to say on the matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In honor of my Reddit Birthday, here's me with James Randi at last year's DragonCon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-04 03:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gee; thanks, Twitter... I think... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-04 02:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long ago, before Chanology, there was... The Cult of the Dead Cow... (Beware: Encyclopedia Dramatica link) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-03 18:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ladies and gentlemen, the world's ugliest firearm. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-01 19:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Picture] Piracy painting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-31 01:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a picture that was presented twice, the first time being pirates storming a ship with something to the effect of "We're here for yer booty." And the words: How most people view piracy.

The image was again repeated, the second time saying something like "How it really is" with the pirate captain stating "We be here to make copies of all yer cargo." Of note was a toothless pirate scab saying something to the effect of "Where be the amputee porn?" Or something. Anyone got this?

SOLVED BY THE RENWALLZ. THANKS, THE RENWALLZ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fancy a drink? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-28 21:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love Atlanta. [x-post from /r/Atlanta] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-27 17:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love our city's sense of humor.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-27 17:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Real funny, L. Ron. (Read the second paragraph.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-25 11:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The latest self indulgent bullshit from $cientology's YouTube appears to have ratings enabled. Oh my! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-21 09:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Return of the king? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-21 08:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A friend told me my microphone was unshielded. This was my solution. Nailed it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-16 08:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My masterpiece.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-15 23:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Accomplishment for the Day [Frozen Synapse] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-15 10:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Universe Sandbox: Am I Doing It Right? (x-post from /r/StarWars) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-10 10:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Universe Sandbox: Am I doing it right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-10 09:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A rolemodel for us all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-08 06:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I would love for this to be a real show.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-02 02:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw this ad on Oglaf. I'm scared, now. It's officially worse than "Become A Baby." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-27 08:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Willie Nelson never ceases to amuse me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-27 08:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Put Down The Phone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-13 22:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Most Important Fish You've Never Heard Of... And It's Running Out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-09 03:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meanwhile, in Japan... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-09 01:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone who can tell me what's going on here would be appreciated. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-08 22:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When a Christian finds out you're an Atheist in the southern United States... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-06 02:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A different sort of creepy... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-31 05:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am quite sorry, friend; but after much rumination, I do believe that this is the music I heard that dumb, aged violinist intone those many years ago. - The Music of Erich Zann </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-28 09:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And with that, the Ponies craze had run it's course... or got more severe. I can't tell. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-28 06:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I thought you guys might enjoy this compendium of Soviet era music. Propaganda songs, mostly; but it's some legitimately good listening, in my opinion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-08 04:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know I'm late, but this took me entirely too long to assemble. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-05 06:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dad and I like to have pun fights. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-27 03:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think someone mixed up the title and description fields... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-25 05:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that they guy who did the music for Psycho also did the score for Citizen Kane and scored for The Twilight Zone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-18 23:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lips Down On Dixie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-17 01:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was there last Friday celebrating my birthday and I have got to know... How on Earth did it take me this long to go there? That was so awesome. Are there any other Lips fans on /r/reddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On the GSU campus, there was a poster full of "inspirational" religious quotes. My friends and I balanced it a bit... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-16 11:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Vera Lynn - singer of the classic "We'll Meet Again" during World War II - is not only still alive, but is still somewhat active! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-07 21:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Battlestar Bears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-04 07:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
