<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9117</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 00:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha my singlet looks nothing like that... It's more of the "wife beater" type of singlet... And that's just my casual doing the gardening clothes. Also I leave all of my clothes at work as they are actually firefighting clothes (I'm in emergency services) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 21:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I will go see one when I'm home for sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 12:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This gorge is actually about a 10min drive from my work... It looks so much better in that picture then when I see it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by putting moisturiser on my sunburn (NSFW?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 12:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it really started yesterday after I finished ripping up my old lawn from my backyard. It took me around 10 hours and I was wearing a singlet. Dumbass me forgot to put sunscreen on my back where my skin shows... So I got sunburnt. My girlfriend gave me some moisturiser to put on it to make it better she told me "this works really well for me" so I put it on. This morning I went to work, putting more on in the morning and also at around 1pm (during lunch) getting towards the end of my shift my sunburn was starting to get pretty painful but because I'm a man... I worked through the pain. It wasn't until the end of my shift I couldn't take it anymore so I went to the medic. Took me shirt off and what do you know... I've had an allergic reaction to the moisturiser and my sunburn is now fully blistered and pussy... Half of which has popped and not very pleasing to look at... The nurse gave me some burnaid and sent me to my room to relax and go back to see her in the morning. So that's how TIFU

Note: I work away from home on a mine site, that's why I had to see a medic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 10:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you guys coming back to tour west australia? Would love to watch you. Sadly missed out last time. Thanks guys you rock! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 21:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so yeah... i watched it for way too long before i realised it was looped... good job sir  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 20:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> isnt that laverne from scrubs at the back? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 19:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R Kelly would love this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 19:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you sir know your helicopters.. i do not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 18:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> kill it with fire! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 18:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> murica </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 16:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "this guy" is my brother... i can confirm he does  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 21:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> congrats. you just stopped another unwanted pregnancy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 21:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> figured it out. i feel pretty damn stupid now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 20:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn, they didn't go with my idea. super mega awesome fun centre </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> can i use my gold credits on my own account? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 15:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok so i have some reddit gold credits on my account and im just wondering if there is a way to apply them on my own account or are they just for giving to people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 15:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> chicago fire... everything is just wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 15:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> michael jackson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 15:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i was the fat/poor/nerdy kid with no friends... now im the kind of skinny/not so poor/nerdy adult with still no friends... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the longest animal scientific name belongs to a species of soldier fly, it contains 42 characters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 13:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 07:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks very much for the pic :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 07:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long story short I'm going to win a weirdest pic comp with my brother and he has to hang all the pics I get in his house </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 06:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry guys I paid up. And will continue to pay if pics I like keep coming in :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 06:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankyou so much that looks awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 06:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankyou very much that is amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 17:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha i didnt think of it like that... but yeah sort of similar i guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [request] NSFW can anyone draw my sad clown? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 17:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok i know its a bit weird but im after a sad clown with male genetalia for a nose, he also has tenticles for arms and is holding a bunch of balloons that are testicles... colour would be amazing and if you can do it for me i will reward you with cookies and some reddit gold (cookies not included) edit: could you also incorporate a poorly drawn robot with the words "a robot by Jacob" under it (as a tattoo or on it's shirt) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [request] can anyone draw my weird request? NSFW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 16:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok i know its a bit weird but im after a sad clown with male genetalia for a nose, he also has tenticles for arms and is holding a bunch of balloons that are testicles... colour would be amazing and if you can do it for me i will reward you with cookies and some reddit gold (cookies not included) edit: could you also incorporate a poorly drawn robot with the words "a robot by Jacob" under it (as a tattoo or on it's shirt) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 21:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an Emergency Services Officer for a major mining company in Western Australia, 2 years experience and earn $120k/year. Previously I was a fitter/machinist with 6 years experience earning $165k/year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
