<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3450</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 21:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put your cell phone in your pocket when getting into your car and don't rake it out till you're at your location, seriously. Don't use it while driving </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 17:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it's only 10am so........ session IPA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 07:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not Chinese, but I swear Ruang (sp?) Thai.  It's in the same parking lot as as the Albertsons at 15th and Custer.  Best Thai anywhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 23:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, no love for Santa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 23:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks btrlilwhtgrl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 18:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know right?  Where in the metropolis are you, the temp jumps are killing my body </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 17:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marrying me?  You know, just sayin... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The brewery I work for throws a holiday bazaar. I dressed as Santa, the results were as expected. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 05:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear redditors , when was the most you have ever felt conflicted with a life decision? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 22:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At what point in your life have you been the most lost and conflicted about making a personal decision.  How did you handle it and what were the outcomes.  If you had to go back, would you have done the same thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 23:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are seriously, CRAZY adorable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 16:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I've been into Neil Young for a while.  29 years old and have been into his stuff since early high school, very cool pic, thanks for sharing it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 22:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never knew he played on a V </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 21:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spot on and very beautiful, glad you got to live it up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 23:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, I'm way too curious for that to be a deterrent  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 23:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From Opie (SoA) to Dopey, sorry man, never shave again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 22:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah my whole plan is to treat it as a donor bike and throw as much as I can on a new rigid frame.  I did have a Honda shadow 750 ace.  Very reliable bike.  Only complaint is it was limited on customization and many parts on the baby that should have been metal were plastic or fiber glass.  Road like a champ though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 22:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the feedback, good knowledge for a HD TIL (no sarcasm intended)  I did find one auction site that sells everything from repo's to totalled out bikes.  Minimum bids start at about $200.  Don't have it saved on my phone but cam send a.link later if you're interested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 00:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> La piccolo buffalo in little Italy was Damn good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 00:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also went to high school with a Brandon, his wife is Caitlynn, there daughter is Braylynn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 00:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend teaches third grade.  One of her students legal birth name's is La-a (pronounced Ladasha)  she's shown me the name while grading papers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 00:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 20:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe you're not allowed to do that awesome spin move to go from reverse to forward that Jason Statham does in every driving movie.  It is acceptable to do so in the afternoon though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 20:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very lovely, happy 21st </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 03:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the lead, but it looks like they only deal in metric.  I have friends into cb750 rebuilds, will forward them here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 22:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Pearl of the Stars" by Coheed and Cambria.  Not because of the content itself, but because of the emotional connection to that song and an ex.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 22:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hotel Palomar is nice too, being is awesome as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 22:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you wanted to use beer or wort product to get a starter going I recommend using whole, fresh, unacidulated and unused grain of your choice.  2 row is cheap, and spin it in a food processor untill it a fine flour, sift and start your starter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 22:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/White_Rock_Lake. We have our very own soppy wet prom date.  Its a great story, my aunts used to creep me out as a kid by telling me the story of The Lady of White Rock Lake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 21:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Last Call" is a great read.  Its everything you'd ever need or want to know about Prohibition in the United States.  It also has a lot of great knowledge of the long term and current effects from the fall out of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DFW Motorcycle grave yards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 06:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone out there in internet land know of any motorcycle salvage yards in or near DFW, looking for a Harley build project </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 22:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, yes I do, very adorable  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 22:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Johnny!  Kill one, fuck one, marry one.  Steve-O, Flo from the Progressive commercials, and the Bull from the rodeo see saw bit. GO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman Died from Doing Meth, Crawling into Her Freezer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-20 23:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neograft knowledge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 05:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone have any experience with receiving a neograft procedure.  Either the strip method or the FUE. method.  Almost 30 and looking quite a bit of hair up there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 07:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is one of my favorite to fap to and have no info on her! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 03:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your question is invalid.  Everything I do naked is sexy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 06:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of shitty father (Or mother) lets his daughter dress like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 05:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Local honey, best with something mildly Spivey like a quality pepperoni  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 21:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 05:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hot Damn, looking good for any age </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 02:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 22:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So he's homeless and caught up on new episodes of breaking bad, and shirtless but not tanned? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 23:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you're gold </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-22 19:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Photoshop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 23:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kill One, Marry one Fuck one.  Joe Rogan, Seth Rogan, Seth MacFarlan, GO! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 19:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slashed a tire on a girlfriends car right after we broke up when I found out she had cheated on me when we were together.  Got away with it, but didn't feel to good about myself afterwards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 20:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A beard as majestic as yours should never be ignored Sir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 03:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who?  For the love of God who is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unnecessary programs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 21:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 16:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never canned it before, I either serve it immediately or cryo-vacced it and gave/sold it to friends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 16:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 celery stalk, 2 carrots and 1 LG red onion small dice lightly sauteed in 1/2C olive oil, when translucent add 2lg cans tomatoes puree and 1 small diced tomatoes.  Season with salt, black pepper and herbage to taste, simmer on low for as many hours as possible, puree and stain if you'd like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 20:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, it's just like dinner, whatever he doesn't want that's more for me ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 22:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would do REALLY well in/ r/palegirls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 20:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the love of all things boobs, who is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 04:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wings with Dad while watching the homerun derby, not a bad way to celebrate! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My one yeard anniversary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 04:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 03:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, no welding experience, i didn't even think of that, i was more concerned with setting the petcoc and running a gas line </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 04:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never done a chop, used to work for HD at a dealership, in parts.  I have a pretty good starting knowledge but some things like gas tank set up and jetting carbs make me a little nervous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 23:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to plan ahead and budget, do this right even if it takes a while </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 22:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look close enough to Beiber's pants you'll get a new appreciation for the term dick face </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 03:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know those story problems in jr. high math that are loaded down with A LOT of extra information that have nothing what so ever to do with the actual problem itself?  Yeah... that's the title for this joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Build Cost? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 02:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do ya'll think total cost would be, as many used parts as possible, to do a build like this, rigid frame, and perferably and 88"

http://www.americanclassicmotors.net/tonystblk1.JPG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 18:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go out to local brewery tours, they're usually fun and you get to have local stuff, which hopefully, is pretty good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 18:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a dough recipe, the one I have is a little spotty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-22 15:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing a can of spray paint couldn't fix </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 00:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will you marry m....  I mean, that's a really good look for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 05:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who?  For the love of God, who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sony Alpha NEX repair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-27 21:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My camera got dropped about 6 feet.  Everything works fine except the shutter button.  Any idea of how to repair it or anyone who will.  Sony wants $250 just to look at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 20:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just big big fans of our beer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 20:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We made sure not to serve before the ceremony,  afterward, well, different story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I work for one of the big Dallas breweries, we got to be a part of this tonight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-25 05:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I work at a brewery, this went down tonight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-25 01:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transferring to a new computer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-19 20:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My old compouter died in the worst of ways. I just got a new desktop, Windowsn 8 and downloaded the most recent version of Zune Market place.  I have a 32G Zune HD,  How do I get everything from my Zune to my desktop.  Apparently syncing it is enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-19 06:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God Bless Texas, where was it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 06:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You ma'am, have the perfect pair! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-12 05:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best place I've found so far is Jerry's Woodfire Dogs in downtown Lakewood.  I actually have the Hot Doug's logo on my shin and spent plenty of time there, nothing here I've found has been that close </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vehicle wrap Help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-11 19:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have some scratches in the (what we hope) surface area of our skin wrap on our company's delivery truck.  Anyone have solid experience on how to buff out the scratches if it's possible?  Any solid links to information would be helpful too, google didn't do much for me on this search. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-28 18:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very Interested, I live near GWB and Custer, I work at The Lakewood Brewery at Jupiter and 635, very close by, I'm interested in what you guys may have to offer.  I know I won't be the first one, but I don't have an athletic bone in my body, would like to turn that around </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-28 17:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> me gusta </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crossfit Gym Shopping </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-28 17:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have any Dallas redditors shopped around different Crossfit gyms?  I was lookking for recommendations on price and quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 00:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pico de Gallo is pretty good, no seasoning other than salt and pepper, also If your more adventurous, small diced shrimp ceviche </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My 15yo Dalmatian Dixie Dog passed away this week, this is how the family remembers her </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 05:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 03:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an awesome brewery too thanks.  See above comment for second half though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 03:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, still somewhat new to posting regularly, doing this on my phone so don't have a way to blur the name, (unless you know a way, then I'm open to info) but match isnt her last name, no worries </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh my god reddit, it might actually happen this time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 02:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-31 17:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preferable standard american parts, not metric </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ground up step by step </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-31 17:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was wondering if anyone knows of any info out there, that breaks down a ground up build, step by step, with an explanation broken down as basically as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-30 19:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better than guitar center </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-30 19:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope these aren't the same guys I'm thinking of.  Last Beer Week 3 guys claiming they were starting a cidery came into the bar I was working at (Jack Mac's) for the cask taping.  We caught them trying to steal beer off of the firkin.  Then they got so wasted 2 passed out at their table, then we caught them trying to walk their tab.  Hope its not the same guys, karma is a bad hangover </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 08:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually have been loosing weight, see comments below.  I have a very physical job at a brewery, hauling kegs.  I've cut back on my drinking and have been making smarter food choices.  Next paycheck I'll be able to afford a membership to a gym already picked one out.  I also throw shot put during the spring (If we get one in TX this year) and will be loosing A LOT of weight during the summer at work whether I try or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 01:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, I think that'll be the first step, I'm gonna start with the longest guard and work my way down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 01:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah...  he's actually a pretty slim guy, but I noticed that too when I first met him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 01:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, i'm working on that, been steadily dropping actually, about 15lbs in 3 months was at about 270, I work at a brewery in TX so I know I'll be loosing a lot more this summer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 01:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to respectfully look at the photo again, my hair is going pretty quickly now, it started when I was 21 and has been going exponentially recently, despite healthier decisions, you might want to look again.  But thanks for the encouragement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 01:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'm gonna do it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend Veronica is an awesome photographer, here's her husband's portraits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 19:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend's wife shot his portrait, what do y'all think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 18:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Be honest reddit, I'm 29, is it time to start shaving the heah? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 17:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey reddit, what's your greatest small joy in life that brings you comfort? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 13:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it has to be a full tank of gas and a new set of tires. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 16:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last I heard snoop canceled </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 16:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, I can't speak for the turkey, haven't  had it, but Mr G's is awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should have been 21 plays of Tom Jone's What's New Pussycat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-21 03:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chris was actually a good friend of mine growing up but we kind of went separate ways around highschool, grew up in the same block, played baseball and did the whole "scouts" thing together.  He was an awesome guy and was always there for a laugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-02 13:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How tall are you, I arrested losing my hair around 20 (28) but I'm just shy of 6'2" so most people don't notice, so I particularly am holding out a bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First attempt at pretzel rolls, not too shabby </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 06:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 22:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not reccomend using honey instead of sugar because it won't cook to the crystalyn state. Sugar will.  Try a very small (one jar) batch to see how it works.l, I may be wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 15:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make a tighter pesto, less oil, more basil and nuts, and spread it as a sauce a little thinker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-18 00:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is a duck, he's a shady SOB, most of his payroll practices are illegal as well as his back of the house staff, I managed under him and his ex wife at the Allen location and it was a nightmare </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-16 05:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My old boss finally made it big! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neighbors seek boycott of Frisco restaurant owner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-16 05:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-16 04:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grapefruit and/or orange marmalade with candied ginger.  You can also make and store an orange cure mix if you cure your own salmon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> one week shy of a 1/2 yeard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 02:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 06:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out Lakewood Brewing instead.  It's the same price, you get to keep a Belgium style glass, and the lines are A LOT shorter.  They have the same music and food trucks, but it's a lot less pretentious and crowded.  Plus their beer is a lot better, if you're a beer knurd, also more consistent and true to form.  Big Fan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
