<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5807</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 21:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprised to see that my hometown TV station made it on r/science. The last time they made worldwide news was for their drunk anchor. http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2071669/Annie-Stensrud-Was-bumbling-news-anchor-drunk-air-Female-presenter-slurs-words-bizarre-broadcast.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Park: "Chef, what would a priest want to stick up our butts?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-22 20:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 17:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's he doing at a World Wrestling Entertainment event? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 17:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One has to wonder about the multitude of ways that sports subtly affect our psyches and actions. The article mentioned that sports defeats also boost chances of traffic fatalities and domestic violence... eeek!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Football fans eat fattier foods and 10% more calories than usual the day after their team loses. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 17:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 16:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% positive feedback: sounds like a responsible mother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to extract better work out of misbehaving employees: guilt them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 18:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 23:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So rigid, methodical, and uninspired... but enough about the current state of scientific publishing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have demonstrated that if the language processing areas of the brain become damaged, language function can switch to the non-dominant hemisphere. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 23:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The human sense of touch is far more sensitive than originally thought. New research shows that we can detect deformations on the nanoscale. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 19:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists don't "believe" in evolution, they accept the evidence for it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 17:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 17:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many people carry around hatred and contempt after being wronged. The accompanying worry and anxiety must feel like a 20lb weight on each shoulder. You don't have to forget -- justice should be done in those circumstances. But forgiveness is the true liberation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Power of Forgiveness: Forgiving linked to mental and physical health. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 07:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 20:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically correct. Though with male animals, vets almost always remove the testicles: simple, cheap, effective.

The downside is that your male cat won't be cooling its balls on the base of toilets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mini-brains with separate working regions have been grown using stem cells in the lab for the first time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 16:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 23:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If fusion reactions don't become self-sustaining, how do you explain stars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 20:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NIF began focused on achieving fusion ignition and it still is. But they've missed so many deadlines over there that it seems they're starting to "diversify their research portfolio," so to speak -- taking on all sorts of projects.

I mean, that HUGE laser has to be used for something! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 20:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NIF's biggest problem is being able to sustain and control the fusion reaction. Judging by the article it doesn't seem that fusion ignition occurred, where the reaction actually becomes self-sustaining. In other words, I'm guessing that they didn't reach the break even point, if they did, that would be the headline.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 04:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We like to have fun in Madison.

http://www.southparkstudios.com/clips/402323/we-like-to-have-fun-here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists uncover the remains of Leedsichthys problematicus, the world's largest fish. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 04:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New device uses electromagnetic waves from TV broadcasts and cell phone and wireless Internet signals and converts them to power </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 16:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 05:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This study was released almost two months ago and already appeared on /r/science. I love how Scientific American simply slapped on a misleading headline and republished it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh hai, Giant Russian Military Hovercraft. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 06:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-21 01:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like they compared the subjects' final fitness scores/metrics to baseline metrics taken at the beginning of the program. Not sure if sedentary controls are really needed for a study of this design. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First scientific study on CrossFit finds that it significantly improves body composition and aerobic capacity across all fitness levels. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 23:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unrealistic comparative optimism: Why we always think the other guy is going to get hit by a truck. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 05:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The deep-sea footprint of the Deepwater Horizon oil spill. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 03:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 00:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> STUNNER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Ugliest Churches in the World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 00:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Subtle thoughts and primes of death increase alcohol consumption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 20:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 16:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a link to the research that I think the author is referencing:
http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/23759244

Psychobiotics: A Novel Class of Psychotropic.

Abstract: Here, we define a psychobiotic as a live organism that, when ingested in adequate amounts, produces a health benefit in patients suffering from psychiatric illness. As a class of probiotic, these bacteria are capable of producing and delivering neuroactive substances such as gamma-aminobutyric acid and serotonin, which act on the brain-gut axis. Preclinical evaluation in rodents suggests that certain psychobiotics possess antidepressant or anxiolytic activity... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Psychobiotic' Bacteria Affect Our Mood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 16:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman murders a talking hot dog in a classic public service announcement about the dangers of LSD. The horror! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 00:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 06:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One time I ripped my boxers deadlifting and mistook it for an anal blowout. For the thirty minutes before I noticed that they were ripped, I was scared shitless that my colon would start leaking out of my arsehole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the first and only transplanted human penis was cut off after two weeks "because of the wife's psychological rejection as well as the swollen shape." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 20:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 00:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops, damn my brain. A billion billion is still less than 10^32, though! ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 23:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only a billion years? Pffft. The proton can live for up to 10^32 years! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exosomes derived from stem cells could cause the brain to regenerate itself after trauma, and may one day be used to treat Alzheimer's </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 23:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 16:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This study is interesting in that people commonly perceive cities as more dangerous due to higher crime and homicide rates -- we fear what we can't control. But in reality, the risk of injury death is higher outside of cities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Major cities are often the safest places in the U.S. The "overall risk of injury death is lower in urban areas compared to outside of cities." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 16:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 16:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One findings that was surprising about this study was that people were least likely to intervene when the conflict was between a man and a woman. Those fights are often of a different nature, I suppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 18:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, here are a couple.

Lesbian parents (PDF): "...although children from lesbian families were more likely to explore same-sex relationships, the large majority of children who grew up in lesbian families identified themselves as heterosexual."
http://www.silveroakcasino.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/3.pdf

Gay Parents: "More than 90% of sons whose sexual orientations could be rated were heterosexual."
http://psycnet.apa.org/journals/dev/31/1/124/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
