<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1490</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 21:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ps your flooring is dope
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 21:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice one man! love the tv in front of the trainer lol. I have a similar setup for those long seshes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 21:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to start living my friend
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 21:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this is when a large tv becomes useful
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 21:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ayy you just read my mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 21:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also think its more just to do with all the similar titles lately. Nice setup man!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 21:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, fair enough. He's not driving under their bedroom windows at night, I get that.

Just a weird teacher with some questionable social media practices.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 21:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the basic level you are right: don't post shit you don't want others to see. But the issue here is more what an incredible display of unprofessionalism it is to monitor your students online presence unsolicited. And the fact that OP is clearly not aware of how negatively his actions are actually being perceived by anyone whose opinion is actually relevant to the scenario.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 21:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow nothing personal but I kinda hope you get fired. Sounds like you're not exactly cut out to be teaching kids when you yourself aren't finished being one.

You said you take "pride" in being in the know about your students, when in fact you are just monitoring their presence online without their permission or the official request of anybody. The fact that you admitted to needing to find out "who liked the girls ass photo" already betrays your creepy personal agenda.

Justify it however you want but you teachers who stalk students are the fucking worst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 20:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I initially read it as a female teacher telling the story and still thought it was creepy as fuck. He literally applies the word "stalking" to what he is doing to his students. Nobody asked him to do that shit. At best he's well intentioned but needs to get a life, at worst he gets kicks out of following his students lives and still needs to get his own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 07:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol nice one! love the shadow being cast by your collectible  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 21:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuckin' dopee
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:Why does Japan have such a huge "cat-girl" culture? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 21:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously does it go back hundreds of years because of cultural tradition, or did it just start with a couple of furry animators and kind of snowballed from there?

I just find it so strange that bestiality is typically regarded as one of the most taboo forms of pornography, yet humans who dress and act (and in some cases even want to be treated) like cats are noticeably becoming more and more mainstream and acceptable, especially in Japan and amongst Japanese pop-culture enthusiasts. Why is this?
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 19:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes when I feel shitty about not going out I remember this is some peoples idea of a public outing and I feel much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 19:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeahhhh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 09:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol ever heard of a bag?
you must be one of those dorks with saggy weighted down cargo pants
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 06:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just described my sleep habits
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 02:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol I like how it's barren... Romans don't like snow

edit: nvm I think I see people just the resolution makes it hard to tell
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 02:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like you haven't actually seen one then
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 01:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1   2 will always hold a special place in my heart. Still played 3 but didn't love it. Age of Mythology is still the shit too, bust it out a couple times annually for some comp stomp
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comment sections on classic techno are always so positive! Screenshot from Maurizio - Domina (Maurizio Mix) Video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 20:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 09:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Club mate! luckyyyy. Can't get that shit at all in Canada. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 09:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Triple reddit?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 09:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you run three monitors off of one laptop? is there any lag?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 09:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like shopping will never become 100% online because sometimes there are things you just don't want to wait for. I don't mind buying the odd jacket or whatever online but i'm not going to have a wardrobe shipped to me. If there are people like that out there that is weird..
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 09:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here in Edmonton we still have ridiculously over the top malls. Case and point: West Edmonton Mall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 09:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> West Edmonton Mall is actually one of the few exceptions with a ton of attractions left. It still has an ice rink, amusement park, water park, arcade, iMax movie theatre, replica ship in the middle of a big flooded atrium that you can book for parties, and multiple mini-putt courses. Plus a hotel, nightclubs, casino, bowling and several sit-down restaurants. The only thing missing is a strip joint. But yeah besides that all our malls are pretty cookie-cutter. H M, VS, Starbucks, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 09:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> West Edmonton Mall is actually one of the few exceptions with a ton of attractions left. It still has an ice rink, amusement park, waterpark, iMax movies, random boat in the middle of a big atrium that you can book for parties, and multiple mini-putt courses. Plus a hotel, nightclub, casino and several restaurants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 07:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also idk why but I like chaotic battle stations like this as opposed to clean ones. Clean looks nice but also like they just moved into the room and then took the picture. I like a battlestation that's clearly been lived in and has evolved to fit the space rather than the other way around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 07:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to have a tv parallel to the bed like that for those lazy mornings...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 02:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gagged
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 20:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the wife is cool with you splitting your time between your marriage bed and a gaming shack?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 08:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you work at home? What kind of job would you need Rokit 8's for?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 08:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dream is to one day have enough desk space to have a perfect clean triple monitor setup like this....
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 08:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are some odd choices for discreet weapons
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 08:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a controller but no speakers o.o
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 08:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 decks is so last decade
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 08:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much asian in this pic
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 06:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice setup but it seems pretty spread out for live production </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 17:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :(
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 02:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "make you" as in give you away. If someone undercover is "made" it means he's compromised. Poor word choice in hindsight.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 20:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back in the late 2000's almost every phone had terrible interference and sometimes you'd be sitting in class (middle school at the time) and when a text came through the radio interference would make you and the teacher would come take your phone away.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 07:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually thought it was Felicia Day for a second... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 07:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yo man your wife looks like Felicia Day... lucky guy.
*edit...Forgot this was posted in a sub specifically for women, assuming now that OP is in fact Felicia Day lookalike..
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 10:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of "Sorry" a Wurmple I got from OT: Ashes Mom
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 20:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if this has already been posted and sorry for the quality of the video (There are newer uploads but the original is the only one with english subtitles - plus the shitty translation adds to the humour imo)

Anyways one of my earliest and best stoner memories is getting high for one of the first times and then stumbling across this video with a friend. Since we were both kinda nerdy we understood most of the references and sound clips, and it just made for an awesome random experience when I was young and new to the herb. Germans and I would get along apparently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lord of the Weed (German Parody) Subtitled (Part 1) First video I ever watched high - sealed the deal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 20:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 18:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright cheers mate!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 18:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooh yeah, that must have been it. I don't think you can get the primal evolutions in it and I had mine holding the mega stone. Want to try again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 17:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah not working :( says "There is a pokemon that cannot be traded in your party" even though it's not in my party in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 17:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here lets try again, if it doesn't work i'll just send over whatever. Weird though, I literally just traded it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 17:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird it's not letting me trade him all of the sudden...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 17:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Last one I need. Any particular mon you want? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 17:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 17:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 17:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it now, thanks for the offer though. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 17:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup! Any dex entries you need in return?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 17:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, thank you! :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 17:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> K sorry got distracted! Added you though.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 17:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> kk! Add you in a sec
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 16:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do people usually go about doing that? Just let me know when you've caught it on here so we can do the tradeback after I guess.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 16:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure man
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LF: Milotic, Huntail, Rhyperior, Jirachi, Glalie, Froslass Dex Entries FT: OR Legendaries, Starters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 16:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [tradeback] Yeah so i'm just looking for these last few to complete my dex. I've given up on a semi-living dex, just interested in having the little pokeball next to em' now.

LF: ~~Milotic~~, Huntail, ~~Rhyperior~~, ~~Jirchi~~, ~~Glalie~~, ~~Froslass~~

I have all of the OR exclusive legendaries and all of the starters available for dex entries. Thanks for the help! I could never have even got this far without this subreddit.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 08:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't but if you still do I definitely could. Also I hate to be petty but I accidentally traded you my everstone lol
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
