<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6188</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Colombian government is ready to consider a bilateral ceasefire with FARC rebels, even before the end of peace talks, the country's chief negotiator said in an interview released Sunday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 13:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis' visit to Andean nations puts leaders' environmental record under scrutiny. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 13:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis' visit to Andean nations puts leaders' environmental record under scrutiny. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 13:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stop buying in bulk: It ends up wasting food and money. Shop more frequently instead. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 13:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new bike sharing business will launch Tuesday when VeloGo rolls out its 300-bike fleet in central Ottawa and Gatineau. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 12:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for DredhackerD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 07:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for goldenicons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 07:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for gladysrau </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 07:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for Giuelith </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 07:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for jontena45 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 07:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americas next crippling drought: Why California is our apocalyptic future. If we stay on our current trajectory, we could be facing a 35-year "megadrought" by the end of the century. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 06:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Windsor is one of the only communities in Canada refusing to sign a non-disclosure agreement with rail companies in order to see a list of dangerous materials shipped through the city. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 06:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The National Congress of Australia's First Peoples says it will push to change a clause in the constitution that allows race discrimination. Indigenous leaders will meet with the Prime Minister and Opposition Leader in Sydney tomorrow, for talks on a referendum to change the constitution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 06:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The National Congress of Australia's First Peoples says it will push to change a clause in the constitution that allows race discrimination. Indigenous leaders will meet with the Prime Minister and Opposition Leader in Sydney tomorrow, for talks on a referendum to change the constitution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 06:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A growing number of Canadians are ditching their traditional television subscriptions, according to a new CBC research report. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 05:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In another surprise ruling, the Oklahoma State Supreme Court has decided that homeowners whose dwellings suffer damage due to fracking-related earthquakes can sue the companies responsible. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 04:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lac-Mgantic marches against crude oil returning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 04:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lac-Mgantic marches against crude oil returning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 04:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New coal plants 'most urgent' threat to the planet, warns OECD head: Governments urged to rethink plans for new coal-fired power plants as study estimates they will release more than 500bn tonnes of carbon dioxide by 2050. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 03:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drought-shamed celebs turn to 'Eco-Boasting': Kelly Osbourne and Cher are among those who post on social media about their recycled bath water or H20-efficient palm trees. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 03:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Royals set for Princess Charlotte christening: Surrounded by members of the Royal Family, William and Kate's second child will be baptised in Sandringham later today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 03:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lion facial-recognition debuts in Africa: The technology helps conservationists keep track of the big cats whereabouts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 02:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL July 4 is a triple holiday for Hawaii  1776, 1894, 1960. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 02:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> July 4 is a triple holiday for Hawaii  1776, 1894, 1960. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 17:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fifteen of the world's largest banks are under investigation on suspicion of rigging the Brazilian currency, antitrust watchdog Cade said on Thursday, the first such probe in one of the busiest foreign exchange markets globally. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 17:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The lifeless body of a middle-aged woman found in a home in the Beaches Friday night is being investigated as a suspicious death, Toronto Police said Saturday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 17:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dogs and drones are first line of defense for Florida's avocado crop. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 17:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dogs and drones are first line of defense for Florida's avocado crop. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 17:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tens of thousands of Hondurans took to the streets Friday night for the sixth consecutive week of protests to demand an independent investigation into government corruption and the resignation of President Juan Orlando Hernandez. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 17:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 'jellyfish invasion' story one newspaper didn't want you to read: TV presenter and naturalist Steve Backshall was asked by a British newspaper to write about the invasion of jellyfish this summer. But they didnt like what he had to say. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 17:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Audubon declares Everglades and Biscayne Bay bird havens. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 16:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New recycling method developed by scientists at Critical Materials Institute recovers valuable rare-earth magnetic material from manufacturing waste and creates useful magnets out of it. Efficient waste-recovery methods for rare-earth metals are one way to reduce demand for these limited resources. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 16:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Regular operations have resumed at Toronto Pearson International Airport, a day after a labour disruption stranded and delayed travellers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 16:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As wildfires continue to burn in Northern Saskatchewan and smoke hazes the skies, Manitoba health officials are warning those vulnerable to the smoke to keep an eye on forecasts and to stay indoors when air quality is bad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 16:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Critically acclaimed Manhattan restaurant Per Se will fork over $500,000 to settle claims it pocketed gratuities that should have gone to employees who worked at private-dining events. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 15:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Duwamish Tribes decades-long quest to gain federal recognition hit a massive roadblock this week, as the U.S. Department of Interior issued its final decision denying such recognition to the tribe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 15:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada's Environment Minister Leona Aglukkaq will sidestep Ontario Premier Kathleen Wynne's international climate change summit to be held next week in conjunction with the Pan Am Games. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 15:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada's Environment Minister Leona Aglukkaq will sidestep Ontario Premier Kathleen Wynne's international climate change summit to be held next week in conjunction with the Pan Am Games. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 15:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> July 4, 1865: First Independence Day after Civil War subdued as nation healed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 15:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Airports Commission has recommended a third runway at Heathrow, advising that this is the best way to expand the UK's aviation sector: others have expressed doubt over whether the UK can simultaneously cater for increased demand for flights and hit its legally binding emissions targets. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 14:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A number of flights in and out of Bali have been cancelled due to the ash threat from the Mount Raung volcano in Indonesia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 14:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Norways justice minister has announced plans to jail asylum seekers if they do not have a good enough reason to seek refuge in Norway. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 14:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for shahroz155 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 09:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for independencedayofusa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 09:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for readth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 09:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for lovemysmile26 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 09:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for rosetrot8 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 09:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aquariums in Japan that continue to use dolphins caught by the controversial drive hunt method in Taiji, Wakayama Prefecture, will be expelled from the Japanese Association of Zoos and Aquariums (JAZA). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 09:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan said on Saturday it would extend 750 billion yen in development aid to Mekong region countries, as China prepares to launch a new institutional lender seen as encroaching on the regional clout of Tokyo and ally Washington. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 09:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Scottish Human Rights Commission has reported concerns about Police Scotlands use of stop-and-search tactics to the United Nations, claiming the practice is still being carried out unlawfully. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 09:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Camping allowed at Ala Moana Beach Park for July 4 holiday: More than 50,000 people are expected to pack Ala Moana Beach Park this Saturday for Fourth of July celebrations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 08:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A woman, who four members of Britain's Royal Navy are accused of sexually assaulting, told a police investigator she fell unconscious following a night of drinking at military barracks near Halifax and woke up to find she was being raped while photos were snapped. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 08:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A woman, who four members of Britain's Royal Navy are accused of sexually assaulting, told a police investigator she fell unconscious following a night of drinking at military barracks near Halifax and woke up to find she was being raped while photos were snapped. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 08:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Alberta Energy Regulator has shut or partially shut 16 oil wells operated by Murphy Oil Company Ltd. for failing to comply with various rules: didnt meet the requirements to capture and flare, incinerate, or conserve all casing gas and tank-top gases. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 06:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where Alice in Wonderland, now 150 Years old, came from: Once upon a time, a shy Oxford don told a child named Alice about a girl who falls down a rabbit hole. The story immortalized them both. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 06:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mass arrests in The Hague as clashes over death in police custody continue: Officers arrest about 200 people for breaching ban on public assembly after fourth night of protests over death of Aruban tourist Mitch Henriquez. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 05:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The forests of Denver, Colo., are currently under attack by an invasive insect species from Asia. So what is the scientists plan to stop this assault on trees? Theyre going with the controversial move of introducing a second invasive species to destroy the first one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advertising coming to EV charging stations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The unsinkable Somatsumaru: After more than four years and 7,000 kilometres, a Japanese scallop fisherman prepares for a reunion with his boat in B.C. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The unsinkable Somatsumaru: After more than four years and 7,000 kilometres, a Japanese scallop fisherman prepares for a reunion with his boat in B.C. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Caught on camera: Woman loads truck with items from a Goodwill drop-off bin in Kunia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baltimore police are investigating a sign inside a police transport van that tells passengers, "Enjoy your ride, cuz we sure will!". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> International peasant group warn about 'Commercial Agroecology'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Mexican soldiers who killed 22 people last year in a town called Tlatlaya had been ordered by their superiors to take out criminals at night, according to military documents presented by a Mexican human rights group on Thursday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One New York bar has decided to underscore the unfairness of gender discrimination in pay by charging women customersjust 77 per cent of their bar tab. The difference equates with the gap between men and womens earnings in the US. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Rutte's government is lobbying for the creation of a UN tribunal, which would prosecute suspects in downing of the Malaysian plane, officials have said. Most of the 298 victims in last year's incident were Dutch. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fraud and reduced public confidence in the electoral system could result if voter information cards are used as valid ID at the polls, lawyers for the federal government argued in Canadian court Friday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Metro Vancouver has issued even more stringent water sprinkling regulations  saying residents can now only water once a week  and warn there could be a full ban later this month if the hot, dry weather continues. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RCMP members will stand sentry at Canada's National War Memorial on Sunday to mark the anniversary an officer who received the Victoria Cross for bravery during the South African War. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The normalization of relations between the United States and Cuba is likely to further North Koreas diplomatic isolation, experts say. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The normalization of relations between the United States and Cuba is likely to further North Koreas diplomatic isolation, experts say. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ecuador is one of the most biodiverse nations on earth, boasting the Amazon rainforest, Andean mountains and the Galapagos Islands, where Charles Darwin formulated his theory of evolution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for kingdomkids </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 16:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for yeuvayeu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 16:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for karthick07 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 16:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for sicana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 16:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for Roxie77 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 16:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The House of Councilors in Japan passed a bill into law on Friday allowing companies to obtain patents on inventions by their employees  more than a decade after Nobel Prize winner Shuji Nakamura launched a lawsuit against his company over the invention of the blue light-emitting diode. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 16:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California residents cut their water use by nearly 29 percent in May compared with the same month in 2013, the steepest reduction since officials began calling for people to conserve last year, according to figures the state released Wednesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 16:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New ground search and rescue standard will help make Canadians even safer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 16:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australia's packaging industry is considering cutting its recycling goal after an internal review found imports of plastics were far higher than previously thought, leaving waste reuse falling further shy of targets. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 16:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A group of Nobel Laureates have signed a declaration calling for urgent action on climate change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 15:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Metro Vancouver mayors and the B.C. government are in a standoff over whos responsible for funding transportation after the regions voters  many in transit-deficient areas south of the Fraser  roundly rejected a half-a-percentage-point sales tax hike to help pay for $7.5-billion 10-year plan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 14:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A national election is months away, but campaigning has already begun. While party leaders talk issues of economy and security, no one is asking the big question: what kind of society do we want? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 14:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girl Scouts reject anti-transgender gift, then triple the money. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 14:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The House of Councilors in Japan passed a bill into law on Friday allowing companies to obtain patents on inventions by their employees  more than a decade after Nobel Prize winner Shuji Nakamura launched a lawsuit against his company over the invention of the blue light-emitting diode. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 14:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A family recently discovered a large 2,000-year-old ritual bath underneath the floorboards of their Jerusalem home during a routine living room renovation, the Israel Antiquities Authority (IAA) announced today (July 1). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 13:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Latest figures released by the State Water Resources Control Board Wednesday show the City of San Diego reduced water consumption by 26 percent in May. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 13:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian lawmakers considering amending law that prohibits police officers from firing into crowds or at women: officers would be granted a presumption of trust and support meaning they would not face prosecution for any action taken while on duty as long as action was taken for a valid purpose. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 13:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese CO2 emissions headed to 2025 peak, may plateau much sooner. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 12:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan's major power firms are seeking to cut greenhouse gas emissions by more than a third by 2030 compared with 2013 levels by relying on nuclear power. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 05:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan's Federation of Electric Power Companies, whose members include the 10 main power monopolies, and 19 other power firms have set a target to curb carbon emissions per 1 kilowatt of power sold to around 0.37 kg in 2030, down 35 percent from 0.57 kg in 2013. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 05:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What BPs $18.7 billion spill settlement means for the environment: Its both bigger and not as big as it seems. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 05:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan and the United States will resume bilateral talks next week over the removal of tariffs and other trade barriers on agricultural and auto products under a multilateral Pacific Rim free trade initiative. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 05:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malaysian Prime Minister Najib Razak had close to US$700 million (448.55 million pounds) in deposits from troubled state fund 1MDB wired into his personal account. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 05:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dozens of non-native invasive plants and animals are established in British Columbia, arriving on the wind, in nursery plants, soil and on improperly cleaned boats. Invasives are more than a nuisance, costing millions in crop losses, ruined infrastructure and threatening natural biodiversity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 05:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dozens of non-native invasive plants and animals are established in British Columbia, arriving on the wind, in nursery plants, soil and on improperly cleaned boats. Invasives are more than a nuisance, costing millions in crop losses, ruined infrastructure and threatening natural biodiversity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 05:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lac-Mgantic Mayor Colette Roy-Laroche, sees hope in devastated community two years after tragedy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 05:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's surprised you the most about life in Hawaii in the past ten years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 05:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a *friend* who's been living off-island for pretty much the past ten years. Sure, he's popped back from time to time, every now and then, but as we all know, playing the tourist and actually living in Hawaii are two different things.

Life being what it is, my *friend* will be moving back to Oahu (not 100% official, but he's 80% of the way there, he's paddling his ass off and can see the Islands on the horizon!) and he'd like to know:

"If you left Hawaii in say, 2005, and came back today, what do you thing has changed the most about life in Hawaii?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Trek-style tricorders on their way to customers: After raising $2.7m on Kickstarter and wowing reviewers, the SCIO molecular sensor is finally set to ship. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 04:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A natural helium leak in Southern California reveals that the Newport-Inglewood fault is deeper than once thought  with a direct line from the Earth's surface to the planet's hot, dense mantle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 04:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A natural helium leak in Southern California reveals that the Newport-Inglewood fault is deeper than once thought  with a direct line from the Earth's surface to the planet's hot, dense mantle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 04:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Bureau of Land Management is seeking public input on a plan to control noxious weeds and invasive species in the Moab area. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 04:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The family of a California college student who died during a grueling fraternity hazing hike sued the organization and the school Wednesday, saying the young mans death was senseless and easily preventable. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 04:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> University of Hawaii officials offer no timeline for reopening the Mauna Kea summit road and visitor center, but some tour operators who rely on the mountain for business say that each day brings them closer to layoffs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 04:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The oceans are in serious trouble, and theres only one way to save them: Rapid, sustained emissions cuts are the last best hope for the world's marine ecosystems. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 03:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> America's BBQ grills create as much carbon as a big coal plant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 03:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wisconsin Governor Scott Walker on Wednesday signed a bill into law that bans the manufacturing and sale of personal care products containing tiny plastic beads that are known to pollute waterways. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 03:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japans population fell 271,058 in 2014, the biggest drop on record and the sixth straight year of decline, to 126.16 million, according to the internal affairs ministry: census released July 1 also showed that 25.90 percent of the population were 65 years old or older. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 03:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea, already one of the least-wired places in the world, appears to be cracking down on the use of the internet by even the small number of foreigners who can access it with relative freedom by blacklisting and blocking social media accounts or websites deemed to carry harmful content. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 03:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea, already one of the least-wired places in the world, appears to be cracking down on the use of the internet by even the small number of foreigners who can access it with relative freedom by blacklisting and blocking social media accounts or websites deemed to carry harmful content. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 03:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea, already one of the least-wired places in the world, appears to be cracking down on the use of the internet by even the small number of foreigners who can access it with relative freedom by blacklisting and blocking social media accounts or websites deemed to carry harmful content. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 03:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boy nets massive 600 lb. sturgeon in B.C.'s Fraser River: Rumours of monster fish that coaxed a New Jersey nine-year-old to B.C. proved more than just a few fish tales. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 03:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Health officials in Toronto have submitted a proposal to the Ontario government, asking that the province start covering the cost of travel vaccines. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 03:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for abuchi12345 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 01:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
