<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4448</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two words: mythical creatures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 06:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For people who have trouble describing/expressing their feelings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 06:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 05:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out the guy featured here: http://www.forevergeek.com/2014/10/wants-star-wars-greeting-cards-giveaway/.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 05:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rivotril FTW! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You never know when you'll be the one who needs to be on the receiving end of encouragement. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 11:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 03:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And when trolling was "just" trolling without everyone getting butthurt; also no real life tragedies as a result. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 03:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything you said, but for me, mainly because if I don't believe that everything is going to be okay, it will only be a downward spiral - and a fast one. I have to believe that it will be okay one way or another; and for some reason, that keeps me going. I don't know if that makes sense for you, but I hope it does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 03:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  'No one can make you feel inferior without your consent." - Eleanor Roosevelt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who pay for in-app purchases, don't feel bad if others call you a sucker. There's psychology to back you up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 03:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 03:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might as well check Twitter, while you're at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I guess we can say Stan Lee's Comikaze Expo was a big win. [Photos galore] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 03:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 04:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good Lord! Yup, it looks so real, I would freeze and not blink if I saw you. Maybe freak out some... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 04:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Swimming pool included, please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 04:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It *is* a good one. Just because I didn't recognize her (I'm really bad with faces anyway) doesn't take anything away from the piece.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 04:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've racked up so many geek creds, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 04:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's such a dearie. Maybe one day I'll get to meet him, so I better think of a pose now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 04:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you make it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 03:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe I don't recognize her, but the art is captivating nonetheless; and the quote, boom! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quotes from children's books that adults should never forget. Inspiring as it can get. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 03:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mythology inspires me, and if you feel the same, here's a quick resource on worldwide mythology. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 06:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 06:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just because you can! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You can still take the subway even with the ebola panic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 06:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 10:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'll just wait for it to come out on DVD; as you said, you're a horror junkie so it made it kinda worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 05:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a strong argument not to see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 05:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, The Conjuring was a total build up till the end; and I was terrified from the beginning not knowing what was going to happen. Annabelle will be "easier" watching then. Though I'm not a big fan of horror movies, I am starting to become more adventurous...is Annabelle worth a try? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On what we are and what we are... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 05:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure you think that I don't understand what you're going through, but I do. It's just that sometimes, our future is dictated by what we are, opposed to what we want. 
 Nicholas Sparks

I keep thinking about this. It's rather difficult to determine exactly what you want for the future in specific terms. Does that make sense? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 05:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is true and has been said many times. It's just not that easy, yes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 05:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talented, definitely. His performance in Eternal Sunshine... tore me up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Before there was The Conjuring, there was Annabelle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 05:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just found out about the Annabelle movie (the doll in The Conjuring) yesterday, which was released earlier this month.  The Conjuring scared the crap out of me, and they did a good job making Annabelle a mysteriously scary "character".

Anyone seen it? Recommendations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 05:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great. Let me know how that goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 05:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "An imaginative player could also weave their own stories between these layersmany hours were spent imagining stories taking place within and between these worlds."

Those good old days. Yes, my cities had stories in my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 06:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the Ithaka one. Beautifully poetic and applicable today. I'm keeping it in an open tab to read again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So Elon Musk is supposed to be Tony Stark in real life. All he needs now is Jarvis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 05:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 05:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only potential downside is that she'll never want to get out of it. Or maybe that's just me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not quite sure what to believe in anymore? There's this way of thinking called 'The Gittite Way'. What do you think about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 05:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 05:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I totally agree with that - it's the PC brigade that thinks of that implication, which I think is overreacting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supposedly the best movies for Halloween. Good list or not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 05:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 05:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL. Those Japanese games are the most hilarious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 05:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I regularly visit the first two sites; yes, they're great for inspiration and spark introspection. The third one is new to me. My thanks for sharing a new site I can read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Be all there... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 05:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw a quote from Jim Elliot, and I think some of you might find it timely:

"Wherever you are, be all there."

I know it's perfect for me, as my mind tends to wander even when I'm talking to someone else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Either you feel despair or feel hope for humanity with these photos. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 04:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 04:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oldie, but still one of the best articles on Comic Sans: http://buff.ly/1y8IN7c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 04:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coffee? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 14:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Khal Drogo looks like a brat. An adorable bunch this is, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 14:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you found it? Link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On self-compassion, or the lack thereof. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 14:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 14:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should have seen that coming. LOL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we autocorrect humanity? You tell me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 14:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 14:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It allows you to connect with someone at the most basic level. Over time it fosters a solid and positive relationship with others while also allowing you to grow as an individual."

I like how you closed the article, because it reminds me that I should not lock away my emphatic side, which I think I have been doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 14:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How come I didn't think of that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diner Dash for iOS is free but... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 06:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...the in-app purchases are getting in the way. Is it just me, or is it too much?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 06:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much sums it up for me. I've always treated work (freelance writing) as fun, so it doesn't bother me at all that I spend 10-12 hours a day working. I thought I had had a good balance, but am totally wrong. So point 2 ( Introduce non-computer centric activities) is what I am working on right now, which is quite difficult because my non-work activity is mainly playing mobile games and reading (still on a mobile device).

I'm working on taking a 1-hour work at least once a week, but I don't know if that's going to stick.

In any case, thanks for sharing this - very timely and apt reminder for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 05:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly what I was thinking. But what if "it" stains in the wrong place? Better to have more flowers cover that area... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 05:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just made me fall in love with her all over again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On burnout - hit me smack on the face. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 05:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burnout is nature's way of telling you, you've been going through the motions your soul has departed; you're a zombie, a member of the walking dead, a sleepwalker. False optimism is like administrating stimulants to an exhausted nervous system. 
 Sam Keen, Fire in the Belly: On Being a Man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 05:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! With more wild, curly hair, this would be even better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 05:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You sexy thing!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 05:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tissue paper. When you gotta go, you gotta go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 05:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now give him a cookie.
Seriously though, good for him. Even if he did have blueprints, not everyone can actually follow those to make something for real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much is an Apple I motherboard (working condition) worth? Guess. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 04:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 04:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys are lucky. I've had a MacBooks conk out on me a couple weeks after the warranty ran out. Apple wouldn't cover the expense (motherboard issues), so it's now a PlaceMac for plates when eating while watching TV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You'll want to go hike, even if you don't normally do, because these photos are seriously inspiring. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 04:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 04:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While the article is geared towards entrepreneurs, it does apply to everyone, doesn't it? Those "ancients" sure knew what they were talking about. I just wonder if they were able to apply their sayings to their own lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 07:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of people are making jokes, but this is pretty serious news. He has worked with many child actors and has a long list of credits according to imdb. This is going to shock and hurt a lot of people...

Yup. Even though it was "just" a character he was playing in 7th Heaven, that show was a huge thing for me as a child, and hearing this sort of thing is rather awful.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 07:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly my point. Is it? I certainly don't think so. Do you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 04:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell me about it. Those who get their beard hair yanked out: SHAVE ffs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Horrific is as horrific does. Or should it be horror? When Halloween meets Twitter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 04:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people just like to scare themselves and have a good laugh while at it. Check out horror movie characters on Twitter: http://socialnewsdaily.com/43865/5-horror-movie-characters-to-follow-on-twitter-this-halloween/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 04:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why bother when they crash Ferraris and Lamborghinis there all the time anyway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Predict the next [insert text] gate hashtag. Seriously, get a life or another phone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 04:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 04:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mesmerizing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And the PC brigade does it again, they made DC go on its knees, though. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 04:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 04:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure you have some pie, as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 04:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh. The truth does hurt, but this in-your-face article should wake some people up. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No need to wait for judgement day. It seems judgement is being dished out every day anyway. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 04:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 13:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suggest Vikings (pretty much the Nordic version of Spartacus in my opinion - wait there's no Spartacus on your list, so you may want to see that, too).

Then there's Salem, which is sometimes slow, but has its moments; and the premise might appeal to you.

Sleepy Hollow is pretty good, too.

For tech TV, try Silicon Valley for humor/caricature of well, Silicon Valley; and then there's Halt and Catch Fire (the start of personal computing in the 80s), which has a more serious tone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
