<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3651</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 17:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...but nobody lost quite as spectacularly as the sage grouse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 16:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH, I haven't read all 178 pages yet... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 16:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of those documents were actually declassified in 1977. Here you go: http://www.nytimes.com/packages/pdf/national/13inmate_ProjectMKULTRA.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 15:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm. Decent point. Maybe we should. If the private sector would agree to fund the research, I can definitely see why we'd be better off without linking science to government money.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 15:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For more than two weeks many American scientists couldnt share their findings with the international scientific community or participate in joint research projects abroad. Government shutdown not only stifled U.S. researchit set back our foreign collaborators, too.

That's why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 14:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Losing two weeks of data collection during a critical research period or two weeks of a key experiment that took months or years to set up will have repercussions for years

...And I thought shutting off the National Zoo's panda cam was bad.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 15:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's crazy that a guy like Culberson can be so into NASA and yet so ignorant when it comes to environmental science.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Paul Simon once invited a fan on stage to play "Duncan" at a concert, after she shouted from the audience that she had learned to play guitar on that song. She was nervous, but Simon kept saying "Go on, Go on!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 21:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 16:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like a story about gecko-inspired gloves comes out every month. But apparently this one actually works (!). Crazy video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 00:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how this impacts studies of video game violence. Does COD teach violence *faster* than, say a violent television show? Interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Science in a Republican Senate: "If Republicans win the Senate, James Inhofe will likely take charge of Environment and Public Works. That would be disastrous for science." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 17:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MIT scientists built microscopic tumbling beads that mimic bacteria to navigate cell surfaces. These early findings, which could have future applications in drug delivery, are published in Physics Review Letters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 16:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists uncover the origins of HIV in Africa and track the genetic differences that allowed the "M group" to spread farther and faster than any other strain. Their findings are published today in the journal Science. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 20:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 19:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We look at these old Archaean crusts, for instance, and we dont see the features that characterize subduction," Rey says.

It's a model that confirms physical evidence. Read the article (and the study, for that matter).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A tobacco plant has been genetically engineered with turbocharged photosynthetic enzymes from a bacteria. The first step toward 35-60% better GMO crop production  UK and American biologists report in the journal Nature. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 19:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have sequenced the genome of the coffee tree. After comparing coffee genes with those of other caffeine producers, they conclude that the ability to make caffeine arose independently at least twice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 20:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 18:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. The NASA Centennial Challenge might help them fix that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Solar-powered blimps can now carry satellites and telescopes above the clouds, into the stratosphere. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 15:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists publish thousands of blog posts and even start their own social network in China to find out firsthand how the government censors content online. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 20:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
