<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8471</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-23 23:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's even a mighty poem about these poor lads:

http://schoonerfare.com/schoonerfare/8886.html

POWDER MONKEY
Words and Music by Steve Romanoff
Copyright 1985

In days of old, so the story's told,
Of boys who went to sea,
All of seven, eight and nine years old they say,
To serve upon the warring ships, their captains and their kings,
To serve the purpose they still serve today,
To serve the purpose they still serve today.
To carry up the powder from the magazine below,
From a hold too dark and crowded for a man,
The called them Powder Monkies, every schoolchild ought to know,
The price we pay to keep a promised land,
The price we pay to keep a promised land.

Send for the Powder Monkey,
Send him down into the well,
Send for the Powder Monkey,
He'll fetch us a pail o' hell
To keep out cannon burnin'
He'll fall behind the gun,
We'll just send for a Powder Monkey,
'Cause there's more where he came from.

They come from the city sidewalks and
They come from the family farm,
To trust their fragile futures to the wind,
They come from the Land of Plenty,
Through the evergreens and corn,
With more to lose than all the angry men,
With more to lose than all the angry men.
Was it the hunger of the family,
Was it the anger of the street,
That drove a lonely child to Satan's door,
Where death was all but certain and
Damnation near complete,
Save all for the holy innocent ashore,
Save all the holy innocent ashore.

From high above the gun deck
Ring the orders of the realm,
To roll out a battle cadence on the drum,
As forward into darkness
Sail the cowards at the helm,
And they shoot the stars to see how far they've come,
Look at their sons to see how far they've come.
In days of old, so the story's told
Of boys who went to sea,
All of seven, eight and nine years old they say,
To serve upon the warring ships, their captains and their kings,
To serve the purpose they still serve today,
To serve the purpose they still serve today.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that there were boys as young as 8 called "Powder Monkeys" serving on the U.S.S. Constitution (and other battleships of The Age of Sail).  Their job was to run between cannon recoiling at speeds of 30-40mph and fetch bags of powder from below-decks to recharge them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-23 23:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-21 22:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just occurred to me: she could've save a lot of trouble if she'd checked the state of his equipment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-20 03:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're asking "did I mean 'compelling' instead of 'compulsive', then no, I meant 'compulsive'", as in this definition: http://www.thefreedictionary.com/compulsive "Caused or conditioned by compulsion or obsession."  This is clearly the work of an inspired and gifted madman.  But the work is compelling, too :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So last weekend I was at an art fair (ArtBeat in Davis Sq.) and saw this madman with the most astonishingly compulsive handmade Neo-Victorian Steam-Powered kinetic sculptures ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-20 03:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately I can't find any videos, or even a website, I'd just assumed that he'd have one that I could find later.  I think maybe he's too busy reinventing the past to upload stuff to youtube.  But I did find these pictures which of course do no justice to the experience of seeing them in action:

http://s579.photobucket.com/albums/ss237/Steamachine/?action=view current=DSCF2686-2.jpg
http://s579.photobucket.com/albums/ss237/Steamachine/?action=view current=DSCF2730.jpg
http://s579.photobucket.com/albums/ss237/Steamachine/?action=view current=DSCF0623.jpg newest=1

Oh, and it was a 90 degree day and I got to watch him tending his propane-powered steam generator! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-17 15:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I just wish his story was less believable.  I wish my government didn't have a history of abducting people and holding them in secret prisons.  I wish it didn't have a history of fabricating evidence as a pretext for an illegal war.  Maybe he's telling the truth, maybe not; I just wish I could say to myself, "No, my government would never do something like that." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-17 03:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you've clearly given up here.  You've got some preconceptions that you won't let go of, even in the face of viable alternatives.

After you've spent as much time researching homeschooling as I have researching public education, maybe we can talk.

Later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-16 21:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you have no research, just an anecdote.  I'd be more reassured if there weren't so many examples of people who didn't develop "thicker skin with everyone out there who tries to build themselves up by tearing you down", but ended up excluded from cliques, miserable, harassed, and sometimes bullied to the point of committing suicide: http://www.cbs3springfield.com/news/local/97624929.html

If public school is really supposed to teach people how to deal with that bullshit, it's not doing a great job.  In real life, you can in fact "bug out" if you decide you're not having a good time, you're not forced to hang out with jerks.

You should read some Gatto: http://www.informationliberation.com/?id=11375 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-16 15:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love for you to cite the research that demonstrates that "forced socialization" is "crucial in developing fully as an individual", or that the lack of it has damaged the thousands of kids who have been home-schooled.  Home-schooled kids have plenty of options for socialization that are much more similar to the "real world" than the highly controlled, age-separated prison-like structure of public school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-16 02:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should seriously consider home-schooling.  It sounds like your wife has the time/inclination, and he'll just be held back by public school.  As many posters have suggested, you shouldn't try to force-feed him a curriculum, but there's no reason not to keep presenting him with opportunities to grow and learn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-14 00:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess I was expecting something more Looney Tunes-ish, you know, with the barrel looking like a banana peel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-11 01:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe I'm bothering to post to this thread, but there is a scene in [The Last Emperor](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Last_Emperor) when the former emperor is in the re-education camp, and is spoken to about this very subject, i.e. when peeing in the middle of the night, he needs to make sure to hit the side of the bowl so as not to wake his cell-mates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-01 20:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this woman's husband dies.  She says to the undertaker, "All my life my husband has worn nothing but black suits.  Just once I'd like to see him in blue suit, but I don't have one.  Can you help me out?"  The undertaker says, "Sure."

A few days later she shows up at the viewing, and there's her husband laid out in a handsome blue suit.  She says to the undertaker, "Thank you so much!"  The undertaker says, "No problem.  As it happens, on the same day there was a woman who wanted her husband dressed in a black suit, but all she had was blue suits."  The woman said, "Oh, so you ... ", the undertaker says, "Yeah, I just switched the heads!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> " 'The black man has never had the right either to keep or bear arms,' and that, until he does, 'the work of the Abolitionists was not finished.' " </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-01 20:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More reddit juxtaposition fun (re: vaccinations). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-27 23:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-27 23:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Removal may be surgical, mechanical, chemical, autolytic (self-digestion), and by maggot therapy.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Debridement).  Yum.  Oh, and an awesome picture to boot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-27 19:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, [Google]( http://www.google.com/search?hl=en q=72! aq=f aqi=h1g10 aql= oq= gs_rfai=)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Possibly more Hidden Valley Ranch Dressing than could fit into the known universe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-27 19:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do so many job descriptions require "the ability to multi-task" when there's so much research showing that humans just aren't good at it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-26 15:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At 1,000 yards the Coriolis deflection is small but not necessarily trivial. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-25 16:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-10 00:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> motherfuckers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Like the attacks by Al Qaeda, the disaster in the Gulf was preceded by ample warnings  yet the administration had ignored them." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-10 00:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks, Internet, for ruining another innocent children's toy for me.  I present: The Elephantine Centipede Project! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-29 16:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-22 19:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While you're at it, compare the asterisks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-22 02:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then he said, "No, you don't understand, 'Chunks' is my dog!" ... oh wait a minute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only person on reddit who thinks reddit gradually diminishes a person's personality?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-21 04:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-19 03:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps a caption contest is in order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-19 03:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I guess it's her business and none of ours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me: "Looks like there's quite a story behind this."  My daughter: "No dad, there's really not" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-19 03:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-12 02:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "When I was a boy of 14, my father was so ignorant I could hardly stand to have the old man around. But when I got to be 21, I was astonished at how much the old man had learned in seven years."

-- Mark Twain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-11 03:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Them!](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0047573/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "More rogues than honest men find shelter under habeas corpus" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-13 15:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  -- Abraham Lincoln

Happy Presidents' Day Weekend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-11 01:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [How to Show off a Scar](http://basicinstructions.net/basic-instructions/2007/12/5/how-to-show-off-a-scar.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ooooh baby, now that we're in the mood, give me a second to put on my "English frock coat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-06 19:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Braille test for taxi drivers.  Really. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-06 17:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-05 03:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What has been seen cannot be unseen! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Survive a 35,000-Foot Fall - Plane Crash Survival Guide - Popular Mechanics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-02 15:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-01-31 23:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Obama Tells Nation He's going out for cigarettes](http://www.theonion.com/content/news/obama_tells_nation_hes_going_out) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know, I really enjoy Rock Paper Scissors, but I just can't handle all that complicated strategery. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-01-30 22:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
