<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3482</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 16:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pizza, my way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 15:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hiding all child comments helps a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 07:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care, I probably don't like them either.  To each his own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 07:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't, there are already too many people here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 07:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no meaning to life.  There is only enjoyment, experience and  opportunity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 07:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They openly admitted building 7 came down as a precaution, so it was planned.  In regards to flight 93, the official story is not believable.  You should add the "plane" at the Pentagon to your list.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 07:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would depend on whether or not your availability is limited because of them.  I was never limited because of them, so, they didn't come up in conversation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 06:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This will not qualify as sexual abuse.  It is, perhaps, abusive in a different way.  Seems he used it more as punishment from what you've posted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 06:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will shoot you in the face with a paintball gun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 06:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find a really good picture of them together and get a canvas made like [this](http://photos.walmart.com/walmart/storepage/storePageId=Wall+Art/).  They're fast and not expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 05:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know from personal experience that this works.  But keep adding the dark chocolate or else you'll end up a nasty slate gray like my aunt.  She's dead now but she's that same gray color. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 05:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instituted specific safety procedures in all departments and provided training and P.P.E. for each of us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 05:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 17 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 04:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 57, a grandmother and I vote yes.  There could come a time when it's the primary reason for electing a particular political candidate.  If they added legalization to their platform I believe they would win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 09:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orange </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 09:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Photobombing.  The best pics are ones you aren't expecting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 09:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nabisco, makers of Oreos.  Accept no substitute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 09:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think she must have got a great deal at the flea mall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 09:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You think that I am impoverishing myself withdrawing from men, but in my solitude I have woven for myself a silken web or chrysalis, and, nymph-like, shall ere long burst forth a more perfect creature, fitted for a higher society."



 [Henry David Thoreau, Journal, 8 February 1857] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 09:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Nanomedicine](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nanomedicine) 

and, 

[In March 2012 the Russian defense minister Anatoli Serdjukov said:
    The development of weaponry based on new physics principles; direct-energy weapons, geophysical weapons, wave-energy weapons, genetic weapons, psychotronic weapons, etc., is part of the state arms procurement program for 2011-2020"](http://www.globalresearch.ca/psychotronic-and-electromagnetic-weapons-remote-control-of-the-human-nervous-system/5319111). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 09:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about these: 

http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1k9ikg/what_is_the_most_paranormal_thing_that_has_ever/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 18:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't matter whether you believe it, recant it or not.  Things happen, always have happened and will continue to happen to people that can not be explained.  I stand by what I said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 16:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's called The Baader-Meinhof Phenomenon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 16:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt there are as many scientists in these threads as you might think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 16:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people think that, until something happens to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 16:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did the little girl wear a long dress with some ruffles and have long hair?  Did you ever see things dart about from the corner of your eye? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 09:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they left it out because you could still see the wires of the contortionist that did the scene.  They digitally removed it for the 2000 release. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 09:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I Spit on Your Grave is a controversial 1978 rape and revenge film. The film received a limited release, with a wider release in 1980. Prominent film critics condemned the film for its graphic violence and lengthy depictions of gang rape, and the motion picture remains controversial to this day. The film was named in 2010 one of Time's Top 10 Ridiculously Violent Movies.

Yeah, I'll pass on that one.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 07:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Transient lightheadedness where I fear I'm about to faint.  I sit down and hold my head down for a couple of minutes and feel alright again.  It's a drop in blood pressure, I suppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 07:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pride goes before destruction, a haughty spirit before a fall.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 06:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's enough to know you haven't developed any critical thinking skills yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 06:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bible doesn't equate killing germs to murder, anywhere.  What are you, 15? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 02:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the same way they can sense earthquakes, as something bad is about to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 02:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost every vegetable there is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 01:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Other humans.](http://www.womansday.com/life/10-worst-celebrity-plastic-surgery-mishaps-103522) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 01:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just click on your name.  It should show it all.  If you don't have Reddit Enhancement Suite you should get it.  It doesn't look like you're being downvoted as much as it does that you just aren't being upvoted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 23:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lived in Grants Pass for many years because I loved it so much.  It's a great place to raise a family.  The weather is great with no humidity.  Camping is fantastic and of course, the wild and scenic Rogue River.  And there are Dutch Bros. which I also like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 23:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a listing from Monster: http://jobs.monster.com/v-manufacturing-l-oregon.aspx.  That said, my favorite areas are Eugene, Grants Pass, Medford and Ashland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 23:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Governments don't usually get permission from citizens before starting a war.  Yes, it'll come one day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 23:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/TedTalks from the MindHub multi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 23:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, it'll get here soon enough on it's own, whether I want it to or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 23:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would depend entirely on the context of it's use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 23:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posts the begin with, "on the flip side" and "alternatively" don't do well in this subreddit.  Rephrase it as if it's an original question (and without those words), then post that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 23:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The info Snowden released directly affects millions of people worldwide.  What Manning released did not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 23:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's kind of a signal that the event is starting.  We don't care if others stand or not, same for the Pledge of Allegience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 22:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never thought I'd grow out of anything, so far I'm right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 22:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can be done, but it's more difficult and can get very expensive if there are two children.  Lots of housework, cooking, laundry, baths and such to do after you get home from work.  It's two jobs in one.  They're better off being raised by a loving parent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 21:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd rather your children be raised by strangers than you or your wife? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 21:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giardiniera has veggies and garlic where this this spread does not.  It's more or less just red and green pickled peppers chopped up into small pieces.  It's delicious.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 20:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haddon House Haogie Spread -hot chili peppers.  It's good on almost everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 19:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Derek Jeter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 19:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I had to just guess, it would be /r/WorldNews, /r/IAMA and /r/pics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 19:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cottage cheese with peaches and pepper.  It's like dessert to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 19:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Subreddits by subscribers](http://stattit.com/subreddits/by_subscribers/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 19:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of the works by [Leonid Afromov](http://makesomethingmondays.wordpress.com/2012/02/19/leonid-afremov-oil-painter/).

Example: http://i.imgur.com/4cFEgr2.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 18:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you go: http://img.weburbanist.com/wp-content/uploads/2007/12/strange-egg-shell-carving-art.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 18:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, just greet warmly and do not touch until you know for sure it's safe to do so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 18:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To a guy - Cialis.  To a woman - a box of tampons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 10:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it is, especially since Obama later described Putin as looking like a bored kid in the back of a classroom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 09:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My vote goes to the [Obama and Putin meeting](http://i.telegraph.co.uk/multimedia/archive/02637/obama-putin_2637988b.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 08:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.wisegeek.com/what-is-the-connection-between-endorphins-and-serotonin.htm

http://www.teachhealth.com/chemmess.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 07:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serotonin, Noradrenalin and Dopamine, the Happy Messengers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 07:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never thought it fair that only the rich can live in nice homes on the beach or in the most beautiful mountain-view areas.  Sometimes I think it would be more fair for people to switch every two years so we all get the opportunity to enjoy what the world has to offer sometime in our lives.  I don't care about their money, I would just like their scenic views. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 05:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://metareddit.com/stalk?user=hebeatsmymom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 05:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but, will they throw some cash at me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 05:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://metareddit.com/stalk?user=abbatron </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 05:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not want my tax dollars going to sterilize someone because they need the money.  This is a terrible idea, with the next step being forced sterilization.  Birth control, not sterilization, is the answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 05:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Done, now and forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 05:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is absolutely no need to surveille, record and store the personal and private business of hundreds of millions of citizens for the potential actions of a few.  There is no guarantee whatsoever that they will observe any citizens' rights now, or in the future.  They aren't observing the laws now and are lying to us about it.  If you trust what any politician tells you then you deserve what you will get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 23:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try /r/Netflix or /r/NetflixBestof for more responses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 17:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop reading the news.  Just stop yourself from receiving all the negative input that we're bombarded with every single day.  It can become overwhelming.  Take a vacation from it.  Knowing all the bad things going on in the world serves no practical use in our everyday lives.  Put yourself to some good use. Volunteer somewhere, take a class at college just because you like the subject. I don't know, just do some things that you enjoy.  Now, about death; it doesn't matter that we're all going to come to the end of this existence, what matters is that you're here now and you got the opportunity to live, love, do, go and just be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 05:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cluttered, but I know where everything is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 19:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Australia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 19:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Transporters to take me on my Mars vacation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 19:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, after while they get archived and you can no longer comment or vote on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 17:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't notice any change you aren't paying attention.  Was he the right choice?  No, he's a great disappointment, as was his predecessor.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 09:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moving air. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 09:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really have an opinion since I wear them too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 08:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He sits in his garage night after night waiting for me to come home.  As soon as I get out of my car he comes out into his yard and just watches me go inside, just like he does when I leave.  There's a window in his garage and I've peeked in when he's away.  On the table is a pair of binoculars.  This is why I have a 95 lb. German Shepard.  Just try to come inside creepy, white-haired blubber man, I double dare you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 08:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call the computer manufacturer customer support number and ask someone directly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 08:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  I don't commit any crimes so I shouldn't have to suffer any losses for those who do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 08:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could check in /r/conspiracydocumentary or /r/Documentaries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 08:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No jokes about anyone's miscarriage, abortion or sexual disfunction.  Far too personal to joke about around my family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 07:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try /r/Colorization or /r/ColorizationRequests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 06:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After spending two days writing a fantastic proposal where time was of the essence, I finished it and handed it my supervisor, sure we'd the contract because it was that good.  After hearing nothing for two days, I finally inquired about its' acceptance.  His response was, "Oh, yeah, that.  I haven't read it yet, but next time for sure." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 06:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James Rosen, chief Washington correspondent for Fox News spied on by the Justice Dept. here - http://www.slate.com/blogs/future_tense/2013/05/20/james_rosen_spied_on_his_case_is_even_worse_than_the_ap_reporters.html

CBS confirms reporter Sharyl Attkissons computer breached here - http://articles.washingtonpost.com/2013-06-14/lifestyle/39967790_1_cbs-news-computer-intruder

No, you aren't wrong, it isn't confirmed.  However, "the intrusions were detected in December while Attkisson was reporting almost exclusively on the governments response to the terrorist attacks on the U.S. compound in Benghazi, Libya.  Attkisson has previously investigated the Justice Departments gun-tracking operation known as Fast and Furious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 05:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember Sharyl Attkisson, the reporter who was spied on?  There's an abuse of the system by the Justice Dept. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 00:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the scariest thing I've read all day.  Remember, we are not all equal in intelligence, competence, critical thinking skills or emotional control.  No way would I join the local militia group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 00:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a right to know about any information collected on us, with or without our knowledge.  Maybe Snowden figured making this info available to us is what it was going to take to wake up America.  He was right, and I consider the release of this information, at great potential harm to himself, to be an act of honor on his part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 17:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This flag is not a cross that represents any of those things.  Your ideas do not relate to my statement at all. You can ascribe anything you want to them, it doesn't change their representation or use.  Perhaps you need to stop judging things based on centuries old practices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 16:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do church crosses in any way relate to this flag or have a bad history?  Church crosses represent belief in a religion, nothing else should be ascribed to them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 09:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if you've read this or not: http://boingboing.net/2013/08/08/lavabit-email-service-snowden.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 09:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd open 55 boxes because 56 is my lucky number and I want to keep it that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 09:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Click on the document #, you'll see why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 09:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some groups use the Southern Cross as one of the symbols associated with their organizations, including groups such as the Ku Klux Klan.  According to Civil War historian and native Southerner Shelby Foote, the flag traditionally represented the South's resistance to Northern political dominance; it became racially charged during the Civil Rights Movement of the 1950s and 1960s, when fighting against desegregation suddenly became the focal point of that resistance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 07:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might be the one you're looking for: http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1gpmc6/what_is_the_absolute_creepiest_yet_unexplained/.



You can also check through these: http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/search?q=unexplained restrict_sr=on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 06:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't have anything that requires a lot of time and maintenance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 06:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't make silly faces or your face will freeze that way.  I know from personal experience that this is true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 06:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course it isn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 06:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Illegal laughing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 06:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it won't happen until 2016.  Relax a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 06:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do this every year in Aug./Sept. but they're moving everything up these days to take advantage of end-of-year sales. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 05:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "For better or worse" was the promise you made.  Wait until things are better for her and then make an adjustment in your relationship.  Then you can both pursue your different paths. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 05:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, some days are harder than others, but through sheer determination I trudge along.  I know this is a temporary thing and something will change eventually.  I look forward to that, but luckily I'm a stubborn one and won't let it get the best of me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 05:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feelings of failure or inadequacy keep us looking back.  Why did they leave me?  Why wasn't I good enough?  What did I do wrong?  Could I have fixed it?  When in reality, it was probably nothing specific we did.  We're different people as we grow and change and aren't always suited to each other during certain phases of our lives.  There's probably something in a past relationship you miss and look to remind yourself of.  Just because we aren't with them doesn't mean the feelings disappeared.  It's ok to look back every now and then, just remember you're not who you used to be and have grown since then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 05:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Work part-time and do both.  That way you can raise a healthy family, have a happy marriage, keep your sanity and contribute in the workplace the way you want to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 05:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never, ever get personally or intimately involved with a coworker.  Just count it as illegal in your life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
