<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9737</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 04:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reasonable fuck-up here. Don't take it to heart, I'd be thinking the same thing if I were you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 04:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the cool kids do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your perfect morning? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 04:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone has one. Is it waking up alongside your SO, shooting up, having the perfect breakfast, smoking a cig, taking the time to put on your face, creeping on the neighbors, or maybe just listening to the outside world?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 21:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was really young when my grandma died, maybe 5 or 6. My memories of her are brief (her love of cheetah fashion, Sunday morning breakfast) and after she passed away my dad was able to grab her perfume bottle. Sixteen years later, I can't help but to unscrew the top and simply smell the perfume dispenser. Everything about her floods my senses for that brief moment. 
I'm scared one day there will be nothing left, so I never spray it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 21:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cookie dough. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 21:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasabi-laced hot wings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 21:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely not sarcasm.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 21:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait. Guys don't find that attractive?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 21:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do females always need a bathroom buddy? I'm pretty sure if one falls into the toilet the other isn't gonna do much to save her. Rapists don't appear in toilets, just peaceful creeps. And lastly, if it's just to talk about dumb stuff -like if he ACTUALLY meant to brush his hand against hers when reaching for their drink then neither if them should be dating anyway. Go get a hobby instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 21:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shards of glass sounds more appealing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 04:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dreams and screams?
Daddy Issues?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
