<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6584</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 18:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His atavistic position on abortion, which should be a fundamental right for all women. Please allow me to remind you of the right's incessant attacks on women's bodies.  Yes, he's a 'libertarian' but his positions on women are extreme right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 17:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, I don't understand your comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 17:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One year of mourning her father. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 17:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd have to search for the source (and can try if anyone is interested), but I recall that there is a tradition from Shakespeare and/or classical comedy, of having the characters group together in a happy ending.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 17:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernie over anyone.  Rand hates women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Classic performance of Don Giovanni - Furtwngler - 1954 Salzburg (English subtitles) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 20:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 21:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He gives new meaning to the phrase 'cheesehead'.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 20:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marital rape is still legal in India, and violence against women is horribly prevalent on a global level.  In Russia, before the revolution, it was common for the landowners (serf/slave owners) and the rich to sexually exploit serfs with no consequences.  Just read about Tchaikovsky's relationship with his servant. 
 
I would like to add that on reddit, in the comments, I observe so  much disrespect and violent thoughts directed at women that it is repulsive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 20:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention appalling grammar and diction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 20:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've observed a fashion for Americans to intentionally americanize foreign names, saying it's "pretentious" to pronounce them appropriately.  How sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arctic ice melt to release 1 trillion pieces of plastic into sea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 20:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 19:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great!  I was unaware of thorium's potential as an energy source.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
