<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4487</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greenspan: Gold Price Will Rise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 23:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bootstrap 3.3.0 released and Bootstrap 4 info </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 22:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2014 Libertads, $19.90 (right now), any quantity at silver.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 20:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> APMEX has Johnson Matthey 10 oz bars for $186 (ends midnight 10/30) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 15:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys think of this safe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 03:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posting for a friend because he's new to reddit and doesn't have enough karma to get his questions listed here...I'm acting as a proxy here.

[What do you guys think of this safe](http://portland.craigslist.org/yam/bfs/4733117842.html)? He's looking for a safe to store precious metals in, possibly up to $40k. He doesn't have the metal yet, he's just looking to get into metals for some diversification. Step 1 is getting a safe.

From his research, here are a couple links to the current model # (SB02):

* [http://beseenontheinternet.com/vasafeandlock/centurion_sb02.htm](http://beseenontheinternet.com/vasafeandlock/centurion_sb02.htm)
* [http://easternsecuritysafe.com/Products/homesafes/liberty.htm](http://easternsecuritysafe.com/Products/homesafes/liberty.htm)

Additional info he gathered from the seller:

*from the back plate  MDL# CNSB02.   There is a plate inside the door that reads: passed 2hr, 1000degree, heat endurance test, drop test   reheating test   gives the test standards #. I couldn't find a weight tag but I have moved it once-my best guess is about 250# -300#.  It is a great safe I bought new in 1995 or 96 to keep papers, etc, in.*

Neither of us are terribly knowledgeable about safes and what would be a good one for his needs so I'm wondering what you experts think of this one.  We both look on craigslist regularly but pickings (for what we think he needs) seems pretty slim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are you looking for a tube to hold 20 (mint roll) Perth Lunar Series II coins? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 03:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I recently ordered 20 Perth Lunar II Series but they didn't come in the mint roll](http://www.reddit.com/r/Silverbugs/comments/2jmme3/would_this_bother_anyone_else/). If you ever find yourself in this situation (and you're annoyed by the stacking inconvenience), or you just want to tube up some loose Lunars you might have, this thread is for you.

What you're looking for are **"I" Cap-Tube Holders**. The Lunar capsules are a little loose in these tubes, but it isn't bad or annoying, IMO. It's certainly more convenient for me to have them tubed than loose coins.

You can [fit 15 Lunars right up to the rim of the tube](http://i.imgur.com/gQJuAUW.jpg). With the cap on, it seals fine. 

You can also easily [cut the tubes down so you can store 10 in a tube](http://i.imgur.com/EUjj3eJ.jpg).

I picked these tubes up on ebay from the seller **onfireguy**, I'm not sure if ebay links are allowed here but you can just do a google search for "onfireguy ebay" and it'll come up as the #1 result. Ships out very fast. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dropcap.js - Beautiful CSS drop caps made easy (interactive demo) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 20:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reqres - a hosted REST-API for testing your front-end against </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 16:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which tube to fit 20 Lunar Series II? Didn't get a mint roll when I recently ordered 20. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 05:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buy gold or silver, what do you think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 00:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The gold to silver ratio is approximately 71:1.

I've had gold on my end-of-year goals but with the ratio it seems it's a better time to buy silver.

Anyone else in the same boat?  What are you doing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is the 1 oz Gold Lunar Year of the Snake the cheapest of Series I? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 00:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The 1 oz series on APMEX](http://www.apmex.com/category/14500/gold-lunar-series-1-1996-2007/all?f_productoz=1+oz page=1)

* Horse @ $1,538.90 mintage 30k
* Snake @ $1,363.90 mintage 30k

The rest have lower mintages so I can understand the fluctuation in prices there.

I've also noticed this [Series II Snake for $1314 over at Bullion Exchanges](http://bullionexchanges.com/2013-1-oz-gold-lunar-year-of-the-snake-perth-mint-series-ii-coin-in-capsule.html). Great deal as it's [$1414 at APMEX](http://www.apmex.com/product/71321/2013-1-oz-gold-lunar-year-of-the-snake-bu-series-ii).

What do you guys think?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fukushima radiation nearing West Coast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 23:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would this bother anyone else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 20:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you order [20 Lunar Snakes, which are advertised as 20 per inner pack](http://www.apmex.com/product/71339/2013-1-oz-silver-australian-year-of-the-snake-bu) and [they come like this](http://i.imgur.com/4s2pbVA.jpg).

I somewhat recently ordered 25 of the Canadian Grizzlies, I believe it was and they didn't come tubed properly, either.  I had to contact them to send out a tube and then remind them it should be a wildlife (blue) tube.

I store silver in a safe deposit box so stacking efficiency is pretty important to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sublime Text Book - speed up development, optimize workflows, become a better developer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 19:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first primary silver miner in the industry just announced that it suspended sales of silver during the 3rd quarter due to the low market price of silver </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 04:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SD Bullion has 2015 Koalas on pre-sale (not shipping before Nov 14th) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 03:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CSS Only iPhone 6 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 16:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are Primary Silver Producers Making Money At The Current Silver Price? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 02:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clippy - tool for generating CSS clip-paths </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 22:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys, stop writing code, start dragging it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 16:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know where I can get my rain water tested? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 03:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would like to send a sample of rain water off to be tested to see what sort of heavy metals it contains.  Has anyone ever done this or know of a lab that can do this?

Obviously I'm interested in the geoengineering aspect of testing the water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wholesale Coins Direct 1 oz Lunar Goats are up to $28/29 now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 03:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CSS Star Wars characters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 20:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Front-end performance heatmap bookmarklet - heatmap of resources loaded in the browser using the Resource Timing API </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 17:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CSS Walter White </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 17:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tamper - locally edit files served from the web, directly from devtools (chrome extension, capture and edit HTTP requests) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 16:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question for those who have recently purchased from Wholesale Coins Direct and paid via credit card </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 04:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their current [terms and conditions](http://pastebin.com/Dt3LzDum) state:

*Credit card or electronic check (ACH) orders for any amounts are processed through security screening.  Failure to provide accurate Social Security Number (SSN) or Driver License information may subject your order to additional documentation or screening and, on occasion, require you to pay via bank wire in order to complete the transaction.  Therefore, we recommend paying by bank wire to guarantee timely completion and delivery of your order.*

I have zero interest in giving them my SSN or driver's license number after giving them my credit card. For those who have recently ordered from them via credit card, were you asked to provide SSN or drivers license info? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fed 'doing everything it can' to suppress gold price - Hot economic news items from top-rated market timer for precious metals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 19:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Easiest way to invest in (falling) price of oil? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 21:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of my portfolio is precious metals but I acquire physical there (no paper).  What is the easiest way to invest in the falling price of oil? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Artist uses hexadecimal converter to intentionally twist and corrupt his photos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 20:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NimbusFoundry - a framework for building front end collaborative apps (Collaborative apps on Google) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 17:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A List a Fart  For people who make websites that stink </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 22:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LetterBolt - the animated JavaScript font </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 19:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Grid Uses Artificial Intelligence To Design Your Websites For You </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 18:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DevTools Tips - a curated list of Chrome DevTools tips and tricks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 16:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Email from Provident's CEO re: shipping delay on RCM 10 oz bars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 00:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Thanks for your recent order and your interest in Provident Metals.  We do sincerely appreciate the trust you've shown in us by ordering some precious metals from us.*

*I just wanted to reach out to you in regards to your recent order of RCM 10 ounce silver bars.  We were supposed to receive a delivery of these bars from the Royal Canadian Mint on September 29th.  Then the date changed to October 2nd.  And then to October 6th.  And then October 7th.  And finally, it looks like they're going to be here tomorrow.  In any case, once they arrive, we will stop everything else we're doing and we will ship out the 10 ounce RCM bars.  As an apology for this unforeseen delay, I will personally include a half ounce of silver in your order and give you free shipping on your next order.  To use your free shipping offer, please call in to one of our traders when you place your order.*

*Again, my sincerest apologies for any inconvenience this has been to you.*

*Kindest regards,*
*Joe*

I honestly don't care about the 1/2 ounce of silver or free shipping (I really don't).  What I really care about is the explanation.

It would have been nicer if they sent it *before* I inquired about the shipping delay and of course it would have been even nicer if, when I inquired, I was told this instead of ["We have plenty in stock"](http://www.reddit.com/r/Silverbugs/comments/2i93su/interesting_email_from_provident_regarding/). But I probably confused their customer service folks when I asked "Do you currently have the RCM 10 oz bar in stock? If not, when do you expect a new shipment?"

But hey, kudos to Joe Merrick, Provident's President/CEO for being upfront about the situation.

Can't wait for that magnet.

**Update** My order finally shipped out on 10-10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FlexSense: A Transparent Self-Sensing Deformable Surface (video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 17:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone here in mining stocks? Interesting article re: Coeur Mining, with other companies declines mentioned at bottom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 21:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interesting email from Provident regarding shipping delay (RCM 10 oz bar related) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 06:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From Provident's automated email that goes out with order status:

*Your order is in the queue to be picked and shipped. Nearly 90% of orders are shipped within 3 business days after confirmed payment and nearly 98% of orders are shipped within 5 business days.*

I rolled into that lucky 2% today (5 days past "confirmed payment") and inquired about when they think my order might ship out.  This response came in this evening:

*We apologize for the delay. You ordered a very popular RCM 10 oz. bar. We do not like seeing orders going beyond the 5 business days. I have put a free rush on your order, which will push your order to the front of the batch with the other orders that have a rush. We are doing our best to get these products out to you as quickly as possible.*

So it sounds like they don't have any RCM 10 oz bars in stock [even though they're advertised as being in stock](http://www.providentmetals.com/10-ounce-rcm-royal-canadian-mint-9999-silver-bar.html).

So if anyone has ordered any RCM 10 oz bars recently, you might be seeing a shipping delay from Provident.

Pretty disappointing, but on the bright side I'm sure they'll throw in a magnet with my order.

**Update:** When their email came in, I replied asking if they had the bars in stock.  This was their reply that came in last night:

*We have plenty in stock. We are shipping out orders in the order they were placed into confirmed payment. We expect your order to ship early next week going off of the number of orders in front of your order.*

I ordered two bars, still seems odd why there would be this big shipping delay if they have plenty in stock. I mean how long does it take to pick and pack an order from their warehouse? On the price dip I'm sure their orders are up and maybe that's coupled with staffing issues, who knows...Still seems a bit fishy to me.

I also love the fact they gave me a "free rush" which costs nothing. I mean, you can't buy a rush order.  Not free shipping (credit) for the next order, a "free rush" in the queue, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Technical Trading: Charts Don't Lie, No Sign Of A Bottom In Silver </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 02:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> juliusjs - a speech recognition library for the web (port of Julius to JavaScript) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 16:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is *not* buying now (spot currently @ $16.73)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 16:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spot is $16.73 as I type this.  Who is not buying now and why? Are you worried it's going to drop to $X? Are you a short-time flipper?  What's your silver strategy and your buying psychology/rationale today? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JPMorgan hack exposed data of 83 million, among biggest breaches in history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 05:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not to be outdone by catnamedbacon...I took advantage of the dip </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 05:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GoldenLayout - the ultimate web app layout manager </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 16:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberty Cabins (northern California, Oregon border) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 21:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> gifshot - JavaScript library that can create animated GIFs from media streams, videos, or images </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 20:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mozilla Brick - a collection of UI components designed for the easy and quick building of web application UIs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 18:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Provident Prospector 1 oz Silver Round </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 22:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Truffle/JS, an Oracle JavaScript engine with high performance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 16:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Rarities 10 oz bars, let me show them to you. These are neat, APMEX has 5 left </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 23:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least it wasn't another god damned refrigerator magnet (then I opened the manilla envelope) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 23:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ship Renderer  WebGL, JS, 3D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 16:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gold price seen near tipping point for mine cuts, closures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 04:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to ID this American Security upright safe. Any ideas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 21:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Posting this for a friend, he's new to Reddit and doesn't have enough karma to get this posted here*

http://salem.craigslist.org/spo/4676467207.html

I'm looking at this safe which is somewhat local to me (about an hour away) and I'm trying to determine the make model number so I can do some online research. The point is to determine whether it's worth the trip to go look at beforehand, as it's "somewhat" local to me. If it were in the same town, I'd just go take a look.

When I asked the seller if he knew the make/model #, he replied with:

"The # on this safe is a sticker. It reads 702 in big bold numbers and 10247 in smaller font."

I don't seem to be having much luck via google.

Does anyone have any idea what make/model this might be? I was hoping for a serial # as I imagine if I called American Security with that, they would have a record of what type of safe. Seller can't seem to locate any other markings.

*These are the only other identifying photos he could get from the seller:*

*http://imgur.com/a/RXxgy*

*The safe is reportedly 15-20 years old.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 100,000 Digitized Art History Materials from the Getty Research Institute Now Available </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 16:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> jQuery.com compromised to serve malware </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 18:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> jQuery.com compromised to serve malware </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 18:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Webknife - web presentation framework for rapid user interface design on the client side (anyone use this?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 16:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone else noticed that we're where we were back in August of 2010 right before the massive run up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 19:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/pdELfLc.jpg

For those that were in the game back then, how was the market different back in 2010/2011? Gold and silver have made 3 recent attempts to run up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 18 CSS Effect Libraries for Creating Beautiful Animations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 15:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newbie web-designers mistakes from programmer point of view </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 15:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PathFinding.js </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 15:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $18 silver is here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 16:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Johnson Matthey kilo bar, let me show it to you </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 03:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/YMEEA

[And JM Bullion has them for $632 with free shipping](http://www.jmbullion.com/1-kilogram-johnson-matthey-silver-bar/). Cool piece to add if you're looking for a kilo - great time to pick one up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Built-in Browser Support for Responsive Images - the picture element is now available in Chrome 38 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 00:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does pay by ACH work with Scottsdale? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 05:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing some window shopping at Scottsdale for a possible purchase on the dip.  I have a loaded up shopping cart and I'm in the checkout section now.

The payment method is either:

* Bank wire transfer
* ACH (electronic funds transfer)

I have the ACH selected but it isn't giving me any info for what that ACH info is for paying online.

I'm looking at a screen with my shipping address, payment method, order summary and a "submit order" button.  I don't really want to just blindly click the submit order button.

Has anyone gone through this?  How does the ACH option work through their shopping cart? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Learning Gulp - getting started with the frontend factory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 17:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The dotJS Prize is a $10,000 award to the most innovative frontend   backend open source projects written in JavaScript </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 16:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> fartscroll.js - everyone farts. And now your web pages can too </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 16:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Firefox Add-on Enables Web Development Across Browsers and Devices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 21:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Sunshine Mint Buffalos with Security Mint Mark @ JM Bullion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 18:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dimensions - Chrome Browser Extension. Measure everything you see in the browser </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 17:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The worst fucking thing about this $18.63 spot price right now... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 16:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being tapped out in the silver fund$ department.  Oh sure, I could reach into savings and place some orders, but the reason I can reach into savings and place some orders is because I have financial discipline.

Please....Spot price, for the love of God, please keep going lower through next payday.  And you know what I want you to do?  Stay there for awhile. Think about renting a nice condo with a view.  Hang out a while, I'm a great neighbor, we can do brunch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> devices.css - pure CSS phones and tablets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 16:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The all-in cost of producing an ounce of gold dropped to $1,331 oz (spot is currently at $1,255) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 02:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Responsive Web Design with DevTools' Device Mode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 16:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has Provident switched to shipping via UPS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 01:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cuz I just received a shipping notification indicating UPS whereas every other order I've done has been via USPS.  It isn't like my order is really large, either, it would definitely fit in a medium flat rate USPS box.

I hate UPS deliveries, they are incredibly inconvenient for me to have to go pick those up.

**Update**: Tracking number shows delivery this Friday.  UPS.com shows the customer center isn't available for a Saturday pickup and they're only open for a pickup M-F until 6pm.  I can't make this time as the god damned customer center is over 20 miles away (one way). No way I'd make it in rush hour traffic. This means I have to take Friday off to sign for my package.  Thanks Provident.  So now every order I make through them I need to contact them beforehand to find out if they can ship USPS.  Looks like I'm done with Provident. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holy shit, spot is up to almost $24 oz this morning!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 17:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Nah, I'm just fucking with you, it just dropped under $19](http://i.imgur.com/YXE0mWP.jpg)

[I picked up a tube of these 1 oz Heraeus, they're hot!](http://www.providentmetals.com/heraeus-1-oz-silver-round.html)

What are you guys ordering? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is APMEX's account/login/cart section jacked up for anyone else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 19:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tossed some stuff into my cart last night, wanted to do an order this morning so I can send it out certified mail today (like within the hour).  Not getting any styling in my shopping cart, just the html output.

Anyone else getting the same thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Introducing the World's First National Digital Currency (backed by liquid assets). Ecuador will begin distributing in December </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 17:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Introducing AM - Attribute Modules for CSS - Moving beyond class-based styling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 17:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone ever purchase from Midwest Bullion Exchange (privatebullion.com)? Minnetonka, MN </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 22:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silverbug search for "Midwest Bullion Exchange" and "privatebullion.com" aren't showing any results.

A [tube of 2014 Kooks](https://www.privatebullion.com/product/2014-1-oz-silver-kookaburra/) (20 count @ $25.69 per coin) can be had for $528.80 shipped. 

They look to take personal checks as well, which is all I do (for the $ discount).

Anyone done business with these guys before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silver is approaching the $18 range (I saw spot go so far as $19.02 about 30 minutes ago). Any higher premium items you can recommend on the dip? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 21:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wondering if prices on higher premium items (like Lunar Series, for example) would be good to pick up on the dip, or if those prices are remaining pretty steady.

What do you guys think?  What are some non-generic deals out there now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shop at Home Depot? Use a credit/debit card to pay? Looks like there's been a pretty huge breach </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 16:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Nearly All U.S. Home Depot Stores Hit By Credit Card Theft](http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/09/data-nearly-all-u-s-home-depot-stores-hit/)

[Here](http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/hd_rescator_zips.txt) is a list of all unique ZIP codes represented in more than 3,000 debit and credit cards currently for sale.

[Here](http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/hd_zips.txt) is a list of all unique Home Depot ZIP codes.

My Home Depot is on the list, yours probably is, too.  Might want to watch your accounts/request new cards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone recently order from the US Mint? Who was your carrier and what was your shipping method (standard/expedited)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 17:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at picking up a couple ATB 2014-P coins.  US Mint doesn't seem to indicate which carrier they use to ship, just that:

The United States Mint selects from a number of carriers to deliver your package.

It looks like I'm getting the expedited shipping (because I am such a high roller):

Orders with Merchandise valued at $300 or more with a standard delivery option chosen will receive a complimentary upgrade to Expedited Shipping.

I really would like this to come USPS as that is so much more convenient for me. Anyone have any recent ordering experience from the US Mint? What carrier was used and what was the shipping method? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gold/silver are down this morning ($1268/$19.22) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 15:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have anything sitting in shopping carts, now would be a good time to buy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Origami Unicorn Done in Pure CSS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 17:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perth Mint Lunar Series roll count - 20 per roll? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 05:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to pick up a roll of the 1 oz silver goats but I want to get them in the shrinkwrap roll.  I'm having a hard time finding the actual count for those rolls.  It looks to be 20, but can someone confirm this?

If I order 20, will I get the shrinkwrap roll?  I really want that for stacking purposes because it would just be easier.  I really don't want to end up with 20 loose capsules.

Anyone order any Lunar Series in those shrinkwrap rolls?  Is the count 20? None of the vendors on my list seem to really be indicating (like they do with tube count). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holla back 100 oz bar playas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 03:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who are the 100 oz bar playas here?  Why did you buy a 100 oz bar (or bar**s**, Mr. Fancypants)?  What are your thoughts on this today seeing as 100 oz bars can be had for $2k...Would you do it all over again or take that 2k and spread it around?  If the latter, what would you drop that 2k on?

If you once had your 100 oz big boy pants and sold, how hard was it?  Where did you end up selling? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts on the 2014 1 oz Gold Howling Wolf | Call of the Wild series? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 02:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.apmex.com/product/81490/2014-1-oz-gold-canadian-howling-wolf-99999-fine

The howling wolf is the **first release** in the Royal Canadian Mint's new 'Call of the Wild' series. 

What do you all think of this -vs- a gold eagle/buffalo/maple/krug/et al? I'd like to get an ounce of gold by years end and I've been spying this.  Seems like there might be some increased premium/collector value over time compared to standard 1 oz coins?

I'm thinking start with this one and hopefully keep up with the other releases...A save the whales, collect the whole set thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Single Div </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 00:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Colors of Motion - color use in films </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 16:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you all seen the new Johnson Matthey kilo bars? Well, have you??? Currently $653 @ JMB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 15:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a tube of 2012 1 oz Canadian Moose (wildlife series). Anyone know vendors who have them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 03:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From my regular vendor list, Provident has them. APMEX and Monarch have spotted ones, though Monarch doesn't have enough for a tube.  I figure if I'm going to get them (they have a higher premium) might as well spend a little more to get higher quality.  Anyone know of any other online vendors (that take personal checks) that have tubes of 2012 1 oz Canadian Moose? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BareKit - a Bare Minimum Responsive Framework (comes with zero styling) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 22:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do (online) bullion dealers do to ensure silver they buy from private individuals is legit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 17:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not talking about new/mint-direct stuff. If you or I were to sell a couple 10 oz bars, a tube of generics or gov-backed coins, *whatever*, to APMEX, Provident, JM Bullion, Monarch, et al...What do they do to verify that silver before reselling it?

In other words, when you or I buy that "secondary market" silver, how do we know it's been vetted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chrome's Device Mode and Mobile Emulation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 16:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else having problems logging into Provident Metals? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 02:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http site is up (shop), but https (user account) seems to be hosed at the moment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will The Fed Bring Silver Further Down? FOMC minutes to be released tomorrow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 23:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who's riding the palladium train? It's at a 13-year high </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 21:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spot price shenanigans at SD Bullion? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 16:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the moment, spot is:

* $19.46 via [silverprice.org](http://www.silverprice.org) (this is the main site I use for spot price)
* $19.44 via http://www.monex.com/liveprices/

[SD Bullion](http://sdbullion.com/) is currently listing spot at $19.70 (and I've refreshed a couple times)?  It isn't like spot is spiking up over $19.50, either and I'm just seeing a delay in the price. 

Wassup with dat? Are vendors listing spot at spot + X? I noticed when I purchased from Monarch they seemed to always list spot around 4 cents over what I was seeing elsewhere.

Just so you know I'm not bullshitting, [here's a cropped down screenshot of two separate browsers, refreshed at 7:28am](http://i.imgur.com/puGOW4r.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who sold back in 2011 when silver was upwards of $50 oz? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 17:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * What was spot when you sold?
* How much did you get per oz?
* Was it difficult to sell?
* How many ounces did you sell?
* What in particular did you sell (i.e., generics, bars, gov-issued coins, etc)?
* What sold for the most?
* What sold for the least?
* Was any item refused (i.e., a 100 oz bar)?
* Where did you end up selling?

Curious what some real-world selling experiences were back around the recent peak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Six Meanings Behind the World Trade Centers New Logo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 16:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pure CSS 3D Polyhedrons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 18:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We're still sub $20/oz and the new "London Silver Price" launches this Friday...Thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 00:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Famo.us raises $25M to double down on its innovative JavaScript framework </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 19:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yo Bootstrap - a list of free Bootstrap templates from across the web </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 16:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tic-Tac-Toe made in pure CSS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 16:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Ultimate List of UX Design and Development Resources </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 23:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Create an off canvas navigation menu with CSS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 17:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Open Source Email Templates (responsive) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 23:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Does Web Page Speed Affect Conversions? If you care about conversions, you should care how fast your pages load </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 19:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Responsive v3 Released - lightweight HTML, SASS, CSS, and JavaScript framework for building responsive websites (anyone ever use?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 16:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> goldprice.com - great silver and gold comparison site I just found </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 03:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many of you are offering drone video on a map? Because you can totally do that now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 23:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chrome extension LessAlert - Set price alerts for product pages, receive notifications when product price is less than your alert price </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 19:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [LessAlert](https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/lessalert/opmiobcflgbbjnfamccilggghdkhfbbe?hl=en-US)

Don't know if this will interest many here...If you're looking for a particular item at a particular price, you might want to give this Chrome extension a whirl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VIDE - easy as hell jQuery plugin for video backgrounds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 19:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NotepadConf - see the latest technological advancements in plaintext editing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 17:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most super basic responsive video background ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 16:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The domain name extension .WTF is available today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 21:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 30 Free Responsive HTML5 CSS3 Templates for Designers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 20:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spot just dropped under $20 (currently at $19.86) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 16:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SD Bullion delivers again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 01:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't see mention of [SD Bullion](http://sdbullion.com/) much here, wanted to give them some praise.

My second order with them came in today, I ordered the [new 10 oz RCM bar](http://sdbullion.com/silver/silver-bars/weight-10-oz/10-oz-rcm-silver-bar-9999-fine-reeded-edge-serial-number) which they're selling for $214 right now.

Let me break down the time frame on the order:

* Placed my order the evening of July 24
* Mailed out **personal check** on July 25
* My cashed/processed check showed up in my online bank account on July 28th
* They sent my "order shipped" notification on August 1st
* Delivered on August 4th

This was advertised as a pre-order that would not ship before August 14th as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need a tube to put my family of Koalas in </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 03:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking to order a full set of Koalas from APMEX tonight.  They look to run from 2007-2014 and all years look to be in stock.  Each Koala detail page indicates they're in capsules and have a diameter of 40.6 mm.

I'm assuming all the diameters listed are really the capsule's diameter?  I ask because I'm looking for a tube to put them in.

I don't really like [the tube APMEX has for sale that says it's fits 40 mm](http://www.apmex.com/product/15341/sure-safe-silver-coin-container) (though it doesn't say 40.6mm).

I like [the tube Provident has for sale](http://www.providentmetals.com/cap-tube-for-airtite-coin-holders.html) which says it fits 40.6 mm.

The Provident one should work out, yes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interesting how prices can vary from one vendor to the other </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 00:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monarch has 10 oz hand poured at $210 (though their shipping is a little high) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 16:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think of Rhodium? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 04:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last Chance For $2.29 over spot Silver Eagles, Ends Today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 21:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's a tiny house for sale near me (though not on a trailer) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 18:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 26 Eye-Tracking Heatmaps Reveal Where People Really Look </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 16:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rebound - a simple library that models Spring dynamics for the purpose of driving physical animations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 20:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perth Mint Year of the Horse @ Dealer Cost now at Provident </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 01:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Insane.domains - a rhyming domain generator using new gTLDs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 16:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The jungle of mobile HTML5 development </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 16:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are you all doing for favicons nowadays? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 22:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A quick google search led me to http://realfavicongenerator.net which generates favicons/html code in the following sizes based on a file you upload.

    link rel="apple-touch-icon" sizes="57x57" href="/apple-touch-icon-57x57.png"
    link rel="apple-touch-icon" sizes="114x114" href="/apple-touch-icon-114x114.png"
    link rel="apple-touch-icon" sizes="72x72" href="/apple-touch-icon-72x72.png"
    link rel="apple-touch-icon" sizes="144x144" href="/apple-touch-icon-144x144.png"
    link rel="apple-touch-icon" sizes="60x60" href="/apple-touch-icon-60x60.png"
    link rel="apple-touch-icon" sizes="120x120" href="/apple-touch-icon-120x120.png"
    link rel="apple-touch-icon" sizes="76x76" href="/apple-touch-icon-76x76.png"
    link rel="apple-touch-icon" sizes="152x152" href="/apple-touch-icon-152x152.png"
    link rel="icon" type="image/png" href="/favicon-196x196.png" sizes="196x196"
    link rel="icon" type="image/png" href="/favicon-160x160.png" sizes="160x160"
    link rel="icon" type="image/png" href="/favicon-96x96.png" sizes="96x96"
    link rel="icon" type="image/png" href="/favicon-16x16.png" sizes="16x16"
    link rel="icon" type="image/png" href="/favicon-32x32.png" sizes="32x32"
    meta name="msapplication-TileColor" content="#da532c"
    meta name="msapplication-TileImage" content="/mstile-144x144.png"

Are you guys using this? If so, what size are you creating your master favicon file that you upload?  Not all the dimensions in the generated code are divisible by 16.  Should I just create the master favicon at 320x320 (which is divisible by 16)? The generator site says your file should be at least 260x260 (not evenly divisible by 16).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xibalba - a WebGL shooter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 20:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Notification Style Demos - simple ideas   effects for website notifications </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 19:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WaveGL = WebGL + Audio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 17:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any research/studies on what income level the average stacker is at? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 20:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do the wealthy stack? Or is it mostly middle-class? Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does r/realestate think of paying off your mortgage early? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 19:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've 40k left on my mortgage, which I can pay off in one fell swoop. I've thought about doing this for a couple years now but I also think about my mortgage being "good debt", if that makes any sense.

My mortgage is my only debt. Not planning on selling/moving anytime soon.

I think my interest rate is 4.25%, perhaps 4.125%, can't remember which.

Any 40k payoff would not be all my cash savings.

I would then take the monthly mortgage payments I used to make and just put those into my various retirement accounts (probably just split the $ up into even monthly contributions).

Thoughts? Anyone gone down this path or a similar one? How did it work out?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does r/finance think of paying off your mortgage early? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 19:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does r/investing think of paying off your mortgage early? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 19:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've 40k left on my mortgage, which I can pay off in one fell swoop.  I've thought about doing this for a couple years now but I also think about my mortgage being "good debt", if that makes any sense.

My mortgage is my only debt. Not planning on selling/moving anytime soon.

I think my interest rate is 4.25%, perhaps 4.125%, can't remember which.

Any 40k payoff would not be all my cash savings.

I would then take the monthly mortgage payments I used to make and just put those into my various retirement accounts (probably just split the $ up into even monthly contributions).

Thoughts?  Anyone gone down this path or a similar one?  How did it work out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone here read Mike Maloney's "Guide to Investing In Gold and Silver: Protect Your Financial Future"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 15:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Gets some high praise in the Amazon reviews](http://www.amazon.com/Rich-Dads-Advisors-Investing-Financial/dp/0446510998/ref=sr_1_1?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1406466239 sr=1-1 keywords=Guide+to+Investing+In+Gold+and+Silver%3A+Protect+Your+Financial+Future), wondering if anyone here has read it and what your thoughts are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RGBAnalyse - a JavaScript client-side image color analyser </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 16:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Image comparison slider with pure CSS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 16:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone use Yahoo's YQL to scrape dynamic html/content from 3rd party domain (via xpath query)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 16:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm building a proof-of-concept app for a friend and I'm using YQL to scrape 3rd party website data/content.  YQL makes this so ridiculously easy I had it working literally in 10 minutes.

Started with two 3rd party domains and when I went to add another, it wasn't pulling in the content.  Looks like that content is populated dynamically, so when YQL goes to scrape it (via xpath), it doesn't return anything.

Does anyone know if you can do this with YQL?  I'd love to keep using it because, as I said, it was so ridiculously easy to flesh out a prototype.

Ideally, I want to bundle this up as a bookmarklet for my friend so it's ridiculously easy for him to use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creating dub delay effects with the Web Audio API </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 16:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stop leaving money on the table with your freelance rate - companies pay for solutions, not hours </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 16:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recommendations for west-side carpet cleaning? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 18:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As it says on the tin, I'm looking to have my carpet cleaned.  I live west-side.

Can anyone recommend a kick ass company you've personally used, hopefully somewhat recently.  Also, how much square feet do you have and what did it end up costing you?  If you have stairs, did they charge extra for those?

Bad experiences are welcomed as well so I can make a note of those to avoid.

Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Generic and overused logos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 17:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mario 3 using CSS3 keyframe animations and media queries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 16:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AniJS Studio - add animations and interactions to any website easily </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 17:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pure CSS One Div Weather Animated Icons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 16:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a better place to buy pick-and-choose junk silver online than... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 16:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Buy gold and silver coins (bgasc.com)](http://www.bgasc.com/category/90-percent-silver-coins)

* [Dimes for as little as $1 FV @ $16.27](http://www.bgasc.com/category/90-percent-silver-dimes-10c)
* Dime rolls (50 coins) in Roosevelts, Mercury, Barber
* [Quarters for as little as $1 FV @ $16.27](http://www.bgasc.com/category/90-percent-silver-quarters-25c)
* Quarter rolls (40 coins) in Washington, Standing Liberty, Barber
* [Half Dollar](http://www.bgasc.com/category/90-percent-silver-half-dollars-50c) Kennedy, Franklin, Walking Liberty. Individual prices seem a bit much, rolls of 20 are better.

I'd love to pick up some of what I don't have in junk silver:

* Mercury/Barber dimes
* Standing Liberty Quarters (though they're out of stock on readable dates at the moment)
* Half dollar walkers

Seems a great place to pick up low denominations in standard dimes/quarters as well.

Free shipping on orders over $250. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Positive for /u/DuckFigg (seller on $475 transaction) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 22:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * [Roll of 20 2012 Libertads](http://imgur.com/a/3l5ah)
* Smooth $475 transaction (my second one here)
* Great packing (entire box was encased in tape, no movement inside)
* You are a very handsome man, sir.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank you /user/DuckFigg for the 2012 Libertads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 22:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * [Roll of 20 2012 Libertads](http://imgur.com/a/3l5ah)
* Smooth $475 transaction (my second one here)
* Great packing (entire box was encased in tape, no movement inside)
* You are a very handsome man, sir.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Rogue Hired a Graphic Designer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 03:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shout out to silver.com and JM Bullion - FAST check processing/shipping times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 03:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Placed a small order with each back on 7/7/14.

Mailed out my **personal check** payments to each on 7/8/14 (Tuesday).

Silver.com attempted delivery was today, 7/16/14 (Wednesday).

Tracking on JM Bullion order indicates it will be delivered tomorrow (attempted delivery, anyways), 7/17/14 (Thursday).

I'll go pick both up this Saturday.

Pretty impressive for paying with personal check.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Designer to developer checklist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 16:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you guys have a list of things your designer is required to provide when handing off designs for front-end development?

Things like color palette, link states, specific interactions, fonts (family/size), form validation, etc. Not necessarily just http://photoshopetiquette.com/ but similar.

What are you guys looking for when you get those designer handoffs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Designer to developer checklist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 16:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you guys have a list of things your designer is required to provide when handing off designs for front-end development?

Things like color palette, link states, specific interactions, fonts (family/size), form validation, etc. Not necessarily just http://photoshopetiquette.com/ but similar.

What are you guys looking for when you get those designer handoffs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome to Utopia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 16:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silver accounting ledgers - here's what I'm doing, what are you guys doing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-13 04:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[This is how I'm planning on documenting my silver purchases](http://i.imgur.com/S06myJH.jpg)**.  

Initially, I plan on doing it old-school style, i.e., a notebook I keep with my stack.  Basically I'm just going to document orders like the screenshot above and at the bottom of each page run a total of ounces and cost per page.

I was thinking of perhaps adding an **ordered** date and **spot** price columns. Not sure if I really care to track spot price as I can ballpark that via any generic purchases and the last two columns. Might be something to add, though.

I can average out my cost per ounce by month, quarter or year, which would probably be interesting to track over time.

I'd probably start a "sell" ledger when the time comes as well, document those there and adjust the purchase book accordingly.

What do you guys think?  What are you all doing?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amagi - review and unboxing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 21:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * [Great packing, arrived with no external damage](http://imgur.com/a/qVuvW). I think someone here recently had an Amagi order where a tube was cracked/damaged. I don't think this is an Amagi issue, but rather a USPS issue where their box got crushed a bit.
* 2 tubes 2014 ASE.
* 1 tube 2014 CML.
* Also in the order was a tube of Philharmonics, but [they couldn't fulfill those for me](http://www.reddit.com/r/Silverbugs/comments/2a6yqu/received_a_call_from_amagi_earlier_today_re_my/). I was really disappointed in their online inventory system not being in sync with actual product.
* A refund check is supposedly on its way to me now.
* On a scale of 1-10, I give this transaction, sorry to say, a 6. 

It does bother me that you order something they say is in stock, lock in a price and then find out they can't fulfill it.  I was hoping they'd throw in a note saying my next order with them will have free shipping or throw some trivial bone at me, but that didn't happen.

Overall, no big deal, but it obviously leaves an impression.

Their customer service is very responsive, though, I worked with Jillian there.  Gotta say, she was great.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SD Bullion - review and unboxing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 20:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * [Great packing, arrived with no external damage](http://imgur.com/a/1IYhs)
* 1 roll of generic buffalo rounds
* 2 10 oz NTR bars
* Solid buying experience, no issues at all
* On a scale of 1-10, I give this transaction a 10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seahero - Positive - he was the seller on a $560 transaction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 20:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * [$35 FV junk silver](http://imgur.com/a/xNz00)
* Smooth $560 transaction (my first here)
* Great packing
* You sir, are an officer and a gentleman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank you /user/Seahero for the $35 FV junk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 20:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * [$35 FV junk silver](http://imgur.com/a/xNz00)
* Smooth $560 transaction (my first here)
* Great packing
* You sir, are an officer and a gentleman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> APMEX - My *first* physical silver was delivered today - no signature required??? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 02:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Via APMEX, **no signature required on the delivery????** That was very disappointing, is this the norm for APMEX? The order was for two 10oz Geiger Security Series bars, came to $453.20, is this below a $ threshold for signature?  Honestly, I think that's kind of bullshit...

Can't believe the size of the box these came in as when I opened it up, [I was a little surprised at the size of the bars](http://imgur.com/a/y1bi7). I thought they'd be a little bigger.

Solid APMEX experience except for the signature deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Best Way to Invest in Silver - Silver Wheaton/silver streaming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 17:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3D CSS typography </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 16:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Received a call from Amagi earlier today re: my order they're about to ship out... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 02:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can't fulfill my 2014 roll of Philharmonics on an order I placed on 6/22/14.

They offered to combine some years to fill the tube but when I order a full tube of year X, I want a full tube of year X (still sealed). They're apparently not getting restocked anytime soon, either. They also offered to exchange it for something else, but it isn't like I had time to go shopping while at work. Besides, I wanted those Phils.

They're sending me a refund, assuming it'll be in with the order, but I didn't confirm this.

Disappointed that their inventory system isn't quite so accurate as I was really looking forward to those Philharmonics.

Oh well, I'll pick them up somewhere else.

Anyhoo, I'll be sharing all my online ordering experiences, whether good, bad or ugly.  I encourage you guys to do the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patternbolt - a fine selection of SVG pattern background, packed in a single CSS or SCSS file </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 00:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Front-End Technology Stack Round-Up - the usage, relationships and trends in the massive jungle of modern front-end tech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 21:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CSS Avengers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 17:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JavaScript library to show fullscreen GIFs on hover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 20:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> css-colorguard - automatically detect colors in your CSS that are close and should be merged </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 17:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An archive of all-fiction pulpwood magazines from 1896 - 1946 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 17:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any silver youtube channels you can recommend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 18:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who are you sub'd to and whatcha watchin' regularly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silver prices rose twice as much as gold in June will this continue? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 05:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Front-End Experiments - plasma and fire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 19:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Entomic - build responsive websites and see them update live on any device </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 17:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did you know Waterfront Park used to be a major thoroughfare (Harbor Drive)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 19:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Intense Image Viewer - javascript library for viewing images in a fully full screen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 17:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Find a Bootstrap theme for your next project </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 17:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WebGL Particle Physics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 16:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Android apps are you using to track silver? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 05:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on KitKat 4.4.4.

[Gold   Silver Price Checker](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.altsoldev.preciousmetaltracker) looks pretty plain jane, which is good.  Anyone using this?

Kitco has [Gold Live! Widget](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=kcast.android.widget), but as a widget, I have a feeling it would suck down my battery more than I want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are Silver Coins Minted? 6 minute video. I'm sure most here already know, but I found interesting as a noob </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 16:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you haggle at a LCS without offending? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 03:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say for example, they're selling a 10 oz bar for $222.  Is it poor form to try and haggle?  Whether it's for one bar or five, i.e., "if you'll take $220, I'll buy it now" or "how about 5 for $1,100?"

I'm new to silver and have yet to hit up a LCS, I've just been buying online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neodymium earth magnets for silver testing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 03:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you guys using [neodymium magnets](http://www.amazon.com/JSP-Neodymium-Magnet-Silver-Testing/dp/B00AJR47FI) to do the [45 degree slow slide silver testing method for bars](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NgSXg-WOEVY)?

If so, would you recommend the one I linked up?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why silver's outperforming gold and isn't done yet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 22:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NOVALIGHT - best viewed with MS IE 6.0 (+), Opera 7.2 (+) or Netscape 7.1 (+) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 20:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justified.js - jQuery Plugin to create Justified Image Gallery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 16:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Maps Street View mosaic of 43k properties in Detroit that were on the brink of foreclosure this year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 16:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silver Short Squeeze Presents New Opportunity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 20:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just placed an online order at SD Bullion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 03:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My second silver purchase, 40 oz, really nice online buying/checkout process. 

My first order was with Amagi, really nice online buying/checkout process there as well.  I've actually been quite surprised and impressed with my two online purchasing experiences.  They're pretty slick and I wasn't really expecting that.

I'll do a follow up post when the order arrives to relay the full experience.  It'll be a couple weeks as I'm paying by check, but I'll definitely follow up.

Oh, BTW, SD Bullion has good prices (for what I shopped around for/compared/bought) and they're running a $8 shipping on any order right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CSS Only 3D Macbook Air Animation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 16:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone regularly hit up Goodwill or other thrift stores on the hunt for sterling silver? If so, how has that panned out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 02:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giving Animations Life - Using Bounce.js and classical animation concepts to bring life to user interfaces </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 16:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any stackers here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 21:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the shops to hit up or avoid from your experience? I work downtown so any recommendations there would be great. Any big shows roll through town somewhat regularly?  Where are they usually held? Is there any sort of stacking community here where people can buy/trade from others? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your average public Dribbble grievance from the under-stroked ego of a mediocre designer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 17:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
