<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7865</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 18:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some feminists are sexist against males because they aren't good at empathy and fail to appreciate it from the other side. They also often spend a lot of time chatting to other feminists with similar views, which validates their own attitudes. There are blinkered people in every walk of life, unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 18:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. The institution of marriage is far older than christianity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 18:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could legitimately argue that many major magazines basically are for white people (eg womens magazines v rarely feature non-white people on the cover). 
Plus, if a magazine specifically identified itself as 'for white people', would enough people actually buy it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 17:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you please give some examples? I'm struggling to think of what you mean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 19:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sharing! That sounds amazing - good luck with it all :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 19:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome, I've always wanted an airstream. Is it as a primary home, or as a holiday home? Do you think you'll kit it out with loads of high-tech bits and pieces, or are you planning to go more off grid? (Sorry for all the questions!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 19:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah not one I normally read, but I stumbled across this and it looked interesting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Escaping the city: The coming rise of mass digital nomadism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 16:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cars that drive themselves starting to chat with each other </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 16:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Identity Management in the age of wearable technology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 16:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The journalists who never sleep: Robot writers that can interpret data and generate stories are starting to appear in certain business and media sectors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 16:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Sotomayor says technology could lead to Orwellian world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 16:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A super-strong and lightweight new material that could be used to build lighter, stronger airplanes and batteries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 16:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 11:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope at least $1000 of that is to pay for sewing lessons  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 10:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it is pretty itchy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zeus, the Great Dane who held the title of worlds tallest dog, has died of old age, two months short of his sixth birthday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 15:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Engineers develop first intelligent, heated clothing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 13:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 13:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you by any chance mean the [Kingdom of Lovely](http://micronations.wikia.com/wiki/Kingdom_of_Lovely)?

It was founded by UK author Danny Wallace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The First Space Vessel Designed Entirely for Tourists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 10:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's How Japanese Pop Videos Depicted Cyberspace Back In 1989 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 10:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 10:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, that's so they can find out who's visiting their site - virtually all modern sites use analytics, and they aren't all selling the info to advertisers. 
Plus, what exactly do you mean by "your tracking information"? You know individuals can't be identified by analytics programs, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 08:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zarrow.co.uk specialises in this kind of work  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Space garbage men: Tracking the movement and spin of orbiting space junk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 14:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Space garbage men: Tracking the movement and spin of orbiting space junk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 13:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chemists create 'assembly-line' for organic molecules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 12:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Incredible Buckminster Fuller-Inspired Bioclimatic Dome Shows Off the Power of Digital Prefabrication </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 12:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chip packets help make safer water in Papua New Guinea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 12:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Android KitKat on 24.5 percent of devices, but Jelly Bean is still king: Google </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 12:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China to launch second space lab in 2016, official says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 12:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The CO2 Increase Rate Has Reached a Three Decade High </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 12:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sharks lose their appetite in acidic oceans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 12:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Do We Get Catbots? We Have the Technology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 11:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 22:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The funniest example of this was one my boyfriend's mum did (she believes in that crap, despite my bf's repeated explanations of cold reading etc) - it was one done over Skype (who knew that was a thing!) and everything the 'psychic' woman said was way off, so she blamed it on the 'bad vibes' of the McDonalds my bf's mum was in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 22:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah apologies, I missed that you weren't in the country. Good luck with it all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New restaurant aims to bring flavour of Caribbean to Ealing Broadway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 21:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 21:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel the same - it's insanely expensive and I'm really starting to consider moving out, but jobs in my field are thin on the ground outside of the city. I tend to escape to Bristol to see friends whenever it gets too much. 

I'd love for there to be some kind of solution to this, but I'm really struggling to think of anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ealing Half Marathon builds on London Olympic legacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 21:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 21:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can transform it into a real voice for the area it could be successful - my suggestion would be to get it going with regular posts and maybe try posting flyers around Ealing promoting it? Maybe try and launch discussions about any local issues and add pictures of any new features in the area for people to discuss. I'm close but not in your borough, but I will post anything I find that's relevant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 21:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sharing - I had no idea this had been preserved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 16:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that might be a bit of a pandora's box issue - Midlanders would probably decry not being given their own specific government and the old Cornwall independence campaign would refire. The UK has a huge number of regional identities - we could easily end up with as many states as the US if we really tried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 16:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true - eureka-alert is just a science press release portal, so it's only as accurate as each university's pr writers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 14:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the rest of England?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The dawn of tiny tech: Molecular electronics closer to reality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 13:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fossil   Intel partner on wearable technology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 13:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The impossible triple star KIC 2856960 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 13:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers look to carbon dioxide as a more environmentally friendly refrigerant gas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 13:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shape-Shifting Architecture That Responds to Heat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 12:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blast from the past: 5 high-impact Apple keynotes that captured our imaginations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 11:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Winter is coming: British weather set to become more unsettled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 10:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new route to making graphene has been discovered that could make the 21st century's wonder material easier to ramp up to industrial scale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 10:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 10:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really depends on the location and geology of the cliffs in question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Would Make You Move To A Space Colony? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 10:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cliff house by Modscape suspended above the Australian ocean </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 10:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 16:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you mean to post this in [/r/gaming](http://www.reddit.com/r/gaming)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 16:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder at what point the pirates will decide to automate too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 14:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you think they'll be built on Earth? I myself think it will happen eventually, but this might be partly because I just think they're an awesome idea! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Space elevators: Sci-Fi dream or future reality? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 13:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where to Watch Livestreams of Tomorrows Apple Event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 13:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 12:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true! I just feel bad for the poor fools who get taken in and hand over their money for stuff like this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buddhist singing bowls inspire new tandem solar cell design </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 12:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Massive BigRep Pro 3D Printer Offers 53 Cubic Foot Build Volume For $79,000 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 12:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Hires Renowned Designer Marc Newson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 12:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers uncover chemistry behind ancient Indigenous art </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 12:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bottle feeding changes infant's immune system </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 12:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This appears to be a campaign for a perpetual motion device </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 12:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bringing gesture-control technology from Hollywood to corporate conference rooms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 12:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tokyo stocks end higher on rise in US shares- Nikkei Asian Review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 11:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Before Android Wear and Apple iWatch: How watches got their smarts over the years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 11:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 17:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but those poorer are largely not paying UK prices </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 11:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't think it happened until I started working in an office in a touristy area of London. Some people seem to think the world is there to serve them. 

Mind you, it only ever happened with British tourists - everyone else has been nothing but polite and appreciative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 09:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> South Park are clearly going to do an episode on the fappening </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 09:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait... there is a use for gold? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 09:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You stubbed your toe and your first reaction was to kick something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 09:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I've missed something here - what has being an arts student got to do with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 08:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! It seems crazy that the person I've been with for over five years gets the same title as in a teenage 'relationship' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Pictures: The future of Londons transport is cycling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 11:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's good to talk: China opens up to psychotherapy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 09:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atlantic slows warming, temperature rises seen resuming from 2030: study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 09:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garden cities: Where will we live in 2030 in maps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 09:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Departments use technology to ID troubled officers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 09:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 09:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> factor-tech.com also does a lot of futurology </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bitcoin hosting center will open in Michigan with the aim of lowering costs for professional Bitcoin miners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 18:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $100,000 in donations help Comcast get merger support from Chicago mayor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 18:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is The Internet Scrambling Our Teenagers Brains? We Dont Know, But Probably Not. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 17:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neuromodulation 2.0: New Developments in Brain Implants, Super Soldiers and the Treatment of Chronic Disease </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 17:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Solar Rain Tree Oasis Could Alleviate Drought-Striken California Using Rainwater Collection and Clean Energy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 17:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 17:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Space-only machinery is a very cool thought - it will be fascinating to see how it differs from Earth-designed stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samsung reveals virtual reality headset powered by a smartphone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 16:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First 3D printer in space to mark start of extraterrestrial manufacturing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 16:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 15:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or screen them for awesomeness  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 15:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting story, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 15:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you mind telling us about it? I haven't heard that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA invites public to submit messages for asteroid mission time capsule </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 14:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weird Facts About 5 of the Worlds Most Famous Logos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 13:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your Next Chevy May Watch You Watching the Road </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 13:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BioShock Game Developer Mocks His Industry in The Magic Circle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 13:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First 3D printer in space to mark start of extraterrestrial manufacturing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 13:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nearly 80,00 Gallons of Crude Oil Spill Into Alberta Waterway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 12:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MasterCard-backed biometric ID system launched in Nigeria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 12:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doctor Who Sonic Screwdriver Cutlery Set </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 11:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3D-printed robotic birds of prey are undergoing trials </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 11:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Micron Technology (MU) Stock Is Down Today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 10:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gulf of Maine: 'Poster child' for global warming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 10:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weaved treehouse with bamboo modules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 10:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Burnt out birds suggest hard work could be bad for your health </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 10:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 00:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A key part of that profit comes from not paying over and above for staff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 23:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a very common practice in large news organisations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 22:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love that picture of him looking out of the window - he looks like he's surveying his kingdom! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 21:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There some decent online-only news sites, although any site that thinks 4chan is a person probably isn't in that group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robots unlikely to take big bites out of employment, expert says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 16:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nanoparticle-detecting microlasers to be used to identify viruses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 14:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homepages are a product of journalists who came from print and thought in print terms - i100 and Quartz prove homepages are increasingly irrelevant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 11:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Windows 9 accidentally teased by Microsoft </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 11:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Behold! The Upcoming Estonian Bitcoin Castle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 11:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook Gears Up In Africa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 10:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan space agency unveils asteroid hunting probe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 10:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Korean Yujin Robot launches meal transport robot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 10:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has microfinance lost its moral compass? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 10:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> United Nations predicts climate hell in 2050 with imagined weather forecasts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 02:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Given that images of 101 celebrities were leaked, why has all the media focus been on Jennifer Lawrence? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 23:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost every news article I have come across has focused on Jennifer Lawrence, but 101 people were affected, including a lot of other high-profile celebs. What's the deal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3D printed concrete castle and plans to create and sell a concrete printer kit for about $30,000 to $50,000 that can print two story houses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 17:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Archaeologists can now say for certain that Stonehenge was once a complete circle after the dry weather revealed the ghostly outlines of missing stones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 16:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan firm showcases 'touchable' 3D technology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 15:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has Dysons robotic dream become a reality? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 14:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Space Pizza and Robotic Gardens: Producing food in orbit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 13:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seismic engineering for tall buildings in Asia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 11:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 14:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I suspect the publisher is the one setting the prices - a friend is currently writing a textbook for a major publisher and pricing decisions are made by them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 22:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be honest with yourself and think carefully about how you could be better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 22:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cider </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 22:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First week-long break in over a year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 21:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed - it was surprisingly good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 20:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of dwarves and nearly being killed by a massive dragon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 20:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Utter silence as everyone stood browsing Reddit on their phones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 19:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only studied history up to the age of 14, but it wasn't mentioned in any of our classes. We mainly studied the tudors and the industrial revolution. Quite honestly I suspect it is something that very few British people know much about.

That was more than a decade ago though - does anyone else have a more recent experience?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 19:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sam Vimes likes cheap boots - they allow him to identify where he is in the city just by feeling the street through the thin soles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 19:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it for this reason. Can confirm it's worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 19:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is pretty awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
