<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7619</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican friend posted this on Facebook. Shall we debunk? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-05 06:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Korn vs Taylor Swift </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-04 03:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> USS Lexington @ Corpus Christi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-04 02:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> USS Lexington in Corpus Christi, TX </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-04 02:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are plays about England considered histories but plays about Scotland, Rome, etc. considered tragedies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-04 01:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This never made sense to me. The following are considered histories:

    King John

    Edward III 

    Richard II

    Henry IV, Part 1

    Henry IV, Part 2

    Henry V

    Henry VI, Part 1

    Henry VI, Part 2

    Henry VI, Part 3

    Richard III

    Henry VIII

While the following are considered tragedies:

    Coriolanus

    Julius Caesar

    Antony and Cleopatra

    King Lear

    Macbeth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So after WWII, it was decided that Palestine would be partitioned to form a Jewish state (Israel), and the first thing that happened was a war in which the brand-new Israel gained territory? And they were allowed to keep it? How was anyone okay with this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-03 23:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Furthermore, how was it ever seen as a good idea to just take someone country, divide it, displace its people, and give it away to someone else? If the UN just suddenly decided that it was going to create a (insert ethnic or religious people) state by dividing the US into West and East halves and give the Western United States away, wouldn't it pretty well expected that Americans, especially the displaced ones from the West, would get pissed? I can't wrap my head around how this ever seemed like a good idea to anyone ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can the Cold War be blamed on George Frost Kennan? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-03 22:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems to me his rabble rousing "Long Telegram" instigated the whole thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When all is said and done, it makes great toast. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-03 17:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I feel playing with my 3-year-old daughter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-02 08:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Of 13,950 peer-reviewed climate change articles, only 24 deny it's happening. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-02 07:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Of 13,950 peer-reviewed climate change articles, only 24 deny it's happening. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-02 07:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In honor of the Character of the Month: The Question's first appearance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-01 23:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many can you name? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-01 23:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice League "X-Men #1" cover parody </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-01 01:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YSK the top 10 misused words... and stop misusing them! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-29 23:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Of all the New52 costume/look redesigns, which is your favorite/least favorite? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-29 23:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Favorite: More detailed/realistic utilitarian/militaristic all black   gray Batman without the yellow oval insignia and no more underwear outside the pants.

Lease favorite: Power Girl. How do you go from [this perfection](http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/c/ce/Power_Girl.png) to [this garbage](http://media.comicvine.com/uploads/6/65157/2195588-pg_large.jpg)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Power of Introverts: Did you know that one out of three Americans are introverts? Check out this new web documentary series exploring one of the least celebrated personality types in modern society. Based on the book Quiet by Susan Cain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-29 05:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the universe have a purpose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-29 05:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the universe have a purpose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-29 05:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Injustice: Gods Among Us has an updated roster list. Whose addition would mean a definite purchase for you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-28 23:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Current roster:

Batman

Catwoman

Cyborg

Deathstroke

The Flash

Green Arrow

Green Lantern (Hal Jordan)

Harley Quinn

The Joker

Nightwing

Solomon Grundy

Superman

Wonder Woman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL an unfinished portrait of FDR remains unfinished because he died whilst posing for it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-27 20:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just read Titus Andronicus for the first time. Is it just me, or is this the schlocky, B-rated, grindhouse horror flick of Shakespeare's time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 23:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The violence of this play is actually so over-the-top, all I could think of is old "B" horror movies.

We have war, ritual butchery and sacrifice, crime of passion, premeditated murder, rape (gang rape at that), mutilation, execution, self-mutilation, cold-blooded senseless murder, torture, the threat of infanticide, cannibalism, honor-killing, child murder, consensual homicide, and if you believe Titus knew he wasnt going to live through it himself, you can call it suicide in there as well.  And layers upon layers of revenge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "It is necessary that laws should be passed to prohibit the use of corporate funds directly or indirectly for political purposes; it is still more necessary that such laws should be thoroughly enforced." ~ Teddy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 22:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some people REALLY love America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 17:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Racially-charged question: do Mexican-American children bully white students, especially blonds? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-25 21:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off, let's get the disclaimer out of the way: I am **NOT** a racist. At all. I recently moved to San Antonio from New Hampshire to be closer to my family, which, by the way, includes quite a few Mexican-Americans. 

I have a 3-year-old daughter who is white with gray eyes and blond hair. Recently, my wife told me coworkers of hers, including Mexican-American women, warned her after meeting our daughter that blond-haired/blue-eyed white girls get picked on by the girls of Mexican descent. 

Is this true? If so, why is it true? My wife didn't want to push the issue with her coworkers at the risk of offending them, but I'm worried for my daughter, who will be entering into pre-K next year. I doubt it's a problem with 4-year-olds, but I don't want her to grow up being bullied, either.

I have no problem with Mexican-Americans or Mexicans in general. In fact, one of the things I love about San Antonio is the Mexican culture, art, and food. 

Another thing that I've noticed is my daughter, being very outgoing and friendly, tends to walk onto playgrounds waving, smiling, and shouting things like, "Hi, friends! My name is _______! Want to play?" and the looks she gets from some of the kids are like... I don't know... mean. Like, "Who is the kid? Why is she saying hi to me? Why is she calling me a friend?" This got her instant playmates in NH. Here, it gets her dirty looks. Cultural thing? Again, this is the Latino/Latina children. The white, black, and Asian kids have been pretty warm to her.

Sorry if this is a TL;DR, but I don't know how to shorten it and I'm very curious.

**EDIT**: I'd be especially interested in hearing from Mexicans, especially those who grew up in San Antonio.

For those downvoting, I don't get you. This is an honest question out of concern for my daughter. It's not an attack on anybody. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best value for a tablet that will be used primarily for Skype? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-24 18:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The secret behind this skills gap is that its not a skills gap at all." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-23 00:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We're always told Hamlet's famous "To be or not to be" was a soliloquy. It wasn't. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-21 03:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Monologue is a speech that is spoken to someone else, or at least another character on the stage hears it.

A Soliloquy, is a speech spoken to nobody, and only the audience hears it, not any other character in the play. 

So which is this? 

When Shakespeare writes dialog, they say what they mean. If hes talking about Love, hes in love. If hes talking about killing someone, hes angry and really wants to kill them. It is, for the most part, difficult to lie in Shakespearean speech, without a stage direction saying, He or She is lying. There are exceptions, but they just have to be supported by the text. The things other people say, or what that character says before or after the incident in question. In other words, they do say what they mean, unless there is evidence to support otherwise.

What is it even saying anyway?

To be, or not to be... 

Be as in existing. To exist or not to exist, to live or not to live. Okay, hes openly questioning if he should live or die. So, this speech is about whether or not Hamlet should kill himself, which isnt totally out of the blue; at the beginning of the play, the first time Hamlet is onstage alone, he contemplates it there as well.

Whether tis nobler in the mind to suffer

The slings and arrows of outrageous fortune,

Or to take arms against a sea of troubles,

And, by opposing, end them.

Which is better? Just take my wealth and position, keeping my mouth shut, but be racked with guilt over it, or to actually stand up for what I believe in, even though it would destroy and kill me and my family?

To die, to sleep-

No more, and by a sleep to say we end

The heartache and the thousand natural shocks

That flesh is heir to  tis a consummation

Devoutly to be wished.

But if Im dead, no more pain, no more suffering, no more guilt, and all the problems I have now just go away. Hey, that sounds pretty good...

To die, to sleep.

To sleep, perchance to dream. Ay, theres the rub,

For in that sleep of death what dreams may come

When we have shuffled off this mortal coil

Must give us pause. Theres the respect

That makes calamnity of so long life...

And if its all just a long sleep, whats on that other side? Its supposed to be so wonderful; thats why we endure all the crap in this world.

It goes on, but we can see its basically a suicide note of sorts, or at least a contemplation on the part of Hamlet.

Just before Hamlet comes on stage to give this speech, Claudius and Polonius, the murderous King and his Crony are talking with Ophelia, Polonius daughter, and Queen Gertrude. The Queen leaves... okay, now 3 on the stage. Polonius
then says:

Ophelia, walk you here.  Gracious, so please you,

We will bestow ourselves.

Hes telling Ophelia, Hamlets Girlfriend, to hang out here. But we will bestow ourselves.? 

The archaic meaning of bestow is to stow, deposit, store. So... lets store ourselves? Lets stow ourselves? Yes! Theyre saying, Lets go hide, which they then do. They exit, and Hamlet enters, talking all morbid.

But Ophelia is still on-stage. There is no Ophelia exits, nor is there Ophelia re-enters, so shes there the whole time while Hamlet talks about killing himself.

So, is the speech an aside that no one else hears? No, because at least one other person hears it, if not three. Hamlet finishes, then sees Ophelia, they have a big argument, and he gets crazy with the nunnery bit.

Exit Hamlet; enter back in Claudius and Polonius, talking about how mad Hamlet seemed because they absolutely heard him and Hamlet knew this. Then Polonius says:

How now, Ophelia?

You need not tell us what Lord Hamlet said;

We heard it all.

So, they did hear it! 

In most all the previous scenes, and the ones after, Hamlet is very active; hes planning, plotting, getting things ready; hes already made some written contributions for the Theatre troupe thats preparing to perform for the Royal Court. Hes been pushing his plans forward to trap the King and give the final proof he needs to show that the King did in fact kill his father. Since seeing the ghost of his dead dad, hes been consumed by this desire for justice and revenge. Suddenly, for this 1 scene, he does a complete 180 degrees and finds it a good idea to kill himself? Yes, he contemplated it in the beginning, but keep in mind, that was BEFORE he found out his father was murdered. He didn't have any motivations as he does now. At that time, it was thought to be natural causes and the will of God, and hence, theres no one to get mad at, because no one did anything wrong. When the issue of murder comes up, that changes everything and revenge becomes his motive.

Suicide is a non-solution. Its a passive thing to do compared to the rest of the events going on. Its the easy way out, and Hamlet has been setting up these plots and plays with Machiavellian precision, which is definitely not the easy way to do anything. One could claim this speech shows another side to the character of Hamlet, but would that do anything to move the story forward? On its own, it doesnt. The full text of this play can run upwards of 4 hours long. How many people will sit for a 4 hour movie when it has parts that go nowhere? Is this speech Shakespeares way of saying, Heres a bathroom break?

NO! It is NOT a soliloquy! Ophelia was on-stage. Claudius and Polonius are hiding, and listening in, and Hamlet knows it! That means his whole suicide speech is by design. Hes already spent a few scenes convincing people that hes gone mad, and there IS method in it. The King and crony are trying to figure out if its true. Now, hes actively deceiving them, so that would make this speech something that moves the plot forward. Its just another part of Hamlets master
plan, and so far, theyre falling right into it.

More evidence: The last time we saw Hamlet on stage, he meets The Players, and asks the head player to give a short, impromptu performance, who readily obliges him. Then, everyone else ends up leaving the stage, leaving Hamlet, alone, for real this time. Here he has a real soliloquy (he even mentions hes all alone) whereupon he marvels at the performance that head player just gave. In fact, he realizes, and is very much ashamed at the fact, that the actor has just
shown more intensity and commitment in his task of that brief performance than Hamlet has in HIS task of avenging his fathers murder. Hamlet has just mentally smacked himself, reminding him to start raising the stakes, or hes going to fail at his task, and also realized the importance of acting as a role in his deceptions.

So I'm supposed to believe that suddenly, the very next words he speaks on stage are implying the direct opposite? That he wants to kill himself? A soliloquy of his innermost thoughts that says he needs to step it up followed by another saying the complete opposite? 

Even MORE evidence: Shakespeares original source for Hamlet. This is NOT an original play by Shakespeare. It had been done previously by other playwrights and writers. The original source is called Historia Danica by Saxo Grammaticus. It chronicles the story of Prince Amlothi, also referred to as Amlethus. Pull off the u-s at the end, move the "H" to the front, and you have "Hamlet." The plot matches the play exactly. The father of Amlethus is murdered by his brother who then marries Amlethus mother, the Prince seeks revenge. A large part of his plan has to do with feigning madness. Two attempts are made to prove hes actually sane, one of which is to tempt him into lechery, the thinking being that any man who lusts for women cannot truly be insane. His uncle arranges for a woman to casually run into Amlethus in the forest to seduce him while they watch, which is the prototype scene for this Hamlet/Ophelia scene. But Amlethus is warned of the trap ahead of time, so he makes his own arrangements to whisk her off to a hidden place away from the eyes of the Kings agents, who gets her to tell him everything. He also has sex with her, because why wouldn't he? But in the view of the Kings agents, he continues his act of being batshit insane.

"To Be or Not To Be" is not a soliloquy; it is a monologue! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This video just made me drop my last belief: I was a fatalist. I now accept that I'm making order of chaos. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-20 22:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The world will be a more peaceful place in 2050 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-20 22:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most Popular Thanksgiving Pies Pie Chart  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-20 22:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hostess To Pay $1.75 Million In Executive Bonuses After Blaming Unions For Bankruptcy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-20 06:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we make a list of atheist comedians? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-20 03:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Show 'em love by finding them on Facebook   Twitter for extra likes and follows:

George Carlin

Bill Hicks

[Eddie Izzard](https://www.facebook.com/eddieizzard?ref=ts fref=ts)

Louis CK

[Tim Minchin](https://www.facebook.com/timminchin?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Hannibal Buress](https://www.facebook.com/HannibalBuress?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Todd Glass](https://www.facebook.com/ToddGlass?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Marc Maron](https://www.facebook.com/WTFPodcast?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Jamie Kilstein](https://www.facebook.com/jamiekilsteinfanpage?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Patton Oswalt](https://www.facebook.com/pattonoswalt?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Doug Stanhope](https://www.facebook.com/officialstanhope?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Jim Jeffries](https://www.facebook.com/pages/Jim-Jeffries/275779855987?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Bill Maher](https://www.facebook.com/Maher?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Bo Burnham](https://www.facebook.com/pages/Bo-Burnham/10947828617?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Keith Lowell Jensen](https://www.facebook.com/kljfans?ref=ts fref=ts)

David Cross

[Ricky Gervais](https://www.facebook.com/pages/Ricky-Gervais/108578005851743?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Christopher Wayne Jackson](https://www.facebook.com/cwjcomedian)

[Ryan Bourassa](https://www.facebook.com/RyanBourassa?ref=ts fref=ts)

Billy Connolly

[Jimmy Carr](https://www.facebook.com/jimmycarrfans?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Joe Rogan](https://www.facebook.com/JOEROGANDOTNET?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Stephen Fry](https://www.facebook.com/pages/Stephen-Fry/104083552960329?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Eddie Griffin](https://www.facebook.com/pages/Eddie-Griffin/73107530966?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Penn Jillette](https://www.facebook.com/PennJill?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Seth MacFarlane](https://www.facebook.com/pages/Seth-MacFarlane/14105972607?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Adam Carolla](https://www.facebook.com/officialadamcarolla?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Kathy Griffin](https://www.facebook.com/kathygriffin?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Paula Poundstone](https://www.facebook.com/PaulaPoundstone?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Janeane Garofalo](https://www.facebook.com/JaneaneGarofalo?ref=ts fref=ts)

[Sarah Silverman](https://www.facebook.com/pages/Sarah-Silverman/162150313835070?ref=ts fref=ts)

Got more?

**EDIT**: Thanks for all the suggestions! Sorry for forgetting so many women! Keep 'em coming! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 90s Superboy (Metropolis Kid) works better when rule 63 is applied </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-18 21:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sam X "Best of Me" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-18 21:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mars radiation levels tolerable to humans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-17 17:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two preaching giants and the 'betrayal' that tore them apart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-17 16:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A brief history of corporate whining </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-16 05:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A brief history of corporate whining </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-16 05:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every Bible "contradiction" countered. Use this the next time an atheist presents you with Bible contradictions to "prove" his or her case. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-16 04:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YSK Abraham Lincoln didn't exactly love black people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-16 04:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sam X "Somebody Help Me" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 03:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Romney: Obama Won By Bestowing Gifts On Voters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 02:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 7 Obama-Hating CEOs Who've Thrived Under Obama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 00:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody know how to get the PS3 Eye to work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 06:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using Linux Mint 13 w/Cinnamon (Maya) and the PS3 Eye was detected and works, but only as a camera. I installed Skype, and even though it uses the PS3 as a camera, it doesn't even give the PS3 Eye as an option for a microphone, instead defaulting to PulseAudio server (local). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody know how to get the PS3 Eye to work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 04:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using Linux Mint 13 w/Cinnamon (Maya) and the PS3 Eye was detected and works, but only as a camera. I installed Skype, and even though it uses the PS3 as a camera, it doesn't even give the PS3 Eye as an option for a microphone, instead defaulting to PulseAudio server (local). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody know how to get the PS3 Eye to work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 04:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using Linux Mint 13 w/Cinnamon (Maya) and the PS3 Eye was detected and works, but only as a camera. I installed Skype, and even though it uses the PS3 as a camera, it doesn't even give the PS3 Eye as an option for a microphone, instead defaulting to PulseAudio server (local). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody know how to get the PS3 Eye to work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 04:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using Linux Mint 13 w/Cinnamon (Maya) and the PS3 Eye was detected and works, but only as a camera. I installed Skype, and even though it uses the PS3 as a camera, it doesn't even give the PS3 Eye as an option for a microphone, instead defaulting to PulseAudio server (local). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red and Green Hot Chili Peppers provide more vitamin C than any other food. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 04:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the US learn from its past? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 03:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every history teacher I've ever had always explained the importance of history as a means to learn from our past. Do we, though? Seems like we always have the same problems in government, wars, laws, civil rights, etc. For example, miscegenation used to be argued against the same way same-sex marriage is now. We said there'd never be another Vietnam, going into a foreign country, fighting non-soldiers without uniforms without an exit strategy, but we did. Do we really learn from our past? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a perfect food? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 02:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The atheist/humanist problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 00:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> States petition to secede from union </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-12 23:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody know how to get the PS3 Eye microphone working? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-11 00:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just did a clean install of Maya (Mint 13 w/Cinnamon). My PS3 Eye, which I had been using as a webcam/microphone for Skype purposes, was plugged in when I booted up the first time, and the camera was detected and works perfectly. The problem is, the microphone doesn't pick up. Can't Skype without a microphone. Any ideas?

**UPDATE**: I found [this forum](http://ubuntuforums.org/showthread.php?t=1785840) which had the following advice which worked for someone:

Quote:

CARDINFO{driver}=="USB-Audio", INCLUDE="usb", GOTO="init_end"

To /usr/share/alsa/init/00main in the section that is '# real ALSA configuration database'

Unfortunately, being a noob, I have no idea what to do with that information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you're charged with a victimless crime, demand a jury trial. Juries can acquit you even if you're guilty. It's called "jury nullification." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 03:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please help me. I want to dump Windows for Linux, but which distro? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 02:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **EDIT**: Linux Mint w/Cinnamon (they couldn't come up with a gayer name?) is fully installed and working perfectly. Thank you so much to both AziMandia and PyroNavi for all the help. Goodbye Microsoft!

I'll just go ahead and subscribe to this subreddit and hope my noobishness fades over time... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Star Wars' Episode 7 Sparks Interest from Harrison Ford, Mark Hamill, Carrie Fisher, Will They Return to the Series?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 23:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asbestos advertisement with chilling 9/11 relevance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 22:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Psychic Twins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 22:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time Travel as a Plot Device: Journey Through the Films that made it Understandable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 22:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YSK: You can click on today's Google Doodle to find out where your local polling station is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 15:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most fappable gif ever? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-05 18:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Misheard song lyrics compilation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-05 18:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Romney Campaign Photoshops Image To Make Crowd Appear Larger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-05 17:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL He-Gassen (Japanese for "Farting Competition" or "Fart Battle") is a Japanese fart scroll created during Japan's Edo period. The scroll features people farting in the direction of other people, animals, and other objects. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-05 16:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the next great plausible scientific breakthrough? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-04 23:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Position: as a 31-year-old heterosexual married man, I cannot believe how much I loved a documentary about ballet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-03 22:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fan theory: Wreck-It Ralph is based on Donkey Kong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-03 22:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mind literally blown </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: In physics, "nothing" doesn't exist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-30 22:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Romney on FEMA Government Spending  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-30 20:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>  Romney/Ryan budgets would 'cut the hell out' of FEMA funding  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-30 20:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Romney Won't Talk FEMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-30 20:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9 habits that may do more harm than good </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-26 18:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone have an intel on green coffee bean extract? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-26 17:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A coworker of my wife's is recommending it for weight loss, apparently featured on Dr. Oz. I'm instantly skeptical when it comes to miracle weight-loss products.

The best I can find is this: http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2012/03/120327134209.htm

But 17 pounds over 22 weeks is only .77 lbs. per week, which has to be less than simply diet   exercise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm new around here and voting tomorrow, so can someone please explain the pre-K controversy? Why would anyone be against pre-K, especially if the tax hike is so incredibly low? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-22 05:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **EDIT** I want to thank everyone who has responded so far, especially those who managed to do it without berating or insulting others. I've already voted this morning, but others won't vote for another week or so, therefore I welcome a continuation of this conversation.

Just *please* keep it civil. People can disagree without resorting to insults. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: For The Tree of Life, some American theaters set up signs warning moviegoers about the enigmatic and non-linear narrative of the movie - following some confused walkouts and refund demands in the opening weeks.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-20 16:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who buys a $150.00 sketch cover variant? Even discounted, what makes a variant cover cost over $100? Are any of you actually buying these? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-18 18:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ideal roster for Injustice: Gods Among Us? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-17 01:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Picasso and Monets stolen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 22:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Captain Jean Luc Picard on theism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 18:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Backwards Land: liberal conservatives and conservative liberals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 06:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jihadists Are Getting the Bulk of Weapons Meant for Syrian Rebels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-15 19:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dating show fail(s) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-12 21:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Facebook cover for Libertarians </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-12 00:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fan-made Gary Johnson song/video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-11 23:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fan made Gary Johnson song/video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-11 23:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The top 10 best and worst college majors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-08 20:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best subreddit you think more people would subscribe to if only they knew it existed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-07 20:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently discovered r/youshouldknow and I'm glad I did! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YSK the top 10 deathbed regrets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-07 19:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 7 inches 45 minutes pwnd </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-05 16:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An honest Internet Explorer ad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 23:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some ways presidential debates could be improved? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 22:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My two ideas:

1.    On-the-spot fact-checking. Lies and misinformation should be called out right then and there.

2.    Mics turn off at time limits.

Any more from Reddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Realistic fighting game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 22:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mother stuffed pages of the bible into her six-week old daughter's mouth before killing her. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 22:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Same post, different subreddits, same exact number of comments, displayed back-to-back on my front page. What are the odds? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 19:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: A misheard lyrics is called a "mondegreen" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-02 22:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bacon Shortage 'Aporkalypse' Theoretically Possible, But Highly Unlikely, Given Basic Economics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-29 19:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Richards Talks About Comedy Club Meltdown on Seinfelds Comedians in Cars Series  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-29 07:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Batman meets Madmen and Boardwalk Empire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-28 21:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: Nintendo planning a knitting add-on with the slogan, "Now you're knitting with power!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-27 03:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Makes statement against Muslim violence, serves dickhead instead. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-23 07:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liked the original statement, but the serve at the end was better. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-23 07:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How cheaply can I build a PC based entirely on processing power and RAM? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-23 00:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't need a monitor, drives, keyboard, mouse, or a big hard drive. All I want to do with it is hook it up to my HDTV (so it'll need HD video output) and surround sound system (so it'll need optical audio output), and it'll be online. I'll only be using it to download and watch movies.

I have a cheap Dell refurbish with a single 3GHz processor and 4GB of RAM and it's just not delivering seamless HD. I end up with skipping, stuttering, audio synching, and other issues. I use VLC, DIVX, and, when all else fails, WMP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting away with murder: step 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 01:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans defined on Facebook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 21:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: There is a gang of women in India that go around beating up abusive husbands and fighting to stop child marriages. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 21:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fence that looks like a llama, I raise you llama fencing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 18:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: Franken Berry cereal contained a dye that did not break down in the body and caused the consumers stool to come out a disturbing pink. This phenomenon came to be called Franken Berry Stool. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 18:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More kids get non-medical exemptions from vaccines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 05:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poor Smokers in New York State Spend 25% of Income on Cigarettes, Study Finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 05:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft, HP avoid billions in taxes with offshore profits, Senate probe charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 05:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marijuana And Cancer: Scientists Find Cannabis Compound Stops Metastasis In Aggressive Cancers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 23:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can ethnocentrism ever be a good thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 22:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 31 and I just wrote a paper for my sociology class on prejudice, discrimination, ethnocentrism, and cultural relativism. Some would consider ethnocentrism and cultural relativism opposites, but I was able to find good and bad aspects of cultural relativism, so I expected to be able to show some examples where ethnocentrism could yield positive outcomes. I could not. Can you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dark Energy Camera whirs to life, begins snapping deep-space photos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 22:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft Warns Of IE 9 Security Bug
Microsoft promises fix for zero-day exploit that puts users of IE 9, and earlier IE versions, at risk upon visiting a malicious website. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 22:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elizabeth Warren takes narrow lead in Massachusetts Senate polls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 22:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Romney campaign faces distractions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 06:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than 130 escape from Mexican prison on U.S. border </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 05:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than 130 escape from Mexican prison on U.S. border </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 05:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Movie theater ninjas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-14 00:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First ever ad for Winnie The Pooh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-11 03:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dalai Lama nails it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-11 03:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creationists reply to Bill Nye </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-09 19:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Say what you will about the sweet miracle of unquestioning faith, I consider a capacity for it terrifying and absolutely vile!" ~ Kurt Vonnegut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 23:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Revealing Moment in TV Network Censorship? The Romney-Koch Handshake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 22:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Make Money Selling Drugs (trailer) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 00:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 50 Renowned Academics Speaking About God  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-29 03:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Newsroom nails The Tea Party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-28 22:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The reality of Obama's perceived lack of achievements and the filibusters that stopped him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-28 21:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9/11 resulted in the death of nearly 3,000 Americans. We spend trillions on wars to avenge them. 45,000 Americans die each year from lack of health insurance. Why do Republicans/conservatives oppose a program that saves money and prevents deaths? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-28 16:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9/11 resulted in the death of nearly 3,000 Americans. We spend trillions on wars to avenge them. 45,000 Americans die each year from lack of health insurance.

Why do Republicans/conservatives oppose a program that saves money and prevents deaths? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-28 16:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AAP Circumcision Policy 'Seriously Flawed', Condemned by Canadian Children's Rights Group  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-28 15:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else see the chicken ghost to the left of the crack on the wall? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-28 02:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A grammar Nazi's work is never done. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 22:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RNC slogan: We built this.

"I wonder... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 17:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...if the hurricane has them watching the government-run/tax-payer-funded weather service on the government-run/tax-payer-funded emergency broadcast system to see if they'll have to leave the government-run/tax-payer-funded building by way of the government-run/tax-payer-funded evacuation procedures using the government-run/tax-payer-funded roads and bridges..." ~ Christopher Wayne Jackson (comedian) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coexist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 16:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You came to the rough part of the forest... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-25 22:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baz Confirmed As Our First Arab-American Green Lantern </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-25 04:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GTA: Gotham City </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-25 04:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rise In Autism Rates Partly Due To Older Fathers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 21:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antarctica warmth 'unusual, but not unique' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 21:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RIP Count Von Count </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 21:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RIP, Count von Count: Sesame Street Actor Jerry Nelson Dead at 78 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 21:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Romney Cites Mormon Tithing As Reason To Withhold Tax Returns  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 20:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Doctor Cosplays As Himself On Doctor Who #1 Hastings Variant Cover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 22:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best cat gif ever? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 21:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: Americans are 8 times more likely to be killed by a police officer than by a terrorist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 15:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two-Face the cat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 00:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bus Monitor Karen Klein Starts Anti-Bullying Org </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 00:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP official says God chooses to bless raped women with pregnancy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 21:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A couple days ago, I posted that an anagram for 
"Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan" 
is 
"my ultimate Ayn Rand porn."

To be fair, an anagram of 
"Barack Obama and Joe Biden" 
is 
"A Banana Jabbered Dick Moo." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 16:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So there's that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some handy Heloise-style life hacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 16:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From a Christian "science" book </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 22:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Nye is a Time Lord </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 22:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mars Rover to Receive Scientific Companion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 22:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan" is an anagram for "my ultimate Ayn Rand porn."

 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 20:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe in coincidences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newsweek's anti-Obama cover story: The conservative historian Niall Ferguson pens an error-filled tirade against Obama, and the struggling weekly concedes that it didn't even fact-check the story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 20:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't always advocate for abortions, but when I do... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 20:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Primrose the baby donkey was born so prematurely that she requires bright pink casts to support her body weight until she's grown a bit more.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 20:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Black Keys using floating LEDs to create pixel rain at concerts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 19:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bizarre beauties around the globe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-19 02:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beautiful Abandoned Yugoslavian Monuments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 20:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why you should risk rejection and ask </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 20:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Laptop/hands X-Ray  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 17:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make everything ok button </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 16:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 1,024-core supercomputer models the universe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 16:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally, Mitt Romney comes clean. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 16:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> X-Ray of you right now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 04:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Human Slinky with some serious how in the F??? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 04:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 50 States of Beer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 04:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iron Man is drunk... again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 03:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Halo 4: Making of </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 03:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Avengers Sequel confirmed, directed by Joss Whedon, officially set for May 1, 2015. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 03:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robot Chicken DC Comics special </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 03:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Rob Liefeld drew Chris Evans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 02:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hyrule Historia, the Book that Exposed the Official Zelda Timeline, is Headed to an English Translation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 02:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why you don't hold shotguns like handguns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 02:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Farmer Who Lost Both Arms in Accident Spent Eight Years Building New Ones from Scrap Metal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 04:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Safe sex rap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 04:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The McGangbang </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 04:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama gets his own Swift Boat attack ad (video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 04:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Demise of Groupons crummy business model. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 04:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boy Escapes From Underwear-Clad Priest in Dahmer-esque Incident  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 04:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 70 years of Batman evolution in one infographic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 03:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mutant Butterflies Near Fukushima Linked to Nuclear Radiation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 03:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daredevil: This is a video cut from other movies and comics used as a pitch for the film director Joe Carnahan wanted to make for the Man Without Fear. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 03:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You misspelled "everything." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 03:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dark Knight Rises wedding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 02:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We're NASA and We Know It (parody of LMFAO's "Sexy and I Know It") </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 02:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas has five of the top 10 fattest cities in America:

01. Corpus Christi, TX
03. El Paso, TX
04. Dallas, TX
07. San Antonio, TX
09. Houston, TX

And yet, Austin is the 5th leanest. Damn you, Austin. You make the rest of us look bad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 23:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Academy of Villains </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 03:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disney Warrior Princesses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-14 18:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
