<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6381</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 04:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone here complains about being lonely, but they resent seeing people happy and in a relationship anyways! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 03:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what's that?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 03:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually safest with him :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No matter how tough the man, at the end of the day he needs some comfort too. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 03:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have never seen this game come up in this subreddit which surprises me, I played it for hours as a kid until I had the highest score and all of the treasure! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 19:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 06:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this one outfit with a hood and an awesome bra that makes me look like a monster haha! But it's winter in Canada and it's cold now so i can't wear tutu's and stuff, I actually need shorts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 06:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are awesome!! haha :) I love seeing themes! I honestly never get pictures when i'm at raves, I do nothing but dance and glove, so this time I got a picture before i went! i'm jealous you have such an awesome pic durring the event! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 06:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for defending me! You understood exactly. I didn't claim it was original and I know others dress similarly because it's a pretty typical attire at raves now, but I still think it can be made into a lot of fun and creativity. You can't see it in the picture but i'm also wearing a homemade mask and light up bow. So it's crafting too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 20:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I invite anyone to post their costumes below!!! I love seeing new ideas! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wish more people posted their fantasy outfits! My favourite part about events is dressing in a way you wouldn't anywhere else and see other peoples costume ideas! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 19:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 15:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A quick, to the point answer. Something I appreciate :) thanks! that's pretty cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why does it hurt so much to bite down on tinfoil or other metallic objects if you have a metal filling? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 14:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 02:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think overbites are cute for some reason! But Olivia Wilde is a good example. Maybe i have less to worry about than i previously assumed haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 02:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look better without them, it draws the attention to your eyes which are very nice :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 02:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well that's my smile so.... bummer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
