<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8279</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This generation will have their entire life (from birth) digitally photographed and recorded and most likely shared online. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 05:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 06:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to wait until your teammate passes it to you. As soon as his foot touches the ball, that where your relative position on the field counts. In this case, it should be behind the last defender. If you look at the video on YouTube you can see he was good to go and used his speed and perfect timing to catch up to the ball </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 01:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then what is conscious of our consciousness? Kind of like a torch in a dark room. (Torch is awareness) when you shine your light at an on object in a dark room (say a chair), you then have perception of an object. But what is aware of the torch (awareness/consciousness/brain)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 16:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you can break them if you feel they are unjust. Not saying it's correct or incorrect. It just is. Slavery, inequality, etc. Not at the same level but same concept.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 20:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take all the legal advice everyone is recommending. A lawyer is a must here. From a father's POV, if that IS your kid, then man up quick and take responsibility. The kid is going to NEED a father in their life who is there for them REGARDLESS of what adult problems happened along the way. It's going to be ok man. Whatever happens, have integrity, take responsibility, and keep your chin up. Judging from what you have already posted, you seem to head strong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
