<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1033</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girl, Rand Paul Will Drone You All Night Long </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 23:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Ryans Sole Intern Is The Delightful Sextortin Sociopath You Expected Him To Be </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 23:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whatever happened to the Amero? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 03:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what's the latest on the NAU? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PATRIOT ALERT!!1! Reddit user claims he's going to organize a "Million Gun March" on Washington DC, then overthrow the United States government. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 20:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Liberty Village cannot afford the "Peace and Quiet Insurance" our local warlord provides. The sonic pain cannons begin tomorrow morning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 01:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A LPT for FWP: Dealing with Messy Burgers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 23:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet This Nice GOP Pennsylvania Mayor Who Tried to Rape a Young Man at Gunpoint </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 18:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confederate History Month: Celebrating Racists, Traitors, and Slavers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 17:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas passes anti-abortion bill declaring life begins 'at fertilization' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 15:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas House Passes Sweeping Anti-Abortion Bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 10:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge orders morning-after pill available without prescription </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-05 15:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alabama Senate passes bill tightening rules for abortion clinics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 04:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is daily life like in North Korea? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-30 12:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colorado Department of Corrections Chief Shot Dead in Home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 12:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1.6 Billion Rounds of Ammo for Homeland Security? It's Time to Have a National Conversation About Prepper Paranoia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 01:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wayne LaPierre: Obama Wants National Registry To Take Away Guns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-24 21:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think there might be antifreeze in the wine I bought from Liberty Vineyards. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-23 03:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Court Convicts International Liberty-Lovers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-23 03:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Koch World Reboots After 2012 Election Failures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-20 12:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Defeating "Southernomics" is the key to restoring the American economy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-19 22:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are so many exorcised over the use of "drones"? Is it somehow worse than when manned aircraft ran the very same missions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-19 20:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The local Freedom Doctor turned my wife away because we didn't have any chickens. Her appendix burst and she died. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 08:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I kept my grandson free from the tyranny of the statists and their "polio vaccinations." Now I have to rig up an iron lung to keep him alive. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 02:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone have any DIY plans? Can I use a kerosene-driven motor? (We're off grid.)

I figure I can salvage an old refrigerator by cutting a hole in the top for his head and then sealing the gap around his neck with rubber from salvaged retreads (along with duct tape to make a good, tight pressure seal.)

Also, is it feasible to combine this setup with a composting toilet? If I can avoid opening the fridge door more than once a year or so to hose out his filth, I'd *really* like to avoid it. (I'm very self-reliant and it is going to be a *real* pain to aim the hose with one hand while manually pumping his oxygen bag with the other, especially with him hanging there by his neck/head like a baseball bat hanging in a rack.)

To be frank this is a **lot** more hassle than an rugged individual like myself is used to. What I really need are Volunteerists to preserve this young man's life. If you *insist* on compensation, I can throw a few Bitcoins your way once in a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Ronpaulshomepage.com" is now LIVE! A must-see for all Liberty-Lovers.
 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 21:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The greatest Liberty website you'll ever see! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 21:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ronpaulshomepage.com goes live! AWESOME! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 21:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steven Seagal/Joe Arpaio collaborate to keep Arizona schools safe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 00:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We're Saved! Steven Seagal Training Sheriff Joe Arpaios Posse on School Security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 00:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We're Saved! Steven Seagal Training Sheriff Joe Arpaios Posse on School Security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 00:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't get my Ron Paul Newsletters delivered anymore because there is no Postal Service. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 20:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I tried to launch a multinational petroleum conglomerate from my shed, but Exxon and BP (allied with the Statists) used "regulatory capture" to freeze me out of the market. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 19:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vending machines won't take my gold nuggets  they only accept worthless fiat currency. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 19:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Despite my "No Solicitors" sign, a Girl Scout violated my property rights and the NAP by ringing my doorbell.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 17:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the Castle Doctrine apply? Should I "Stand My Ground"? Can I blow her away? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My daughter is dating a Keynesian. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 17:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of my Debt Slaves wants the day off to give birth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 15:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Republican consultant, off the record, on the Tea Party wing:  "Theres a lot of underbrush that has to be cleaned out . . . the cranks, haters and bigots." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 06:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got a papercut while turning a page in "Atlas Shrugged" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 21:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Libertarian Paradise Update: 'Suicide blast' at offices of Somalia's leadership </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 10:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gunman kills officer, wounds two deputies after fatal trailer fire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 09:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hero Patriot Ted Nugent on Vietnam in interviews: 1977 vs. 2013 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 03:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ted in 1977, to *High Times* magazine:

"I got my physical notice 30 days prior to. Well, on that day I ceased cleansing my body. No more brushing my teeth, no more washing my hair, no baths, no soap, no water. Thirty days of debris build. I stopped shavin and I was 18, had a little scraggly beard, really looked like a hippie. I had long hair, and it started gettin kinky, matted up. Then two weeks before, I stopped eating any food with nutritional value. I just had chips, Pepsi, beer-stuff I never touched-buttered poop, little jars of Polish sausages, and Id drink the syrup, I was this side of death, Then a week before, I stopped going to the bathroom. I did it in my pants. poop, piss the whole shot. My pants got crusted up."

Ted in 2013, to the media at a Las Vegas Gun Show: 

"But here is what is wrong with America today. We have a president, and everybody better write this down, and memorize this. The president of the United States goes to the Vietnam Memorial Wall and pretends to honor 58,000 American heroes who died fighting communism and then he hires, appoints and associates with communists. He pretends to pay honor to men who died fighting communism, and then he hangs out with, hires and appoints communists. He is an evil dangerous man who hates America and hates freedom. And we need to fix this as soon as possible."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is no question that the tides have shifted. The time is now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 11:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2013: The Year of Linux on the Desktop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could steer a major disaster into a certain country (or region, or state) and its populace, who would it be and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 10:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iowa GOP members caught on live mic deriding the crazy, give-a-handgun-to-a-schizophrenic bill. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 02:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any way to view Reddit so it doesn't appear to be a web page from 1996? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 19:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mitch McConnell Campaign Email: Obama Wants To Take Your Guns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 17:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ayn Rand is for Children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 16:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron Paul Action Figure! OMG SO COOL! - YouTube </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-18 06:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what's the deal with this "Webpages are not responding" business in Safari? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-13 07:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once or twice a day . . . well, you know.

Also a fair amount of unexplained beachballing.

Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former MS Gov. Haley Barbour linked to deadly barbeque shootout   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 10:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TN Suspends Handgun Carry Permit Of Tactical Response "Start Killing People" CEO  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 23:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rep. Michele Bachmann (R-MN) still hasnt paid presidential campaign staffers  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 02:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dick Armey confirms "Tea Party" Payola Scandal; FreedomWorks made direct payments to both Rush Limbaugh and Glenn Beck. Thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-05 01:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LIARS! Ron Paul Won! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 22:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why The Violence Against Women Act Died  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 22:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are the Ron Paul Newsletters of such great significance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 02:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they are the only time Ron Paul has been truly honest about what he believes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Question for Eisenhower-style Republicans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-30 23:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your sincere opinions on the "Tea Party," End-Timer Evangelicals, and the general "if lib'ruls is fer it, I'm 'gainst it" Archie Bunker-types that have come to dominate/define the Party?

Do you have any reasonable hope/chance of reclaiming the Party, or will it require a major political realignment for any sort of sensible, reasonable Conservatism to take hold? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Question for Eisenhower-style Republicans:  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-30 02:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your sincere opinions on the "Tea Party," End-Timer Evangelicals, and the general "if lib'ruls is fer it, I'm 'gainst it" Archie Bunker-types that have come to dominate/define the Party?

Do you have any reasonable hope/chance of reclaiming your Party, or will it require a major political realignment for any sort of sensible, reasonable Conservatism to take hold?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Essential Reading for All Liberty-Lovers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 02:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atty: Hobby Lobby Won't Offer Morning-After Pill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 03:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do so many on the American Right call themselves "pro-life" when they are in reality "pro-birth"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-27 02:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They seem to lose all interest in children post-birth, to say nothing of their persistent contempt for the mothers.

Why? Is it similar to the fetishization of puppies and kittens, which often mutates into the neglect and dispossession of millions of dogs and cats?

What happens to the "Respecting a Culture of Life^TM" crowd after "God's Littlest Angels^TM" are launched into a world of neglect and abuse that these "pro-lifers" have created for them with their toxic, regressive politics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican Senator/Practicing Mormon Mike Crapo (R-ID) Arrested for Drunken Driving  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-24 05:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most beneficial thing honest, law-abiding gun owners can do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-21 22:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ***RESIGN THE NRA.***

Then, vow ***never*** to give them another penny of your money, ***EVER***.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indiana Man with 47 Guns Arrested After Elementary School Threat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 19:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where is the National Rifle Association's Wayne LaPierre hiding? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 17:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why isn't he on the Sunday morning news shows? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Merry Christmas! -- from the National Rifle Association </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 01:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Make sure to check the list twice!](http://www.latimes.com/news/nation/nationnow/la-na-nn-sandy-hook-shooting-victims-20121215,0,1042668.story) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "If Roger Ailes Does It, It Isn't a Scandal" - POLITICO.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-05 22:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Media Scandal: Fox News Chief Attempted to Enlist Gen. Petraeus as Presidential Candidate - Washington Post's Bob Woodward </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-05 01:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five takeaways from the Fox News-David Petraeus conspiracy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-05 01:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do the French really believe that Jerry Lewis is a genius? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-29 18:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Politics at the Thanksgiving Table: Share Your Stories! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-23 08:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was everyone able to get along, or did your crazy right-wing relatives roll out the bizarre conspiracy theories?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did your right-wing relatives disrupt Thanksgiving today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-23 07:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron Paul Departs With Our Constitution Has Failed - [Comment Gold!] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 08:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OH NOES!!1! I was banned from r/Paul!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 16:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if it's because I posted this?

http://mypetjawa.mu.nu/archives/over-lution.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adobe Flash keeps trying to do a "Security Update." Can it be safely ignored? Can I delete Flash entirely? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 04:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to see this shitware driven from the face of the Earth. Can I safely ignore it, or is it a valid "security update"?

Better yet, can I delete Adobe Flash entirely from my Mac? Any special steps? Since we're in an HTML 5 world now, I don't see the point of even having it.

Thanks in advance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mitt Romneys Guide To Flood Management </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-30 22:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Windows 8 My Balls. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-27 08:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Windows 8 My Balls. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-27 05:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Windows 8 My Balls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-25 18:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron Paul campaign spent $718,000 last month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-19 09:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Libertarians could be spoilers in key Senate races </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-15 17:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wisconsin GOP Lawmaker: "Some Girls Rape Easy." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-12 00:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Romney vows to be 'a pro-life president' after newspaper interview </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-10 23:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Longtime GOP Operative Trailed by Voter Fraud Claims - NYTimes.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-05 04:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whatever became of "Disturbing Search Requests"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-02 06:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bloggers would report the strange, disturbing, morbid and often profane search strings that searchers had used which led to their webpages.



Is there any current equivalent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Say Glenn Beck May Have Raped and Murdered a Young Girl in 1990. Has Glenn Beck Ever Addressed this Issue?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 21:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron Paul campaign's busy August - POLITICO.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 03:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> August Numbers Show Ron Paul Campaign Ceaseless in its Pursuit of Liberty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 23:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chuck Woolery, Tea Party Ranter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 00:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron Paul Fan Club Reunion Set for This Weekend in TN </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-14 07:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Ron Paul Spammers Just Can't Realize. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 18:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They just don't get that they've violated the "Non-Spamggression Principle."

If they had just left everyone on the Internet alone and gone about their own business, everything would have been just fine.

But after millions and millions and millions more of provacative, deliberate, and direct violations of the "Non-Spamggression Principle," they forced our hand. A man can only take so much Spamggression before he stands up for himself and fights the PaulSpam Machine.

We're just defending ourselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joe Arpaio's "Birtherpalooza" Cancelled Due to Low Ticket Sales </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 17:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is our satellite technology advanced enough to find future "Oetzis" as ice continues to recede? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-08 21:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Lindsey Graham (R-SC): "The demographics race we're losing badly. We're not generating enough angry white guys to stay in business for the long term." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 05:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Lindsey Graham (R-SC): "The demographics race we're losing badly. We're not generating enough angry white guys to stay in business for the long term." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 05:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Day Two of P.A.U.L.Fest is in the Books! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-26 08:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Ustream PaulFest chat disabled, or is it "technical difficulties"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-26 04:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yellow Bag Lady: America's New Shining Beacon of Liberty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-26 02:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pictures from "The Greatest Celebration of Liberty Ever." Add your own! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-25 08:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So . . . what do you guys think about Day One of P.A.U.L.Fest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-25 08:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What accounts for the American Right's massive obsession with microscopic cum-boogers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 16:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican platform salutes Va. abortion law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 05:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PaulFest: Only ONE WEEK Away! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 00:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHOO-HOO!!!

Many of you are on the road to Tampa right now! Let's see your pictures! Post links to your blogs! (Starbucks and McDonald's have free Wi-Fi so you can check in from the road.)

How many vehicles are in your Ronvoy? I hope you all brought your signs and are posing for lots of pictures at roadside attractions to spread the message of Liberty!

Can't wait to see you all! Where is everyone staying? Tell us your stories! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Within seconds of texting someone, they will often call me wanting to talk. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 10:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I wanted to/were available to talk, I would have called rather than texted.

Why do people insist on doing this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Camp Liberty" in Tampa has been cancelled. :'( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 03:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atlas Teabagged: Romney chooses darling of the American Right, Paul Ryan.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-11 08:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goodbye Florida. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atlas Teabagged: Romney chooses Ryan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-11 07:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> By choosing Paul Ryan, Mitt Romney just lost Florida. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-11 07:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once the seniors of Florida find out about Paul Ryan's plans to dismantle Social Security and Medicare, it's even more over for Mitt than it was before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atlas Teabagged: Paul Ryan is Romney's VP choice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-11 07:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only TWO WEEKS Until PaulFestival in Tampa! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-11 00:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please post where you're from and how you'll be getting to Tampa (plane, bus, Ronvoy, car, etc.)

If you're going by car, some of you may be on the road already. Are you keeping a blog of your travels? If not, start! Post links here so we can all see them!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EPS: It's *really* unfair to compare Ron Paul's followers to Adolf Hitler and the Nazis.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-08 08:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After all, Hitler's followers were able to successfully plan and carry out rallies in support of their candidate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only Three Weeks Left Until PaulFestival! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-02 15:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are people getting excited out there?

This event has so much potential to make the Liberty Movement even more well-known. Thank you Dr. Paul for making it all possible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Damned Statists Emerge in Somalia! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-01 22:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CRTL+OPT+COMMAND+8 no longer switches to "night mode" in Mountain Lion.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 04:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know the new shortcut? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Get PaulFest Back on Schedule and on Budget. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-25 09:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Libertarians should form an alliance with the Church of Scientology and get SEA ORG on the job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exactly One Month Until Paul Festival Begins in Tampa! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-25 02:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you bought your tickets? How are you getting there? The lineup of bands and speakers looks pretty awesome. Are there any hotels offering special Paul Festival rates? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Paul Supporters: When did you first realize that you'd been taken in by a Confederate huckster? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-22 02:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it when you learned of the Ron Paul Newsletters?

Was it the Moneybombs begging you for your "worthless fiat currency" rather than gold?

Was it when you realized he'd been a longtime compatriot of American White Nationalists?

Please share your stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Paultards: When exactly did you realize that you were a fool for worshipping a Confederate huckster? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-21 01:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please share your stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Road to Paulville. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-12 23:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Rick Perry planning another rain dance for August? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-12 22:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been almost a year since Perry organized "the Response" to beg God for rain in Texas.

Is he going to do it again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analysis: This was Mitt Romney's "Sister Souljah" Moment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-12 00:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just as Bill Clinton distanced himself from the "Jesse Jackson" wing of the Democratic Party by criticizing Sister Souljah's Black Nationalist lyrics, Mitt Romney's criticism of "ObamaCare" [a deliberate, derisive term the American Right has sought to implant as strongly negative in America's id] was designed to get the NAACP booing at him, thus strengthening the resolve of his own Party's Obama-haters. This will get Mitt Romney donations and volunteers, as well as convey a much wider message.

The Republican dog-whistle: "if *those people* think 'ObamaCare' is good, *you* should hate it, because *'morbidly obese welfare queens in new Cadillacs with 8 kids with 8 different fathers buying vodka at the liquor store with Food Stamps'*."

Just think how many thousands of times Fox News and American Right SuperPACs will run this from this moment up until the election, reference it in their blogs, and AM-spam it 24 hours a day. Look at what they did with the "New Black Panthers" clip, for example.

To deny that this was a calculated move on the Romney campaign's part would be as foolish as denying that Bill Clinton's "Sister Souljah" speech was meant to clearly separate the modern Democratic Party from any association with the rhetoric of the Extremist Left of the late 1960s. (It's important to note that most people had never heard of Sister Souljah before, or since.) Both were messages sent out to/clearly received by their respective intended multiple audiences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Image: Mitt Romney Clowning Around with a Gun. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-11 21:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vast Deposits of Gold and Other Ores Lure Seabed Miners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-10 00:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guise! GUISE!!! PaulFest is now accepting sponsors! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 00:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be a part of history...
Details
Published on Tuesday, 03 July 2012 17:37
 Request Sponsorship Information for PAUL FESTIVAL NOW!!!

Paul Festival is now accepting Sponsors!
Become part of history as you take part in the largest festival for freedom the world has ever seen! 

Celebrating Ron Paul's 77th birthday, as well as his lifetime of achievements; promoting freedom and liberty and inspiring a movement! Paul Festival is all about unity and strives to bring a diverse group of people together in celebration of the philosophy of liberty. 

Paul Festival will be held at the Florida State Fairgrounds in Tampa, FL, August 24th,25th,26th with a capacity of over 50,000 attendees.  The Festival will be held on two stages, one indoor and the other a massive outdoor stage for big acts.  Additionally there will be 275 indoor vendors booths and additional 20 outdoor vendor booths available.  VIP Tents will be set up and campaign and RV parking is available at the fairgrounds. 

We have a sponsorship package for any type of budget and hope you will join us is making this a successful event!  Your sponsorship package will get your company logo featured on our website, or our printed material such as flyers and brochures and your logo and mention on our social media sites.  All Sponsors will receive the following:

Company or organization name/logo on:

All written materials.
Paul Festival Official Website
Paul Festival Official Social Media Sites
Paul Festival poster and rack cards.
Additionally:

10x10 Booth
Event T-shirts
Three day passes to the event
Gold and Silver Sponsors will receive all the benefits listed above plus more!

SPONSOR PAUL FESTIVAL NOW!

Do you want even more exposure? 
Become a Presenting Sponsor!

Imagine when it is Paul Festival Presented by (Your Company)!!  Request a sponsorship package today and become part of it all;  Paul Festival will be a family oriented event with a children's activity area and will feature great speakers, bands, comedians from up and coming to some of the big names!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the latest on PaulFestival? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-05 18:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Three Daddies: California Eyes Multiple Parenting Law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-03 23:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Religious Right Wingnut Apocalypse is Here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-03 23:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Observation: Libertarians are the Scientologists of Politics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-02 16:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When will PaulFest be cancelled? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-02 06:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Submit your guesses.

As always  please, no wagering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In This Thread: please copy/paste the best "Right-Winger Absolutely Blowing a Gasket over ObamaCare Decision" comments. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-28 17:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And not just from Reddit.

Paste the ones you find from all over the web. (Be sure to give proper credit.)

Alternatively, summarize any crazed rants from friends/family/co-workers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron Paul Sat Out 1992, Endorsed Pat Buchanan for the Republican Nomination </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-26 19:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many of you were aware of this?

http://www.tnr.com/sites/default/files/January1992.pdf

Lew Rockwell and Murray Rothbard backed Ron on this:

http://www.tnr.com/sites/default/files/RRR.pdf
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PaulTards Continue to Throw Away their Money: Ron Paul Raised $1.78M in May </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-19 14:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cast Your Ballot for Ron Paul HERE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-16 06:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else care to share their Ron Paul ink? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paultard Boasts About Horrible, Prison-Quality Tattoo Containing Misattributed Quote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-14 18:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Revealed: the Mantra of Denial that Loops in Republicans' Minds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 23:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *The Sixties never happened.*

*The Sixties never happened.*

*The Sixties never happened.*

*The Sixties never happened.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And Here Is A Youthful, Smiling Mitt Romney Pointing A Gun At His Jaw </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-29 23:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How badly will Ron Paul get his ass kicked tomorrow in the Texas Republican Primary? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-28 23:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As they know his record the best, I think he'll get clobbered in every county. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's a great chance for the Liberty-Minded. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-28 02:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this the Competing Currency the Rontroopers are Looking For? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-22 06:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Q: Why do Paulbearers hate Keynes so much? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-21 21:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A: They've never heard of Galbraith. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can a politician be judged by those he associates with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-17 23:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Why, yes. Yes he can.](http://newsone.com/1748295/top-10-racist-ron-paul-friends-supporters/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Q: Why did President Lincoln drop Hannibal Hamlin as VP for his second term? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-17 21:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mr. Anonymous   the Origins of the Libertarian Movement  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-17 20:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the cause of the GOP's endless fascination with preserving, protecting, and defending cumboogers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-16 22:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a shame they have ***ZERO*** regard for mothers and their children *post-birth* as they do in dictating their radical belief that blastocysts are sentient beings.

Nonetheless, there are a lot of good, honest, sincere Republicans out there. If any of them are reading and would care to address this, we'd all really like to know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
