<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4565</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 20:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, Jak 2 had the worst checkpoint system of any game I have ever played. It's one of the hardest games out there IMO. Jak 3 is fantastic, though easy in comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 20:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This art](http://cdn1.gamepur.com/images/feature/the-last-of-us-2-concept-art.jpg) by a former Naughty Dog employee (which might have been from the sequel development) *might* make you change your mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 20:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This World Ain't Big Enough for the Last of Us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 12:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (spoiler: yes) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 12:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ellie has more story left in her. Next game should be about Ellie becoming an adult. That concept art featuring [17-18 year old Ellie with a guitar](http://cdn1.gamepur.com/images/feature/the-last-of-us-2-concept-art.jpg) (Joel said he'd teach her) is amazing. She's got a long life ahead of her, being immune to the infection.     
**Edit: provided link** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 12:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only on the Season Pass or Remastered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 03:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's slang. You read it properly, therefore it worked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 02:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot they changed the name :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 01:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also the most fun platinum I've ever had. It's extremely short, but the battle arenas are extremely fun and challenging. You have to complete every challenge for the platinum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 01:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember to play on Hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 00:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ewww, that was clearly an effects bugger-up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 00:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ditto here actually, except I didn't see the beginning of Season 3 (the first seven episodes) until after Season 4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 20:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah, as a massive fan who thought he knew everything about the show, my mind was just blown to pieces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 20:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait...is that why she and Jack boned the night before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 20:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Different territories? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 00:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facebook vs North Korea is the showdown the world needs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 22:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dies. Totally worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 12:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I maintain that The Brig (3.19) is a highly underrated episode of TV and possibly one of the best of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 07:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the original and I'm definitely curious, so thanks! Probably going to hate it but at least I'll have seen it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 05:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Played the games before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 05:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easily the hardest Insanity mission for me was the Collector trap. I spent hours on that. It's the second hardest video game level I've ever played. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 05:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It took a long, long time for me. That 1% will move along. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] About something that has always confused me... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 22:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So...when Isabella, Jacob and MIB's mother, Ben's mother etc. appear to our characters, are they themselves?     
When and when aren't they themselves?    
Appearances I specifically want clarification on:    
+ Isabella - On the Black Rock (because that is her at the end of the episode, right?)   
+ The twins' birth mother    
+ Ben's mother    
+ Christian to Michael    
+ Ana Lucia when she pulls Hurley over    
+ Libby constantly haunting Michael </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 21:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now play Grounded difficulty :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 09:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After Grounded, I first went back through chapter select to get all collectibles (never overwrite your main save!), and I've finally finished Grounded Plus today.      
I initially took 22 hours on Grounded (wasted over an hour on the bookstore trying to trigger the joke), but I only took 13 and a half on Grounded Plus. It's much easier knowing your previous methods. Still need to go through Easy++ for weapon upgrades, but only up to the suburbs for the Shorty.     
My advice: go for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 04:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or viewers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 04:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which was the one with his seahorse, Mystery?     
"Wee-snaw!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 08:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they really change the name in the US to Sorcerer's Stone? Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 06:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started played TLoU just over three months after I finished Mass Effect 3 (I'd only played 2   3 at the time, once each). Gotta say I was initially disappointed. The trophy structure was bad, the story progression felt forced (having no choices) and I just wasn't that into the gameplay.     
However, after having played so many games since October 2013, I recently picked up Remastered for pretty cheap. I gave up on Survivor difficulty earlier this year because I lost interest (wasn't even very hard); so this time I jumped straight into the new Grounded mode and it's an entirely different game in that it literally feels more "Grounded" in reality. The stakes are higher because resources and ammo are so scarce. I felt an actual connection to the characters because of it. The character deaths don't seem groan worthy anymore. I'm replaying it on Grounded+ after collecting all collectibles and conversations on chapter select.     
What I'd suggest to you is to come back to it in a few months on Grounded and struggle through that. It makes the game feel so much more genuine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 05:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're playing the PC version of AC2 or the Game of the Year edition on any platform, you already have the DLC integrated into the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 21:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right; nowhere close to two months. Less than 5/8ths of it.     
And, yeah, shit should work at launch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 10:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20mb patch upfront and nothing since, which is pretty fantastic for those who have data caps (Unity's updates being gigabytes each and crucial for the game to function is pretty ridiculous). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 05:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Nothing brewing" is a very vague sentence, though. "We have nothing to announce" is what they said about TLoUR on Beyond's Left Behind interview, when we now know they'd been working on it for the better part of a year. It's what Bioware's Aaryn Flynn said about Mass Effect Remastered right before he went on Neogaf and asked everybody for their wishlists.     
Let's keep hoping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 07:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Interstellar spoiler](/s "In hindsight, that does spoil the ending a bit.") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 07:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Breaking Bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 10:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would have been disappointing. I like the allusion to the beginning where Joel is running through the hospital carrying Ellie, alluding to him running with Sarah at the beginning. He calls both of them "baby girl" and they're all soldiers with assault rifles and flashlights, just like the one who killed Sarah. It's all so chilling and powerful and emotionally charged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 04:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It must be tough for people who aren't massive zombies fans. My mates and I just got most of them automatically on local co-op, and Sacrificial Lamb took one try while we were biding time. Can't imagine getting the Dead Ops trophies, though. Arcade is boring.     
Good job on Veteran, though! I shudder thinking about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 02:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not out in the US? I was wondering why it wasn't getting much attention. Those 1v1 fights are so good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 02:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy gets it. The title should have been *(Spoilers) The best scene in Gone Girl* or something. It's too specific. She does something with a boxcutter and it involves the heaviest possible spoilers. Most people would believe she's hardly in the movie especially since the title is "Gone Girl". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 02:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Otherwise it wouldn't be called the boxcutter scene, it would be called the box scene. Exactly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 23:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They must all be provided with visually attractive templates. [This video is really good](http://youtu.be/VXJiBkFgprQ). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 22:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They originally said "other books". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 22:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might be an AC Unity situation where they kept the original pressing date in early October but delayed the game so they could patch it. The Order was supposed to be released this year, so this is actually rather likely. You know what that means: MASSIVE DAY ONE PATCH! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 20:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your money would be better spent elsewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 19:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Revelations will be impossible. Matchmaking still doesn't work, and it's even worse now no one plays on it :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 19:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may be completely right (and probably are). Nonetheless, it's a suggestive title because it points out that the scene where she uses a sharp object is a scene involving, in OP's words, the heaviest spoilers possible.    
All I ask is that you don't shower me with downvotes :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 19:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's quite suggestive if you haven't seen it. I'm not trying to argue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 19:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on what you're after. If you want an even story, this is not it. The weak ending cheapens the better moments of the game. AC fans, like myself, are disappointed with the story. It was not made with franchise fans in mind.     
I wouldn't recommend it. How cheap is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 19:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article is basically a link to another. Why not post *that*? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 19:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks just like the poster for Battleship, and 30 other movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 19:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a contextual spoiler. Saying there's a really powerful scene that she uses a sharp object is a spoiler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 19:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *It doesn't?!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 19:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That movie was made to put people into depression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 18:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not reading the text because I haven't seen the film. Don't put that there's a boxcutter scene in the film. I'd suggest reposting without that in the title, because knowing she's dealing with sharp objects feels like a spoiler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 08:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heartwarming episode right here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 08:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Photo mode was also great for surveying your surroundings during forces combat on Grounded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 08:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Last of Us was *more* cinematic at 60fps, ffs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 08:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Graphics-wise? Not too much (considering it was always stunning), but get it for 60 frames-per-second, 1080p, fantastic story dlc, most multiplayer dlc and the new difficulty level. Remastered has it all, while PS3 version is just the base game and you won't get an online pass with any used copies, so possibly not even multiplayer. Gladly, Remastered doesn't require a pass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 08:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never. It didn't even redeem any of my progress in Uplay actions until after I completed the game.     
In fact, after a few weeks my entire profile was wiped and I was pushed up to level 13 (where I should have been the whole time). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 07:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A week, infrequent play for me. Played through 100% on good, got all good karma trophies, then played through on hard as evil, got all random evil karma trophies, finished game again. One of my easiest platinums. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 07:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You actually can hide it from your account, but only through using a PS3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 07:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhh, my first platinum. Loved this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 04:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't remember the Man in Black's name because he never had a name :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 02:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edge of Tomorrow takes place over three days, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 02:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inside porno mags.     
EDIT: Well, now my comment isn't funny anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 23:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'll make the bet that Hank will die and it will motivate Hope to become the new Wasp (her mother being the first). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 20:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Delicate one is magnificent. Doesn't Hurley's discman break at the end of that one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 20:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are some pretty ambitious platinums. I'd think Shadow of Mordor would be the one least likely to drive you insane. So, SoM would be my suggestion.     
Last of Us requires you to play the great but depressing story mode more than twice and I think more than a month in consecutive days of multiplayer. GTA V requires you to get to Level 100 online. Dragon Age almost certainly requires over 100 hours of gameplay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 09:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last four episodes of Season 3 are widely regarded as the high point of the entire series. You're up to a point where you might watch only episodes 3.13 - "The Man from Tallahasse", then 3.19 - "The Brig". A character disappears between these episodes, and The Brig is mostly about what happened in between those episodes (though it does spoil a bit of the episodes in between). They're why Terry O'Quinn won the best supporting actor Emmy that year and they might convince you to get back on track where you left off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 09:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've watched all of the show, read the first book, I'm two quarters through the second, and I still don't care for the characters. It's like every sympathisable character is the underdog. Even when Danerys became the one on top in Season 3, Season 4 comes around and now it's about her actually kinda *not really* being on top of things. Her storyline goes backwards.      
Look, the dialogue, the production and the direction are all fantastic. There are characters, but there's hardly a plot. It's all subplot. Some people like that though and that's perfectly fine with me. I still miss [spoiler](#s "Ned"). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Spoilers) Favourite episode of the entire show (that isn't The Constant or Through the Looking Glass)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 09:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **What's your favourite episode of the show (excluding the two common favourites)?**    
And, don't diss my non-American spelling of favourite ;)     
     
Mine's definitely The Brig. Ties up Locke and Sawyer's deepest issues with one of the best scenes of the entire show: the death of Anthony Cooper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 08:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the deep trailer voice *did* say "sometimes". Oh well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 05:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'd have to be an indie title or free-to-play. You'd die pretty quickly, so fun might wear out faster for some. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 04:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In many regions, Disc 7 has Exodus part 3 - in the US, that's included in Disc 6's Part 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 04:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They made it out of sheer determination, obviously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 04:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Advice: Watch the first three episodes in succession! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 04:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Pfffffft*. Yeah? And where is it "hidden" - their wrist or something? What a terrible idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 04:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were pretty good, but this is an awesome poster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 04:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But she's not a man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 01:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Third one has some pretty good parts but it was too wacky and tried to hard to be sentimental at the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 00:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With Camilla Ludddington back, hopefully? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 00:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much better than any other promotional material they've released. Has anyone heard the *horrible* tagline in that 15 second teaser?     
***SOMETIMES THE BEST MAN FOR THE JOB...IS A WOMAN.*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 00:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The /Filmcast! For movies fans obviously. These guys are really relatable and don't take themselves too seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 04:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arno and Elise have great actors, but their arcs are far too messy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 22:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you planned on the ally trophies from the start? God, I've completed it on Insanity without any ally trophies. I can't imagine playing the game 3 more fucking times ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 21:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, nothing to address the ridiculous amount of bugs in Remastered single player? Hunters jumping through boarded up or closed windows, psychic and instantly materialising runners, Henry not moving at all when he's supposed to help you, prompts not appearing, prompts appearing and not activating etc.     
EDIT: Friendly AI walking in front of you straight away at the beginning of a bloater fight when you should be lining up a quick shot (Bill, you prick), friendly AI running in circles, friendly AI phasing through you (I told you Ellie, you're not actually Ellen Page), hunters never noticing friendly AI when they run into them and against them, clickers not noticing friendly AI when they push into them (Bill, you're still a prick), hunters *not* noticing you when you choke out the person right next to them etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 07:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got platinum for 2  amp; 3, but, 1? Yeah that's way too much time. Insanity was enough for me.     
Good job persisting! What was your process? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 03:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 80s action movies in general then :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 02:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No shame in plugging :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 22:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gladly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 20:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the horses chase, kind of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 20:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's an extra gold trophy. I want it :) There are so many parts to bypass, but some of them force you into combat. It's cruel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 11:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both: my first platinum - Mass Effect 2. Because having my ass handed to me on Insanity and eventually overcoming all of my weaknesses was one of the greatest gaming experiences I've ever had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 11:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm playing Grounded, and man it's soooo cheap. Starting the generator in the hotel: no matter what you do, a runner immediately comes up behind you if you haven't grabbed the keycard. You need to have full health to survive that at all.    
Not to mention that all infected are psychic and that you will, thousands of times, watch a stealth-killed hunter drop a loaded weapon and you'll have no way to use their ammo because their gun vanishes into thin air. Fuck Grounded.     
I can't imagine the patience the platinum takes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 10:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How far in did you get? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 10:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starts out painfully average, then BOOM: Fitz/Simmons feels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 10:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Close. From what I've gathered, Marvel Studios' new Netflix shows will definitely be set in this universe (there's no evidence to the contrary, so there won't be a source to confirm it); though I highly doubt they'll impact anything else, so you're sort of right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 10:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The Brig", "The Man Behind the Curtain", "Greatest Hits" and "Through the Looking Glass" are the last four episodes of Season 3, and all pretty much A+. Best succession of episodes in any TV show in my opinion. Breaking Bad S4's final four are fantastic as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 07:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He provided his voice to the E3 trailer, so the immortal Sullivan will undoubtedly be back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 06:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Living Daylights is crucial for anyone who loves the Uncharted games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 05:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The end of Season 3 (the last four or so episodes in succession) is up there as some of the best television ever made. Easily the best use of flashbacks in the entire series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 05:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For anyone who doesn't get it, Credit Where Credit is Due plays when the first "Starring" *credits* begin showing along the bottom of the screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
