<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8834</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-01 04:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the best things I have ever read on Reddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-30 04:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real laughter was produced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-29 18:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am going to go against the grain and say Ned Stark would make an amazing King. Ask yourself where we would be today in the world of Westeros if Ned was king instead of Robert. The kingdom would not be in debt, no bastard children, the people would be well taken care of and justice would be handled properly. I also don't see treachery getting as close to Ned as it did Robert, as the latter made increasingly bad decisions over the course of years (as king, and with his wife) to end up in the situation that he was in.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-26 21:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like...shaving? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-26 18:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless of whether you agree with the current wars we are involved in, the man is putting his life on the line in the defense of our nation. That deserves thanks. 

EDIT: Not saying you were disrespecting him or anything. I apologize if it comes off that way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-26 17:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, probably $300-$400 worth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-26 17:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You probably hear this a lot, but Thank You

EDIT: ...and have an upvote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-26 14:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MEG! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-25 17:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has been a while for me, but didn't Theon claim Robb "King in the North" first in aGoT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-23 02:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That song was amazing. Also, now I suddenly have the strong urge to play a JRPG... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-17 03:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are not redoing the animations, just tweaking them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-16 23:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That seems like something to me that can be easily remedied. It is not some game breaking combat glitch or graphical issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-16 21:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As well as new melee attacks (which look to be class specific). Also weapon mods, more customization under skill trees, smarter AI, and more responsive controls.

Plus, you are also only taking into account the combat we have seen thus far. There also looks to be some pretty cool on-rails combat sequences as well as a much more epic scale to the battles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-16 20:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game doesn't come out until March, so I think there is more than enough time to smooth out the animations on characters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-16 19:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knowing BioWare, Mass Effect 3 is probably going to be a lot more than that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-16 18:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would visit newegg.com and look at some of the available laptops they have on their website. Usually there are user reviews that accompany each laptop that will speak towards their gaming performance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-16 17:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for the advice! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mass Effect 3: Squad Leader Gamescom 2011 Trailer (HD) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-16 17:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-16 17:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [For if the IGN link doesn't work...](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LQH3_Fydt-4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mass Effect 3: Squad Leader Trailer Video - Xbox 360 - IGN </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-16 17:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-15 18:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am as I. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-15 18:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second this. Could use a new desktop background.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-11 02:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not how I pictured him but HBO knows what they are doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-11 02:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly how I pictured him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confirmed: Michael McElhatton to play Roose Bolton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-10 21:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-10 18:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could only get to the 54 second mark before I could watch no more... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-10 17:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and this is the post that should be upvoted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-08 20:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will it ever stop? Yo, I don't know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-08 06:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it worked.

The only part I heard... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-05 05:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R'hollor be praised </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-27 20:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  See, it sounds like you're trying to rape them.

Sea: It sounds like you are trying to rape them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-27 20:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  See, it sounds like you're trying to rape them.

Sea: It sounds like you are trying to rape them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another theory about Jon Snow (aDwD Spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-23 14:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets just say that Jon snow was killed by his attackers, then was brought back to life. That would mean that his vows would have been fulfilled, and he no longer is bound to the Nights Watch.

*Night gathers, and now my watch begins. It shall not end until my **death**.*

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-23 14:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it was from Winterfell. In my OP, I was referring to the fact there was no raven from Winterfell sent to the king at Kings Landing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-23 05:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was never a raven sent from Winterfell bearing news of the battle to Kings Landing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-21 05:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. There should/would have been a raven from Winterfell if Stannis was defeated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-21 05:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have to agree with your last statement. Theon and Jeyne are both with Stannis last we read, so if Stannis truly was defeated then it stands to reason that he would already have found Jeyne and Theon again. 

Mance probably gave up that Jon sent him, but I doubt that in that short span he was able to defeat Stannis as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-21 05:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished aDwD and was pretty pissed off when I read that Jon was killed. You have just gave me a small glimmer of hope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-16 19:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been eyeing it up for a while, but was always afraid to click...haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How's about putting the Page # in the title of ADWD spoiler discussions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-16 06:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a thought, but I think it would allow a lot more people to discuss the events of the book without having to worry about accidently running into spoiler events from later on in the book.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-01 23:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if there was alcohol involved? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-01 23:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should be noted that you cannot have sex temporarily. I don't see this as such a big issue. The man that you are with is probably going to spend a lot of time with you "working" on your condition, so it's not like any kind of sexual interaction is off the table. Also, the potential payoff should things turn around is pretty high.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-01 16:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think was important to show these people so the reader can understand the motives behind their decisions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-01 02:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked it a lot. Jaime's chapters were great, as well as Brienne's. I also thought the way Cersei's character developed over the course of the book was pretty interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-25 18:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't count Jon as one of Catelyn's children </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
