<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3615</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. State Dept. Approves $600 Million Sale of Tank Rounds to Iraq...Over $10 Billion in Weapons for Iraq has been Approved by U.S. in 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 20:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. State Dept. Approves $600 Million Sale of Tank Rounds to Iraq...Over $10 Billion in Weapons for Iraq has been Approved by U.S. in 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 19:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Navy Exercises In Persian Gulf Bring Iran and China Closer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 09:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Air Force's Terrifying Replacement for Cluster Bombs...New munitions are slightly less likely to kill civilians </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 09:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Bombing in Afghanistan Hits 2-Year High </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 21:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ISIS Uses Ammunition Made in the United States </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 23:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just another LIE by George Tenet...In 2004, Tenet wrote 9/11 Commissioner Roemer that he flew to Texas August 17, 2001 to give a briefing to President Bush (page 2...from 9/11 Commission archives) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 02:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 1957, Syria became the first Arab country to expel an American diplomat--after they busted up a CIA plot to overthrow the Syrian government. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 03:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> from *Legacy of Ashes: The History of the CIA* by Tim Weiner (pages 137-138)...free pdf at [r/TSBD](http://np.reddit.com/r/TSBD/)

--------------

In 1949, the CIA installed a pro-American colonel, Adib Shishakli, as the Syrian leader. He won direct American military assistance along with covert financial aid. The CIA station chief in Damascus, Miles Copeland, called the colonel "a likeable rogue" who "had not, to my certain knowledge, ever bowed down to a graven image. He had, however, committed sacrilege, blasphemy, murder, adultery and theft." He lasted four years before he was overthrown by Ba'ath Party and communist politicians and military officers. 

In March 1955, Allen Dulles predicted that the country was "ripe for a military coup d'etat" supported by the agency. In April 1956, the CIA's Kim Roosevelt and his British Secret Intelligence Service (SIS) counterpart Sir George Young tried to mobilize right-wing Syrian army officers; the CIA delivered half a million Syrian pounds to the leaders of the plot. But the Suez fiasco poisoned the political climate in the Middle East, pushed Syria closer to the Soviets, and forced the Americans and the British to postpone their plan at the end of October 1956.

In the spring and summer of April 1957,they revived it. A document discovered in 2003 among the private papers of Duncan Sandys, Prime Minister Harold Macmillan's defense secretary, spells out their effort in detail.

Syria had to be "made to appear as the sponsor of plots, sabotage and violence directed against neighbouring governments," it said. CIA and SIS would manufacture "national conspiracies and various strong-arm activities" in Iraq, Lebanon, and Jordan, and blame them on Syria. They would create paramilitary factions and spark revolts among the Muslim Brotherhood in Damascus. The creation of the appearance of instability would destabilize the government; border clashes manufactured by American and British intelligence would serve as a pretext for the pro- Western armies of Iraq and Jordan to invade. The CIA and SIS envisioned that any new regime they installed would likely "rely first upon repressive measures and arbitrary exercise of power" to survive.

Roosevelt identified Abdul Hamid Serraj, the longtime chief of the Syrian intelligence service, as the most powerful man in Damascus. Serraj was to be assassinated,along with the chief of the Syrian general staff and the head of the Communist Party.

The CIA sent Rocky Stone, who had cut his teeth in the Iran operation, to serve as the new chief of station in Damascus. Accredited as a diplomat, a second secretary at the American embassy, he used promises of millions of dollars and unlimited political power to befriend officers in the Syrian army. He represented his recruits in reports to headquarters as a crack corps for an American-backed coup.

Abdul Hamid Serraj saw through Stone in a matter of weeks.
The Syrians set up a sting. "The officers with whom Stone was deal- ing took his money and then went on television and announced that they had received this money from the 'corrupt and sinister Americans' in an attempt to overthrow the legitimate government of Syria," said Curtis F. Jones, a State Department officer sent to clean up the mess Stone left behind. Serraj's forces surrounded the American embassy in Damascus, seized Stone, and interrogated him roughly. He told them everything he knew. The Syrians identified him publicly as an American spy posing as a diplomat, a veteran of the CIA's coup in Iran, and a conspirator with Syrian army officers and politicians to overthrow the government in exchange for millions of dollars in American aid.

The revelation of this "particularly clumsy CIA plot," in the words of the U.S. ambassador to Syria, Charles Yost, had consequences that reverberate today. The Syrian government formally declared Rocky Stone persona non grata. That was the first time that an American diplomat of any stripebe he a spy working undercover or a bona fide State Department officerhad been expelled from an Arab nation. In turn, the United States expelled the Syrian ambassador to Washington, the first expulsion of any foreign diplomat from Washington since World War I. The United States denounced Syria's "fabrications" and "slanders." Stone's Syrian co-conspirators, including the former president, Adib Shishakli, were sentenced to death. A purge of every military officer who had ever been associated with the American embassy followed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if the Senate/House 9/11 Investigation was Spied On (and dealt with) by the CIA-NSA-DoD? The CIA spied on the SSCI--why not the 9/11 Investigations? The 9/11 Commission also had its offices in a CIA owned building </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 23:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could the 2 year+ delay of the official 9/11 Commission also have served to allow the CIA-NSA-DoD Cabal to neutralize any individuals stepping forward with information which the Cabal didnt want to become public? 

from Page 84 of *The Commission: The Uncensored History of the 9/11 Investigation* by Philip Shenon (2008):

The offices were in a seemingly undistinguished nine-floor federal building between the White House and Georgetown. The building was secretly owned and operated by the CIA, used as downtown office space by the agency. It was ideal for the commission because it qualified as a so-called SCIF, the acronym for secure compartmentalized information facility, which meant that it had security measures that allowed for the storage of highly classified documents. Apart from witnesses called to private interviews from the commission, only people with security clearances would be allowed to enter the commission's offices; all cell phones and other electronic devices had to be left at the door. Each of the staff members at K Street was provided with two computer hard drives--one for classified information, one for unclassified information.

-------------

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Joint_Inquiry_into_Intelligence_Community_Activities_before_and_after_the_Terrorist_Attacks_of_September_11,_2001 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WH Dep Chief of Staff Josh Bolten on 9/11: Shortly after the VP confirmed the shootdown of 93, the VP placed a call to prez to let him know he did it (notes from interview, page 4) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 07:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WH Dep Chief of Staff Josh Bolten on 9/11: Shortly after the VP confirmed the shootdown of 93, the VP placed a call to prez to let him know he did it (notes from interview, page 4) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 06:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Q: The US has spent $1,000,000,000 to kill (maybe) 1,000 terrorists--how much does it cost to kill each terrorist? A: $1,000,000 to kill each terrorist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 21:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Q: If we spend $1,000,000,000 to kill 1,000 terrorists--how much does it cost to kill each terrorist? A: $1,000,000 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 21:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boeing to Cut 2,000 defense jobs in Seattle area </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 17:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Bamford (mid-1970s): Never before or since has an entire agency been the subject of a criminal investigation. Senior officials at the NSA were even read their Miranda rights. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 21:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People Are Figuring Out The MSM Dont Print The Full, Complete News--New York Times to Cut 100 Jobs...(Goodbye to CBS, NBC, ABC, CNN, FOX news as well). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 18:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. almost Bombed Its Own Syrian Allies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 21:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LIST OF CHEAP, DIRTY CONSPIRACY BOOKS--MANY FOR ONE CENT (plus delivery)... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 17:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. [*LEGACY OF ASHES: The History of the CIA*](http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0307389006/ref=s9_psimh_gw_p14_d0_i1?pf_rd_m=ATVPDKIKX0DER pf_rd_s=center-2 pf_rd_r=0WJZG9WBMNRCT1VYKEVC pf_rd_t=101 pf_rd_p=1688200382 pf_rd_i=507846) by Tim Weiner (2007)...from **ONE CENT** + $3.99 shipping in U.S.

2. [*THE BUREAU: My 30 Years in the FBI*](http://www.amazon.com/The-Bureau-thirty-years-Hoovers/dp/0393012360/ref=pd_rhf_dp_p_img_2) by William C. Sullivan (1979)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

3. [*THE WAY OF THE KNIFE: The CIA, a Secret Army and a War at the Ends of the Earth*](http://www.amazon.com/The-Way-Knife-Secret-Earth/dp/014312501X/ref=pd_cp_b_2) by Mark Mazzetti (2013)...from **$2.27 CENTS** + shipping

4. [*THE POLITICS OF LYING: Government Deception, Secrecy   Power*](http://www.amazon.com/The-Politics-Lying-Government-Deception/dp/0394479327/ref=pd_rhf_dp_p_img_5) by David Wise (1973)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

5. [*OVERTHROW: Americas Century of Regime Change from Hawaii to Iraq*](http://www.amazon.com/Overthrow-Americas-Century-Regime-Change/dp/0805082409/ref=sr_1_1?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1412090258 sr=1-1 keywords=overthrow+stephen+kinzer) by Stephen Kinzer (2006)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

6. [*THE SECRET TEAM: The CIA in Control of the U.S. and the World*](http://www.amazon.com/The-Secret-Team-Allies-Control/dp/1616082844/ref=pd_sim_b_1?ie=UTF8 refRID=0672JR0ZF8CMWWE0EREM) by L. Fletcher Prouty (2011)...from **$9.79** + shipping

7. [*FAMILY OF SECRETS: The Bush Dynasty, Americas Invisible Government and the Hidden History of the Last 50 Years*](http://www.amazon.com/Family-Secrets-Americas-Invisible-Government/dp/1608190064/ref=pd_cp_b_1) by Russ Baker (2008)...from **$1.03** + shipping

8. [*DEEP POLITICS AND THE DEATH OF JFK*](//www.amazon.com/Deep-Politics-Death-Peter-Scott/dp/0520205197/ref=sr_1_5?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1412092034 sr=1-5 keywords=peter+dale+scott) by Peter Dale Scott (1996)...from **$2.25** + shipping

9. [*9/11 and AMERICAN EMPIRE: Intellectuals Speak Out, Vol. 1*](http://www.amazon.com/11-American-Empire-Intellectuals-Speak/dp/1566566592/ref=sr_1_8?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1412092253 sr=1-8 keywords=peter+dale+scott) by Peter Dale Scott and David Ray Griffin (2006)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

10. [*9/11 SYNTHETIC TERROR*](http://www.amazon.com/11-Synthetic-Terror-Made-USA/dp/1615771115/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 qid=1412111653 sr=8-1 keywords=webster+tarpley) by Webster Tarpley (2011)...from **$11.99** + shipping

11. [*ANOTHER NINETEEN: Investigating Legitimate 9/11 Suspects*](http://www.amazon.com/Another-Nineteen-Investigating-Legitimate-Suspects/dp/1489507833/ref=pd_sim_b_2?ie=UTF8 refRID=1EM761BQPD7VKSPEQSGQ) by Kevin Ryan (2013)...from **$11.35** + shipping

11. [*CROSSFIRE: The Plot that Killed Kennedy*](http://www.amazon.com/Crossfire-Plot-That-Killed-Kennedy/dp/0881846481/ref=pd_sim_b_4?ie=UTF8 refRID=05YDCJTVTR8CYP3Y2AZ5) by Jim Marrs (1993)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

12. [*LBJ: The Mastermind of the JFK Assassination*](http://www.amazon.com/LBJ-The-Mastermind-JFK-Assassination/dp/1620876108/ref=pd_sim_b_2?ie=UTF8 refRID=1GSDV22H3X1YPMCCNE40) by Philip F. Nelson (2013)... from **$5.50** + shipping 

13. [*ENEMIES: A History of the FBI*](http://www.amazon.com/Enemies-History-FBI-Tim-Weiner/dp/0812979230/ref=sr_1_1?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1412093800 sr=1-1 keywords=enemies+a+history+of+the+fbi) by Tim Weiner (2013)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

14. [*CONFESSIONS OF AN ECONOMIC HIT MAN*](http://www.amazon.com/Confessions-Economic-Hit-John-Perkins/dp/0452287081/ref=sr_1_1_ha?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1412094049 sr=1-1 keywords=confessions+of+an+economic+hitman+john+perkins) by John Perkins (2005)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

15. [*THE SECRET HISTORY OF THE AMERICAN EMPIRE: The Truth About Economic Hit Men, Jackals, and How to Change the World*](http://www.amazon.com/The-Secret-History-American-Empire/dp/0452289572/ref=pd_bxgy_b_text_y) by John Perkins (2008)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

16. [*TOP SECRET AMERICA: The Rise of the New American Security State*](http://www.amazon.com/Top-Secret-America-American-Security-ebook/dp/B004QX07FU/ref=sr_1_1?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1412094502 sr=1-1 keywords=top+secret+america) by Dana Priest and William Arkin (2011)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

17. [THE SHADOW FACTORY: The Ultra-Secret NSA from 9/11 to the Eavesdropping on America*](http://www.amazon.com/The-Shadow-Factory-Ultra-Secret-Eavesdropping-ebook/dp/B001FA0JLY/ref=pd_sim_kstore_1?ie=UTF8 refRID=1AHKMC28T4G7A5KTRVGZ) by James Bamford (2008)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

18. [*SPYCRAFT: The Secret History of the CIA's Spytechs*](http://www.amazon.com/Spycraft-History-Spytechs-Communism-Al-Qaeda/dp/0452295475/ref=sr_1_1?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1412095321 sr=1-1 keywords=spycraft+robert+wallace) by Robert Wallace and H. Keith Melton (2009)...from **25 CENTS** + shipping

19. [*THE OFFICIAL CIA MANUAL OF TRICKERY AND DECEPTION*](http://www.amazon.com/The-Official-Manual-Trickery-Deception/dp/0061725900/ref=pd_sim_b_1?ie=UTF8 refRID=14NTXCVFYKXJ8YEWVVA3) by H. Keith Melton and Robert Wallace (2010)...from **$4.25** + shipping

20. [*KILLING HOPE: U.S. Military   CIA Interventions since WWII*](http://www.amazon.com/Killing-Hope-Military-Interventions-Since/dp/1567510523/ref=sr_1_5?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1412112075 sr=1-5 keywords=william+blum) by William Blum (1995 edition)...from **$3.76** + shipping

21. [*AMERICAS DEADLIEST EXPORT: DEMOCRACY*](http://www.amazon.com/Americas-Deadliest-Export-Democracy-Everything/dp/1780324456/ref=sr_1_1?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1412095898 sr=1-1 keywords=william+blum) by William Blum (2013)...from **$6.95** + shipping

22. [*SECRETS: The History of the Pentagon Papers*](http://www.amazon.com/Secrets-Memoir-Vietnam-Pentagon-Papers/dp/0142003425/ref=sr_1_1?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1412096231 sr=1-1 keywords=daniel+ellsberg) by Daniel Ellsberg (2003)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

23. [*A BRIGHT SHINING LIE: John Paul Vann and America in Vietnam*](http://www.amazon.com/Bright-Shining-Lie-America-Vietnam/dp/0679724141/ref=sr_1_1?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1412096504 sr=1-1 keywords=a+bright+shining+lie) by Neil Sheehan (1989)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

24. [*THE SECRET HISTORY OF ASSASSINATION*](http://www.amazon.com/Secret-History-Assassination-Paymasters-Revealed/dp/1845297660/ref=sr_1_1?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1412103627 sr=1-1 keywords=history+of+assassination+belfield) by Richard Belfield (2008)...from **TWO CENTS** + shipping

25. [*THE COMMISSION: The Uncensored History of the 9/11 Investigation*](http://www.amazon.com/Commission-Uncensored-History-11-Investigation-ebook/dp/B0010SIPKS/ref=sr_1_3?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1412107500 sr=1-3 keywords=philip+shenon) by Philip Shenon (2008)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

26. [*THE LAST INVESTIGATION*](http://www.amazon.com/Last-Investigation-Federal-Investigator-Conspiracy/dp/1560250526/ref=sr_1_2?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1412107686 sr=1-2 keywords=the+last+investigation+by+gaeton+fonzi) by Gaeton Fonzi (1993)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

27. [*RUSH TO JUDGEMENT*](http://www.amazon.com/Rush-Judgment-Mark-Lane/dp/1560250437/ref=sr_1_1?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1412108004 sr=1-1 keywords=mark+lane+rush+to+judgement) by Mark Lane (1992 edition)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

28. [*ON THE TRAIL OF THE ASSASSINS*](http://www.amazon.com/Trail-Assassins-Investigation-Prosecution-President/dp/B00722U9G4/ref=sr_1_10?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1412108370 sr=1-10 keywords=jim+garrison) by Jim Garrison (1991 edition)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping 

29. [*A FAREWELL TO JUSTICE: Jim Garrison, JFKs Assassination and the Case that should have changed History*](http://www.amazon.com/Farewell-Justice-Garrison-Assassination-Changed/dp/1597970484/ref=sr_1_3?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1412108592 sr=1-3 keywords=joan+mellon) by Joan Mellon (2007)...from **44 CENTS** + shipping

30. [*STATE OF WAR: The Secret History of the CIA and the Bush Administration*](http://www.amazon.com/State-War-Secret-History-Administration-ebook/dp/B000FCKO3Q/ref=pd_sim_kstore_9?ie=UTF8 refRID=0HQ0KXAG5MVJ28Z69707) by James Risen (2006)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

31. [*AN ACT OF STATE: The Execution of Martin Luther King*](http://www.amazon.com/Act-State-Execution-Martin-Luther/dp/1859846955/ref=sr_1_6?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1412113130 sr=1-6 keywords=martin+luther+king+assassination) by William Peppers (2003)...from **ONE CENT** + 

32. [*DAY OF DECEIT: The Truth about FDR and Pearl Harbor*](http://www.amazon.com/Day-Deceit-Truth-About-Harbor/dp/0743201299/) by Robert Stinnett (2001)....from **ONE CENT** + 

33. [ANGLER: The Cheney Vice Presidency*](http://www.amazon.com/Angler-Cheney-Presidency-Barton-Gellman/dp/0143116169/ref=sr_1_1?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1412830216 sr=1-1 keywords=angler+barton+gellman) by Barton Gellman (2008)...from **ONE CENT** + 

34. [*THE SECRET HISTORY OF THE CIA*](http://www.amazon.com/Secret-History-CIA-Joseph-Trento/dp/1567318479/ref=sr_1_1?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1414127258 sr=1-1 keywords=joseph+trento) by Joseph Trento (2007)...from **ONE CENT** +

35. [*INTELLIGENCE MATTERS: The CIA, The FBI, Saudi Arabia and the Failure of Americas War on Terror*](http://www.amazon.com/Intelligence-Matters-Arabia-Failure-Americas/dp/0700616268/ref=sr_1_1?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1414691344 sr=1-1 keywords=intelligence+matters+graham) by Senator Bob Graham (2008, updated)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

36. [*HOUSE OF BUSH, HOUSE OF SAUD: The Secret Relationship between the Worlds Two Most Powerful Dynasties*](http://www.amazon.com/House-Bush-Saud-Relationship-Dynasties/dp/0743253396/ref=sr_1_2?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1414691601 sr=1-2 keywords=bush+saudi) by Craig Unger (2004)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

37. [*THE DAY WALL STREET EXPLODED: America in its First Age of Terror*](http://www.amazon.com/Day-Wall-Street-Exploded-America/dp/0199759286/ref=sr_1_1?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1414693651 sr=1-1 keywords=beverly+gage) by Beverly Gage (2010)...from **$1.55** + shipping

38. [*THE PLOT TO SEIZE THE WHITE HOUSE: The Shocking True Story of the Conspiracy to Overthrow FDR*](http://www.amazon.com/Plot-Seize-White-House-Conspiracy/dp/1602390363/ref=sr_1_1?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1414693930 sr=1-1 keywords=the+plot+to+seize+the+white+house) by Jules Archer (2010 edition)...from **$1.99** + shipping

39. [*BLACKWATER: The Rise of the Worlds Most Powerful Mercenary Army*](http://www.amazon.com/Blackwater-Powerful-Mercenary-Revised-Updated/dp/156858394X/ref=pd_sim_b_1?ie=UTF8 refRID=1XKP90BCKQFD53N5BQ3Y) by Jeremy Scahill (2008, revised)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

41. [*THE LOOMING TOWER: Al Qaeda and the Road to 9/11*](http://www.amazon.com/The-Looming-Tower-Al-Qaeda-Road/dp/1400030846/ref=pd_sim_b_3?ie=UTF8 refRID=0BWE4Z5XGZFN9113TG64) by Lawrence Wright (2007)...from **ONE CENT** + 

42. [*WASHINGTON RULES: Americas Path to Permanent War*](http://www.amazon.com/Washington-Rules-Americas-Permanent-American/dp/0805094229/ref=pd_sim_b_7?ie=UTF8 refRID=0SFY0EYY0417037YPR1S) by Andrew Bacevich (2011)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

43. [*BLOWBACK: The Costs and Consequences of American Empire*](http://www.amazon.com/Blowback-Consequences-American-Empire-Project/dp/0805075593/ref=sr_1_6?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1414696066 sr=1-6 keywords=american+empire+project) by Chalmers Johnson (2004)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

44. [*MONSTERING: Inside America's Policy of Secret Interrogations and Torture in the Terror War*](http://www.amazon.com/Monstering-Inside-Americas-Interrogations-Torture/dp/0786717769/ref=sr_1_1_twi_2?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1414708398 sr=1-1 keywords=monstering) by Tara McKelvey (2007)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

45. [*LIVES, LIES   THE IRAN-CONTRA AFFAIR*](http://www.amazon.com/Lives-Lies-Iran-Contra-Affair-Wroe/dp/1850435588/ref=sr_1_cc_1?s=aps ie=UTF8 qid=1415206273 sr=1-1-catcorr keywords=ann+wroe+lives+lies+iran+contra) by Ann Wroe (1992)...from **ONE CENT** + shipping

46. [A QUESTION OF TORTURE: CIA Interrogation, from the Cold War to the War on Terror (American Empire Project)](http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0805082484/ref=pd_lpo_sbs_dp_ss_3?pf_rd_p=1944687542 pf_rd_s=lpo-top-stripe-1 pf_rd_t=201 pf_rd_i=0299234142 pf_rd_m=ATVPDKIKX0DER pf_rd_r=1EVRY4N9N3Z7RFCJR2YD) by Alfred C. McCoy (2006)...from **3 CENTS** + shipping

47. [THE MAN WHO KNEW TOO MUCH: Hired to Kill Oswald and Prevent the Assassination of JFK](http://www.amazon.com/Man-Who-Knew-Much-Assassination/dp/0786712422/ref=sr_1_1?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1417396453 sr=1-1 keywords=the+man+who+knew+too+much) by Dick Russell (1996)...from **$4.69** + shipping </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9/11 SYNTHETIC TERROR: Made in USA...by Webster Tarpley (2004) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 00:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THE TERROR CONSPIRACY REVISITED: Deception, 9/11 and the Loss of Liberty...by Jim Marrs (2011) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 23:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US bid for secret Guantnamo force-feeding hearings prompts cover-up fears...The Guardian is among several news organisations planning to file a motion to challenge the administrations secrecy request </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 17:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OVERTHROW: Americas Century of Regime Change from Hawaii to Iraq...by Stephen Kinzer (2006) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 03:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THE WAY OF THE KNIFE: The CIA, A Secret Army and War at the Ends of the Earth...by Mark Mazzetti (2013) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 08:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, Usama bin Ladens son-in-law was given a life sentence today for terrorism charges related to 9/11...Ironic that Americans know more about the Casey Anthony and George Zimmerman trials </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 06:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nobel Peace Prize Winner Mairead Maguire: U.S. Genocide in Iraq Has Killed 3.3 Million since 1990--including 750,000 Children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 18:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nobel Peace Prize Winner Mairead Maguire: U.S. Genocide in Iraq Has Killed 3.3 Million since 1990 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 17:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THE BEST ENEMY MONEY CAN BUY by Antony C. Sutton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 00:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THE MAN WHO KILLED KENNEDY: THE CASE AGAINST LBJ...by Roger Stone (2013) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 07:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9/11 Commission Report Burned In Front of U.S. Embassy by Victims Brother </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 19:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9/11 Commission Report Burned In Front of U.S. Embassy by Victims Brother </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 19:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Best Enemies Money Can Buy...1980 Interview with Antony C. Sutton (53 minutes) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 03:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Couldnt See It Coming? CIA Internal Newsletter from 2000 featured NSA Director Michael Hayden Describing an Intelligence Failure Very Similar to What Happened on 9/11 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 02:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The conflicts of the Cold War were "not fought to restrain communism", since the U.S., through financing the Soviet Union "directly or indirectly armed both sides in at least Korea and Vietnam"; rather, these wars were organised in order "to generate multibillion-dollar armaments contracts". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 16:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> September 18, 1947: The National Security Act became Law--giving us 67 years of CIA and Military Interventions (some would say Perpetual War). Happy B-Day to WAR, INC. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 09:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The conflicts of the Cold War were "not fought to restrain communism", since the U.S., through financing the Soviet Union "directly or indirectly armed both sides in at least Korea and Vietnam"; rather, these wars were organised in order "to generate multibillion-dollar armaments contracts". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 05:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTC 7: 'We built in enough redundancy to allow entire portions of floors to be removed without affecting the building's structural integrity, on the assumption that someone might need double-height floors,'' said Larry Silverstein </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 23:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even Glenn Greenwald Has Abandoned the Subject of 9/11 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 20:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Q: Its 1961, the height of the Cold War, the U.S. has 40 nuclear-capable Inter Continental Ballistic Missiles--how many ICBMs did the Soviets have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 22:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to Daniel Ellsbergs *SECRETS: A Memoir of Vietnam and the Pentagon Papers* (2002):

However, in the fall of 1961 a highly secret, dramatically revised national intelligence estimate turned the strategic world that had preoccupied me for three years upside down. The missile gap favoring the Soviets had been a fantasy. There was a gap, all right, but it was currently ten to one in our favor. Our 40 Atlas and Titan ICBMs were matched by 4 Soviet SS-6 ICBMs at one launching site at Plesetsk, not by 120, as in the latest national estimate in June, or by the SAC commanders estimate of 1,000 I had heard of at SAC headquarters in August. The specter of a deliberate Soviet surprise attack suddenly appeared, with the new estimates, to have been a chimera. 

...the new estimate was kept effectively secret from Congress, the press, and the public, and it had a comparably imperceptible effect on military programs. It was after this secret recognition that the Soviets  had deployed four liquid-fueled ICBMs to our forty that the Kennedy administration decided, in the late fall of 1961, on the appropriate size for the projected force of U.S. solid-fueled Minuteman missiles: one thousand. That was less than the 1,600 to 6,000 that the air force had earlier requested, but it was down only to the level that Secretary McNamara had earlier decided on *before* the new estimate. (pages 32-33)

**THREAT INFLATION**

------------------------

The 6 paragraphs below are taken from Chapter 7 of a free online book *The Pentagon Labyrinth* (2011). Full article "Follow the Money" by Andrew Cockburn (2011): http://pogoarchives.org/labyrinth/07-cockburn-w-covers.pdf

------------------------------

Recall that following victory in World War II, the U.S. rapidly disarmed, disbanding its huge conscript army and slashing weapons production. The economies of our allies and enemies in the recent conflict lay in total ruin. Although the Soviet Union controlled eastern European states overrun by the Red Army during the war, this was by prior agreement with the U.S. and Britain. Suddenly, in the spring of 1948, senior officials of the Truman Administration suddenly began issuing ominous warnings that the Soviet Union was bent on war and might attack at any time. A warning to that effectwar could come at any timewas solicited by the chief of army intelligence from the U.S. commander in Germany, General Lucius Clay, and duly leaked to the press.

Why?

The answer is clear for anyone who remembers to follow the money. The aircraft corporations who had garnered enormous profits during the war on the back of government contracts had discovered by 1947 that **peace was ruinous**. Despite initial high hopes, the commercial marketplace was proving a far harsher and less accommodating environment than that of wartime, especially as there were far more companies than required by the peacetime economy. Orders from the civilian airline industry never lived up to expectations while efforts to diversify into other products, including dishwashers and stainless steel coffins, proved disappointing and costly.

Something had to be done. In the spring of 1948 senior officials in the Truman Administration, including Secretary of Defense James Forrestal, suddenly began warning that the Soviets were on the brink of unleashing a surprise military attack against Western Europe. There was **no evidence** that the Soviets had any such intentions, a point, as declassified documents now make clear, that was well known to the senior officials. In fact Stalin, the Soviet leader, was enjoining the powerful western European communist parties from any revolutionary action and refusing to aid the Greek communists in their civil war against the U.S.-backed government.

This cause (need for stimulus in the aerospace industry) and effect (war scare leading to sharp increase in defense appropriations) was pithily summed up at the time by Lawrence D. Bell, President of the Bell Aircraft Corporation: As soon as there is a war scare, there is a lot of money available. And so it proved. The aircraft procurement budget soared **57**% as the overall Pentagon procurement budget exploded by almost **600** percent from less than $6 billion in 1947 to more than $35 billion in 1948 (in contemporary 2011 dollars). The industry, not to mention powerful institutions linked to its fortunes, such as **major banks**, was saved from collapse.

Apart from a brief relapse pending the outbreak of the Korean war in 1950, war scares, otherwise known as **threat inflation** would thereafter be a regular feature of the U.S. political and economic landscape. It mattered little what the Soviet enemy was actually doing, or in a position to do. All that was required was for an announcement that intelligence had revealed an ominous gap between U.S. and Soviet capabilities, and the money flowed. The missile gap on which John F. Kennedy rode to victory in 1960 yielded an immediate fifteen percent hike in defense spending. Years after the money had been appropriated and spent, **it was openly admitted by the relevant defense secretary, Robert McNamara, that in fact the gap had been entirely in favor of the U.S.** Similar, if less infamous episodes recurred featuring bombers, tanks, ships, anti-ballistic missiles and, most comprehensively, defense budgets themselves.

Embarrassing realities, such as serious shortcomings in our putative enemies capabilities, have generally been kept out of sight of the taxpayers. Equally, explosive cost overruns and technical disasters generate, at most, short term scandals. Pleas to cut the defense budget have rarely yielded much of a political dividend. Indeed, in former days, the very size of the budget, irrespective of its components, was touted as a necessary part of our deterrent. One of the more successful gaps of the cold war years was the greater size of the Soviet defense budget. **The Soviets didnt announce how much they were spending on defense** (even if they knew the real cost themselves, which is dubious); so the figure publicized by the military industrial complex was based on an ersatz calculation of the presumed cost to the Soviets of duplicating U.S. programs and systems. I.E., the cost of a Soviet swing-wing bomber would be assessed on the basis of the cost of a similar U.S. effort. Therefore, as Ernie Fitzgerald, the consummate Pentagon whistleblower of the 1960s, 1970s, and 1980s, once observed, every time the B-1 bomber has a cost overrun, the Soviet defense budget goes up! In other words, the more dollars we wasted, the more dangerous the other side became, which justified our wasting even more dollars, and so on.

---------------------

Full book [*The Pentagon Labyrinth*](http://pogoarchives.org/labyrinth/full-labyrinth-text-w-covers.pdf) was edited by Winslow T. Wheeler and released online for FREE--hope you get a chance to read it further.  

[*The Most Dangerous Man In America: Daniel Ellsberg and the Pentagon Papers*](http://www.veoh.com/watch/v20946070MKKS8mr2?h1=The+Most+Dangerous+Man+in+America%3A+Daniel+Ellsberg+and+the+Pentagon+Papers) (1hr 33min)

[*Why We Fight*](http://vimeo.com/22543212) (1hr 42min)

[*Buying the War*](http://vimeo.com/33033186) (1hr 23min)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran-Contra: Secret Teams and Covert Operations in the Reagan Era...by Jonathan Marshall and Peter Dale Scott </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 09:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What If...the fake cellphone towers outside U.S. military installations are not aimed at civilians, but instead were put there by the CIA to spy on the miltary??? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 17:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guantnamo Military Lawyer Resigns; Talks of Show Trial Tainted by Torture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 18:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those who think the U.S. would never consider an Operation like 9/11--heres a partial list of what the CIA and the Pentagon have done since the end of WWII... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 00:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guantanamo Costs $443 Million Per Year to Operate--about $3 Million Per Prisoner...FYI: The 9/11 Commission Initially Received Just $3 Million to Investigate 9/11...Priorities!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 00:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than 800,000 Foreign Students in U.S.--Up from 110,000 in 2001 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 19:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than 800,000 Foreign Students in U.S.; Most Study Business, Science and Engineering </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 19:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While we wait 5+ years for the redacted Senate Torture Report--at least 3 books have been written and enriched former CIA brass (Jose Rodriguez, George Tenet, John Rizzo) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 08:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Senate-CIA fight on interrogation report, another controversy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 20:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9/11...8:45 to 9:37 AM...Secret Service Does Not Use Its Stinger Missiles to Protect NYC and Washington, DC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 18:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THE INVISIBLE GOVERNMENT by David Wise   Thomas Ross (1964) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 10:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BODY OF SECRETS by James Bamford (2002) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 04:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DRUGS, OIL AND WAR by Peter Dale Scott (2003) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 02:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New subreddit, the Texas School Book Depository (r/TSBD)...Free books + author interviews on conspiracies: FBI, CIA, NSA, DIA, JFK, MLK, RFK, 9/11... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 03:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI Criminal Database Includes 77 Million Americans...List Grows By 10,000+ Names Every Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 17:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI Criminal Database Includes 77 Million Americans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 17:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Ferguson is 67% African-American, Why are the Mayor, the City Council Majority and 50 of 53 Police White? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 19:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Torture And Rendition: Diplomats 'Trying To Censor' US Senate Report On British Role In CIA Activities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 17:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraq's Maliki Steps Down "To Stop Bloodshed", Blames CIA, Supports Abadi As New Prime Minister </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 23:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russ Baker: "As with most people, I was baffled by how Building 7--a smaller, 47-story tower that had not been hit by a plane and was separated from the Twin Towers by low-rise buildings-would come down at all. It just made no sense." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 17:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Hedges: America Is A Tinderbox (2013, 18 minutes) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 19:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ROGUE STATE by William Blum (UK, 2002) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 03:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CIA Drone Control Huts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 23:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Erbil: The REAL Reason for New U.S. and French Military Involvement In Iraq </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 19:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Complete History of U.S. Presidents Bombing Iraq </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 16:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The CIA hatched two plots to assassinate Nixon and sabotaged the Watergate break-in because they didn't want the Vietnam war to end, claims explosive new book by Roger Stone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 20:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The CIA hatched two plots to assassinate Nixon and sabotaged the Watergate break-in because they didn't want the Vietnam war to end, claims explosive new book by Roger Stone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 20:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CONFESSIONS OF AN ECONOMIC HITMAN by John Perkins (2004) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 18:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GHW BUSH: UNAUTHORIZED by Webster Tarpley </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 04:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Still No Answers 4 months after "CIA Senior Official" Commits Suicide by Jumping from 5th Floor...No Name, No Time/Date of Death, No Location... Suspicious Timing--SSCI had just approved release of Torture Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 00:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senators to Obama: Stop Censoring the Torture Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 18:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Spies Ponder CIA's Future After Torture Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 18:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kandahar, Afghanistans second largest city, could go without power when U.S. subsidies for diesel fuel phase out next year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 04:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ALL THE SHAHS MEN by Stephen Kinzer (2003) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 21:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NATOs SECRET ARMIES by Daniele Ganser </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 08:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SPYCRAFT by Robert Wallace + H. Keith Melton (2008) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 08:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THE PENTAGON LABYRINTH by Winslow Wheeler, et al (2011) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 07:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zapruder Film Mystery (1hr 23min, 2013)...Interview with Doug Horne, former chief analyst of military records at the Assassination Records Review Board </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 21:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Intelligence Agencies Have All Been Busted Lying Again and Again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 20:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Broken Record: U.S. Intelligence Agencies Have All Been Busted Lying Again and Again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 20:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THE SECRET TEAM by L. Fletcher Prouty (1997 edition) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 01:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25 Bush-Cheney Era Torture Enablers (lots of good article links) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 01:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FINAL JUDGEMENT by Michael Collins Piper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 09:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Secret Team: The CIA and Its Allies in Control of the United States and the World... "It will be interesting to see what 'enemy' develops in the years ahead." --L. Fletcher Prouty, 1997 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 04:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bush-Cheney Torture Timeline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 02:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Garrison was convinced that CIA was behind the assassination of JFK. As he said, when he looked at Oswald in Louisiana during the summer of 1963, he noticed that Oswald was not only never alone, but that everyone he was seen with had some connection to CIA." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 04:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its About the Lying: Dan Froomkin Calls for Obama to Fire John Brennan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 03:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unmasking a CIA Criminal (60 minute lecture by one of the "Press For Truth directors) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 20:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since 2001, All of the Countries which the U.S. has Regime Changed (Afghanistan, Iraq, Libya) have descended into Brutal Chaos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 10:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All of the Countries which the U.S. Regime Changed  Iraq, Afghanistan and Libya  Have Descended into Brutal Chaos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 10:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All of the Countries which the U.S. Regime Changed - Iraq, Afghanistan and Libya - Have Descended into Brutal Chaos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 10:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Q: Do you think there should be another 9/11 Commission? (former commisioner) Max Cleland: There should be fifteen 9/11 Commissions!!! (at 2009 book signing) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 07:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venezuelan government joy as Aruba frees former military intelligence head; President Maduro's supporters jubilant after Hugo Carvajal is released instead of facing extradition to the U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 07:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> August 4th Cover of Time (FULL propaganda mode): All red cover (danger, danger) with a 4 photo of Vladimir Putin (full body shot, walking in a suit) under the headline COLD WAR: The West is losing Putins dangerous game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 00:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a google image link to the current cover of [TIME](http://www.google.com/search?q=magazine+covers+time+august+4%2C+2014 rls=en tbm=isch ei=QH3VU62sN4ucyATOmIH4AQ#facrc=_ imgdii=_ imgrc=nj3tllrlS6Vj6M%253A%3B_EGLmLgGA)

---------------

Seems to be pure Fearmongering 101...INFLATE the threat and fund some more Defense/Intelligence NOW!!!

The 2014 National Security Budgets of the U.S. and Russia are estimated at:

**FACT:**  U.S. has gone over $1 TRILLION for 2014 (if the last $65 Billion goes through that Obama requested for Defense in early July goes through).

**FACT:**  Russias 2014 National Security Budget is not even at $75 Billion

SO, the U.S. spends OVER 10X what Russia is spending on National Security in 2014. In fact, the additional $65 Billion Obama recently requested is almost the *entire* amount that Russia will spend for National Security in all of 2014. 

-----------

http://thediplomat.com/2014/04/russian-military-spending-soars/

http://www.pogo.org/our-work/straus-military-reform-project/defense-budget/2014/americas-one-trillion-national-security-budget.html

-----------

CORRECTION: The Headline is actually

 **COLD WAR II**

**The West is losing Putins dangerous game**

(I accidentally omitted the II after "COLD WAR) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oklahoma City bombing centre stage in brother's court battle; Heres the FULL version of A Noble Lie (which seems to be hard to find on youtube for some reason) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 19:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> De-Dollarization Spreads: Chinese and Swiss Central Banks Enter Swap Agreement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 21:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Boomerang Effect: Sanctions on Russia Hit German Economy Hard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 20:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Belushi Gets Upset About the U.S. Government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 09:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Was Flight MH 17 Diverted Over Restricted Air Space?...zerohedge.com Scoops abc, nbc, cbs, fox By Pointing Out the Flight Path Variation of MH 17 Was 50 Miles North of Normal Route...Then Source flightaware.com Gets 403 Forbidden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 07:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was Flight MH 17 Diverted Over Restricted Airspace? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 03:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9/11 (Analytical   Intelligence Comments) "It suggests that certain key unknown figures in the Federal Reserve may have been in collusion..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 01:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top 10 Most Inhuman Henry Kissinger Quotes...It is an act of insanity and national humiliation to have a law prohibiting the President from ordering assassination. (Statement at a National Security Council meeting, 1975) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 03:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congratulations r/worldnews--you are becoming IRRELEVANT--12 of top 25 stories from the Guardian or BBC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 18:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disgraced Congressman Randy Duke Cunningham Is A Free Man Again; Ready to Move Into His 2600 Square Foot House In A Gated Community with 9 Golf Courses, Nature Trails, Tennis Courts (etc.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 08:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disgraced Congressman Randy Duke Cunningham Is A Free Man Again; Ready to Move Into His 2600 Square Foot House In A Gated Community with 9 Golf Courses, Nature Trails, Tennis Courts (etc.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 08:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disgraced Congressman Randy Duke Cunningham Is A Free Man Again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 08:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Farnborough Airshow: F-35 combat jet fails to take to skies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 06:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Farnborough Airshow: F-35 combat jet fails to take to skies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 06:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pentagons Big Budget F-35 Fighter Cant Turn, Cant Climb, Cant Run According to RAND Corp Study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 06:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pentagons Big Budget F-35 Fighter Cant Turn, Cant Climb, Cant Run" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 05:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The KILL TEAM movie: Immorality and Impunity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 04:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 2011, Danny Jowenko, a Dutch Demolitions Expert, Claimed WTC 7 Was Clearly a Controlled Demolition--3 Days Later Danny Was DEAD in a One Car Accident with a Tree (sound familiar?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 02:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Angela Merkel "does not want to complete full term as German chancellor and is considering quitting ahead of the 2017 elections--interested in UN Secretary-General or President of the European Council roles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-13 21:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Defense Intelligence Agence (DIA) has been embroiled in numerous controversies, including those related to its intelligence-gathering activities, its role in torture, as well as attempts to expand its activities on U.S. soil. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 23:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dose of Irony: Angela Merkel Awarded U.S. Presidential Medal of Freedom from Barack Obama (2011, 1 minute) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 17:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Case You Missed It: Obama Awarded GHW Bush the Medal of Freedom in 2011...Whos next--Dick Cheney??? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 07:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Britians new F-35 jet fighter to miss International Debut--Blow for F35 programme after jets grounded in US and expected to miss debut at RAF Fairford airshow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 05:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Britians new F-35 jet fighter to miss international debut--Blow for F35 programme after jets grounded in US and expected to miss debut at RAF Fairford airshow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 04:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Britains new F-35 jet fighter to miss international debut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 04:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4 out of 10 Bostonians Skeptical of Official Marathon Bombing Account </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 04:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4 out of 10 Bostonians Skeptical of Official Marathon Bombing Account </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 04:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4 out of 10 Bostonians Skeptical of Official Marathon Bombing Account </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 04:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Albuquerque (NM) Police Dept. to buy 350+ AR-15 rifles--the same type used to kill James Boyd in the foothills last March </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 02:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Albuquerque (NM) Police Dept. to buy 350+ AR-15 rifles--the same type used to kill James Boyd in the foothills last March </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 02:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Albuquerque (NM) Police Dept. to buy 350+ AR-15 rifles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 02:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CORE of CORRUPTION (2009, 2hr 27min) primarily uses main stream news sources to piece together the upside-down intelligence operations behind 9/11 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 04:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ABLE DANGER: Pre-9/11 the Armys Information Dominance Center collected 2.5 Terabytes of Info on Al Qaeda--but destroyed the data instead of sharing with the FBI or CIA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 19:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Insider Threat initiative, a government-wide crackdown on security threats that relies on profiling federal workers for certain behaviors, has been targeting 60,000 U.S. Customs and Border Protection officers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 08:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Insider Threat initiative, a government-wide crackdown on security threats that relies on profiling federal workers for certain behaviors, has been targeting 60,000 U.S. Customs and Border Protection officers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 08:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House GOP proposes $3.3 million budget to investigate Benghazi--more than for VA committee (and more than 9/11 Commission initially received) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 00:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surprise, Surprise: Obama has requested an additional $65 billion in defense funding--which erases the planned Decrease in the 2014 National Defense Budget </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 22:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Im sure that when we leave office were all going to be hauled up before congressional committees and grand juries. --David Addington, Legal Counsel/Chief of Staff to VP Dick Cheney 2001-2009 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 21:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quote from *Angler: The Cheney Vice Presidency* by Barton Gellman...page 312

---------------

If you rule that way, the blood of the hundred thousand people who die in the next attack will be on your hands. 

--David Addington attempting to ensure the Presidents Spy Program is renewed while speaking to Justice Department official Jack Goldsmith...page 294

--------

Mike Hayden and Vito Potenza drove down from Fort Meade after lunch on February 19, 2004, to give Jim Comey his first briefing on the program. In the Justice Departments sixth-floor SCIF, Hayden got Comeys attention fast. 

Im so glad youre getting read in, because now I wont be alone at the table when John Kerry is elected president, he said. The witness table, Hayden meant. Congressional hearing, investigation of some kind. Nothing good. Kerry had the Democratic nomination just about locked up and was leading Bush in national polls. Hardly anyone believed the next administration would climb as far out on a legal limb as this one had. That was one reason Hayden pushed for some kind of congressional notification. 

(page 292)

----------------

Seems to be a PATTERN here--as if they clearly KNEW they were breaking the law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama has requested an additional $65 billion for defense--eradicating a proposed decrease in defense spending for 2014...and bring the total for National Defense to over $1 TRILLION </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 10:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 2005, Congressman Curt Weldon went on a 45 minute rant on the floor of the House regarding DIAs cover-up of ABLE DANGER--which identified 4 of the 9/11 hijackers over a year before 9/11 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 09:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "On 72 occasions, according to the 28-page FBI summary, Cheney equivocated to the FBI during his lengthy May 2004 interview, saying he could not be certain in his answers to questions about matters large and small in the Plame controversy." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 09:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. grounds entire F-35 fighter jet fleet after unexplained fire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 09:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. grounds entire F-35 fighter jet fleet after unexplained fire...Latest incident in hugely expensive weapons program threatens plane's participation in two UK air shows this month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 09:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As federal highway fund nears empty, DOT warns states to expect less </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 08:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad Roads? Sorry. $10.5 Billion for federal highway funds is running out--but U.S. spends over $1 Trillion for National Defense (Obama just requested another $65 billion) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 08:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did the CIA give Iran blueprints for a nuclear bomb??? (James Risen) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 05:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SYSTEMIC FRAUD: a law in effect since 1992 requires annual audits of all federal agencies--and the Pentagon alone has NEVER complied. It annually reports to Congress that its books are in such disarray that an audit is impossible. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 00:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a May 2011 speech, then-Secretary of Defense Robert Gates described the Pentagons business operations as an amalgam of fiefdoms without centralized mechanisms to allocate resources, track expenditures, and measure results.  My staff and I learned that it was nearly impossible to get accurate information and answers to questions such as How much money did you spend and How many people do you have? 

http://www.reuters.com/investigates/pentagon/#article/part2

A search in the Budget Overview document for the word "audit," for example, will take you to page 7-34, among others, where you will find that DOD set a goal of reaching 100 percent readiness to audit its assets and liabilities by the year 2017, but the last column shows that the indicator of progress made toward that goal in FY 2010 was deleted at the request of the Comptroller, who happens to be the chief financial officer of DOD! Furthermore, the auditability asserted for 2017 would not include any audits of specific weapons programs!
The Pentagon Labyrinth (2011) is a free book edited by Winslow Wheeler--its about 100 pages (great read): 

http://pogoarchives.org/labyrinth/full-labyrinth-text-w-covers.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ABLE DANGER: Pre-9/11 the Armys Information Dominance Center collected 2.5 Terabytes of Info on Al Qaeda--but destroyed the data instead of sharing with the FBI or CIA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 22:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look at these cable news ratings: CNN is Dying--lets KILL it with an official boycott...(thanks for selling us phony wars, fake food and one-star movies) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 17:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look at these cable news ratings: CNN is Dying--lets KILL it with an official boycott... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 17:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good/Good News: Hillarys book sales crash 44% after 1st week; Reviews are disastrous </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 08:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VOLTAIRE Sums Up 9/11 and U.S. War Crimes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 18:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> F-35 fighter jets to resume flights after fire led to grounding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 07:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spook of the Day: CD Jackson, Psychological Warfare Expert for OSS, CIA ... Bilderberg ... Time/Life Executive...Purchased Zapruder Film...Died Sept 18, 1964 (he was 62) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 21:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 16 News Organizations Seek Access to Guantanamo Force-Feeding Videos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 07:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks to Cryptome for pointing out that Wikileaks has a free pdf version of Glenn Greenwalds NO PLACE TO HIDE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 02:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks to Cryptome for pointing out that Wikileaks has a free pdf version of Glenn Greenwalds NO PLACE TO HIDE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 02:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ON COMPANY BUSINESS...Phillip Agee, Victor Marchetti, John Stockwell discuss the first 30 years of the CIA (174 minutes, 1980) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 23:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "There is no federal agency of our government whose activities receive less scrutiny and control than the CIA. -- Senator Stuart Symington (Member, Joint Senate Committee for CIA Oversight...November 23, 1971) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 06:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "It is the function of the CIA to keep the world unstable, and to propagandize and teach the American people to hate and fear, so we will let the Establishment spend any amount of money on arms. (Excerpts from THE PRAETORIAN GUARD by John Stockwell) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 08:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "It is the function of the CIA to keep the world unstable, and to propagandize and teach the American people to hate and fear, so we will let the Establishment spend any amount of money on arms. (Excerpts from THE PRAETORIAN GUARD by John Stockwell) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 08:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Defense Contractors Have Scored Over $3.3 TRILLION Bonanza since 9/11 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 09:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge in Guantanamo force-feeding case wants more evidence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 08:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We need more PEACEFUL acts of COURAGE like this... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 07:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can the 9/11 Commission Report cost $15 million and take 16 months to produce--while the Senate Torture Report cost $40 million and took 4 years to produce??? (link is to a series of Salon articles on torture) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 07:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Ive discovered in looking into the history of CIA is a concerted effort by this Agency to substitute itself for the elected government, executive and legislative branches both. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 06:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can the 9/11 Commission Report cost $15 million to produce and take only 16 months to produce--while the Senate Torture Report cost $40 million and took 4 years to produce??? (link is to a timeline of torture investigation) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 05:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9/11 Commission: Our investigation was obstructed. The bipartisan co-chairmen all but accuse the White House of committing serious felonies in destroying the CIA videos. (by GLENN GREENWALD, Jan. 2, 2008) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 11:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9/11 Commission: Our investigation was obstructed. The bipartisan co-chairmen all but accuse the White House of committing serious felonies in destroying the CIA videos. (by GLENN GREENWALD, Jan. 2, 2008) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 11:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9/11 Commission: Our investigation was obstructed. The bipartisan co-chairmen all but accuse the White House of committing serious felonies in destroying the CIA videos. (by GLENN GREENWALD, Jan. 2, 2008) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 11:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9/11 Commission Funding Woes: BILLIONS and BILLIONS for War, Just $3 Million to Investigate 9/11 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 19:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dont Reform the CIA, ABOLISH IT (2007) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 17:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dont Reform the CIA, ABOLISH IT (2007) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 17:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FACT IS: CIA Torture Allegations Were First Reported In December, 2002...12 Years Ago...We Are Still Waiting for the $40 Million Senate Torture Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 19:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FACT IS: CIA Torture Allegations Were First Reported In December, 2002...12 Years Ago...$40 Million Senate Torture Report Still Not Released </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 19:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jailbreak: The U.S. Paid $11 Million for an Afghan Prison with Cracked Walls, Major Structural Flaws...and A Missing Security Fence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 10:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9/11 Commission Deceived: An Unintentional Work of Fiction Based on Cheneys Torture Program </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 06:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FACT IS: CIA Torture Allegations began in December, 2002...12 Years Ago...We are still waiting for the $40 million Senate Torture Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 06:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FACT IS: CIA Torture Allegations began in December, 2002...12 Years Ago...Today we are still waiting for the $40 Million Senate Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 06:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> December, 2002: CIA Office of Inspector General begins Report on CIA performance regarding 9/11...Report is NOT released until August 2007 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 19:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> USA: 124 Wars in 239 Years...In War We Trust" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 21:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter Goes Evil and Blocks VeteransToday/PressTV Messages...Who Will Be Next??? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 03:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy 90th Birthday to the LIAR Extraordiaire GHW Bush!!! (Iran-Contra, BCCI, Drugs, Noriega, First Civilian Director of CIA, etc) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 17:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTF: no cryptome??? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 16:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The one weapon the CIA used with surpassing skill was cold cash. The Japanese described the political system created with CIA support as "structural corruption". In 1948 enough CIA money was laundered in Italy to ensure that the elections did not go to the Communists; "spreading democracy by deceit" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 12:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The one weapon the CIA used with surpassing skill was cold cash. The Japanese described the political system created with CIA support as "structural corruption". In 1948 enough CIA money was laundered in Italy to ensure that the elections did not go to the Communists; "spreading democracy by deceit" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 11:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York Review of Books Slams CIA with Twitter Attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 10:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CIA: We can neither confirm nor deny this is our first tweet...Amnesty International and Wikileaks respond </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 09:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americas TRILLION Dollar National Security Budget </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 07:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> June 20, 2002: Dick Cheney Threatens to Terminate 9/11 Inquiry over NSA Leak </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 21:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Kiriakou Calls for Independent Investigation of CIA Torture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 20:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> J. Edgar Hoover...1967...Memo title: Disruption of the New Left... "Consider the use of cartoons, ridicule is one of the most potent weapons we can use. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 21:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Deline of Editorial Cartoons after 9/11 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 22:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 2005, Scott Ritter Called for Prosecution of GW Bush and Bill Clinton...(surprises inside, 15 minutes) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 23:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 2005, Scott Ritter Called for Prosecution of GW Bush and Bill Clinton...(surprises inside, 15 minutes) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 23:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stephen Kinzer discusses his book Overthrow: Americas Century of Regime Change from Hawaii to Iraq (2006) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 00:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
