<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7049</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 20:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your ways aren't evil, it sounds like what everyone goes through.  I'm not trying to make your problems sound insignificant, but if you keep calling it evil it will make you feel terrible about yourself....  And masturbation is fun and healthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 07:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> K </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 07:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not getting what you're throwing I guess.  How can my assumption be that off if you affiliate with a Christian religion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 06:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume that since you identify under a certain denomination,  that you have at least minimal respect for the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 04:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't claim that there are *any* books written by anything but fallible humans... 

But I sure as hell wouldn't do anything as drastic as follow a religion written by them.  

I mean fuck, a lot of people think the Mormons are crazy because a couple hundred years ago Joseph Smith talked to God and created a religion.  If someone does that now, we put them in the psych ward.  What the hell is the difference?  In my eyes, crazy people wrote the book you're defending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 22:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you live by a book that was written by fallible men? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 17:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know people are born gay and don't have a choice, great.  

The fact that they can't control their orientation is something that hasn't been known for a long time.  When all we had thousands of years ago were lines like this to refer to, 

"If a man also lie with mankind, as he lieth with a woman, both of them have committed an abomination: they shall surely be put to death; their blood shall be upon them."-Lev.20:13 

...people were well convinced it was a choice.

But thats humankind for you, learning evolving, continuing to gain information. You are helping me make my point.  

*This book has gotten things wrong.* 

I know what you might say, "of course a book written so long ago wouldn't have all the answers..." "it must be interpreted correctly to understand it's significance/meaning..."  but it got equality wrong, a human right that people are still fighting for!  People shouldn't be able to  blame it on the interpretation or time it was written.  Not acceptable to me, considering how many people live their life hanging by every word of that book.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 08:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is telling you that the bible, or any part of the bible, is not meant to be taken literally?  The only answer that I'd accept is God, or the people that wrote it.  

Since they're not here to explain themselves, it's up to the people who preach to the masses with their own ideas, interpretations and agendas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 07:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5,700 and 10,000 years, I'm sorry.  And when I say, "that's what the bible says," I'm only speaking of a literal *interpretation.*   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 05:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are an example of what I'm talking about, no offense.  If you literally interpret it, it does say the earth is that old.

"Young Earth creationism (YEC) is the religious belief that the Universe, Earth and all life on Earth were created by direct acts of the Abrahamic God during a relatively short period, sometime between 5,700 and 10,000 years ago. Its primary adherents are those Christians and Jews who, using a literal interpretation of the Genesis creation narrative as a basis, believe that God created the Earth in six 24-hour days."

Edit:  Like you said, you can easily say that a literal interpretation of Genesis is ludicrous because the age of the earth has evidence that it is billions of years old.    

But is that how everything will go in the bible once we find enough evidence against it?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 04:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  They might have a hard time admitting to themselves they feel that way, but never in a conversation or debate has any Christian admitted that to me.  If it was my religion, and I felt like the only connection I had to a religion was a holy book, I'd feel the same.  I feel like questioning the book, would be the start to losing faith. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 03:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you that there are different genres of the bible.  I really should have worded it better, because you are absolutely right.

Let me put it this way.  I'm not referring to the miracles, the prayers, the mythical creatures.  I'm talking about history, human morality, very black and white topics where there isn't and shouldn't be a gray area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 02:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I don't know how you'd come to that conclusion, I don't believe it to be either.  The Christians that celebrate Easter I'm sure think it actually happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 02:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could figuratively be a sheep, but literally neither. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 02:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people?  I am talking about the people who have nothing more than common knowledge on the subject.   Every religious person that has crossed my path, had their own way of interpreting things in the bible.  

The ones that think the earth is 6,000 years old, take Genesis literally.  The Christians that believe what the scientists say to be accurate, say it's up for interpreting and that science fits with the bible.  Of course there are people that say science fits with the bible, because there's an overwhelming amout of evidence to support the age of our planet and they'd be crazy not to agree.

The same with homosexuality.  It's a sin.  Gay people are a large group, that are shunned by numerous religious organizations.  But then other groups say God loves everyone and excepts everyone.  

It seems to conveniently come down to whether or not an individual is personally accepting or not of the lifestyle but they just blame it on the interpretation of their bible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 00:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just always wonder how people decide what to take literally, or figuratively in the bible.

Whether it be how old the earth is said to be, or the view on homosexuality.  Everything..

People will say that the earth isn't *literally* 6,000 years old, and that you shouldn't interpret Genesis as literal.  

Who are they to interpret it the way they feel it should be?   Not only that, but interpret the whole thing the same way or don't.  The picking and choosing is all over the place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 18:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 20:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the span of a few decades we went from smoking on planes to grounding them over a match.  I agree that's its dangerous, but I could see how someone from that age might disregard the danger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dog's sexy dance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 18:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 16:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to help you, but I've never used that brand.  Pomades aren't suppose to dry stiff, the base it's made of is usually beeswax or oil.   But this could have other properties that give it that effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 08:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By far the best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 07:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How exciting!  Love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 05:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I ask the time span that this covered?  I love looking at hair transformation albums like this, thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 00:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since facial hair is more coarse and resistant than normal hair, sometimes the formula is stronger.  

It's absolutely safe if it gets on your skin, but if the color is darker it could stain your skin.  That's the only thing you'd wanna worry about, is staining.  So avoid the skin as much as possible.  Just lightly paint it on with a q-tip and let it process for the time specified.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 09:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Young Adult.  I just love Charlize Theron in that movie.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 08:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How old? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 05:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely Chi flat iron.  If she requests a big curling iron, I'd get her at least a 1 1/2" one.  The flat iron is important to get a good brand, the curling iron, not as important.  But Hot Tools brand is good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 05:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But while you are letting the top grow, you could fade the sides.  It usually makes the overall shape more desirable when the sides are shorter.  Her advice is sound.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 01:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's an amazing question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 01:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very common!  They do sell facial hair dye.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 01:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that like a 3 on top, 2 on the sides?  It's very short, but what do you usually do, 5 and a 4?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-10 17:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must be pretty young </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 05:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed, the times when it foams the most, there is some sort of cleaner in the toilet, or residual cleaner left over from the previous flush.  Might not be relevant, just my observation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 05:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like these the best, out of all these posts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 03:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *I think I'm doing okay for a 15 year old with a wife and a baby.* 

That shit cracked me up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 17:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that emphasis was necessary.  I find many people saying there is this blurred line when it comes to attraction to the same sex for females.  A lot of women do it for critical acclaim, and I think that's where it gets messy.  It creates this weird stigma for the ones with genuine attraction.  My opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 08:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am female.  I *do* find myself staring at certain females sometimes, but I never reach the point of sexual attraction, ever.  I am very straight.  I find it hilarious when I stare too long.  But it feels like human nature to appreciate immaculate appearances. ::shrugs:: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 19:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly it.  On the strip and under the Fremont Street Experience,  anything can be open, it's legal!  But East Fremont,  just outside the main drag where all the hipster bars are, is where the law changes.  The rest of the city is not open-container legal, just strip and under Fremont Experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 09:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if she has been pregnant multiple times but has had multiple miscarriages and can't conceive?  And everytime she sees her face on a magazine with that headline she is forced to be reminded... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 07:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that the most simplistic is the healthiest.  Everything you listed are single ingredients, therefore the healthiest.  

When it comes to overprocessed, majorly artificial,  super-refined shit, our bodies don't even recognize it as food;  another reason why it's hard to feel full on junk food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 01:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She fucking nailed that Joan Jett persona!  That was the one movie that made me appreciate Kristen Stewart's acting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 05:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww, you killed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 04:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 04:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so sorry, what happened in FL?  Has this already been implemented?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does reddit think about drug testing people who are on welfare? I keep seeing people in support of it, or that disagree with it, I'd love to here anyone's thoughts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 03:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 23:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's got your baby.

That scene in 2 made the scene from 1 scarier to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 23:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't get through to the end of that one.  He was too repulsive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 23:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has the smallest molecules, stains easy and slips out easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 19:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't want to sound mean, but it looks like an 80's jerry curl.  Maybe you should try it shorter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 18:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He tastes like you, but sweeter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 18:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely agree.  But I get the vibe he seems like a really nice guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 17:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the short-lived yoga in the park scene.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 16:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's so weird that women can be divided on this, but I hate when a guy sucks on it!  Soft, repetitious licking feels the best to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 07:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That warms my heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 06:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Her Shoes.  Toni Collette should have won an Oscar, in my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 04:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bottom left! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 16:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, you should feel the vibe pretty easy whether they say they are or not.  Good luck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 22:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a stylist who is very comfortable with fading.  You may not find that everywhere.  Read reviews and find a good barber in your area.  Just remember to take that pic with you lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 21:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you would rock that style wonderfully.  Just remember to take that photo with you, because consultations can be confusing and it's not the normal way of fading a man's cut.  But, fucking go for it dude! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 09:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree.  This seems like a popular look, so it'd be easy to tell you with a better view of it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 17:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks nice, a lot of different colors, I can't really tell what's going on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 17:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We would really just need to see your hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 18:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
...I agree with you?  I feel like you're yelling at me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 18:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Four Rooms!  Tim Roth, Tarantino,  Madonna... very interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 17:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do I get there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 17:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it weren't for the believers of scientology,  there would be no scientology.  They might be pawns, but they fuel the fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 11:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They just did this multi-million dollar renovation on Caesar's Palace Buffet, holy shit, best buffet in town now.  http://www.caesarspalace.com/restaurants/bacchanal-buffet.html#.UlpiWaO3PFo  No one can argue this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 11:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A miscarriage feels like labor pains.  It's terrible, I don't wish it on my worst enemy.  Instead of the pain giving you a child, it just gives you more pain :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 10:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/wheredidthesodago

Funny, wholesome, doesn't make me sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 10:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep forgetting this specific movie scene.  Broke my heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 10:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They would post fundamentalist pictures, I'd share my opposing opinion.  They unfriended me, but last I saw on Twitter,  they now share my beliefs... I feel I contributed somewhat to their switch, but it wasn't my intention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 10:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soooo accurate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 07:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Four Rooms!  Tim Roth, Tarantino,  Madonna... very interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 18:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I respect your judgement on scientology,  but there is more bullshit in this world than you think.  My christian ex sister-in-law was forced to go to this place in TX as a teen.   http://www.recoveringalumni.com/?m=0# </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 08:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 08:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://m.reviewjournal.com/news/fine-day-hike-leads-blm-fines-red-rock Not in my town, they are assholes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 08:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't put the employees to work to keep the parks up and running, but they make sure there are people working that can give citations. http://m.reviewjournal.com/news/fine-day-hike-leads-blm-fines-red-rock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 07:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not wrong, but he isn't either.  His comment is referencing The Fremont Street Experience, and your article's gray matter is just outside the Fremont Experience,  Fremont east.  As long as you're in the main drag,  drink up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 18:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the magic I was hoping for.  It was this joint concert back in December,  he was playing with The Reverend Horton Heat in Vegas.  He was suppose to be out first.  Nothing was said, no one apologized, just a complete no-show.  The fucker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 18:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was really teetering, but I agree we shouldn't have responded at all.  There is absolutely nothing we could say, and after reading the response billboards again, I definitely agree they are probably the most juvenile way to get the message out.  This is a crucial time for atheism, we can't look lower than they are.  Those response billboards should've been so much more thought out anyway, It shouldn't be that hard to make Ken Ham look like an ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 12:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is your job physically exhausting?  That would be a big factor for me.  But anyway, take off when you can, everyone is right when they say life is meant to be lived. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 09:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  Double negatives are fucking terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 09:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article says the opposite.  http://dictionary.reference.com/help/faq/language/g09.html

I'm not trying to argue but, this makes more sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 08:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jello Biafra of the Dead Kennedy's... the asshole didn't show up.  I still think highly of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 07:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before my grandpa died, he was sitting next to me when that music video came on.  He said, "He wrote that song because of his troubled life, and he knew it would be his last."  I thought it was sweet that he felt the song's emotions, I couldn't bring myself to tell him it wasn't written by Johnny.  No music has ever effected my grandpa enough to talk about it.  This definitely is a good one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 07:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy my life in Las Vegas.  When you get away from the strip, we have some beautiful desert landscaping, beautiful master-planned communities, wide open streets and friendly people.  If you *choose* to be on the strip, we have world-class restaurants and hotels;  and don't forget, debauchery of your choosing.

I don't understand all the hate, if I go to North Town off of Fremont, I could find drug addicts.  They are there, they are in lots of cities.  But it's your opinion to hate our region.  For every bad area of the city, there are good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 05:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their ad is much more distasteful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 03:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is so insane that my situation is identical!  Ultrasound Tuesday. Was planning scheduling d c Wednesday.  All day Wednesday (yesterday) was unbearable pain and between huge clots was oceans of blood.  

I opted for the d c to avoid that whole situation :(  but I had the brunt of it naturally.  They did my d c today, no more blood coming out, still have moderate cramps.  

Hugs xoxo, I wouldn't wish this on my worst enemy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 07:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to help you out, but it's really hard to give advice when I can't see what you're working with.  If you can't post a picture, maybe explain your hair's natural texture and desired length.  It sounds like you want some asymmetrical style, and that's cool, just very vague. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 06:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, you don't see that too often! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 17:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Expensive window cleaner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 16:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crybaby was always a cult classic to me,  then I watched it recently and I realized how cheesy it is.  I still love it, but I can see where people get the hate from.  I honestly haven't talked to a lot of people that have even seen it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 10:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't really tell what's going on with the hair color in these pics.  Post pictures that better shows your hair color and we might be able to help more.

Edit:  If it's something you really desire, you should go for it.  There are some cons.  Short haircuts are a lot more maintenance and upkeep and the picture you chose is an intermediate style to achieve on your own.  It might look easy, but it is a little harder than it looks.  It's not impossible though, you should just be prepared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 08:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cherry Poppin' Daddies.  Everyone thinks it's shitty swing revival band, but they span across many genres.  Plus their energy and stage presence are unparalleled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 07:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes toning it when it has a lot of damage makes it mucky looking.  I would let the hair cuticle calm down and do some conditioning treatments before toning.   

There are so many medium blondes that would be gorgeous against your skin tone.  Brass doesn't suit many people.  Dont give up hope! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 05:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop googling!  Lol.  You have a reason to be positive, the heartbeat!  Stay strong mama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 01:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, what he's saying is she doesn't have to pay til she reaches her destination... where the babysitter could pay for her.  Get it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not a very good ultrasound :( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 19:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 11w 6d.  We were so excited today my nurse was giving us a sneak peek, just for fun because my insurance only covers one US per pregnancy.  She looked for 2 seconds and said "it doesn't look 11 weeks, come back tomorrow for a size and dating ultrasound."  :(  

I had one at 8w5d just for fun and it measured fine with a good heartbeat.  But now I'm feeling very sad.  It did look very small, but she didn't try to move around or find a heartbeat.  I'm trying to be realistic and not overly optimistic,  but we will see.


Edit:  Nightmare confirmed, will be scheduling a D C tomorrow, hope to see all you guys in the future sometime.  :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 07:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something pointless happened every two seconds... jesus, it was over the top with the cheap scares. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 07:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious of your critique. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 13:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vagina bacon knows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 12:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's a good point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 12:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny because it's fake.  But for the first 10 seconds, my brain thought it was real and I was very sad I just watched someone die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
