<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1576</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge rejects Menendez's request for venue change in corruption trial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 00:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dealing with a tough day | wet basement update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 00:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here on the westside of Cleveland we have been in this wet weather loop for some days.  So the ground is saturated and where I live close to the edge of Lake Erie our storm sewers backed up and flooded our basement about 7:30 PM last night.  My son was temporarily residing down there and a lot of his belongings are lost.  Quick action saved it from being worse; but it's been stressful as I dealt with work, my son, the disaster clean up folks, the insurance company and the SO.  The pice de rsistance was when I jumped into the ice-cold shower at 5 AM because the flood knocked out the water heater.  I was able to successfully re-light the water heater before I went to SBUX to hang with the dude. 

So somewhat stressful day, but all in all it has worked out so far.  It worked out and I even got a bike ride in, met with some people on a work matter, and hung out on some on Reddit.  Compare and contrast with 6 years ago.  I would have absolutely exploded at the situation, resentfully responded to my poor family and probably sulked in my room sneak drinking.  Yikes.  

I am so glad I did not drink TODAY. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 23:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/TZ840 to /r/stopdrinking -- yeah, I wouldn't worry about telling anybody for awhile unless it's smart because you want to keep booze out of the residence, e.g. the GF drinks.  So at this [link is a post called the Baby Steps](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) which lays out what I did to stop drinking and to get sober.  I hope something there will help you with "next steps."

Good luck and welcome aboard the lifeboat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 23:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations, my friend on showing us that it can be done.  An invite to join us on /r/dinos will shortly follow in your inbox.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-Ravens cheerleader Molly Shattuck pleads guilty to rape </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 23:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 23:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good work, keep doing what you're doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 23:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/sarmst12 to r/stopdrinking.  When I stopped drinking I was fortunate enough to run into a friend of mine at an AA meeting and he sketched out the [some of the ideas that became the Baby Steps post](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) which gave me sufficient directions that enabled me to stop drinking and to get sober.  Now, I have shared them with you.

Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-NFL Cheerleader -- Guilty of Raping 15-Year-Old Boy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 22:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge rules in favor of DOJ in suit against Arpaio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 22:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Odds on Republican Contenders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 22:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Area restarauteur guilty of molesting and raping a child, jury says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 20:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 20:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> B-e-n-g-h-a-z-i </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gowdy Says E-Mails Handed Over by Clinton Associate Raise Questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 20:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was the EXACT title *at the time* I linked it.  I don't alter titles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smash-mouth politics has arrived. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps spectacular, unending, utterly baffling, often wrong campaign announcement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all know what that was about!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FedEx will pay $227M to settle suits alleging it misclassifiied its delivery drivers as "independent contractors" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama bans trans fat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or the taxing authorities looking for a way to tap small winnings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regularly someone will post about this experience, and periodically I like to suggest a [glance at this post from the FAQ where I describe my email exchange with dream researchers](http://www.reddit.com/r/stopdrinking/comments/2dit1m/what_do_drinking_dreams_mean/) and what I learned about drinking dreams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 17:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations, I just added you to r/dinos, sorry I missed you previously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 17:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Torture reduces us to the level of primates; lower, maybe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 17:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything about this announcement screams WWE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 17:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You won't have Bush-Rubio since they are both from Florida.  VP has to come from another state.  I actually think Kasich is a VP candidate only.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio Lottery considering cashless payouts to winners at stores </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 17:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Indeed?: A Few Words in Favor of Per Curiams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 16:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tess Gerritsen Fails Again in 'Gravity' Lawsuit Against Warner Bros. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 16:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Menendez Confident Cuba Trade Embargo Will Hold </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 15:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress paddles toward brink of a government shutdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 15:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 14:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Highly technical information, then?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 14:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole [Magna Carta](http://www.bl.uk/magna-carta/articles/magna-carta-english-translation) argument is not very useful since it also has fairly obnoxious things to say about Jews and interest rates; and some pretty bizarre things to say about fishing in the Thames. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 14:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's a total bummer.  I got up this morning to take a shower--ice cold water.  The basement flood extinguished the water heater.  A quick cold shower and I was able to re-light the water heater for the SO's shower so I got that going for me.  I meet the disaster clean-up people at 9 AM.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High School Basketball Coach Kills Himself After Being Charged With Sexual Assault </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 13:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 13:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great news!  Keep doing what you're doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope's Missive On Environment, Poverty Could Affect Habits Of Millions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 13:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arpaio's pattern and practice of Stalinistic intimidation and harassment of those who probe his violations of human rights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 13:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greek Showdown Puts Merkel's Teflon Legacy at Risk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 13:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twists Outnumber Judges (So Far) in Case Against Arizona Sheriff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 13:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bushs 4 percent solution | Bush pledges an economic growth rate last seen nationally during the Clinton administration  though he achieved it as Florida governor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 13:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sheldon Adelson Beats 2016 Drum for Marco Rubio Through Free Israeli Newspaper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 13:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jebs logo cant hide the troublesome family name </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 13:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 12:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious, why? The knighthood? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 12:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not drinking TODAY no matter what happens good or bad; even if my basement flooded over night.  Oh noooooooo... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 10:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great link. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 10:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My agnostic AA meeting and our brief AA readings are highly supportive of belief and non-belief.  We do not bash religious belief.  Also, having said that there is one character who goes off (like the guy you called) while most of us just roll our eyes.  In my experience of having been the secretary and chair of many AA meetings over the years and  bearing in mind that usually the secretary is deemed by the membership to be the "sickest" person-- leadership do NOT govern meetings, they are there to serve.  

BTW, here's an AA [position paper to professionals on our many paths.](http://www.aa.org/newsletters/en_US/f-13_winter09.pdf)

Edits:  Yikes, I'm still not sure the above makes any damn sense, once again confirming that I should not try to comment before my first cup of coffee in the morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 03:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/purplepurple77 to /r/stopdrinking -- at this [link is a post called the Baby Steps.](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) The post describes what I did to stop drinking and to get sober.  I'm pretty sure that it's a pretty good place to start the process of stopping.  Let me know.

And good luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 03:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [My **Saturday Share** is at this link. ](http://www.reddit.com/r/stopdrinking/comments/25u6cc/saturday_share_im_train_subject1576_and_i_am_an_alcoholic/)

By the way, I doubt that I will ever drink again; but even now I haven't "quit drinking," instead I make a renewable decision every morning that I am not going to drink TODAY.  In other words, I stopped drinking one day at a time.  That works pretty well for me.  It works much better than all those sober years ago when I told myself that I had permanently "quit drinking." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BTW, there is no SD limit on how many posts or comments you can make a  day ; ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good job, /u/Shawder11 -- progress, not perfection, but you did that perfectly.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations my friend, an invite to join us in the Dino-den will follow shortly in your inbox! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 02:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend /u/1literCC -- this gets increasingly astonishing.  I am so proud of you.  Whenever you hear that little voice, refer to this post.  113.86 gallons of alcohol not processed by your stomach, kidneys, liver, pancreas, bowel, bladder, and most importantly your brain.  Welcome back to life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 23:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not drinking TODAY no matter what happens good or bad--in solidarity with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 23:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'll delete.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just how fast the Truncator chainsaw saw horse is </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 23:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 23:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally resembled that thinking process; until I stopped drinking and until I learned that sustained time stopped changed all of that into a process that looks something like this (sorry no pie graft):

Get up!  Make a decision not to drink TODAY.  Memorialize the decision by logging into the morning Check-in.  Do the simple things on my list for the day: coffee with friends read the New York Times; work, household chores, personal errands, recovery meetings;  improve my life.  Go to bed SOBER.  Repeat.  

The result is that my life when from ruination of health, wealth and reputation to a mainly happy, free and valued SOBER life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 22:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Even now, writing this, part of me is ashamed and embarrassed that I would pray, but hey, it works for me.

Please, don't ever be embarrassed by this.  I am astounded by your courage in posting this.  I am positive there are many, many SDers who feel the same way you do and don't have the courage to admit it on the Sub.  Listen, my friend, many times I've been asked about my morning ritual and while it is true that I am a real agnostic and sometimes atheist--my re-written 3rd Step prayer is what I slide out of my bed and say every morning.  It works for me.  And before I go to bed at night I repeat it in gratitude for my sober day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 22:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's where I was at 25 days in recovery: my wife was having an affair with her then (sociopath law partner); my daughter who was a high-school senior was newly pregnant; my son was trying out his gay-period as a high-school sophomore; and I would be going to federal prison for tax evasion.  In short we were living the whole dysfunctional American dream. 

Flash forward nearly 6 years: my wife and I fully reconciled (yeah, 27 year marriages are complex); my legal troubles are behind me (Orange is the New Black is my new fav Netflix series); my 41/2 year old grandson Riley is the light of my life; and, my son is knocking down theater awards including a rave review in today's paper for his "hilarious" performance as the Nazi playwright in the Producers.  

I'm sure what I'm saying is obvious: don't drink and life is one hell of an interesting adventure.  Even my feelings of betrayal and my broken heart healed with time.  Good luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 21:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if that's the binary, it's a no-brainer.  I'd trust HRC with IT, and not trust Rubio with making nominations to lifetime federal judge-ships, especially the Supreme Court. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 21:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Racheal Dolezal followed this advice and see how well it worked out for her?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 20:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True story: many years ago I had a client who was killed after being crushed by a casting at a steel factory when an overloaded crane collapsed.  Should have been a no-brainer workers' compensation death claim but on autopsy the pathology report noted 12 nanograms of THC.  The claim was disallowed because--my man was presumptively high.  I hired the leading expert in that era on the subject of THC intox who testified that he and other scientists tried to arrive at a scale of THC intox based on the blood-alcohol model and had utterly failed.  He indicated that there is no means of objectively measuring impairment from THC based on presence in the bloodstream.  I won my case.  Frankly, this should not have been an issue since my deceased worker was not involved in any operational respect as it related to the casting or crane that killed him, but why let a little logic get involved in depriving a widow of death benefits.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Billionaire former chief executive of the American International Group, prevails in lawsuit against the US on Monday, awarded $0 damages. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 20:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maurice R. Greenberg, the former chief executive of the American International Group, prevailed in his lawsuit against the United States government on Monday, but a federal judge declined to award any damages. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 20:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/SuckMyKaHawk to r/stopdrinking.  I hope you feel free to fall right in.  Check out the daily check-in post.  Oh, and here's the [link to the Baby Steps.](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/)  Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blogger gets 5 years for video of ailing wife of US Senator Thad Cochrane published in online "hit piece" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blogger sentenced to 5 years for taping Sen. Cochrans ailing wife </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asked to appeal death sentence, pro bono lawyer gets innocent client freed from prison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or your tie knot.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rachel Dolezal Steps Down As President Of Spokane NAACP Chapter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 18:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pa. girl, 2, found dead in woods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 18:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Van Morrison is the WB Yeats of music, say friends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Robin Cannon, the plant expert at Lake View Cemetery (photos) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been to lots of AA meetings over almost 30 years; and, I've been to a few crazy meetings, too.  Usually, I need to stay attuned to "the winners."   There are always two types of examples in recovery: good examples and bad example, but even the bad examples can be good examples if you know how to unpack the meaning.  ; ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colorado Supreme Court: employers can fire their workers who smoke pot when not at work </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colorado Supreme Court affirms lower court rulings that employers can fire employees who smoke pot when not at work </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine if the media covered alcoholism for the public health crisis that it is--it would make the horror over Aids and Ebola pale in comparison.

Thanks for the link! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I can't help but think that AA is doing me more harm than good, I do suffer from depression and AA seems to amplify that due to some of the self defeating and negative attitudes that go on in the room. I feel like I need self empowerment not self depreciation which I feel like is what some AA members preach.

I've never been to a meeting like this, let alone several meetings so that I felt that a pattern was emerging.  I have been in dark or depressed places where I had the reverse of rose-colored glasses on; and, I processed what I saw and what I heard in a way that lead me to believe as you seem to believe and which you ascribe as an AA message.  

But by all means, try a SMART recovery meeting!  I give you a lot of credit for persisting in seeking help.  Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mitt Romney: Hillary Clinton's Eyes Saying Where's My Latte? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 16:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 6th Circuit criticizes federal judge who told lawyer to shut up, improvised jury instruction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 16:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 15:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Plain English translation.](http://www.bl.uk/magna-carta/articles/magna-carta-english-translation) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Coyote Cafe and its bulldog of a lawyer have survived the worst of times. Santa Fe is better for having both of them healthy again | Lawyer survives heart attack at Cafe` due to owner's quick thinking; helps Cafe` overcome debt-threat to existence of business </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 15:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 15:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skid-no-more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 15:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine too!  Everyone of his novels has been a total delight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 14:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both excellent points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawyer charged with hiring hitman, indicted for poisoning wife </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 14:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, good for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Motorcyclist Linda Skidmore, 68, who died in crash with truck wasn't wearing her helmet, police say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carl Hiaasen: Would you trust Rubio with nations finances? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude walks into a local bank, no mask, no disguise--demands $400 bucks.  The teller gives him $400 in singles; he pats his pocket says something like, no big bills.  She exchanges the $400 in small bills for 4 Benjamins.  He drives off.  Identifying him was apparently not a problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cleveland police ID suspect accused of robbing bank in flip-flops, Cavs shirt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations on 300 days; in 2 months I look forward to adding you to r/dinos! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Take A Swing At This: Golf Is Exercise, Cart Or No Cart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Archbishop John Nienstedt, Deputy Resign After Archdiocese Of St. Paul and Minneapolis Charged With Sex Abuse Coverup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also check out the Morning Check-in; it's how a lot of us ritually memorialize our decision not to drink TODAY.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So as outrageous and racist as this is--how is this not Free Speech? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Student charged with putting noose on Ole Miss statue of slain civil rights leader, James Meredith, to plead guilty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Blues Brother' Aykroyd supports law enforcement, Mississippi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christie on Clinton: 'How would she know' about 'real Americans'? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stop Revering Magna Carta </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal government keeps declaring Alabamians dead when they are not: Wake Up Call </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mitt Romney Decries GOP Infighting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I did the [the Baby Steps, at this link.](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) The Baby Steps are the things I did and do to stop drinking and to get sober.  Good luck.  I hope you get traction and join us on the SOBER journey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not drinking TODAY no matter what happens good or bad; in soggy Cleveland I still believe: Go CAVS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 12:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're not feeling well please call a doctor.  Otherwise hang in there, personally I have been there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 11:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome out of lurk, /u/runinjagal. Please keep posting as you go along. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 10:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did the things I describe [at this link to a post called the Baby Steps.](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/)  I still do these things TODAY.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 10:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We talk about this, but probably not enough.  I honestly can't think of a time in my drinking where I was happy with only one or two drinks or beers.  In fact given the choice during most of my drinking career between one drink or beer and not drinking at all--I'd usually not drink at all.  A single drink or two would simply set off cravings, make me uncomfortable, and make me more likely to flee a social situation to "feed my disease."  Personally a funny fact: I met my wife the night I was sitting at an upscale bar doing the crossword puzzle and drinking a diet coke.  I was "pacing" for that evening's drinking; it was far too early in the evening to do the kind of drinking I would end up doing that night.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 10:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is totally on topic as evident from the responses.  Income inequality it the animating issue of both the Clinton and the Sanders candidacies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 02:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can say in hindsight, jumping into AA meetings helped me enormously with all of that.  Again, just my personal experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 02:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The political argument is about income inequality.  Of course, your comment is one of the arguments being made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The top 25 hedge fund managers earn more than all kindergarten teachers in U.S. combined </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 00:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new complaint against Washington's Pierce County Prosecutor Mark Lindquist accuses him of trying to improperly influence a judge, calls for a federal criminal investigation of his office and declares that Lindquist is unfit to practice law. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 22:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feuding Lawyers Facing New Showdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 22:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leonard Pitts, Jr.: What do you think of the death penalty now, Justice Scalia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 21:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 21:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> P-e-r-f-e-c-t! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 21:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well-done /u/mac_question it sounds to me like you're in the right place.  Let me share the [Baby Steps post with you](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) which is a description of what I did to stop drinking and get sober.  Maybe some of the ideas there will be helpful to you too.  Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton champions voter rights. Christie gets defensive. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 21:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 20:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations, my friend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 20:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Right now I am just thinking "I will never drink again." but then questioning that, because I've said that so many times.

If I were thinking that way I'd be lost too.  But I don't think that way at all.  In fact despite 2000+ days of continuous sobriety I still do it one day at a time.  At this [link to a post called the Baby Steps](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) I explain exactly what I did.

Good luck on finding yourself.  If you stay on this sub, I'll bet you anything that you will begin to find yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Female Scientists Show Just How Distractingly Sexy They Can Be </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 20:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 19:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unbelievably smoking hot in [Anatomy of a Muderer](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0052561/) possibly the greatest but least known lawyer-courtroom film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nikki Haley, Bobby Jindal explain their faith during The Response prayer meeting Saturday po </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 16:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 16:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, this is the corollary of Voltaire's famous aphorism:

*Dans ses crits, un sage Italien
Dit que le mieux est l'ennemi du bien.*

In his writings, a wise Italian
says that the best is the enemy of the good.

Enjoy your lazy Sunday, VE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 16:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you, /u/Andrew_Tefft--I hope we're stuck with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 14:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, /u/hhhlo -- I hope you will be handling the check-in when you have 30 days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 14:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I forgot to thank /u/flow_morpheus_flow for the service to us all in putting up the check-in last week!  Thank you friend.  And welcome to /u/chinstrap!  Thanks for taking it on this week.  I love this ritual, it's really part of what I look forward to, every morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 14:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so glad you're here, /u/hhhlo -- you are part of the whole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 14:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> REO Speedwagon and fans frozen in time circa 1978; but, sagely singing:

So if you're tired of the

Same old story

Turn some pages

I'll be here when you are ready

To roll with the changes
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 14:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you; hang tough.  It's worth it.  

Listen, if this were easy there would be no alcoholism.  Heavy or abusive drinkers would stop or moderate--end of story.  Instead we lose hundreds of thousands of lives worldwide directly to this disease.  If ebola did this to our populations we would be in a worldwide medical emergency and we'd recognize the seriousness of what we are grappling with in terms of a health crisis.

Here's what I can say from my personal experience: active alcoholism was killing me; and, sobriety is a beautiful alternative ALTHOUGH in the early days of sobriety it often doesn't feel that way.  It took time for my body and brain to recover and worse I continued to believe that I was missing out on the party.  That latter piece of the puzzle is particularly dark--because that message is my old alkie thinking in the throes of trying to send me back into my disorder.  My answer: don't drink TODAY and trust the experience of others that its well worth the struggle because it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a long time AA, I would encourage you to definitely make the effort to get to one of those agnostic/atheist meetings.  Perhaps you will find the person you think will be an ideal sponsor at one of those meetings.  In the interim I would for sure use the phone numbers and ask the same question you ask in this post to your friends.  Finally, pro-tip--when you connect with a running crowd of like-believers or non-believers you may well find a set of meetings that closely align with your belief or non-belief that are not advertised as agnostic/atheist meetings.  And, as you go along feel free to ask for help among your friends to start an agnostic/atheist meeting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I quit smoking cigarettes 23 years ago using willpower.  I lost 60 pounds using will power.  I trained and ran a marathon using will power.  But I could not recover from alcoholism through willpower.  I needed a power outside of myself.  I found that power outside myself in the fellowship of other people in recovery.  I accessed information about my underlying problems; I received explicit directions to address my issues connected with recovery; I was supported in success and failure; despairing I had phone numbers to call; I found positive social activities that did not involve my former drinking milieu; I found a road map through the chaos of my pass; I discovered a way to objectively check my condition and progress; and, I found a purpose for my life.  None of these things were available to me via my self-will or willpower.  These directions came from outside.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big lie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps you misunderstand my comment on what I call the 4 goals or purpose of recovery (actually paraphrasing The Natural History of Alcoholism, at p. 365 Vaillant, Harvard University Press 1995).  Officially, AA does not have 4 goals.   In fact AA's official "primary purpose" is stated succinctly in the "Preamble" which is to stay sober and help other alcoholics.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nixon gets $50K from UAW days after veto on right to work </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michigan Gov. Rick Snyder is hailed as a 'moderate', but he signed anti-gay bills anyway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poll: Would Christie's brash demeanor help him with foreign relations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Failed Attempt to Rebuke Lawmakers Riles Texas GOP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sorry, vegans: Eating meat and cooking food is how humans got their big brains </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After I make my morning decision that I am not going to drink TODAY, alcohol is not in my movie.  This idea, this belief, this personal reality means other people's drinking has NOTHING to do with me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my experience true RECOVERY was not possible without help from outside myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...or you create your own agnostic meeting and discover how quickly you attract fellow agnostic participants.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rich Californians balk at limits: Were not all equal when it comes to water </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 12:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not drinking TODAY no matter what happens good or bad; I'm keeping Sunday SOBER all day, here in Cleveland! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 10:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I'd try to do is remember that alcoholism is a well-recognized medical disease and TRY to treat my in-law with compassion.  More than even that I would remember that as an active alcoholic in the immediate past I personally was no prize to my wife and children.  Out of respect for my immediate family, I would practice love and tolerance of my troubled in-law during his brief stay.  

Most importantly for myself, I would continue to make the daily decision not to drink TODAY, doggedly persist, and above all remember that it is One Day at a Time.

Best of luck with this tough situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 02:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  alcoholism is a disease of the spirit.

This is so true.  Well said, my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lindsey Graham with the quote of the week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 02:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lindsey Graham campaigns with a smile, one wisecrack at a time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 02:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 02:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How dare you tell us what's moral or not moral!  Who do you think you are?!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> But the real solution in AA is built on 4 simple ideas: 1. Give the alcoholic a substitute for the dependence on booze; 2. Remind the alcoholic RITUALLY that even one drink will lead to pain and relapse; 3. Repair the social and medical damage that was done; 4. Restore self-esteem. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 01:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're very smart to seek as much support at this stage of the journey because in early sobriety we need to extinguish the old reinforcers of drinking friends, drinking venues, and drinking activities. That is why successful recovery is almost always a journey of fellowship. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 01:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 00:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two things: 

1. I posted this in /r/law and /r/badlawyer yesterday; 

2. /r/politics deletes many of my links for myriad stupid reasons including my link to an article this morning where Scott Walker was called a liar by the British Prime Minister over false claims Walker made about President Obama.  "Off-topic."  A link to the endorsement of Rick Perry by the American Sniper widow was deleted as off-topic.  It's gotten to a point where most mods no longer bother to respond to my objections or inquiries.  The deletions are indefensible under their own rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 00:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the US, our Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 better known as HIPAA is similarly implicated, but the right to recover for a breach of confidentiality would not survive the decedent.  It's interesting, I'm dealing with a family of a gentleman who died of lung cancer and the Cleveland Clinic is making access to the decedent's medical records nearly impossible even for the surviving widow, again because of HIPAA.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 00:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly believe that those of us who KNOW for ourselves that we are alcoholic and that we should get help--have already taken the first 3 steps the day we walk through the doors of our first AA meeting.  I think that it's useful, though, to get a sponsor and "work through" every step with the sponsor even 1-3 at a pace most comfortable for you and the sponsor.  The "clean up steps" 4-9 are best addressed systematically over the course of the first and possibly second years.  I posted earlier in the week about a difficult financial amends with the IRS that I'm working on and I'm just a couple of months shy of 6 years if that gives you any idea of how these can take time.  Finally, all this work is about creating a blueprint for living your authentic life and helping others.  So 10, 11, and 12 are all about that aspect of your new life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-DeMaio aide admits faking email threats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 23:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 23:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The issue with human remains is fairly settled in most states (and to be clear, state not federal law governs this question).  The human corpse and its attendant organs are supposed to be the PROPERTY of the decedent's estate and thus belong to the executor or next of kin.  But the disposition of the body otherwise--i.e. the pathology, tissue donation, or errors in switching corpses have not successfully given rise to lawsuits.  

Frankly, I'm the OP of this link and an attorney and I mostly find the story interesting from the standpoint that nearly every aspect of "personhood" creates rights and remedies and this slightly ghoulish example was a colorful but not terribly important situation except to illustrate that outrage does not mean actionable lawsuit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 23:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I an so sick of the GOP claiming they are the ones who represent Vets 

As a US Army veteran of the Viet Nam era, I totally agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 23:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple of years ago I got into this discussion using the lifeboat metaphor.  For me, if I were drowning and I was thrown a lifeline about to be pulled aboard a lifeboat I KNOW I wouldn't question the belief system of my rescuers, but that's what we alcoholics seem to do  reflexively.  Of course, AA language has ingrained references to God and prayer--but the real solution in AA is built on 4 simple ideas:

1. Give the alcoholic a substitute for the dependence on booze;

2. Remind the alcoholic RITUALLY that even one drink will lead to pain and relapse;

3. Repair the social and medical damage that was done;

4. Restore self-esteem.

That is the point and the purpose of the 12 Steps.  AA is the simplest and most accessible model for achieving these 4 simple ideas IN MY EXPERIENCE.  BTW, I believe SMART Recovery and Rational Recovery are designed to do the same 4 things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fired director calls Arizona Governor Ducey a 'lying, puffed up evil Barney Rubble" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 20:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Four Texas Members of Congress Took Trip Secretly Funded by Foreign Government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 20:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guns in Your Face </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 20:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Des Moines, Bernie Sanders' Supporters Nearly Steal the Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 20:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican elite convene at Romney summit in search of a Clinton foil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a shop vac! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at my home group Thursday night and after listening to the prayers and mentions of God, I made sure I said--if your new here (we always have new people at this meeting) you do not need to believe in God, or a higher power, or prayer.  You are welcome here.  No one will look down on you over your belief or non-belief.  

I hope that you will remember to do likewise when you feel strong enough and included-enough in your meetings to make sure the newcomers hear that message--the message of inclusion.  The only requirement for membership in AA is a desire to stop drinking and I'm personally glad you are giving it a shot.  Now having said all that -- I needed to get over myself and the notion that my objections to religious belief were an obstacle to my getting sober when in reality MY ego was my biggest obstacle.

Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice!  sniff  Nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes!  Social anxiety is a fairly normal part of early recovery.  Can you think of any reasons why apart from your individual psychological make up?  It's actually pretty simple if you think about it.  When we do drugs and alcohol we are intentionally cutting ourselves off from engagement with others.  Often we isolate in order to do whatever our drug or drugs of choice are--undisturbed by family, friends or acquaintances.  Now that we're sober we do the whole social thing without the aid of chemicals--it's like learning how to ride a bicycle in public without training wheels.  But guess what?  Training wheels are available at the closest AA meeting.  It's how I successfully reintegrated.  Don't be afraid to speak up--we want you to open your mouth and tell us your experience!  Someone in the room may need to hear what you have to say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/Germain_Goldchain to r/stopdrinking.  You may already have come across [this link to the Baby Steps](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) which is what I did to stop drinking and to get sober.  These are the simple next steps to start stopping for many of us.  Good luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/wannabechefjojo to r/stopdrinking--so [at this link is the post known on the sub as the Baby Steps](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) which lays out simple "next actions" we can take to stop drinking and to get sober.  I did these things and the Baby Steps are a daily part of my life.  Best of luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did AA.  I met a bunch of lunatics that I began hanging with.  We did  golf, softball, bowling, meals, dating, and everything I thought I was doing when I drank.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heck, /u/fear2111 -- I thought you were going to ask a hard one!  So at this [link is a post called the Baby Steps](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) which describes in detail how I stopped drinking and how I got sober.  Now let me be specific about getting away from beer.  When I make my conscious daily decision not to drink TODAY no matter what happens good or bad, alcohol is out of my movie for the day, all day. This includes beer.  But let's go one baby step further--I need new friends, new situations and new activities BECAUSE I need to extinguish the old reinforcers--my beered-up buddies, bar rooms, and drinking activities.  For me this mean recovery, and AA was the easiest, most accessible route to recovery.  In doing this I needed to get rid of my preconceptions about what this might involve and dive in.  I did and it worked for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Source.](http://www.aaagnostics.org/agnostic12steps.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I created a stand alone post with the Agnostic 12 Steps.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Agnostic 12 Steps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Agnostic 12 Steps:

1. We admitted we were powerless over alcoholthat our lives had become unmanageable.

2. Came to believe and to accept that we needed strengths beyond our awareness and resources to restore us to sanity.

3. Made a decision to entrust our will and our lives to the care of the collective wisdom and resources of those who have searched before us.

4. Made a searching and fearless moral inventory of ourselves.

5. Admitted to ourselves without reservation, and to another human being the exact nature of our wrongs.

6. Were ready to accept help in letting go of all our defects of character.

7. With humility and openness sought to eliminate our shortcomings.

8. Made a list of all persons we had harmed, and became willing to make amends to them all.

9. Made direct amends to such people wherever possible, except when to do so would injure them or others.

10. Continued to take personal inventory and when we were wrong, promptly admitted it.

11. Sought through meditation to improve our spiritual awareness and our understanding of the AA way of life and to discover the power to carry out that way of life.

12. Having had a spiritual awakening as a result of these steps, we tried to carry this message to alcoholics, and to practice these principles in all our affairs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 14:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stunning post, Sam.  You do have way more than booze and drunken conversation--you have a blueprint, a road map for a whole new way of life.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 13:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 90 degrees yesterday!  Raining cats and dogs this morning and cool.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christie's foreign trips cost N.J. taxpayers nearly $124,000 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 13:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 13:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or "W." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News Targets New Jersey Newspaper for Posting Clips of Its Political Coverage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 13:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 13:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's one of the coolest things about sobriety--you get to discover what is your new normal.  

You're very smart to seek as much support at this stage of the journey because **in early sobriety we need to extinguish the old reinforcers of drinking friends, drinking venues, and drinking activities.**  That is why successful recovery is almost always a journey of fellowship.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge Throws Out 'New Girl' Idea Theft Claims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 13:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Best Jokes About the White NAACP Leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 13:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mitt Romney gives a brutal PowerPoint critique of Obamas foreign policy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 13:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keeping it classy, NYPOST calls NY Prison escape arrest "Shaw-Skank" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 11:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Murphy plots a win for Jeb Bush in the land of Hollywood liberals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 11:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 10:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/MuiLaV to /r/stopdrinking -- I found it useful not to think of myself "quitting drinking" which implies permanently changing my habits.  Instead I stop drinking TODAY, only, and I can renew this commitment, daily if I choose.  But, let me give you MY broader blueprint: [it is at a separate post called the Baby Steps.](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/)  The Baby Steps are what I did to stop drinking and to get SOBER. Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 10:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will not drink TODAY no matter what happens good or bad; I'm doing rainy Saturday in Cleveland SOBER, all day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 03:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very insightful for someone at 6 days!  Good for you.  

I think it's a pretty common experience in recovery that at some early point--if we are sincere--we find that we have become new people.  We start to live with a new purpose to become who we thought we might be. We become interested in passions and interests that we dreamed we do someday if we could ever get off the bar stool or out of the club.  

It's all out there, keep doing what you're doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 03:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weekends were never my problem, drinking was.  If I make a daily decision that I am not going to drink TODAY no matter what happens good or bad--alcohol is out of my movie for the day, no matter what day it is.  The fellowship of other sober pals is my reinforcement. My commitment to myself and to my sober friends is all that I need. Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 02:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations, /u/royalobi!  So, this whole getting SOBER thing is working out for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British Leader to Scott Walker: I Never Dissed Obama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 02:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
