<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8959</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-01 19:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Four days ago, I suffered a heart attack. Pretty fit, early 30's, completely unexpected. I had some incredible plans for New Years Eve and suddenly, in what seemed like one split second, everything changed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When have you had a well thought out plan completely fall apart, and what caused it to happen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-01 19:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This letter from a lesbian fan of 'Duck Dynasty' could single handedly brings more rationality and sense to the issue than every person arguing about It over the past week combined. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-25 13:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 22:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you own a dashcam and you are not a police officer - you might be an asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this Tim and Eric? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 16:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit - Did Han Solo shoot first in the original Star Wars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-30 04:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israeli Redditors, what are your thoughts on the recent Iran nuclear deal in Geneva? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-24 19:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-24 18:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can be swayed on a subject as serious as the death penalty because of a comment on Reddit, you are a shining example of idiocy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-24 15:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Begun, the Israel spin machine has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 05:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you are incredibly weak minded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bloomberg journalist writing article exposing corruption in China allegedly suspended "because of fears that Bloomberg would be expelled from China" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 20:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-16 15:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I vomited in my mouth. A lot. And had to gulp it back down. Because of you. And I've voted Democrat for 20 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-16 02:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> End existence of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-16 01:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From my standpoint as an American, it seems more countries are voicing dismissal/rejection of American policy. Brazil, Albania, even Mexico seems to be much more independent of US influence lately. I'd like to get perspective from other countries on this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors around the world - do you feel the United States is losing influence in your area? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-16 01:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 18:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so impressed with this post. I am flush with envy at the stardom you are exposed to as you lick peoples boots. I would trade anything to be in your position, basking in the dying, faded light of the celebrity of others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 05:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only by the lowest denominator of voter, so I doubt it will do much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 05:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean Governor McAuliffe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 05:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You either win or you lose. Pointing out the margins is just petty at this point, and crying "Obamacare" while complaining about how much Dems spent is just ludicrous. You know that, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 04:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the party that supported unlimited corporate cash in elections is bitching that it was "outspent"? I am loving every second of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 04:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Republicans had won, it would have been a "referendum on Obamacare". When a Democrat wins, its "lesser of two evils". WTF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 06:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My vote is Money by Pink Floyd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What song best represents the 20 century? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 06:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What song do you think represents the previous century most accurately? Not albums, not bands - just one single song, taken at face value.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA 'monitored 60m Spanish calls in a month' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 11:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 20:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, stay in your basement and hide, that'll show them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 16:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure he'll beat the charges. And the people issuing the charges. And the camera crew on the steps as he leaves the court. And the girl waiting for him in the car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 16:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This attitude is the result of a concerted effort over many years to disparage and disillusion the very core group that could actually influence voting outcomes. The fact that you are apathetic and "rebelling" via abstaining reflects a resounding success in their efforts to prevent change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Brown jailed on felony assault charge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 16:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wikileaks publishes Bohemian Grove guest list. Names include Donald Rumsfeld, Clint Eastwood and Jimmy Buffet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 04:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 02:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you taught your kid a lesson by dressing like a convicted pedophile? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-26 18:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ben Affleck will be Batman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-26 18:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-26 18:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still laughing at this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could send a message containing 5 words or less to your past self, exactly 10 years ago, what would it say? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-26 16:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-26 16:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this is considered "in the gutter", I've done things that would keep you up for days on end, sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 06:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite reddit post, ever. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 06:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Threadjack much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 06:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wondering if Google is testing empty defenses of poor business decisions on reddit now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 21:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hide my bottle of chloroform. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 16:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Article said they have 5 million max. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Transformers' Director Michael Bay Attacked on Set </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 21:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CBS '60 Minutes' Bob Simon: Detroit reminds me of Mogadishu, Somalia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 03:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Madonna Banned From Alamo Drafthouse After Texting During '12 Years A Slave' NYFF Premiere </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 20:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best description for a 'Nightmare on Elm Street' toaster you'll read today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 15:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you don't want Google using your face in advertisements to your friends in Google+, here's the opt out link. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 23:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 00:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am looking right now to find out if there are any polls reflecting the percentage of Americans that approve of painful brain parasites for  comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Latest AP poll shows only 5 percent of Americans approve of Congress. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 23:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silk Road investigation broadens to Britain, four arrested </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 18:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cute yet creepy? Somersaulting MIT cube robots can self-assemble </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 14:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 21:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is becoming increasingly obvious the NSA is carrying out a war on humanity as a whole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secret NSA documents show campaign against Tor encrypted network </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 21:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 17:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it makes you feel any better, he was shot to death and didn't die of cancer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 17:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Criminal complaint detailing the FBI case against Ross Ulbricht, the suspected admin of the 'Silk Road' marketplace. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 19:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 23:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breaking Bad was a prequel to Malcolm in the Middle. Walt fakes his death, escapes, flees and starts a new life when he meets Lois. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To those on Reddit that initially believed Edward Snowden was a traitor, have you changed your mind? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-21 21:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If so, curious what finally caused the change? If not, why do you believe he is a traitor? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syrian rebel al Qaeda groups now attacking Western targets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 15:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 02:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, everyone is downvoting and I didnt even mention the fact that she is a cow. Weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 02:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pictures of awful parents are hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 02:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to hear your definition of the word 'art'. I'm a long time hitRECord member and a huge fan, but the concept of art is something I don't hear you discuss in detail so anything you could throw my way would be appreciated thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 15:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember that his dick is none of your business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 23:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google has zero credibility at this point. They can backpedal and try to suddenly appear concerned, but it's too late.

We are the kids that walked into the bedroom and found our mom Google in bed with her hands around the NSA's throbbing shaft. There is no way they can erase those awful images from my mind. Not happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 01:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you stole saline and IV tubing and set it up without an order? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-08 01:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine that sucked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-08 00:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For myself, it was working in a storage clearinghouse for a large grocery chain. Below freezing temps in the freezer, no breaks, barely lunch and horrible coworkers. All boosted by 12 hour shifts and no benefits. Was curious what others have gone through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what was the worst job you ever had? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-08 00:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 00:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the most recent revelations regarding NSA accessing their networks, Microsoft supplying Outlook encryption keys and other data mining policies, I don't believe one fucking thing Microsoft or Google have to say on this issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 00:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marriage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 03:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't yiff but if I were to yiff, I would yiff Gadget until she called the cops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian Nerds Have Started a Cult Around Gadget Hackwrench from Rescue Rangers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 03:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 01:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oil. Israel. Capitalism. 

Apathetically rearrange, wash, repeat. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-04 05:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Don't take the highroad. Kill her." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-04 04:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha ha molestation signs are hilarious... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those of you familiar with the 9:30 club in Washington DC, 'That Guy' Josh Burdette passed away. RIP. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 21:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 18:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The moment you put Reverend in front of your name, you volunteer for a higher level of scrutiny than the "rest of us" in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Jackie Kennedy despised Dr. Martin Luther King for allegedly showing up to JFK's funeral drunk. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 02:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN has stooped to an awful new low </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 03:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the moon rock that was given to the Dutch prime minister by Neil Armstrong, Buzz Aldrin and Michael Collins in 1969 was actually a piece of petrified wood. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 01:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 00:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pork stool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 01:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That girl deserves better than a guy who posts pictures of plants to reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 05:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the new definition of mistake to me. If anyone I know ever comes to me and says something like "I'm thinking of starting up heroin" or "I think I should spend all of my money on Zynga stock" I am going to say "You are possibly making a major Ben Affleck is going to play Batman in the next Man of Steel film". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ben Affleck to play Batman in 'Man of Steel' sequel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 05:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 01:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would disagree on this, imo nothing is more dangerous to our immediate society than letting those under 18 think they can murder someone openly and not suffer consequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 01:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Questionable actions by a kid at night, creeping around a neighborgood then gets shot while assaulting a guard - Obama calls him his son, leads a firestorm of racist supposition.

Clearly innocent kid gunned down randomly by an openly racist kid and his friends - Obama hasn't said a word.

Interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IT LOOKED ME DEAD IN THE EYES AND SAID THIS IN A VOICE THAT SOUNDED EXACTLY LIKE CHRISTOPHER WALKEN </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 00:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 01:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The two are about neck and neck imo. Both show the depths government is willing to go to get its way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could name one single song that summarizes your entire life, what would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 00:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tool That Looks For Consciousness In The Brain Could Change End-Of-Life Decisions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 18:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 18:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think any of them are capable of feeling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA document: What to say, and not to say, to 'our overseers' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 21:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police find letters from Hannah Anderson at Dimaggios home, also note the pair contacted one another 13 times before alleged kidnapping. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 00:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YOU WAKE UP TO A RUMBLE, A THUMPING, WATER IN YOUR GLASS RIPPLING. AS YOU WIPE THE CRUST FROM YOUR EYES YOU SEE THIS. WHAT DO YOU DO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 00:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 03:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who cares? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Miami man posts gruesome Facebook photo of dead wife with apparent murder confession </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 22:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 12:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Transgendered people suffer from a form of body image distortion in my opinion. I'm not sure it's the same thing. I am frustrated when they are lumped together with bi/homosexual men and women. Trans is a different animal. It's like saying "All blacks,Asians and Arabs are the same because they are all minorities!"

Not the same at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 12:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dated a gay man once who didn't believe in bisexualism. He did not handle it well when I left him for a woman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 03:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SAY THAT TO MY ONLINE FUCKER, AND NOT FACE AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS FAGET </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> St. Pete man calls 911 and asks cops to bring him Kool-Aid and drugs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-04 16:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-27 09:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOU -'- RE A FAGGOT, FAGGOT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never too soon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 15:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-14 05:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets ogle at bones. Theres nothing primitive about that at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 20:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Racism isn't funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 20:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, not only do you know how to link to my profile but you can post links to? Look at you go! Next you'll be pooping all by yourself! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 19:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No time today but I will as soon as I can. She has band practice Saturday so I probably can email them to myself and clean up before she's back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 16:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it isn't. We give Israel the money, there are zero repayment terms for Israel. They are waived. No repayment. No interest. Nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 16:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that I have to explain myself to anyone, but sure. A country that dictates our policy, ridicules our economics in open public addresses and has less national debt than we do should be, in theory, able to support themselves without attaching their lips to our nipples. Just my opinion, but handing aid to a country that has repeatedly been caught spying in our government and repeatedly acts without consulting us (normally to the detriment of the entire middle eastern region) is not someone we should be shoveling hundreds of millions to when we have major economic problems in this country that could use those funds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 03:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, posting random figures without checking them is great work... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 03:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? We have caught, in the past 15 years, more Israeli spies working in our government than any other country. They openly refer to us as cattle.  The blatantly refuse to end the temper tantrum known as the Gaza incursion and are dragging us and every other democratic society into the fray. In fact, I can't think of one single thing Israel has done for us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone explain why we are giving Israel over 175 million dollars in "foreign aid" to begin with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 00:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.haaretz.com/news/diplomacy-defense/israel-will-lose-175-million-in-u-s-foreign-aid-due-to-sequestration-cuts.premium-1.506024 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 01:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now this is an answer that makes sense to me. Thanks. It would technically not be searching ones PC, but their use of open lines. Gotcha, thanks for shedding some light on that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 01:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now name calling. Your intellect and penis size must be genuinely profound sir because I for one am impressed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 01:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is what I found interesting. I was curious if this argument has ever been applied to corporations. Can the use of a service forfeit certain rights? Radical example, could a woman working for WalMart legally be told by the company that she is not allowed to vote? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 01:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. You're assuming I mean this to apply to me. Poor stance.
2. You're assuming a stranger on the internet could not possibly read. Poor presentation.
3. You use arbitrary betting and worthless words instead of facts or sources. Wasted time.

Thanks though. Appreciate your effort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 01:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the federal ruling granting students the right to privacy from their educational institutions, which are not government entities, is incorrect?

For reference:
http://education-law.lawyers.com/school-law/Students-Have-Privacy-Rights-Under-the-Fourth-Amendment.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 01:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on what precedent? This is what I am trying to ascertain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 01:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it doesn't specify government.

"The right of the people to be secure in their persons, houses, papers, and effects, against unreasonable searches and seizures, shall not be violated, and no Warrants shall issue, but upon probable cause, supported by Oath or affirmation, and particularly describing the place to be searched, and the persons or things to be seized" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 01:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on what? If you're using Mcdonalds drive through, can they search your car? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-24 21:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We as a country have a little bit more to worry about right now than a pretty little soundbite that they can throw up in the 2014 election cycle. This is nice, but since the research was PAID FOR BY US, it isn't exactly a nice gesture to GIVE THE RESULTS TO US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
