<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject893</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Bill Gates distributed his net worth equally among every US citizen then he could give every man, woman, and child $242. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 08:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did you get into a fight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 07:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How has your life changed since you first contracted an STD? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 01:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The episodes in season 5 of Rescue Me is completely out of order </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 08:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched the first episode of the season and the second made no sense. So I looked at the order of episodes on the wiki and it's completely different from Netflix. 

Edit: I'm also down a few drinks so sorry for the grammar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have any of you done the whole Jurassic Jeep thing? How much did it all cost? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 05:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Convertible/roadster style trucks other than the wrangler, bronco, and scout? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 02:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want an open air truck but the broncos are too expensive, the wranglers are too common, and there aren't any clean scouts around these parts. Is there any other type of open truck?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In every generation in the US that is alive right now a significant portion of the male population has gone to war and killed someone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 08:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do YOU hate the sbpartyscene guy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 03:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did he do to you? I know that he spreads the party school rep, but that doesn't really seem like enough for most people I've talked to to dislike him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is there a pink horse at the top of the reddit home screen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 17:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do we have open container laws? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 06:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do most gyms have assisted pull up machines? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 06:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The weight room in my high school has an assisted pull up machine. I have never seen one of those before in my life. Have I just not been looking hard enough or is it a rarity?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/Talks_about_cogSci calculates the odds of coming into contact with an unconvicted murderer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 21:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deltopia Faces Stricter Enforcement; noise ordinances and music festival regulations will be strictly enforced. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 05:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think I injured my lower back doing deadlifts improperly yesterday, what to do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 17:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So yesterday I was weightlifting and one of the guys I was lifting with wanted me to do deadlifts. The form he showed me felt off but I went with it, legs straight and at shoulder width back bent when picking up the weight. After a few reps I felt a twinge on the lower right side of my back, initially I didn't realize what it was because it wasn't excessively painful, but I soon stopped when I realized ehat was happening. Since then I've had sort of a dull soreness in that lower right area of my back. I can't really feel it when I'm standing or lying flat on my back. Yesterday it seemed to go away when I was taking a hot shower. I really don't want to deal with a doctor but I also really don't want to screw up my back permanently. I know for certain that I won't use anymore free weights or do back exercises until I've researched proper form.

**tl;dr** Was deadlifting with straight legs and bent back yesterday and felt slight twinge. Today I have a sort of dull pain on the right side of my lower back that goes away when standing or lying flat. What do I do?

**edit**

I did a sort of stretching exercise and if I lift my knee so thet it's at a 90 degree angle while my body is turned to the right of my waist then when I put it down I feel a popping in my back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stay safe out there </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 02:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is an FZ6 too big for a first bike? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 21:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My only riding experience is the MSF course. I was just offered a great deal on an FZ6 but I'm worried that it might be too much bike. I am a big guy, ~260 lbs so I have been looking for something bigger than a 250. My other options are an SV650 naked, and a ninja 500. I know the SV650 is tame for a 650 so I'm not as worried about grabbing too much throttle and launching myself to my death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can something smell bad to dogs in the same aay that things smell bad to us? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 08:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to submit a request for something to be added to Netflix instant? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 05:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want to watch Common Law which aired for one season during the summer of 2012. It's a USA show so I'm surprised that it's not on instant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does tap water in places like Southern California and Arizona taste so bad, whereas water in places like Oregon and Washington is seemingly tasteless or tastes good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 22:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do we use crop dusters, wouldn't some sort of sprinkler system be a safer and cheaper alternative? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 19:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So one of the colleges I'm looking at offers surfing as a PE class </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 17:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Southern California is just American Australia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 16:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EMSKR: A simple way of knowing which sunglasses and glasses frames to purchase based on your head shape. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 04:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/lightworld realizes he asked for advice on trimming his fig tree in the wrong subreddit, still gets advice on trimming his fig tree. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 03:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quality aviator style sunglasses for less than $100? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 02:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got two pairs of prescription ray ban sunglasses and now I need a non script pair for when I wear contacts, not looking to spend another $200. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do executioners sterilize the needle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 20:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Christie-ordered probe finds governor didn't know about Bridgegate: report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 21:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any conversion kits for cheap modernish bikes other than the Blue Collar Bobbers ninja kit and the RYCA kits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 06:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Southern California has the scariest roads I havr ever been on </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 22:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm visiting SoCal and it seems like every other driver is looking at their damn phone, nobody signals their lane changes, everybody is going a good 10-20 mph over the limit, and there is debris everywhere. Holy fucking Jesus this place is insane. I feel bad for you CA riders. I could not ride here.

/rant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Classic LAPD police motorcycles from the Reagan Museum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 21:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Santa Barbara day trip, what to do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 02:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're staying about an hour south of SB but I'm going to go check out SBCC this week. Our entire group is coming. What can two high school seniors and four middle aged parents do in SB for a day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I saw a seal at the beach today! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 03:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have any of you built or ridden a RYCA CS-1? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 20:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How's it ride? How hard is it to build?  Is it comfortable for longer rides? 


[For those that don't know what I'm talking about](http://www.rycamotors.com) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even if I live to be 100, I'll only have lived for about 36,500 days. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 18:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in the '90s, Fast n' Loud star and Gas Monkey Garage owner Richard Rawlings was shot while fighting off a car jacker that was trying to steal his '65 Mustang fastback. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 06:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened to my car? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 00:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I saw some scratches on my car today located below the driver's side headlight.

http://imgur.com/a/eN8rO#0

I don't know what did it. There have always been scratches there, but I'm not sure if they were that bad. I feel like if I was hit/sideswiped at some point,  or conversely,  scratched someone else unknowingly then I there would be scratches above those. I do tend to pull forward pretty far when I park so it could be damage from a bush but I'm not sure. Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What movies and books from the last 10 years will be considered classics in 50-100 years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 21:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nobody tells Arnold what he can and can't do! (from /r/cigars) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 03:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did/do seemingly helpless creatures like hamsters and goldfish ever manage to survive in the wild? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 03:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Also in honor of St. Paddy's day - The Black Donnellys - Four brothers living in a poor Irish neighborhood in NYC take on the Italian mob. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 05:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Sunglasses for the upcoming spring/summer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 03:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are aviators and wayfarers still cool? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dublin Airport is asking tourists not to say St Pattys Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 16:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts on using a storage unit as a garage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 00:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be moving soon for college. The campus is sketchy to say the least... There are at least two days out of the year that I know for a fact I won't be able to keep my bike on campus, and there's still a lot of vandalism and theft and shit year round. Have any of you used a storage unit as a garage? I want to at least be able to take the bike out on weekends. I don't see why there would be any problems, but before I try to figure out the logistics I'd like r/motorcycle's opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best driving roads around here to blow some steam? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 17:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not looking for anything difficult. Just looking for swooping curves and straights to really open the car up on. Preferably out in the country.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's not salad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 22:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Is polygamy/polyamory a sexual orientation or a lifestyle preference? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 22:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a Facebook friend "come out" as a polygamist today. He had recently been married but they got divorced. He is now in a relationship with a couple he met online.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why are combat sports legal, even the very dangerous ones, but a consensual fight in any other setting is illegal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-08 05:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Washington state has a mutual combat law that makes it legal for two parties to fight so long as the rules are decided ahead of time. The most famous use was when a real life superhero and a vandal had a consequence free fight in front of two cops. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-08 04:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the average American has gone from consuming 20 teaspoons of sugar per year to 150 pounds of sugar per year, or nearly a half a pound of sugar per day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-08 01:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the remake of Dallas worth watching? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 02:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to watch Dallas, the remake of the show about the oil family, and I made it about halfway through the first season before I gave up. My mistake may have been trying to binge it, but it felt like it was just dragging on and a bit overly dramatic. Should I give it another try? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Dallas worth watching? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 01:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to watch Dallas, the remake of the show about the oil family,  and I made it about halfway through the first season before I gave up. My mistake may have been trying to binge it, but it felt like it was just dragging on and a bit overly dramatic. Should I give it another try? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Friday Night Lights - The show is centered around a championship winning high school football team in small town Texas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 06:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dylan Sprouse had something to say about Jennette Mccurdy's leaked pictures. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 08:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How come computers can complete an action so much faster than us, but even super computers take several minutes to simulate one second of human brain activity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 08:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a residency for tuition purposes question. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 03:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'll be attending a CCC in fall with the goal of transferring to a UC and becoming a resident. My parents will be sending me the maximum amount of money possible without claiming me as a dependent so that I can pay off tuition and housing. Now, my question is, once I become a resident can they claim me as a dependent again without putting me in danger of losing my in state tuition or residency?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is loose skin from weight loss preventable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 02:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 18 and have about 100 lbs to lose, but the thought of having saggy skin for the rest of my life concerns me. I'm going to lose the weight regardless because that's a bigger issue, but as long as I'm at the very beginning stages of weight loss, are there any preventative measures I can take? I know I should take it slow, but I also want to lose as much as possible before college starts in august. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What arguments can you make for or against raising the minimum wage yo the requested $15/hr? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 22:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Arizona and Hawaii don't observe daylight saving time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 20:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can /r/trees settle this debate once and for all for my friend and me? Do cigarette filters filter out a noticeable amount of THC? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 07:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've been debating for about 15 minutes now. I say no, he says yes, and the internet seems undecided. Unfortunately we're not able to test our respective hypotheses at the moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your biggest problem with Reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 04:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Reddit is very pro Edward Snowden, at least on the surface, can anyone make a good argument against his actions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 00:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do Bars have such a high failure rate compared to other businesses? It can't be hard to find people that love to drink. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 05:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: The term "Rape Culture" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 02:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never really understood it because nobody is actively promoting rape or saying it's ok, and rarely do people defend rapists. But the term "rape culture" implies (to me) that most of society is actively promoting, committing,  and defending rape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a future SBCC student, when it comes to interacting with UC students, what will life be like for me when I'm living at Tropicana Gardens in IV? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 10:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wanted to go to a mid-top tier UC as a freshman, but alas it proved to be too hard to do as an out of state applicant. I have made the decision to attend SBCC and attempt to transfer to UCSB, USC, UCLA, or any other solid California school. In an attempt to squeeze the most enjoyment out of my few years of higher education I have also decided to stay in a private dorm (Tropicana Gardens). My concern is that I was going through some posts regarding SBCC on this sub, and it seems like SBCC students are discriminated against. Apparently they are even forced to wear a wrist band to get into Isla Vista (wtf? I didn't realize that IV is a gated community). Will being a CC student cause me much grief? I'm mainly going to SBCC so that I can transfer into a good school, but I'd be lying if I said that stuff like Deltopia didn't help me make my choice. I don't want to get kicked out of parties or hassled for being a CC student. So, what's the deal? Will I be able to live happily alongside you guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there anywhere that I can rent a scooter/vespa or a low displacement motorcycle while I'm visiting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 09:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm going to be visiting SB with my parents during spring break to check out Isla Vista, SBCC, and downtown SB. I'm looking for a place where I can rent a scooter or a small motorcycle so that I can kind of explore without my parents. The only place that comes up on google is Moto Loco, but their website doesn't seem to confirm that they rent any motorized two wheeled vehicles. Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just finished watching the documentary "Where Soldiers Come From" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 08:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is one of the best war documentaries that I have ever seen. It's as powerful as Restrepo. The premise is that a tight knit group of childhood friends enlist in the National Guard together. They are deployed to Afghanistan in 2008. The movie starts with them preparing for their deployment, but by far the most powerful part is that they interview the family members as well as the soldiers during their deployment. Finally, it follows their transition back into society and their struggle with PTSD. It'll make you want to cry, it'll make you want to laugh, and it'll make you angry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bones - An FBI agent teams up with a forensic anthropologist and her team to solve gruesome murders. Humor is often times used to alleviate the intensity. Bones stars Emily Deschanel and David Boreanaz. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 03:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where Soldiers Come From - A documentary following a tight knit group of friends, starting from when they receive their deployment orders, through their tour in Afghanistan, and ending with their return to the US. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 00:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Restrepo - Two cameramen follow a platoon to a remote outpost in the heart of the Korengal Valley. It features raw footage of combat, life as a soldier, and the people of Afghanistan while leaving the politics out of it. It's the first movie that has made me cry in a long time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 08:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spam Musubi recipe - $3 for ten spam musubi sandwiches or 30 cents each. They're easy, portable, and can be enjoyed both hot and cold. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 08:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Foxes -- Youth (Adventure Club Remix) [dubstep] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 07:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Texas technically has the ability to split into five states. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 07:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Guardian - As part of his punishment for a drug conviction, a high power corporate attorney must volunteer in the confusing, and often times heartbreaking, world of free legal aid in Pittsburgh. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 00:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rules of Engagement - it's kind of like HIMYM if Robin and Ted had never broken up. The quality is a bit lower and the jokes are a bit raunchier, but it's worth a try. It stars Patrick Warburton, Megyn Price, Oliver Hudson, Bianca Kajlich, and David Spade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 21:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Chicago Code- A seasoned detective and his new partner are tasked with tackling political corruption in Chicago. They are aided by an undercover that has worked his way into the Irish mob. It's a nice twist on the standard cop show formula and it is both well written and masterfully directed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 07:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's a company that I'm very interested in working for, but they haven't advertised that they are hiring. Would it be okay to send the owner an email with my resume attached? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 05:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So there's a really cool tour company located in Hawaii that I'm very interested in working at for a summer. A youtuber that I follow is friends with the owner and he is frequently featured in videos. I wouldn't work as a tour guide obviously, but if I sent him a resume with my qualifications and said that I'd be willing to do any job for near minimum wage, do you think I would get a response?

A bit about me, I'm in college and my work experience is limited. I'm studying business/marketing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Black Donnelly's- Four Irish brothers in NYC take on the Mafia. It's incredibly well written, although it can be slow at times. It stars Olivia Wilde, Tom Guiry, Jonathan Tucker, Bobby Lush, and Kirk Acevedo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 08:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Defenders - The bromance is strong with this one. Two Vegas defense attorneys take on cases involving strippers, gamblers, celebrities, and murderers. It's both hilarious and serious with a twist of Vegas and Sinatra. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 04:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know where to buy spam musubi? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 08:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was talking to a Hawaiian friend and he was complaining thaf nobody sells spam musubi here. Now I want to try it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just came across /r/RedditTherapy. It's a great idea, but unfortunately it failed miserably. How can we make it a reality? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 07:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts that won't go away and tricking myself, symptom of depression or anxiety? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 07:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm wondering if these are symptoms of depression and/or anxiety. [I posted a related question here yesterday](http://www.reddit.com/r/mentalhealth/comments/1y1mg7/can_depression_cause_you_to_blur_or_confuse/)

So about six months ago a thought popped into my head. I won't say what it is because it makes me uncomfortable. Basically the thought was, what if I'm a (x)? From there it started spiraling out of control.  I couldn't get the idea that I'm a (x) out of my head. At first it was no big deal, but eventually whenever I started planning for my future (college, after college, etc) the thought would pop into my head and I would tell myself that I couldn't do the things I want to do for fear that I'm a (x) and won't be able to control myself. That made me sad, but I pushed on. Around two months ago (when i was at the peak of my depression) I had a horrible intrusive thought related to the idea that I'm a (x). Basically in reality the course of events went one way, but the intrusive thought took them another way. However, in the past day or so I haven't been able to separate the two in my memory. Consciously I know that one is false and the other is true,  but something in me keeps trying to convince me that the intrusive thought is reality,  which it is not. It's really messing with my head. 

I decided to test this problem I have with keeping reality and my thoughts separate. Minor stuff was easy. If I told myself that on Monday I went out to lunch with John when in reality I went with James, could always pick out the lie. Same with very major stuff like when I tried to convince myself that I didn't get a traffic ticket two years ago. But there were some things that happened anywhere from two months to two years ago that I consciously know which one is the truth and which is the lie, but something in me says otherwise. 


**TL; DR** 

Consciously I can separate truth from reality,  but somethinv between my conscious and my subconscious is trying to convince me that something I imagined is reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did ADHD/ADD serve a purpose at one point in our history, perhaps during the hunter-gatherer times? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 01:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can depression cause you to blur or confuse memories with intrusive thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 07:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect I have depression. I plan on getting checked or tested or whatever, but something peculiar has been happening to me recently. I seem to be mixing a memory with an intrusive thought that happened at the same time (a month and a half ago) as the event I'm remembering. Now, I know which one happened and which one was the intrusive thought, but they're slowly becoming less separate and I fear that if this continues that I wont be able to distinguish them in 5, 10, 20 years from now. Now, the event in question happened during a two week span in which I was more depressed than I had ever felt in my life. Like I was seriously fucked up. I had a lump in my throat the whole time, intrusive thoughts were happening multiple times a day, I was nervous the entire time, I nearly had panic attacks. It was the first time I had ever thought to myself "Fuck... I need to get help". I was even crying when I was by myself which is very unusual for me. Now, my second question is, once I'm on meds, or my depression is gone, will it be easier to distinguish memories? One of the reasons I'm sure that I have depression is that I'm only 18, yet all of my memories have been blurring together. Like on thursday I couldn't remember whether several events had happened on monday, tuesday, or wednesday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can depression cause you to blur or confuse memories with intrusive thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 07:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect I have depression. I plan on getting checked or tested or whatever, but something peculiar has been happening to me recently. I seem to be mixing a memory with an intrusive thought that happened at the same time (a month and a half ago) as the event I'm remembering. Now, I know which one happened and which one was the intrusive thought, but they're slowly becoming less separate and I fear that if this continues that I wont be able to distinguish them in 5, 10, 20 years from now. Now, the event in question happened during a two week span in which I was more depressed than I had ever felt in my life. Like I was seriously fucked up. I had a lump in my throat the whole time, intrusive thoughts were happening multiple times a day, I was nervous the entire time, I nearly had panic attacks. It was the first time I had ever thought to myself "Fuck... I need to get help". I was even crying when I was by myself which is very unusual for me. Now, my second question is, once I'm on meds, or my depression is gone, will it be easier to distinguish memories? One of the reasons I'm sure that I have depression is that I'm only 18, yet all of my memories have been blurring together. Like on thursday I couldn't remember whether several events had happened on monday, tuesday, or wednesday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors in non-traditional relationships (same sex, polyamory, etc) what is the strangest/funniest/worst reaction a stranger has had when you were out in public? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 04:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He went to Walmart 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 22:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the Hawaiian island of Niihau has a population of 130, comprised of native Hawaiians. It is closed off to non-Hawaiians with the exception of a few tours and hunting safaris. On the island they speak Hawaiian and at the school they are taught to survive off of the island's resources. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 21:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would I go about becoming a Catholic if I've only set foot in a church once in my life, and how long would it take? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 07:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never been baptized or anything like that either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do some people choose not to get vaccinated and not have their children vaccinated? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 05:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the official stance of the Catholic Church is that they support the theory of evolution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 04:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that there is an island town in Michigan that has banned motor vehicles except for snowmobiles and emergency vehicles. In the summer it's a tourist attraction, but in the winter it has a population of 500 and is unreachable without a plane until the ice bridge forms. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 04:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California must allow law-abiding citizens to carry concealed firearms in public, a federal appeals court ruled Thursday, striking down the core of the state's permit system for handguns. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 06:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The trailer for Paul Walker's new movie, Brick Mansion, is out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 23:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your best absinthe story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 23:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell me about the time you went dancing with the green fairy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EMSK: How to recover from a skid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 06:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shia LaBeouf sports paper bag over his head on Berlin red carpet, walks out of Nymphomaniac press conference </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 21:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a cheaper dual sport to get me started? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 20:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never owned a motorcycle but I've been wanting one for a while. Accidental broadcast has convinced me that owning a DS would be the bee's knees. I've got no more than 2750 to spend. Is there anything that's smaller than 500cc, reliable, and fun in that price range? I'm looking to do ~80% commuting and 20% trail, sand, forest type exploring. 

There's a '99 WR400F on Craigslist in my price range if you think that's worth getting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A chainsaw and weed wacker work after being buried in the Hawaiian jungle for a year and a half. (Skip to end if you just want to see the power tools, watch whole video for funny context and commentary) [semi-NSFW for language] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 20:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have experience with Blue Collar Bobbers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 07:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their [Ninja Cafe Racer Kit](http://bluecollarbobbers.com/kawasaki-ninja-250-cafe-racer-aka-gpx-250r) intrigues me. How is the quality and ease of installation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a heads up if you haven't gone out lately, there is about 1/5" layer if crusty ice on top of the snow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 06:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia arrests 4 gay rights activists on opening day of Winter Olympics opening ceremony </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 06:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [50/50] A pile of dead puppies (NSFL/NSFW) | Puppies (only bad if you hate cute things) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 05:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We might be looking at a foot of snow with a half inch of freezing rain on top by the end of the storm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 01:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite curse word variation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 05:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parents of reddit, how did you explain to your children why "Santa" gave different presents to children of different social classes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 04:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three Savannah cats, the largest domestic breed in the world, playing fetch. They are a cross between a wild Serval and a domestic house cat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 02:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The Savannah is the largest domestic cat breed. It resembles a small leopard and behaves like a dog. They can grow up to 40 lbs, have an eight foot vertical jump, and can be trained to walk on a leash and play fetch. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 02:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Walker's Skyline GTR from the Fast and Furious goes on sale after his death. Proceeds to go to his charity, Reach Out World Wide. It's estimated to bring about 830k Euros. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 04:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frank Sinatra and Dean Martin looking classy as can be at the London Airport </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 01:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has the connectivity of the internet made it impossible for first world countries to go to war with each other ever again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 07:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the past if two countries were going to war with each other it was very easy for the respective Gov'ts to spread propaganda that demonizes the other country and it's citizens. Today I communicate with Europeans, Asians, and South Americans on reddit every day. I predict that most if not all of the wars involving first world countries for the rest of civilization as we know it will be fought against insurgents and disconnected third world countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]What's the scariest thing that has ever happened to you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 06:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best morning radio show in Eugene? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 05:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually listen to the KNRQ morning show on 103.7 but lately I've been wanting to mix it up.  I don't really care about the music,  at least in the morning, I mainly listen for the banter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How come I can eat a burger from a fast food restaurant and feel hungry 30 minutes later, but if I make or get the same burger from a real restaurant I'll feel full for several hours. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 22:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just showed my mom the Hurt Report, she feels a lot better about me getting a motorcycle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 23:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She still doesn't think it's a good idea, but she agrees that squids inflate the crash data. [The findings can be found here](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_findings_in_the_Hurt_Report)

Some interesting points:

23) Motorcycle riders with previous recent traffic citations and accidents are overrepresented in the accident data.

24) The motorcycle riders involved in accidents are essentially without training; 92% were self-taught or learned from family or friends. Motorcycle rider training experience reduces accident involvement and is related to reduced injuries in the event of accidents.

27) Almost half of the fatal accidents show alcohol involvement.

35) Motorcycle riders in these accidents were significantly without motorcycle license, without any license, or with license revoked.

43) Seventy-three percent of the accident-involved motorcycle riders used no eye protection.

44) Approximately 50% of the motorcycle riders in traffic were using safety helmets but only 40% of the accident-involved motorcycle riders were wearing helmets at the time of the accident.

55) Less than 10% of the motorcycle riders involved in these accidents had insurance of any kind to provide medical care or replace property. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You guys are right. This sub definitely needs more activity. [Very NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 22:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well he is supposed to come back this year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 05:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/RealNikkiSixx (Nikki Sixx from Motley Crue) gives Justin Bieber some advice on letting his fans grow with him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 23:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Standing up on a moving motorcycle in a bikini </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 07:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL you can make google translate beat box by writing "pv zk pv pv zk pv zk kz zk pv pv pv zk pv zk zk pzk pzk pvzkpkzvpvzk kkkkkk bsch" in the text box </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 04:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Zimmerman agrees to celebrity boxing match for charity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 22:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the creepiest thing that you've ever seen at night? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 05:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is one thing that should have never been invented? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 06:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started a circlejerk. Damn you, Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most hilariously stereotypical stoner does multiple dabs. Can't count to three. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 06:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, I need to make $1500-2000 in a month's time. How do I do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 04:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got school, so I can't get a job. I plan on selling stuff on ebay, but how else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gnarly high side motorcycle crash. Rider gets airborne. (X-post /r/motorcycles) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 01:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could banish one popular internet thing to oblivion what would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 08:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most immoral thing you would be willing to do for $10,000? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 05:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apparently there's a Batman motorcycle suit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 01:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Add this to the list of pro's for moving to Hawaii. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 01:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Mac and Dee aren't the only It's Always Sunny characters married in real life. Charlie is married to the actress that plays the waitress and Glenn (Dennis) is married to the girl from the DENNIS system episode. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 01:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is superdrugsaver a good source? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 01:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.superdrugsaver.com/

They've got [provigil generic](http://www.superdrugsaver.com/generic-medicine/451/Provigil.html) and [nuvigil generic](http://www.superdrugsaver.com/generic-medicine/563/Nuvigil.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trey Radel resigns from Congress after cocaine scandal: 'Professionally I cannot fully and effectively serve' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 17:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AMA Request] The former Wolf of Wall Street, Jordan Belfort. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 17:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **My 5 Questions:**

1. By making this movie you have become more (in)famous than ever before. 20/20 hindsight,  do you regret making it?

2. Did all of the drugs you took leave any lasting damage?

3. Do you think that the sentence you got was fair considering how many people you swindled?

4. What is your greatest regret?

5. How accurate was the scene where you were on qualuudes and trying to save Jonah Hill's character? 

**Public Contact Information:** 

http://jordanbelfort.com/

http://jordanbelfort.com/contact_us/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the term "mass shooting" used too much? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 08:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The term "mass shooting" has become synonymous with aimless killing, usually involving schools, or someone firing into a crowd. But I've noticed that recently many shootings that would have been reported on as gang violence five years ago are being called mass shootings. The same goes for murders perpetrated in a public place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google acquires artificial intelligence company DeepMind </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 07:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We talked about Dave Asprey, lets talk about Victor Pride. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 05:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Victor Pride from [Bold and Determined](http://boldanddetermined.com/) does a great job of introducing people to nootropics, or life hacks as he calls them. He does an especially good job of [introducing people to Modafinil](http://boldanddetermined.com/2012/07/12/become-mighty-modafinil/). Here's the issue, he makes it seem like using nootropics, especially modafinil, will turn you into a Greek God capable of taking on armies and solving the riddles of the universe. He makes it seem like if you pop some modafinil today, then tomorrow you'll wake up as a billionaire. The issue is that when Victor Pride tells some kid that using Modafinil is going to be like using NZT-48, and it isn't, that kid is either going to tell everyone and their mother that nootropics are modern day snake oil, or he's going to try something stronger, like a high dose of adderall. I think that while he introduces people to nootropics, he is ultimately going to cause harm to the nootropics community. You've heard *my* opinion on the matter, but I'm genuinely curious to know what you think. I'm also curious to know if you think newcomers should be warned about him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found a Buell Blast for $2,335 on cycle trader, worth it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 05:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been saving up for a while now to get my first bike. I really want a WR250R, but they are so expensive used that I think I might just get another bike and trade it in when I get more funds. I found this Buell Blast:

http://www.cycletrader.com/listing/2009-Buell-Blast-110572701

I like the looks of the bike and I've come to the realization that I won't have any use for a D/S until I move to California in nine months, so maybe a street bike is just what I need. My concerns with the Buell is that they've been discontinued so parts will become scarcer and scarcer, I'm not sure how easy it is to get them serviced, and I'm not sure if it's as good a first bike as say a Ninja 300 or 500 or a CBR250R. I'd like your thoughts on the matter though. Buy this and ride it while I save up for a WR250R or just wait until I can afford the bike I want? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> *SPOILERS* If you're not caught up with the latest episode - The mother in HIMYM is dead when future Ted is telling the story. (old theory, with more supporting evidence) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 05:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My evidence:

- The Mother has never been referred to in present tense by the narrator

- Whenever future Ted talks about her he sounds kind of sad. Definitely the whimsical, romantic Ted we've come to know and love.

- The last episode is titled "Last Forever"

- At the end of the last episode Ted makes a comment to the mother. "Nothing good happens after 2 AM (future Ted then interjects to say to his son, "except for you, luke)" before they set off to the hospital. After 2 AM.

- The producers decided on the ending early on. No matter how much they changed the plot around it wouldn't mess with an ending that results in her death.

- at the end of the "Time Travelers" episode Ted is seen pleading for more time with the mother. He wants 45 more days.

- The mother never narrates.

- She is never in any flash forward beyond 10 years or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A (small) victory for men's rights/gender equality! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 23:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all! I'm new to this sub, but we recently had a men's rights victory at my school that I felt like sharing. My school has a daycare center that students are allowed to volunteer at. They receive credit for volunteering and if they do it for more than two semesters they become a paid employee. In the years prior to this school year, male student volunteers were not allowed to change diapers or escort the kids to the bathroom, even the boys. One of the male students saw the inequality in this and petitioned the parents of the daycare children to allow male students to change diapers and escort kids to the bathroom. He succeeded! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jet -- Cold Hard Bitch [Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 20:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nick Offerman before he got Ron Swansonized. Holy shit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 09:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robots May Replace One-Fourth Of U.S. Combat Soldiers By 2030 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 20:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is what I get for growing up in the most liberal place in America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 22:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fighter jet fuel tanks dumped over Vietnam during the Vietnam war have been repurposed and are now used as canoes (x-post /r/MilitaryPorn) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 06:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why doesn't the US have national traffic laws rather than states setting them individually? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 05:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially when it comes to things you wouldn't think to look up when driving in another state. Like lane splitting in CA or no right on red in NY. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it legal to turn left on red from the right lame of a one way street to the right lane of a one way street? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 01:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did it today but I'm starting to think it was illegal. Here's a drawing I made if the turn: 

http://imgur.com/XEaDwNf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shia LaBeouf Says Plagiarism Was Performance Art </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 06:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could my laptop play the Dayz Standalone game? Came here because I don't know anything about PCs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 23:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mainly use my PC for netflix, school, and minecraft. It runs minecraft just fine. It's a Sony Vaio S that I bought new like 10 months ago. The specs I can find:

RAM: 12.0 GB w/ 11.9 GB usable 

64 bit operating system, x64 based processor

windows 8

Intel Core i7 processor

and I know it has some sort of nvidia graphics card



Edit:

On the "Windows Experience Index" the processor score is 7.7, RAM is 7.7, graphics is 5.9, gaming graphics is 6.5, and primary hard disk is 5.9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Motorcyclist rescues coffee cup from rear bumper of SUV - LiveLeak.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 19:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A drive through downtown Pyongyang, NK. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 18:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where and when do you think the next major US conflict will be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 09:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Marine sitting on one of the KLR 650's used by the Recon Marines. Probably during early Iraq or Afghanistan (x-post r/motorcycles) [923x606] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 08:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> you have a month to legally make $2000 from scratch without getting a job, how do you do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 01:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the deal with High Point University in NC? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 22:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AMA Request] A former Scientologist who has spent time at one of the Scientologist compounds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 03:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **My 5 Questions:**

1. Why did you defect?

2. It's common for defectors to be fined, did this happen to you?

3. What was life like at Gold Base (or whatever compound you were at, although I think I've only heard of one other)?

4. Did it feel like you were being imprisoned?

5. What was "The Hole" like?

**Public Contact Information:** If Applicable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How is the Church of Scientology legally allowed to have a heavily guarded base and prison? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 04:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the Church of Scientology has a paramilitary branch called Sea Org. It's modeled after the Navy and even has a special SEAL unit. It's common for Sea Org members to work 100 hr weeks for less than $50. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 22:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Why is it that so many celebrities are Scientologists? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 08:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the Church of Scientology has a private prison called "The Hole". Prisoner's are tortured, interrogated, subjected to strange punishments like licking the bathroom floor, and are forced to sleep side by side on the ground. Often times within inches of each other with no room to move. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 07:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which drug(s) will you never try? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 04:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Nolan Gould, the actor that plays "Luke" on Modern Family, graduated high school when he was 13 and has an IQ of 150. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 05:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that James Franco has an undergraduate degree from UCLA, and simultaneously attended graduate school at Columbia, NYU, and Brooklyn College. He is now a PhD student at Yale. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 05:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that when Cocaine and Alcohol are used at the same time they mix in the liver and form Cocaethylene. It increases the risk of heart attack, instant death, and propensity for violence, and is thought to increase addictiveness and long term damage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 05:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that some streets in NYC have heated sidewalks to melt snow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 03:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AMA Request] Someone who has used the Oculus Rift "Crystal Cove" prototype. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-12 23:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **My 5 Questions:**

1. Did it truly feel like you were in another reality?

2. How did the experience compare to playing a game on Xbox or Playstation?

3. Did you ever forget that you were playing a game? 

4. Would you want to play a FPS on it?

5. If you could choose one existing game to play on it what would it be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
