<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9731</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 13:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He cringes even more when he vapes it and I tell him that he's got my PENIS Juice in his mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 12:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't remember his name on here, but if you see this, thank you for the naming idea! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I made a label for my Juices.. My work colleague was not amused. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 12:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 06:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, if that's the risk you have to take, so be it.

The US does it all the time, they apologise for it, and the world forgets.

We live in a shit world, and that's the reality of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 15:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you.. As someone who never has and never will bookface, you're a champ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 15:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankfully the sound also failed on the video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 14:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peggy!, the boy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 14:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just googled up Zoe Quinn.. 

It would need to be a cold day in hell and about 40 bottles of JD before I would even consider seeing her naked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 04:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're running a single coil and not dual?

I'm waiting for my first dripper to arrive and not sure if I should hit a dual coil or single coil setup.

I did a dual .8 coil setup in my Kayfun and it was horrible, but I'm guessing it will be different in a dripper.

I was planning a single 1.1 coil as I prefer the cooler Vape </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 03:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sold mine by word of mouth to a fellow vaper that was on an evod..

The SVD is a great unit, but it's too big and ugly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 03:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your setup mate?

Mod, tank, coils etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 18:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're being down voted for expressing your own personal opinion.. 

Post a cat video, that's what this place (Reddit) thrives off.

I'm with you, fuck ISIS and nuke the shit out of all of them.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 02:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fat Bastard from Austin Powers - 'I'm sad cause I eat, and I eat cause I'm sad, its a vicious cycle' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 18:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That cop at the end had the same attitude, he was walking up like a curious bystander with his hands behind his back..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 17:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah Nah, the professor Finks on here ruined that for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 14:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankfully I'm using Reddit on the mobile, each link comes up with the address instead of launching. 

Its 11pm here and really didn't feel like making any of them purple if they were live leak vids :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 14:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All was awesome in your post, until the last line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 14:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm.. Poor bastard suffered the whole way through, there goes my theory and hoping he had some sort of luck in the situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 14:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sex, wife and condom.. One of the three don't fit in the equation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 14:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be terrifying but probably not painful?, I need someone sciencey to back me up, but he would've knocked himself out with the lack of oxygen that he used up and the carbon dioxide that he was exhaling..

I reckon drowning would have to be the most terrifying way to die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 08:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not specifically for heating in the use you are after.

Where are you based? As you can buy the stuff for a dollar a meter at most vape places 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 08:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hats, t-shirts and kids parents telling stories about their kids saying Yolo and when they did it. I blame you America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 08:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, my background is eastern European, I can relate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 08:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Australia is late to catch on to American fads.. Its here and its painful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 07:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In your awesomeness, can you please kill off yolo as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 05:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your post reminds me of that old meme where there is a smoking hot girl in the pic, sub titled 'she's someone else's headache' - so very true. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 05:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gave you an upvote, a sympathy one.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 05:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.. Only thing I change is the cotton when I'm switching flavours or if its starting to taste a little burnt. 

A couple hits of the coil dry burns all the crap off it ready for a re-wicking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 05:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's their stance on abortion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 05:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read all of these articles and it still doesn't change the facts of our society and world we live in.

Breathing in vapour will always be safer than inhaling burning matter and smoke, but the amount of money governments will lose on tobacco tax won't help us get vaping mainstream.

All smokers have basically covered themselves and 2 others for medical bills when it comes to the amount of tax being paid per packet smoked.

The only way I see vaping getting anywhere is when it is taxed severely and vape companies start donating ludicrous amounts of money to government parties.

The tobacco industry has been a controlling asshole for many years, and will continue to be.

tl;dr - government will lose too much money if vaping takes over, tobacco industries will always stranglehold us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 00:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you just remove the legs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 00:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is on its way as we speak :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 14:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did, I never said I realised it was only for AMA's did I? 

Now fuck off back to your hole you crawled out of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 11:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Installed  opened  love the design, hate that its only AMA  uninstalled </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 10:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate appreciate it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 05:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember watching the behind the scenes of that episode, the cast and crew actually didn't know what her name was going to be until the very end of the shoot.. 

One of the crowd members guessed it as Delores, and funny enough they only thought of the name a few moments before  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 05:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Nemesis clone which is now all battered and bruised.. Is the stingray clone any good? 

I have a Chi You, but its too chunky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 15:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read your comment in Samuel L Jacksons voice from Pulp Fiction.. When he was discussing his knowledge of giving a foot massage.. "I'm the foot fucking master" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 15:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check the post history.. The same tone of comments are littered all across Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 13:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The troll seems legit..

From the post history, I can make out that she's a fat black woman that was more than likely backhanded a few times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 01:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly my story, same as Seinfeld as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 01:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the one!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 21:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you flying from?

I was up there over the weekend and I don't know what it is with that place, my tank kept on leaking like a bitch of a thing! Must be the humidity or warmth etc.

Drove me insane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 21:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dale, why are you removing the bug from the Bugabago?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 20:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're doing gods work there son, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 20:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a clip of the wedding where they were shaking hands in front of the cake..

Hank is so square and PG that it just makes his character funnier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 13:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one actually made me laugh out loud. Well done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 00:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, but on Reddit the majority come across just like he did </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 13:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Settle down there Neck beard.

r/atheism wants you back over there.

Fucking atheists are worse than hardcore religious types. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 10:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol you know some of the words I said? :)

Mate, I'm happy to help you out with whatever you need to get started, PM me any questions you may have.. I started off on the evod and every single step between till I found my mech mod and tank that I love.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 10:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally just drove back from Qld, I spent the whole weekend Vaping, and not a word said by anyone.

The only thing I heard was someone whispering 'look at his ecig thing.. Its a bit big' - had my nemesis running an 18650 and a Kayfun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 10:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad was using YouTube to Google search up until 6 months ago.. No matter how much explaining I do, it will all just be jargon.

He knows the 'Blue E' is how he gets to Google.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 23:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I worry about on a daily basis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 23:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might, but it works a lot cleaner and smoother than IE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 14:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I did that with Chrome. 

Its cut the 'what's wrong with the computer?' Phone calls by over 80% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 14:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Count me in as a PM target as well, happy to chat and with some experience behind me (personal) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 13:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flick me a PM mate, I'm now 30, all was going well in life for me until s lot of crap came my way and sent me in a spiral. There is light on the other end and I'd be happy to chat with you whenever you feel. Anytime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 15:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was home for a week with a bad flu, did 1-13 in a row! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 01:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is more to every story than what the media portrays to you.

There is always a LOT more.

In the case of Aborigines, unfortunately, the majority ruin it for the minority, and not the other way around.

There are a lot that genuinely try hard, are successful, and lead a great life.. Then there are the ones that take everything for granted, get given everything on a silver platter, get free housing, free schooling, free medical, free or heavily subsidised EVERYTHING, and still manage to ruin it and disrespect it.

I'm not racist towards any race in particular, I'm equally racist towards everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 22:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh really?.. 

Don't worry about WA, go for a walk through redfern and then tell me how many 'Aboriginals' even deserve to see a doctor (paid for with my tax dollars)

This is a bait thread.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 14:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because, too-tsunami must not use the phone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 12:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will this work at officeworks in Australia? :(

We rebadged your store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 11:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The commercials here in Aus always state 'if you're a non smoker, the average price will be...' Technically I'm not a smoker.. Considering its not smoke I'm inhaling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 11:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> www.nicvape.com - buy the nicotine, then support your local vape shops and buy juice here.. It tastes awesome and you'll get it straight away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 09:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ironic part of it is, this table doesn't exist in Aus..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 09:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fedora, Trilby, same-same.

Still tacky as hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 07:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well... I guess you are!

Where's your falcon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 04:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shi SHAAAAAH!, Squirrel Tactics! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 03:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are just backing up the internet in case it breaks one day.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 03:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No!, this is why his wife left him, and why he's fat, and Bald. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 02:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OBJECTURE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 22:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am Dale, shut up Bill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 04:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, but I'm a stickler for finishes, and they way you have that installed looks absolutely horrible.

You could've at least used clear tape and not that bright blue painting masking tape.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 02:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 12:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing 3ml a day at the moment... In a Kayfun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 09:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that was Dennis Leary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 09:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the life of me, I've never heard of someone polishing off a 15ml bottle of juice in a day!

That used to last me 2 weeks in my Evod! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 15:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only company that hasn't fucked me around yet is nicvape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 15:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with the button?

All I did was the magnet upgrade and it didn't even need that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 05:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most reliable for me is my Nemesis clone and the Kayfun clone. 

There isn't anything to really malfunction here.

Most reliable VV has been my SVD with a protank 2, and least reliable is my Sigelei Zmax v5. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 23:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 23:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's horrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 13:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can vouch, watched a few docos on those guys.. Seriously evil bunch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 13:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They MS13 for short? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 22:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohh nooo.. The card says Moops! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 14:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 05:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This video doesn't show a crazy girlfriend, it's just a video of a soft-cock that will always be treated like one if he keeps this up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 17:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never really knew remixes like this existed, some of the other tracks are even better  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 11:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they're a bunch of fucks that were raised in a shitty family and were starved for attention.

Now that they're grown up, they'll do anything to get that attention, even if it means making others suffer.

I hold a special place for people like this piece of shit, and it's called 'I hope he gets hit by a car driven by that boys parents'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 09:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No lie, everyone has their own beholder. 

You may not be attractive to one person but you may be very attractive to another. 

So, I_have_so_many_names - you're a beautiful person too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 09:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't stress OP, I think you're pretty / handsome in your own little way. 

Everyone is.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 09:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone have a list of their own personal Dale Gribble episodes they recommend?

Shi Shaaaa! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 08:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Amiga 500 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 16:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He might've been checking if the grass really was greener on the other side? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 16:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I need now is a portable Amiga 500 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 22:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hucci - Cashmere.

The best part of the track is in the video.. The rest of it is pretty ordinary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 22:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey bud, you've become my favourite reviewer. Keep up the good work and humour!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 22:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or that being too clever can make you look like an asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 15:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've so far seen a guy jam an elephant sized dildo up his ass, a hand blown off, a hole in someone's face, all whilst I've been in this sub.. 

This has been the most mentally disturbing one of all, it had me physically cringing as well.

Those kids will be mentally scarred for life  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 15:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is some interesting info and thank you.

I've seen the hardware get better and better, and with the new software and control it will bring, hopefully the 2 can  match.

The OS is where it needs to be from a look and feel perspective, its buttery smooth, its fast, and now can work on minimal hardware specs. Its about time they sort out the camera. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 14:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 14:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really though? Isn't it just another interface lift? I haven't really seen much posted about camera improvements on the N5, hoping someone running L can verify the difference for me, if any.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
