<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5457</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-04 15:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i know it's sad.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 21:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree.  Enters 8 non-major events and wins 5.  Competitive in Masters and British but still  gets no credit.  He will get number 15 but then it will be what about number 16. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 20:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the link directly from PornHub
http://public.tableausoftware.com/shared/HR9SZ66TW?:display_count=yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 01:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had a back spasm. It's unbelievably painful.  You just fall to the ground and hope it ends soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-25 02:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately I do not.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 18:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have that same putter. Love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 03:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All heroes die after Trinity event. We all knew it but why do they need to promo the ending? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 20:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> agreed.  He's exactly right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 04:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations. I've done it a couple times  and I might as well have beaten Tiger Woods. I felt so proud.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 03:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny and accurate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 15:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 16:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She reminds me of Jem from the 1980s
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jem_(TV_series) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 21:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologize.  I actually looked to see if it was posted didn't see it. I will delete it. Thanks for heads up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 20:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apologize if I pushed the rules.  Just letting everyone know it released today and that unlike previous game it does have in-app purchases PopCap is calling "micro-transactions."  Thanks for letting me know.  Have a good rest of the day.  PS.  I love the game and so do my children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 19:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It comes out today and it has numerous in app purchase opportunities unlike the original game.  I can editorialize about anything I choose whether you agree or not.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 16:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.ign.com/wikis/plants-vs-zombies-2/Microtransactions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 22:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found it entertaining  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 20:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read Justice League, Phantom Stranger, Justice League Dark and Pandora book.  Since the Trinity War started, the two main books are Justice League and Justice League Dark.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 21:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% agree.   wins, two top 10 finishes in majors.  year isn't even over yet but Tiger's lost it.  Imbeciles.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 13:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cartman's going to be pissed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 14:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amen!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 14:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had that book as a kid.  Bet my it's still at my parents house.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 00:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 00:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's amazing to look at the amount money that golf generates today compared to 59 years ago.  Jack to only make that amount of money is insane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 23:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome. They look tough! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 16:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's damn funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 15:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chris Berman and golf don't mix.  actually, Chris Berman and anything don't mix </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 15:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are fantastic.  Thank you!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 16:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a DC guy so don't know much other than the original movie.  Agree this Loki better than the original (sorry couldn't resist) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 21:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 7 year old sons favorite movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 20:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i do as well.  Apparently, winning 5 tournaments thus far in 2013 is not enough.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 15:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> agree with you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-04 21:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was by far the best Flash Point series </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-04 16:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Underwhelming but fitting is a perfect description.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-04 04:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got 3 boys 7,9   12. They all play and love it. Best dad bonding on experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-03 18:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who shouldn't play the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-03 18:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's nasty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-03 18:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How'd you hit it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-03 17:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My apologies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-03 15:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're as bad if not worse than the NCAA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-03 15:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Takes a set of balls to do that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-03 15:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a deal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 14:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And write bad movies. Who would have thought? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 14:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 20:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mask part 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-27 15:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New 52 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-25 04:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scariest thing I've ever seen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-17 21:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i will take a lifetime supply please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-22 20:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-19 21:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i want one.  i want one .  i want one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-10 02:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OR THE POST CAN PROVIDE THOSE THAT WOULD HAVE NOT OTHERWISE KNOWN THAT IGN WAS COUNTING DOWN THE TOP 25 WII GAMES OF 2010 THE OPPORTUNITY TO NOW FOLLOW THE COUNTDOWN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-09 21:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry, I was under the assumption it was all 25 games.  my fault.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-08 23:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> read slow and read carefully.  it's a wild ride that i am still not sure if I liked or disliked.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-06 12:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad so very sad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-06 04:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go fuck yourself you lazy piece of shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-29 16:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the whole run of ex machina.  social and political commentary is well done regardless of your political or social persuasion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-28 22:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tiger Woods would be proud! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-28 20:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> beautiful!!!  Lucky Kids! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-28 16:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the official r/comicbooks is a good list to start but I would also recommend Judd Winick's "Barry Ween," Bill Willingham's "Fables," Green Lantern saga by Geoff Johns starting with "Green Lantern Re-Birth," Brian K. Vaughn's "Ex-Machina," Grant Morrison's "All Star Superman," Brad Metzler's "Identity Crisis."

I could do this all day so let me know if you need more suggestions. Y-the Last Man by Brian K Vaughn is a great comic book to begin with because it is captivating from page one.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-26 16:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fantastic find </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-25 20:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The interview (or portions of it) have been all over various news outlets.  I am not making the assumption about Batman and Superman being together in a movie. I'm just providing a portion of the interview that everyone seems to be focusing on, "We talked about it."  Read the full interview. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-24 17:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait for this to be released.  It's been too long </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-22 23:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> agreed.  Winick's run at DC has been less than stellar but Barry Ween is his Starman.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-22 19:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-21 15:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry, didn't see it but I guess more publicity for this brave little boy the better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-21 01:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similar but yet different.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-20 22:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> who doesn't like big boobs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-20 22:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Locke   Key is a great suggestions.  Also Image Comics' Chew and Morning Glories are very good and relatively new so easy to jump in to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-20 22:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can tell you attended a top notch community college using the verbiage "Dude" and "I dunno". I guess English is not a prerequisite for obtaining a journalism "degree" at the University of Phoenix or other online school you may have attended in your esteemed collegiate career. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-20 21:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shocking you would use your real name since I have read some of them.  The one maybe two two original articles that you have written during your esteemed journalistic career.  The rest I read on my blog three days prior to you posting them on Geeks of Doom.  I guess it takes a while to duplicate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-20 21:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the official r/comicbooks is a good list to start but I would also recommend Judd Winick's "Barry Ween,"  Bill Willingham's "Fables," Green Lantern saga by Geoff Johns starting with "Green Lantern Re-Birth," Brian K. Vaughn's "Ex-Machina," Grant Morrison's "All Star Superman," Brad Metzler's "Identity Crisis." 

I could do this all day so let me know if you need more suggestions.  Y-the Last Man by Brian K Vaughn is a great comic book to begin with because it is captivating from page one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-20 20:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just proved my point, "Dragon*Con states in it's official policy that if you attend the convention you will be photographed and wave any legal right to ban such photography."  

How many other people took a picture of Tron girl?  How do you prove that was your photo?  I assume other dragon-con attendees had cameras and took pictures as well.  Perhaps, you were the only attendee allowed to carry a camera?  Maybe you were the official photographer of dragon-con?  

By the way, hard hitting journalism Woodward:  http://geeksofdoom.com/author/techgonzo/.  looks like zero original content to me.  just posting other stories on Geeks of Doom.  

Although, your hard-hitting, investigative stories featured in the Nashville Scene are surely Pulitzer worthy.  

As Judge Smails in CADDYSHACK said, "Well, the world needs ditch diggers, too" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-20 18:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's nice to have an objective moderator.  Who knows what would happen if a reddit moderator was subjective in it decisions?  I guess different rules apply for gfest than every other redditor in this specific genre.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-20 17:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still haven't addresses the legalities of the photo?  You keep ignoring that aspect for some reason.  I guess it's subjective when it comes to journalistic legalities.  It's easy to be the tough guy from a blog but like any cyber-bully as soon as you get in over your head and demonstrate to the world your ignorance you run and hide.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-20 17:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First you proved my point.  We are not the same person because I do not know what post you speak of.  

Still didn't address the legality issues.  They teach you that in journalism school?  

Fortunately, Law school, 10 years working for the speaker of the House and President of the Senate and now a decade of professional lobbying taught me how to play by the legal rules.

Also, congrats on your journalism career.  Seems to be going well for you.  Everyone hopes to graduate from journalism school and have a sexy Tron photo as their claim to fame.  hard hitting shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-20 17:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do attempt to post original content with each post and I do not just post from gfest if you like at my profile.  I give my personal take on that image, story, etc.  I notice that 'tchd' has numerous posts in other reddits that are nothing more than picture without comment.  If i just upload an image (via imgur) like him and then post it (similar to 75 percent of the folks on reddit), am I abiding by the rules?  Will I not be singled out?  Will a thread be blocked that personally attacks me without merit or fact?  Seems to me 'tchd' is cyber-bullying for his own gain.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-20 17:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apologize for my friend not giving you proper credit for your Power Girl photo. 

By the way the photo has been all over the web without your name on it. 

How do I even know you took the photo?  Are you the only one that took the photo of this woman in a Power Girl outfit?  Are there 35 photos of the same woman by different photographers? Do you have a signed contract or waiver of liability from this woman that specifically spells out the licensing of the photo?  Does this woman know that you profited off her photo?  Did she give you written permission to utilize her photo for any type of media?  These are the questions that should be asked, prior to claiming ownership of a photograph taken outside of a closed, credible shoot.  

I feel sorry for you.  I've never seen someone so obsessed with something so trivial.  Unfortunately, It underscores your age and most likely professional capabilities.  Thus, why you are clamoring for attention over a photo of a woman in a Power Girl outfit. It's really quite sad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-20 16:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nightwingblows and I are not the same person.  I have been reading comic books for nearly 40 years and love every aspect of the comic culture.  I Don't believe (or nightwingblows) spam we just put up content we feel others will enjoy.

 I am married with four children and have a career.  I do the blog for fun, nothing more. I apologize if anyone has been offended by the blog or it's content.  It's a hobby for an old man (compared to most folks on here) that very much enjoys comics and comic related material. 

 It's funny because as you get older and become a parent you try your best to teach your children how to develop into a human being that respects all people and not to single someone out and/or bully for personal gain. When I see a reddit post such as this it reminds me that this practice continues on past childhood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-12 14:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sources are at bottom of post.  with the exception of the girl post all the others bullets were confirmed by WB, Zach Snyder, Darren Aronofsky and/or David Goyer. Don't mean to span just put up content i feel others will enjoy.  I do the blog for fun, nothing more.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-30 05:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always planned on reading thus book kept putting it off good review.  Getting it tomorrow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-29 20:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now you are all just being picky.  We've all brought home worse at one-time or another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-29 20:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> great list KBPrince0.  Thanks!  Looking forward to heading to these sites to read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-27 20:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 52 issues of countdown that I will be happy to give away to some unsuspecting kids.  It will be the scariest thing they get all night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-24 22:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well said </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-24 20:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eric Cartman would be proud </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-03 23:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean Marvel's Whore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-03 21:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These prints are wonderful and very creative.  I am definitely getting the Batman/Penguin for my office </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-03 16:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it was everything i hoped for and more.  Time Travel episode was excellent, "looks like we are going to have to go around again." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-01 21:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope Apple TV is good this time around </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-30 21:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree Bruce Wayne has, is and should always be Batman.  DC is just confusing the the fans with too many titles with too many different Bat-men </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-26 22:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The complaint is that Dick Grayson is the Batman in the new JLA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-24 21:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is amazing.  Love the rough sketch. powerful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-24 18:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my new religious philosophy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-20 21:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From his lips to God's ears </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-19 16:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry.  should have posted the deviantart link.  here it is - http://mikepmitchell.deviantart.com/art/Darkwing-Duck-175589621?q=sort%3Atime+gallery%3Amikepmitchell qo=0
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-18 19:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> still the greatest picture i have ever seen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-17 01:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you read comics and are following the DCU right now then you should not be upset with the post.  DC released the image for a reason.  not a spoiler.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-12 22:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Craig McCracken created the Powerpuff girls not Genndy Tartakovsky Although they met in school and have been very good friends ever since.  Even collaborating on some projects.  McCraken also created Foster's Home for Imaginary Friends.  Tartakovsky created Dexter, Samurai Jack and the original star wars clone wars cartoon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-12 21:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seaside Florida is the best in my opinion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-12 21:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hulk meets the mask </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-12 16:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depending on your age and sensitivity some of these may be offensive but all good places to wet your comic whistle: Bone, Rasl, Preacher, Y-The Last Man, 100 Bullets, Invincible, Walking Dead, Mouse Guard, Boys, Ex Machina, American Jesus, Wormwood, Fables, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-11 21:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These aren't so much independents but are outside the typical comic book genre and most importantly are fantastic reads. Bone, Rasl, Preacher, Y-The Last Man, 100 Bullets, Invincible, Walking Dead, Mouse Guard, Boys, Ex Machina, American Jesus, Wormwood, Fables, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-11 21:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the review.  very well done.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-11 05:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-10 21:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My library books are overdue and i need to pay off my fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-10 21:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blackest Night ran in three books.  Blackest Night was a stand alone book but also the story continued in Green Lantern and Green Lantern Corp.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-10 20:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My fingers are crossed that the Ryan Reynolds Costume will not look as bad as it did in the picture.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-10 03:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he's fantastic.  love his art.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-09 22:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no offense taken.  good to chat with you.  least we both love comics.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-09 20:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is how you pull apart Legos http://enveeapparel.wordpress.com/tag/legos/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-09 19:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, i read the book.  I read any comic or graphic novel.  I like the premise of the book.  Millar hooked me with Superman Red Son and American Jesus.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-09 18:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the book.  Didn't know it was posted already.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-09 14:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, did see it on the board before my post. Apologize if I re-reddited  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-09 01:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's weird looking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-07 23:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd sprinkle some of my Fairy dust on her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-06 22:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Becareful.  His poop is really dark matter and it is real heavy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-06 22:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Story reads wonderfully.  Superboy needs to carve out his own identity.  He now seems regulated to a background character despite his re-birth.  I also love the Robin/Superboy team-ups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-06 19:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this will help.  http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Superman_%28Earth-Two%29
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-06 19:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you 100 percent about the content of this series, but the cover is nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-05 01:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fry Bitch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-05 01:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> poor bastard.  I have four kids too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-03 21:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I read when I log into reddit this morning, "Hopefully I'm not the only person here who finds that site's "breaking news" updates to be tedious and uninteresting, among other complaints." 

It put me in a bad mood.  Hard to swallow when one hypocritical person (Inquiry FM) takes it upon themselves for no reason to start a negative reddit against a blog. 

With that being said, If i offended you I apologize.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-03 17:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it's OK for you to link people to your hour-long podcast, but it is not OK to link people to content on another page?  Seems reasonable.  Or maybe you are just jealous that Gfest blog gets thousands upon thousands of unique visitors a day and it looks like your podcast traffic consists of one unique visitor a day, which would be you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-03 15:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care one way or another about your thoughts on gfest but it seems hypocritical when you are promoting your shitty podcast (Inquiry FM.) to reddit.  FYI, the acoustics in your parents basement don't help the podcast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-02 22:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well hello Tobias Russell, how is the Bluth family today? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-02 21:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sad, sad, I had one of those... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-31 00:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i've wasted hours, days, weeks.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-30 23:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definetly worth the read.  Jack Horner arc is fantastic and the new jack (jack frost - his son) has been very good as well. No jump the shark.  Hood art and good writing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-30 23:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freaking amazing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-29 03:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss it.  BKV never disappoints.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-29 03:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great post! Great list.  Huge Batman fan excited to read a few of these titles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-28 20:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> blow job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-28 19:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i want one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-28 16:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amen! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-28 16:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dead-on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-27 21:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's nasty regardless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-27 21:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fantastic.  I couldn't even make a square </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-26 22:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> need a citizen petition to start a referendum to ensure big tit s are not a crime.  I will be happy do the casting for the TV ads.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-21 20:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chick magnet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-16 14:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite what the jackass named crunchmuncher posted below, I like the posts and information.  Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-16 14:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't Freakin Wait! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-15 21:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are fantastic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-15 20:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did it pop out of her stomach? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-15 20:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awesome and true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-15 04:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second the last post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-14 21:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like spicy food </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-14 20:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The graphics remind me of playing the old Atari 2600 but very creative and well done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-14 01:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd pay whatever took to kick him in the balls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-13 21:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I LOVE THIS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-12 21:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder the pulp tasted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-12 19:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am laughing but i feel bad about doing so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-09 20:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hard you were good in Precious Miss Sidibe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-09 19:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-08 21:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'd hit jake before i was forced to hit that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-07 22:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three Blind Mice, baby! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-07 21:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> beautifully done.  old suit too.  way better than the new one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-06 20:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i've caught the fever as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-06 19:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this comic.  Damn funny.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-06 19:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wonderfully cleverl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-05 14:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweeet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-02 17:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well written and well drawn.  Kudos for developing such a wonderful story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-30 16:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree, terrible pick for Wonder Woman despite what, Morgue, the overly obsessed Tori Black fan believes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-30 16:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't think you could make Wonder Woman less relevant but DC is working hard to do just that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-24 22:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard Steve Jobs got married recently, but he lost is iPhone at a bar on the honeymoon
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-24 19:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love that book. My boys love it too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-23 16:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope Robot Santa brings this to me for Christmas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-23 16:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even watch soccer and that's damn funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-22 16:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> completely awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-21 22:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is that Biden? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-21 21:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like playing paper mario </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-21 16:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Timmy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-21 15:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christopher Reeves really is Superman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
