<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9956</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Matching velocities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 20:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After playing a real obscene number of hours in Kerbal Space Program, I got into Simple Rockets pretty well, even landed on the Smoon and Smars - it is a bit easier thanks to being 2D - but I can't seem to be able to match velocity with rendezvoused-with ships. Docking was one of my favourite activities in KSP and I was quite good at it, but afaik there is nothing like relative velocity nullifying marker in SR. I managed to dock only once, and it was not very graceful, which is displeasing.
I don't know how to use that grey thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT][Video] Short soap opera parody movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 20:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was on Reddit some months ago, it was a project of a group of students of Spanish language. I need it quickl, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little girl got it right, didn't she? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 20:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rotation bug + Jettisoning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 21:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a) Every so often I experience a bug where the ship starts to rotate (using reaction wheels, it consumes power) by itself and only SAS keeps it in check and I can't get rid of it (not even by reloading). I suspect it has something to do with using physical/time warp or SAS toggling while rotating. Does anyone else experience this? How to get rid of it?

b) Is it possible to jettison an engine without having it set as an action group? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EXTREMELY LONG] My debate with a creationist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 00:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The beginning of the conversation is lost (it began at Omegle, it was basically that he is a Messianic Jew and he believes in the creation by Yahweh). This is copy paste of our email conversation (without names, emails and greetings); I would like to know what do you think of my reasoning, if I should improve something. Thanks.

http://sharetext.org/yG6f

He hasn't responded since that last email a week or two ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have been playing Kerbal Space Program for 637 hours now. AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 22:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Dude, you can't kitten and beard on the same internet. That's just fucking cheating." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 09:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Sometimes when I dream, a real-world event can be incorporated into the dream seamlessly as a consequence of dream causality. How is that possible? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 09:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> E.g. if I was dreaming about riding a rollercoaster which was about to smash into a wall, a cat jumping on me in the real world would project itself into the dream as the impact.

My brain doesn't have any way to predict the future, does it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think of this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 23:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vVkDrIacHJM feature=youtu.be

I don't think that the message needs to be spelled out. In this form it is quite obvious.

Aside from the message, it is extremely well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST][STEAM] Space Engineers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 22:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello!
I am quite fond of KSP, and this caught my eye as something I would surely enjoy (building bases/ships/...). It is on sale, however, I can't spend money on it this month. I would be very thankful to whoever would be so generous as to gift me,  and I make sure to pay it forward in the future. :)

[Steam ID](http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561197997373039) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which animal is better off - the one which lives with a homeless person or that which roams free? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 17:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was an issue we came upon today in school while discussing animal mistreatment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the long face? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 14:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do KSC radars point at something specific when turning? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 13:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This question occured me today - do the turning radars at KSP point at some specific point or trajectory in space? Is is possible that there are some undiscovered easter eggs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Id rather make toenail soup" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 22:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Joke] Czequestria - Manly ways to relax </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 20:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Czequestria 2014 - The beginning of something special </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 11:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A comment under a YouTube video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 20:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kneel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 17:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't decide if this is creepy or not </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 20:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Towel Day! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 14:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Towel Day 2014! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 11:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fellow froods and froodesses!
Every Earth year on May the 25th, we hold a tradition of visibly carrying towels around with us, because on this date, there is a regular increase in flying saucers fly-bys, though we can't see them easily due to SEP field, and we have to be prepared for sudden untold adventures, Earth demolitions or serendipitious petunia materalizations.

In every case, this act also serves as a homage to Douglas Noel Adams, who ~~wrote~~ received from extraterrestrial beings this utterly extraordinary trilogy in five parts, and decided to share it with us.

Whatever happens this day, don't panic. Or every other day, for that matter... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was Discord's thinking tree this one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 20:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (NSFL)(NSFW) Bloodshed in CAR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 15:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://viiphoto.com/articles/terror-car-bleasdale/

Just reading this makes me sick. They use religion as an excuse to slaughter each another. It is surreal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does the discovery of gravity waves affect "universe from nothing" hypothesis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 20:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am interested in reading Krauss's book Universe from Nothing, and I'd like to know if the recent discovery of gravity waves affect that hypothesis in any way, and how?

If this question makes no sense, I am sorry, I am no scientist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't give a flying fuck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 22:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The human imagination is amazing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 22:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HD] MLP - The Finale Fight between Twilight and Tirek (Twilight's Kingdom) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 22:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grab yourself Czequestria ticket before it's all sold out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 21:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Czequestria ticket sale begins today at 19:30 CEST </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 16:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Czequestria ticket sale begins today at 19:30! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 11:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HELP] Game-spoiling bug </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 22:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever since 0.23.5, I am often experiencing a weird time warp/gravity physics bug, where all parts of my vessel except the main part (capsule or whatever) go limp (as if in a freefall without horizontal speed), it becomes fixed (meaning it doesn't move and it is not affected by neither pressing keys or burning) and the trajectory changes rapidly even when not burning. When I try to time warp again it says that the time warp cannot be used under acceleration, or it disassembles rapidly. 

It happens in orbit around Kerbin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why there are no bigger asteroids? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 18:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a mod that adds giant asteroids (FSAA or something like that) as parts, but no mods that make them appear like vanilla asteroids. I understand that they would be virtually unmovable, but cool bases could be built on them. Is there any engine constraint preventing this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can anybody actually believe that a god created the whole universe for them, while looking at images like this, where the size of the Earth would be just an invisible dot on an invisible dot? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 17:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They look creepy, yet amazing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 17:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [English] Should I go for B2 or C1? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 20:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have passed both levels in practice tests, but I have a dilemma. I was almost bored when doing B2, but I am not very sure I can pass C1 again, though I did good in the practice test. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is my contribution in SETI@Home still meaningful in any way? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 00:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run it on an old notebook (to process one chunk of data lasts several hours) and I don't know if I actually contribute to anything. And I heard some skepticims about whether one should run it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best use for an old notebook with broken screen? SETI data computing cat sofa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 22:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know, for kids </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 22:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ticket tiers for Czequestria revealed! Available to buy soon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 07:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Learning sloth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 20:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new movie is coming out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 11:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interesting crossover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 18:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PMS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 11:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cuties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 23:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>  3 posts in a row  mod be like "whatever" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 22:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh crap I visited the sub again... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 21:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Raven Revisited </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 21:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Think with portals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 09:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just reminding of a new Czech con Czequestria, which will take place in August </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 19:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We need to replace "the other one" with this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 21:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's okay... I guess </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 12:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Think with portals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 18:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Internet essence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 18:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why isn't FAR/Deadly Reentry a part of vanilla already? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 12:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems to make the game a lot more realistic, if harder. Or there could be an option to toggle KSP/realistic gameplay.

What is the reason for not having incorporated it in the game yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we just dedicate a minute to how awesome MLP comic books are? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 23:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sudden inpirational quote in Ace of Spades Classic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 19:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today I decided to play Ace of Spades Classic once again, so I go to a server and join the blue team. After changing several maps, one turns up where blue team is having its ass kicked really hard, when a message suddenly appear in the chat:

 We may not be winning in the game, but we are winning in our hearts.

Thank you, random stranger, for encouraging me a little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one who is not ashamed of the pilot two episodes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 16:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where does consciousness come from </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 12:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/iz3FWBK.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 0000001000001100001110001111 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 19:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on sucker, lick my battery! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was Twilight studying at the beginning of latest episode? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 23:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think it had some connection to THE box or to Rainbow Power? Surely if she was studying somethingunrelated, they could just make her sitting and reading silently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Staring contest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 21:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poor Spike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 21:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first asteroid (Medium) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 02:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This was perhaps the creepiest thing in Snuff Box </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 21:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glorious </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 18:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ride on the rhytm of space </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 18:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make me feel better about spaying my cat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 22:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's an indoor cat, and we don't plan her to have kittens anyway, so we're going to get her spayed. I googled about it and what are the benefits, but I still feel bad about how drastic it seems and that she won't be able to reproduce. It is just sad :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A pillow would be better, wouldn't it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 11:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Went on Christianity sub again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 01:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sometimes go there to see what retarded things people say there, and it never fails me laugh. But it also enrages me a little, when I what turds can people spew of their mouths, and how ignorant some of them are - religion serves them as an excuse to not seek reason, to abandon critical thinking, to embarras themselves. Cattle do not see the stars and think they are special in the universe. In comparsion with immersity of the universe, we are uncomparably less than nothing.

I hope there won't be a shortage of people who publicly present reason, science, atheism etc. to people, because I have a grave feeling that it might actually be possible for the world to become a place where non-believers would be put ot death, if there would be no vocal opposition.

Just wanted to get this off my chest, carry on, or discuss it, if you wish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is that even similar, TasteKid? Oh, i see, they're both fairy tales </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 23:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have replaced all stations above Kerbin with these </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 20:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do Disney movies work so well? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 20:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am watching Frozen right now (had heard that it is a nice progressive fairy tale) and it is well known that Disney movies work for majority of people, they can make people smile and cry at every age. Why exactly is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fist of Jesus gets sequel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 19:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't follow discussion about AT that much, but I have one question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 18:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if all those things with right arm are just a running joke to tease us, just like with the snail? Are there some solid pieces of evidence implying that he is really going to lsoe his arm?

I just watch the series, I haven't read comics or anything other yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 44 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 17:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pale Kerbal Dot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 13:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does it mean? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 07:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [In the newest infostorm](http://forum.kerbalspaceprogram.com/content/265-Kerbal-Space-Program-Asteroid-Redirect-Mission-The-FAQ) there was this passage.

 **What is this Claw thing?**

The Advanced Grappling Device, or claw, is your primary means of capturing an asteroid. The Claw works very much like a docking port, however, it doesnt require a mate node to dock to. That means it can grab on to almost any object. Once grabbed on, you can even transfer fuel from the grabbed objects (provided they have any). 

Does this mean that regular docking ports become less useful? This wording implies that I can just launch a fuel tank tank with a probe on it into orbit and suck from it with this claw thingy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A journey's end </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 22:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tested my rover at Kerbin's South Pole and took a walk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 22:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I enjoy making photo cutouts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 21:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted some shops to /r/photoshopbattles a few times, but I actually enjoy more cutting people/things out than think what witty should I do with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't struggle with God's love </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 18:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U wot m8? (cross-post from /r/KerbalSpaceProgram) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 23:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> KSP developer in a spacesuit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 19:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb's face is not a face of mercy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 19:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pale Blue Dot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-09 18:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Floating stations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-08 14:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few weeks ago I have read an article about possible human colonies floating in Venusian atmoshere, and a question occured to me whether something like that would be possible to build in atmosphere of some Kerbol system planets?

I read on the wiki that lighter probes don't even need a parachute on Jool, so I don't think it would be completely impossible. What do you Kerbal rocket scientist think?

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Colonization_of_Venus#Aerostat_habitats_and_floating_cities </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gimme towel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 20:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stop pretending already [2400x1600] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 20:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bundle Stars newsletters can be disturbing _ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 21:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My longest orbit aka Long Way </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 23:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Possibly very NSFW/NSFL random image finder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 11:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE know this obscure show? I've got a DVD. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 20:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I write about PC games. AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 22:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do it just as a hobby, don't get any money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There will be a new European con - Czechquestria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 16:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NO A </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 16:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I haven't heard it in months. It was exactly what i needed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 22:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This got me the most excited about today's episode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 00:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I would like to be Bartledanian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 17:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Life would have been much easier.

**Edit:**

Utterly meaningless coincidence: 

Bartledanian books are 100 000 words long. According to the [Words to Pages](http://www.wordstopages.com/) converter, a book with 100 000 words written in Arial font size 12 with double spacing would have 365.3 pages. That is almost exactly the same number as number of days in a year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you realize how insignificant you are, you understand that giving me upvote is not that big of a deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 12:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OFFER][PC][Steam] Universe Sandbox </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 10:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoever posts best inspirational quote wins and I'll send them the key. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi, I subscribe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 01:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because it is so nice and quiet here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It was a nice touch [Foster's] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 00:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paper books are better than readers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 19:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that you can carry 1000 books in a reader everywhere, but paper books are flexible, have "personality", last potentially a very long time and frankly, do you really need to read 15 books at a time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/DirtyPlates for adoption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 23:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No posts. I am not longer interested in it, so anyone else can take care of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You train anal every time you poop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 10:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That must be quite intense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 22:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My take on Fluttershy in the Sun [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 22:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Figure skater </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 21:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I never understood why it looks so creepy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 20:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Luna sleeping on my lap after kneading at the blanket a bit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 00:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you make a base in vanilla? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 17:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know there is no point to it without mods beside satisfying feel, but i would like to ask you what do you think should be there, how big it should be and so on.

EDIT: Without mods of any kind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I ever went insane, I wouldn't realize I am insane. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 17:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scunthorpe problem to Hitler (no countries or languages) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 14:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST][Steam] Octodad: Dadliest Catch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 01:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Steam ID](http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561197997373039)

I will make sure to pay it forward :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch the rest of the Ham/Nye debate OR play Kerbal Space Program OR play Plants vs. Zombies and write about it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 16:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST][Steam] Octodad: Dadliest Catch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 22:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will make sure to pay it forward.

[SteamID](http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561197997373039) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST][Steam] Octodad: Dadliest Catch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 18:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved original Octodad, yet when the sequel finally releases, i have no money. :/

I'd make sure to pay it forward. :)

[SteamID](http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561197997373039) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suggestion: Verse bot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 18:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we should get a bot which would after typing something like "BibleVerse: Part XX:XX" respond with corresponind verse from standard King James Bible.

Commenters on this sub often adress some verses, so this could be useful. I wonder whether this idea have been proposed before, if it was, i am sorry.

Same could be done for other holy books too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do people like to use quotes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 14:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's because of authority of the person who said them? Or because the quotee formulated the idea so well that a quoter feel they don't need to add anything?

And why some people hate quotes so much?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heavy Metal Sloth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 13:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Search engine indexing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 23:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL there is a series of books about dinosaur-on-human sex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 22:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb suddenly disappeared </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 21:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was on Minmus with Bill and Bob. On the top of a lander there was a rolling probe, so i rolled it about 1,5 km away, did some measurements and flew with Jeb to collect data (well, more slid than flew).

When i was a few tens of meters from it, i switched to probe to slightly angle it for convenience. When i wanted to switch back, there was no Jeb.

He disappeared.

I was confused at first and looked for him all over, but he simply vanished. I went to Astronaut Complex and he is listed as MIA.

What the hell?

BTW when i planted the flag i named it Jebediah's Vision after that creepypasta; coincidence much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST][Steam] Octodad: Dadliest Catch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 02:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [SteamID](http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561197997373039)

It released yesterday, but i don't have any money. It is on sale now. I would be very grateful and make sure to pay it forward later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which settings will hit my performance the least? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 19:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play on lowest setting due to my old PC, but i was thinking if i could afford to make my game a bit prettier without losing performance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I liked this pony very much! (SPOILER) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 18:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am very ashamed to admit this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 15:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After almost 300 hours of playtime i found out how to rotate parts in 5 steps and how to clone. I feel stupid. I was thinking how people make Death Stars and bowling balls and lithobraking stuff and it never occured to me to google it.
If i did not watch some Manley's video i wouldn't know it... I thought i figured the game by myself. Well, i have a lot to learn yet.

Edit: And of course the rest of controls too, i forget to mention it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST][Steam] Octodad: Dadliest Catch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 01:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am browsing interwebs and what i don't see like announcement that the Octodad sequel finally came out! I am extremely happy, but i remember i ran out of my allowance for this month and will have to wait and buy it when it will be not on sale anymore.

So please, if someone could give it to me, i would be very grateful and make sure to pay it forward later.

[My SteamID](http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561197997373039) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favourite planet/moon and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 22:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This monstrosity went to Kerbol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 22:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I will never be a real scientist. :( AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 16:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Draw my friend, please :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 15:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was looking for a subreddit for The Oatmeal cartoon strips, and i found this sub </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 21:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am pleased. I love oatmeal. I think i am going to make myself a cup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What could humanity achieve in 100 years if all nations would join together in an effort to have the best space programme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 12:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The question of money would be put aside, because people would realize the utmost importance of expanding into space, so all materials and workforce would be for "free" (people could even volunteer for working on some tasks like manufacturing parts, which would then be send to ~~World Space Center~~ Starfleet from all over the world; those who participate in programme would get all they need from governments) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This episode gave me cancer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 00:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel new meme coming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 00:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost didn't make it (had only a few seconds worth of fuel), but i managed to land on Eeloo for the first time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 21:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To all lovely people on this sub </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 20:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shooting adorableness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 20:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Government in a nutshell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 16:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just finished latest episode of Doctor Who, here is my boring little wall of text (really, nothing interesting) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 16:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note: I am a fan of 2005's Doctor Who. I am not planning on watching older series, i am quite content with the new.

I must say it is one of the best series i've seen. About a year ago i started to hear from my friends how good it is, they posted DW related things on Facebook and i am naturally quite open-minded, so i put it on my imaginary "To watch" list, but i did not rush in any way, actually, it was one of my new classmates who gave me needed push.

First episodes were feeling like it was a cheap TV production - it probably was, and i do not complain - and it got better with time. I love series which have consistent universe, and DW satisfied me in this way.

Not everyone may see it same, but i like how they put homosexuality in there every so often - i am not a homosexual or in LGBT community, but i am happy for those people, i support them (of course i like gay jokes and so on, but that is different). I also felt some atheist themes in the series, that was pleasant too. I also very like the Doctor's "no guns" policy, it's not something you can see very often today.

I sure am going to continue watching, though i call myself just a fan (don't really have urge to call myself whoovian yet; maybe this will be my backup fandom) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kingdom Come: Deliverance is a new realistic non-fantasy RPG set in Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 21:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calmly confident in what he does </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 17:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to punish a cat properly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 23:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "Oh, you wicked, wicked little thing!" cried Alice, catching up the kitten, and giving it a little kiss to make it understand that it was in disgrace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plushies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 23:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Discord </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 08:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My fingernails grow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 21:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They grow on my fingers. They grow slowly. They are hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flying fu*k </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 00:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OFFER][STEAM] Saints Row: The Third </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 17:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoever post cutest kitten image in this thread gets it. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Repost) Your worst enemy is yourself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 01:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my cat is hanging on chair's backrest just by paws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 01:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only upvotes will help him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 19:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hurry! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 23:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cats in a nutshell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 21:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got my first Kraken of this type yesterday. I hate it, it's so freaky :c </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 10:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justin Bieber might use his Reddit throwaway account right now and giggle at your pun comment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 22:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carbon black </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 17:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cave diggers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 15:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many space stations have you got? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 14:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How often do you use them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My cat goes crazy when i don't pay attention to her </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 14:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is running arround in a highly wild manner, meows as if she was getting hurt and is overly highly active. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We literally pay for bits of space to live in </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 15:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dawn at the Mun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 01:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My cat was standing on my keyboard and typed this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 23:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cv                                                                                                                                                                           11111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111++++++++++ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There si a theatre in Czech Republic which plays plays by Jra Cimrman, a fictional character conceived by group of actors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 10:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I used Imgur Roulette </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 14:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What am i doing with my life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 09:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think reposts are good </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 09:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is always someone who hasn't seen something yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate my life :D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 19:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I flew to the Mun and collected high amount of scientific data, but i underestimated needed power to get back to Kerbin, and poor Kerbal must have EVAed (of course with data) and set himself on stable orbit. So i send first rescue - it was a probe with four solar panels, i don't know how, but i managed to position the way that no light could reach them, thus rendering probe dead. For my second try i attached two 1x6 automatic panels to it and i even managed to get rendezvous orbit - but in the wrong way! Now i am going for my third try. Wish me luck!

EDIT: Finally! That was insane, it took 4 tries before i managed to pick up poor Kerbal, and then i had to position vessel hanging on a parachute so he won't fall off his seat (another valuable lesson - always using capsules). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Hohmann transfer significantly more efficient than waiting for Mun/Minmus and flying moreless straight up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 12:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about modding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-29 00:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If i add an addon, will it render my vanilla profile save unusable in vanilla again, even if i don't use modded parts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any actual video footage from Mars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-29 00:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have googled a bit, but i can't see nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if my cat is a superheroine and saves the world by performing naps? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 22:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lucky crash landing! (first with rover) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 21:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A few questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 10:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the point in rescuing Kerbals?

Have you ever collided with a piece of debris from your earlier launches?

Do you consider mods cheating? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've made quite a progress during past few days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 01:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I landed dozen or so manned modules on Mun, i learned to dock on orbit (i started to build a space station) and i got a few new upgrades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GOG] Thanks /u/Papolux for The Stanley Parable! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-25 10:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much [Papolux](http://www.reddit.com/user/Papolux) :) May you live long and prosperous life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last played: Tomorrow... OK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 14:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Small things :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 11:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST][PC/STEAM] The Stanley Parable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 09:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Steam ID](http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561197997373039/)

I am interested in this game, i played a demo and i quite liked it. Unfortunately, after Christmas shopping i have no money left, so i would be thankful to whoever would buy this for me (it is on sale). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And this here is where darkmuch held the grand 24-hour fap off. He masturbated for so long his cock chafed and his right hand developed a charley horse, forcing him ton continue with is left hand. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 08:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am begginer in Kerbal Space Program. AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 18:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Group photo from Czech Bronies karaoke meetup [15.12.'13] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-19 21:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MFW i manage to land on the Mun for the first time ever (and in Career mode) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-19 21:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Czech policeman playing piano </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-19 16:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your kerbfessional opinion on the landing of China's probe/rover? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 21:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.nasaspaceflight.com/2013/12/china-jade-rabbit-lunar-arrival/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST][PC/STEAM] The Stanley Parable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 12:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have already ordered Christmas presents for people i like, thus leaving no money to buy this. If someone would be so kind and gifted me, i will play the kindness forward when i get money.

[Steam ID](http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561197997373039/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
