<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7734</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The mirrors in this bathroom all had video ads implanted in them. Do they know what a fucking mirror is used for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 02:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The runner in this New Balance ad appears to be wearing Adidas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 02:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's amazing to me that when people sing, their accents rarely show up. What's that shit all about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 00:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course this isn't across the board but it seems in English speaking groups and some closely related it is impossible to notice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those of you who are drinkers. How has it been going? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 23:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was one of my worst fears before hand. I didn't have a drink the first 2 days. Since then over 2 weeks I have tied one on about 5 times. That means about 12-18 beers each night. I still haven't given in which blows my mind. I thought it was impossible. I honestly think I am just finally fucking done with these things. It feels great.

How has it been for you?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the first things I saw this morning. It cracked me up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 13:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today I have surpassed one week. I never thought it was possible. Today I had a really rough day and I know I was an ass to some people. They understood. It's amazing. The feeling of choosing *not* to smoke. I swear I always thought I would never have that choice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 02:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for reading. I know this isn't mind blowing or some great story but I am glad this sub exists so I am able to get it off my chest to some people who it means something to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any flaws in this article? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 15:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Went to my fishing spot this morning. Found this. Classy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 19:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just ran into this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 19:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stay classy Deep River. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 18:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, I have a bunch of songs that i recorded and put on up on myspace about 6 years ago. How in the fuck do I get them back. I don't have the pc that i was using or the username/password that i used for that account. Am I fucked? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 00:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> side note. What is myspace now? A wall of instructions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am on day 4 of being a non-smoker and am currently taking chantix. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 22:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only side effect I have come across so far is being a bit spaced out and super super vivid dreams. No nightmares just super realistic mundane everyday shit with all of the people I know and in all the places I know them. Every night since my first day of being a non-smoker I have smoked in my dreams. Yet, in my dream I knew it was wrong and it was not good. I have woken up each morning thinking I had cheated. 

So far chantix has helped me deal with what I could not. Cravings. Now it's all mental. I have an argument with myself about 20 times daily. It's usually me trying to convince myself to just have one after a trigger. Not happening. I am able to get past that withing 5 minutes. I started carrying around those [plastic floss sticks](http://img.dxcdn.com/productimages/sku_47578_2.jpg). They are a great way to get the oral fixation out of the way and keep my teeth clean.

I have smoked since I was 14. I am just about to turn 35. The past ten years I was up to a 1.5-2.5 a day depending on circumstances. I feels so strong that I am on day 4 and am actually proud of myself for once in many many years. 

Thank you for reading my quick rant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friends kid doing a flying ninja kick. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 00:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey reddit. What's the best joke you have ever made up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 01:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, and no variations on any others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The inside of this apple slice looks like an apple blossom. No, this is not normal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 21:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wednesday is my quit date. Tried cold turkey dozens of times over the years. I'm on chantix now. Anyone have any tips. Not looking for horror stories, okay? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 15:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The main thing I am anxious about is what it's like to have that last cigarette on Tuesday night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An interesting way to play Jenga. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 05:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me and my girlfriend won the egg toss at a family reunion. It would be great to see what you magicians could do. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 04:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The typos on this postcard are both atrocious and hilarious. (resubmitted because my linked sucked ass before) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 04:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am a catering chef. I recorded some timelapse videos from the summer of plating for weddings. This is their story. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 03:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pretty sweet spider I saw the other day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 03:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An awesome present I got through a redditgifts exchange. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 03:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Come at me, bro. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 02:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The edge of this storm looks like a baby's head with a huge forehead. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 02:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ya, Fuck that guy with COPD. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 02:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am using a Samsung Tab 3 7.0. I have set up the WatchOn set up. It seemed to recognize everything but when I choose a show and hot playontv it doesn't change the channel. Any ideas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 01:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These two peppers are conjoined. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 23:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of these is not like the others. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 15:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron Paul at this very moment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 06:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron Paul at this very moment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 06:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holy smokes. (mild spoiler) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 03:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alfonso on blow is not somebody I would want to run into.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The two Coreys had some serious shit go down when they were young actors. Sexual abuse by someone in the industry. (Corey Haim   Corey Feldman) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 01:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You#know#those#people#who#hashtag#everythinng#?#!#...... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 01:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most awesome woodworking/living room (x-post from r/woodworking) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 00:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I havce been searching around but cant find a full proof way to get flash to work on my samsung galaxt tab 3 7 inch. Anyone know a way? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 00:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sure hope that I can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coolest phone ever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 22:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any fans of the Hooker Brewery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 05:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I have been trying to upload a couple of pictures to imgur and all it does is says it uploaded and then goes straight to the frontpage of imgur. What is going on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 23:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I even tried taking them with two different cameras. I also tried uploading separate older pics on my laptop and they work but these wont. Anyone else experience this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dad builds rc boats from scratch. About 20 years ago he held a speed record. He just got back into building them. This is his latest boat. (x-post from r/radiocontrol) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 22:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dad builds rc boats from scratch. About 20 years ago he held a speed record. He just got back into building them. This is his latest boat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 17:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know what this is about and what should i do about it. It keeps popping up whenever i play video on my laptop. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 00:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I skip this aisle because I'm not rich enough to have dietary restrictions. Ever notice that you don't meet poor people with special diet needs? A gluten intolerant house cleaner? A cab driver with Candida?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 02:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did you know that Essex is one of only a few places in America that have been attacked by a foreign power? (War of 1812) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 23:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This guy sticks fishing hooks in his arm...to demonstrate how to get them out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-16 19:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey fuckfacers. I'm here like santa and would like to put out my hand to help someone out if they need some cash or something. I was helped out by a fellow ca earlier this year and it is now time for one of you to get some help. No, I'm not paying your child support. Anyone in need of some help. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-15 00:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything goes...except child support and menthol cigarettes.

Creative is always good, but not needed. You got a phone bill or car insurance bill that is behind? Maybe you want to see a concert/show and can't swing it right now (thanks josh) let me know. 

Don't be ashamed to ask for help, okay?

Edit: One electric bill shut off notice and one swedish drinker taken care of. Cheers guys. I love all of you fucking booze faces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ladd Martin, are you out there? How cool was this shit? (kid wins a contest to have Weezer play at his high school in the 90's) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-15 00:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ladd Martin must have gotten laid like a million times for this. Ladd Martin, are you out here? (kid wins a contest to have Weezer play a show at his high school back in the 90's) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-14 23:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ladd Martin must have gotten laid like a million times for this. Ladd Martin, are you out here? (kid wins a contest to have Weezer play at his high school back in the 90's) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-14 23:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A great protest song from 65' by Tom Paxton. It sure would be nice if this generation would follow in these footsteps. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-14 23:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A great protest song from 65' by Tom Paxton. It sure would be nice for another generation of musicians to follow in these footsteps. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-14 23:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Picturing Pat Robertson spending his quiet evenings at his desk in his room searching for homosexual activities in San Francisco. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-14 22:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi Wethersfield. I'm up here catering a wedding at the Webb Barn. Where is a good spot to get a beer afterward? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 22:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is a lapse in the weather near me and it looks like some kind of crazy fireball must have come through and cleared it all away. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 02:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is what Phish sounds like to people who don't like Phish. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 00:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My buddy fought this cow a couple night ago in Old Saybrook area. I kick myself for not heading out with them at midnight. Any other anglers out here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 00:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Macaroni Dome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 17:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jon Stewart and Bill O'Reilly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 23:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pootoo bird. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 21:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fishing last night in Old Lyme and we came across this adorable little freaking green tree frog. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 16:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most likely the coolest gift I have ever received. Thanks to a fellow redditor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 02:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wouldn't swim in the pools in this town. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 00:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Risky sneeze. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 18:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unfortunate placement of the ladder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 15:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not sure if this is the right place but I thought I would try. I am getting a replacement laptop from dell for my xps1640. I have the extended care warranty. They want to give me the Inspiron 15r special edition. Does this seem fair to you guys? Specs in text. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 23:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is the original configuration of my xps1640 when it sent](http://www.dell.com/support/troubleshooting/us/en/19/servicetag/CX3CYK1)

and

[this is what they want to send me](http://www.dell.com/us/p/inspiron-15r-5521/pd? ~ck=mn)

I see that the specs seem to be pretty much okay but I am worried about build quality. I really like the way my xps has a flat screen as opposed to one of those edged screens. 

Thank you for any assistance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pepperoni and cheddar of tortilla. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 02:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If we were to wipe out mosquitoes would that be a bad thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 19:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know everything in this world serves a purpose...but come on. Ticks too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Rhode Island. I'm in Connecticut and I just began my 9 day vacation. I plan on exploring/photographing abandoned places in this region. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 18:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you give me any spots I should check out?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey everyone. Nutmegger here. I am on vacation for the next 8 days. I plan on traveling around exploring/photographing abandoned structures etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 18:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you give me any spots to check out? I have nothing but time and don't mind a good drive. Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My girlfriends daughter doesn't like the shirt she got as a present. Hell, I'd like to find it in a mens large. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 15:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World record 515 pound halibut caught in Norweigian waters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 05:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The minute hand in my computers clock is just slightly behind. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 22:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I started fishing about a year and a half ago...mainly in fresh water. Last week I went to the bait shop and had them gear me up with some surf/pier gear. This happened in my first couple days. I'm HOOKED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 22:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I started fishing about a year and a half ago...mainly in fresh water. Last week I went to the bait shop and had them gear me up with some surf/pier gear. This happened in my first couple days. I'm HOOKED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 21:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I started fishing about a year and a half ago...mainly in fresh water. Last week I went to the bait shop and had them gear me up with some surf/pier gear. This happened in my first couple days. I'm HOOKED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 21:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best part of pulling out clothing from the last season. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 20:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hallway in abandoned asylum (Connecticut)[(1060 x 1600)] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 21:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The way this floor wore down made it look like a happy monkey. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 01:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The recent post about the lady friend peeling potatoes reminded me of the jokes I have played on new hires in the kitchen. What types of jokes do you play on newbies in your field of work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 22:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such as, "Hey, can you go grab the water strainer" or "I need you to finely dice this pound of flour" or "go get the bacon stretcher"

Lets hear your best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found on the beach in Watch Hill, Rhode Island. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 00:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Empire of Light (Savoir Adore) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 00:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, it's been over a week. How is everyone with the new multi-reddit layout? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 23:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you been utilizing it or did you hide it and have since forgotten about it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your experience with a fishfinder for a kayak? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 00:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I own a pompano 120 if that helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone on hear had any luck with meetup.com for kayak groups? I joined a couple different ones but was hoping one of you might have some experience with them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 00:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am yet to join an event only because they seem so rigid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ten most easily stolen ATM card pins. (whats the deal with 1004?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 00:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feds: California teen alleges captivity, sexual abuse on marijuana 'farm' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 00:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coming soon to Facebook. God damn tv style commercials. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 00:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spy agency OK'd to share information that could lead to torture (Canada) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 00:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spy agency OK'd to share information that could lead to torture (Canada) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 00:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunset on my yak catching nothing but thats just fine. To relaxing to care. Connecticut river. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 01:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Went shopping for fishing gear. Ladies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 22:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Went shopping for fishing gear. Ladies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 22:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy 30th birthday to one of the best movies ever made. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 03:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waffle dipped in a homemade chocolate milkshake. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 02:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waffle dipped in a homemade chocolate milk shake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 02:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch "NEWS UPDATED : George Zimmerman and Trayvon Martin / Afterburner With Bill Whittle" on YouTube </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 21:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just found a penny made in 2013. Why are these still being made? Shouldn't we have more than enough? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 18:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They cost more to make than they are worth, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great dane/bull mastiff 8 week old I met this morning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 16:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bull mastiff /great date 8 week old I met this morning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 16:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunrise on the Connecticut river this morning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 16:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats on your mind? Whats wrong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 05:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets all try and figure it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The original Man vs Food (John Candy) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 04:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The dog throughout this video is freaking hilarious. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 07:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Show yourself, lady. U/IRAPECATS I'm looking at you "I Had Sex With My Cat And Everyone Knows," Aggrieved Oklahoma Woman Explained To Arresting Officer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 01:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Show yourself, lady. "I Had Sex With My Cat And Everyone Knows," Aggrieved Oklahoma Woman Explained To Arresting Officer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 01:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holy freaking smokes, boys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 01:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone into late night fishing? Boat, kayak etc? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 00:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for a few people to join. I am the Chester area. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bunny Rabbit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 00:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I'm in a bad mood or just plain ol' sad I watch this video of Stephen Colbert dancing accompanied by the Scissor Sisters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 23:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whenever I'm in a bad mood or just plain ol' sad I watch this video of Stephen Colbert dancing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 23:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there anything I can do with this to improve it? Does it do anything for any of you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 21:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I freaking lost it when he came into the frame in the beginning. Hilarious, but this is actually a really cool video. He goes over how he built a fishing kayak mainly out of things he already owns. The Poor Mans Kayak. If you are low on funds I would suggest watching this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 05:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Takes the cake for my inspiration. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 01:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys. Been posting a little bit on here over the past year. I got back into fishing last year after not doing it since I was a kid. I'm 34. It is all trial and error for me as I have no friends that are into it. yesterday was an awesome day for me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 02:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesterday I finally caught a large mouth while out on my kayak. I ran into a guy on his bass boat and we got to talking. I was dragging a worm across the bottom by the weeds and my freaking pole went nuts. 

When I finally got him about 10 feet from my kayak he took my pole about a foot into the water. The guy who is an avid bass fisherman was actually amped/ "Holy shit dude that a biggy"

This fish finally came up and jumped over the tip of my kayak. Coolest looking thing. It was such a rush. 

Sadly I was not able to get a picture and as I was pulling it up next to me it got loose. :( The dude on the boat said it was probably a 6-7 pounder.

I know to most of you this is old news in a bucket but for me it was like christmas morning. 

Anyway I just wanted to tell my tale of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just so everyone knows. Bear Grylls is making everyone boil their own piss right now and then having them drink it...for tv. I figured you guys would appreciate this tid bit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 03:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's some new show on NBC and I figured you guys would like to know. Now, drink your piss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is everyone dealing with the heat? I have had to force myself these past few days just to get out on the water for an hour or two. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 02:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone down for a quick trip tomorrow at around 6pm at Seldens? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "What's Connecticut?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 02:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Threw my waterproof camera in the water when I was reeling this little guy in. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 02:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Musicians of redddit. Do you ever get so discouraged after listening to a favorite song/band of yours that make you want to throw your hands up and forget all about trying to make it? (because you think you will never be that talented/original) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-06 00:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wont mention any bands myself as to not make this a circle jerk of taste in music. Have you ever dealt with this? Do you constantly deal with this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Home recording question. I haven't done any home recording since my tascam mk411 about 20 years ago...so please bare with me. I bought an audiobox usb interface and a sterling audio studio mic. I'm sure one of you can diagnose my stupid issue quickly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-04 02:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I plugged the sucker in and windows couldn't find the driver. I am using a windows 7 64 bit laptop. So, I went and found the driver(s). The first one installed just fine but the second one (legacy software download) didnt. It said a a time out error. Anyway I go and download audacity because I have fiddled with it over the years and know it is a really stripped down program that some buddies of mine would use when we would write songs. Now I am able to choose the audiobox from the output/speaker menu in Audacity but it is nowhere in the input/mic menu. Does this make any sense to any of you? I am sorry for putting this in the regular askreddit sub but if any of you know a really specific sub for this please let me know and I will move it over there. I am just dying to get some of these songs down on (tape?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Home recording question. I haven't done any home recording since my tascam mk411 about 20 years ago...so please bare with me. I bought an audiobox usb interface and a sterling audio studio mic. I'm sure one of you can diagnose my stupid issue quickly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-04 02:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I plugged the sucker in and windows couldn't find the driver. I am using a windows 7 64 bit laptop. So, I went and found the driver(s). The first one installed just fine but the second one (legacy software download) didnt. It said a a time out error. Anyway I go and download audacity because I have fiddled with it over the years and know it is a really stripped down program that some buddies of mine would use when we would write songs.
Now I am able to choose the audiobox from the output/speaker menu in Audacity but it is nowhere in the input/mic menu. Does this make any sense to any of you?
I am sorry for putting this in the regular askreddit sub but if any of you know a really specific sub for this please let me know and I will move it over there. I am just dying to get some of these songs down on (tape?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a loner, Dottie. A rebel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-04 02:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Home recording question. I haven't done any home recording since my tascam mk411 about 20 years ago...so please bare with me. I bought an audiobox usb interface and a sterling audio studio mic. I'm sure one of you can diagnose my stupid issue quickly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-04 01:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I plugged the sucker in and windows couldn't find the driver. I am using a windows 7 64 bit laptop. So, I went and found the driver(s). The first one installed just fine but the second one (legacy software download) didnt. It said a a time out error. Anyway I go and download audacity because I have fiddled with it over the years and know it is a really stripped down program that some buddies of mine would use when we would write songs.

Now I am able to choose the audiobox from the output/speaker menu in Audacity but it is nowhere in the input/mic menu. Does this make any sense to any of you? 

I am sorry for putting this in the regular askreddit sub but if any of you know a really specific sub for this please let me know and I will move it over there. I am just dying to get some of these songs down on (tape?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a loner, Dotty. A rebel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 13:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who's making mashed potatoes in the backyard? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 15:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi neighbor. I will be camping at burlingame tomorrow to Monday and then going to dome surf thing at Narragansett. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 04:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be bringing my kayak and fishing gear for the lake t the campground. Any tips etc? Am I able to get a fishing pass/license for a day or two or do I need to get a full license?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For anyone who knows of The Griswold Inn in Essex and it's history, this a quite the typo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 04:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found this on he side of the road. Looks like someone couldn't wait. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 15:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got my arbitrary gift today. A floaty for my waterproof camera and a funky travel book. I can use it to dream of where I would go if I had enough money to do so. :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 03:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Admit it ladies and gentelman. What was your first song as a kid that formed your musical taste. Dont even try and be cool. Just say it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 04:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I live in Connecticut in a very historical area. I want to get into this hobby. What should I buy, first off and what should I be looking for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 02:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My backyard leads directly into a state forest and there are many stone wall property barriers strewn about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It wasn't me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 01:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do you guys shop for gear online? Best prices, best customer service, best selection? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-19 23:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gear can really ring up after a bit when I'm at the local shop. I love supporting them, but I would love to find a good site that can give me a break here and there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The storm as it moved over us yesterday along the Connecticut River. It didn't bring much severe weather but it looked like the end of the world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 23:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blue Jay giving me the stink eye. What should I work on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 00:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, I guess it was all just hype. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 00:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skip to my Loo my Darlin' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 05:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Connecticut and Rhode Island are the only two states that never ratified the 18th amendment. (Prohibition) Cheers, Rhode Island- Connecticut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 23:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I post something from wikipedia so that when you guys click the link it brings you to the subject I am posting about...and not just the top of the page? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 23:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does that make sense? I've seen it down before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys. Quick question. Does anyone know of a way I can watch the Sox game tonight online? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 23:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend has seats right behind home plate and I want to see how awesome her seats are. I don't get it with my basic cable package. Any ideas? I am having no luck. I went to the nesn website but I can't figure out if the streaming is actually live or not...or if they will even be showing the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a previous resident of Seattle I was happy to learn this news. Can someone send me a Special with like 10 tartars to Connecticut? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 00:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boy Scouts of America vote to allow members to be openly gay. Another step forward. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 00:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boy Scouts of America vote to allow members to be openly gay. Another step forward. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 00:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boy Scouts of America vote to allow members to be openly gay. Another step forward. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 00:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Week 53, I guess. Tell me somethig to say and however you want me to say it and I will post it as I am. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 02:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will work out the tangles, okay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "My car is ugly, but then...I'm ugly too" The Magnetic Fields </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 01:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How everyone feels when they are on 95. Especially anything south of New Haven and north of Old Lyme. I think he is flipping off the highway. Maybe it's one of you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 23:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bald Eagle takes fish right off of guys line. Yes, it's that awesome. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 14:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have been fishing for 2 years now, but still... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 22:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 00:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At the bank today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 18:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abandoned family resort. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-02 03:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perfect timing? This was caught on a local news weather camera. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-01 23:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forget about first world problems. This is Connecticutworld problems. A town is being offered 10 million dollars to change its name...to accommodate the wealthy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-01 23:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any kayak anglers here in Connecticut? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-01 22:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got into it last year and I am looking forward to this season. Anyone out there wanna join me and a buddy tomorrow? It's a long shot but I would love some tips on bait, lures and techniques.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi fellow paddlers. I am in Connecticut and looking for some people to get together and have a great season. I have been out a half dozen times so far and it has been amazing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-01 00:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a recreational kayaker/angler and would love to meet up with some of you for this upcoming season. I created a subreddit @ [r/connecticutkayakers](http://www.reddit.com/r/connecticutkayakers/) for us to plan trips, give location pointers and share pictures/videos. I personally am going to be out for the the next few days after work and this weekend is shaping up to be great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IIL] Lou Barlow (Sebadoh, Folk Implosion] [WEWIL?] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 23:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been revisiting my youth and honestly it started with listening to the Kids Soundtrack again after almost 20 years. Yes, Dinosaur Junior and KRecords. What else you guys got? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Way too much funny. A best of "Between Two Ferns" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 22:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know how much the cost of living has gone up since late 2009 or how I would go about finding out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 14:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am planning on asking for a raise and would like to be able to use this as some reference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In regards to the boom people heard last week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-23 18:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look everybody, I guess we all apologized about the Boston Bomber situation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-23 05:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ready for emergence of the 17 yr. Cicadas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 13:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dude?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 23:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seriously, dude? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 23:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't get me in the middle of this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 18:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who enters their address? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 17:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Knowum sayin" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 06:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "takin' a "know im'census?"" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 04:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey everyone, horrible things have been going on forever. We live in a safer world than we ever have. How about we concentrate on honoring the victims and stop re-posting stories of the "suspects" life. Do us all a favor and quit it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 01:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I figured some of you might get a kick out of this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 23:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The woodwork at this bar looked like a bunch of Lego. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 00:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [1024x678] [OC] This house was super creepy. Came across it in the sticks in Connecticut. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 00:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ITAP of the house from Lets Scare Jessica to Death a few weeks ago. Thought you guys might enjoy it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 23:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big guy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 06:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This moulding reminds me of something. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 05:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the composition on this okay? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 03:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This pile of garbage and foam looks like a picture of an island from space. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 02:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Isle of Willimantic, CT as seen from space. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 01:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know how I file just my ct state income tax online. Every software i use wants me to file fed as well which I have already done. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 15:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a simple return. Just one w-2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> His songs are usually flawless and this does not miss that standard. Video and all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 03:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To the moms and dads of reddit. What do you do with your crusts from the sandwich? They are personally my favorite part. Let us know. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 01:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the app that lets me control my phone and data/pictures from my computer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 00:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first day out today. It was amazing. Empty river, wildlife was really abundant and I even got a good size cat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 00:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First day out on the kayak today. (Ct River) I even snagged a good size cat. Let the season begin! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 00:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Obama in Hartford today in regards to the recent gun laws...also today in Connecticut this happened. (very small town) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 02:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the difference between Best and Top in reddits filter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 04:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yah, so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After a crazy journey with the USPS my t-shirt made it today. Just what I wanted. A simple reddit t-shirt. :) Thanks a bunch t-shirt SS. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-05 02:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every...2...fucking...minutes... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 00:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Real funny, guys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 22:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Okay, this may be a long shot, but does anyone out there know of any advocacy or nonprofit groups that help advise people with a lot of student loan debt? Thank you! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 21:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Living in New England and saw my first wasp of the year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 17:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, spring is ruined.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where is that [picture of the squirrel at the front door with a monocle and holding a top hat asking for more bird food? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-31 14:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know what thread it came from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone out on the water yet? It's supposed to be above 50 through Monday at least. I am thinking of heading out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 22:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll grab some beers and my fishing gear and snag some trout on a big lake. Who's in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I followed a turkey vulture around for a bit until it gave me a chance for a shot. What do you guys think? (1024x678) [oc] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 22:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey vulture I came across today. I followed him around until he finally let me take a good shot. You guys see them often? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 21:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can any mechanics help me out with figuring out what is wrong with my engine? Youtube link to the sound it is making when starting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 20:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An impeccable Patrick Bateman impersonation over The Talking Heads. Holy Moly!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 04:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just heard a swamp full of peepers screaming bloody murder. Spring has sprung here in Connecticut. Strap on your kayaks and lets get to it! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 02:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone heard them yet this year? Was tonight the turning point? I am just waiting for the freaking hornets to start crawling out and messing my entire day up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My should fell off as I got out of the car and I noticed the line on the sidewalk is the same color as my worn down sole.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-28 16:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
