<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7720</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> help with making a turn based rpg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-11 12:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My playmat i am currently using.  I'll be making more and I'm up for commissions to challenge myself :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-24 23:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-19 09:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all ten in a core set is not unheard of remember the pain lands? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-30 20:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in idaho where i am, they have abandoned trick or treating all together in favor of mormon kids lining up around cars at the mall and getting candy and businesses giving it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> why batman knows everything. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 01:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> very far shot, but the bat computer is a very powerful machine and the d.c.u. obviously uses alien tech, so i think that the bat computer and thus batman have access to Wikipedia in our world and thats how it has so much info on everything because its been written beforehand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-10 00:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my money is on the undertaker being he normally is around in the back, and vince would listen to him plus ive heard taker say hell in a hand basket lots of times on air </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-29 08:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what part of idaho? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Carpenter's Halloween Returning to Theaters This Fall  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 04:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> so a friend of mine is trying to get our towns seminary to offer religious and non religious release time instead of lds seminary, i know this isnt normal atheism but can you help?  the shit storm is already starting for her </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 21:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 08:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://doaw.proboards.com/index.cgi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> magic tcg playmat i did still in use to his day, basically drawn on mouse pad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 12:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-13 10:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the best wrestling related troll ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
