<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9958</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 20:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the linked article:

S P, a unit of McGraw Hill Financial Inc, has said statements about the integrity of its ratings are "puffery" that cannot be a basis for the fraud lawsuit, filed on February 4 by the U.S. Department of Justice.

"Puffery" is a legal term amounting to [promotional statements and claims that express subjective rather than objective views, which no "reasonable person" would take literally.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Puffery)

That has to be one of the most fatuous statements I have heard in a long time.  They SOLD their ratings not on the basis of "puffery" but clearly as intended to be factual assessments of the given securities they were rating.

Seems a court got this right this time.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge lets U.S. pursue $5-billion fraud lawsuit against S P </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 20:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 19:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The main purpose of the One Ring was to dominate the will of the users of the other nine rings.

Men succumbed almost instantly to this.  The Elves figured out what was up with their rings and took them off before they could be used against them and I forget what the Dwarves did with their rings.

That said only Sauron could wield that power.  If others used the ring it came to dominate them and would have them seek out Sauron to return the ring to Sauron (the ring was imbued with Sauron's spirit to an extent).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 19:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Richard Feynman (great scientist) explains this well: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6tuxLY94LXw

Short version is it gets front/back reversed and not right/left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 18:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no limit to the amount of data they could collect in principle.

The problem lies in cost and how big the unit is to be able to hold all that additional information and still remain as resilient as they are.

Over the years more and more data has been added to the black box so they record more than they once did.  Whether there are still some things they'd like to record that they don't or they feel this is enough to determine what happened I do not know.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 15:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should do something to make your your first sentence that is a quote more obvious it is a quote.  I suspect a lot of your downvotes are because people think you are the one espousing that notion (on a first quick read I almost hit the downvote button till a second check I realized you were quoting the article).

*Italicize it* or use the quote function:

E.G. this thing

Or not as you like.  Just saying.  Carry on.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The World Cup Groups Are Laughably Uneven, And It's Proof That FIFA's System Is Broken </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 15:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 07:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Battlepaws Galacticat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 00:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John McCain [voted against a bill he himself had originally sponsored](http://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2010/12/when-john-mccain-was-a-democrat-almost/68291/).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 22:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 483 comments and only one original comment (all the rest are responses to that one top comment as of this writing).  

Must be some kind of record.  

I guess barring accidental ass bleaching which is apparently rare no one wants to admit to doing it on purpose.  That or Redditors are not a target market for ass bleaching.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 19:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This a hundred times.

The ending and the [look on their faces](https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage v=3JTH5VPAT4Y#t=166) is some of the best move making ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 15:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Germany had two fronts. Their ability to manufacture was easily bombed.

Actually German production [increased year-to-year](http://chris-intel-corner.blogspot.com/2013/05/wwii-myths-german-war-economy-was.html) throughout WWII despite the bombings.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 15:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amen brother (or sister as the case may be).

You can eat a hundred steaks from a local supermarket and they'll be fine...good even.

Then you have a steak that is top notch.  The cow was raised well, the butcher knew their stuff and the chef knew how to make the best of that and you have something truly remarkable.

I've only had a few like that in my life (tends to be very expensive) but seriously...WOW!

Put it this way...I have had hundreds of steaks in my life.  I still remember those few distinctly many years later.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 15:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are three grades of beef:

- Prime
- Choice
- Select

Prime is of course best and also expensive.  Choice is still very good and reasonably priced.  Select is cheapest and it shows.  For the most part steer clear of "Select" cuts.  By eye you can generally distinguish the cuts by the [amount of marbling](http://www.kansascitymamas.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/02/beef-grades.png) they have (more marbling = good).

----

Try to understand the main parts of the cow and where a given cut comes from.  There is a lot of fiddly detail that can be learned but that would be class 301 and 401.  For 201 just try and remember this image: http://0.tqn.com/d/culinaryarts/1/0/i/Y/-/-/US_Beef_cuts.jpg

Note that in general the further away you are from the horn and the hoof the more tender the meat is (muscles that work more like leg muscles are tougher).  As such the tenderloin is the most tender cut.

This is not to say tougher cuts are bad...far from it.  They just need to be cooked a bit differently and/or longer for a desirable result.  That said in general the more tender cuts tend to be more expensive (doubtless there are exceptions).

----
Avoid the Round part of the cow.  I am sure there are some recipes that make good use of it but I cannot think of one off the top of my head and would have to look it up.

That said the round is cheap...probably the cheapest part of the cow so if you are on a serious budget it can be a consideration.  You'll just have to work harder to make something good of it.

----

When buying meat make sure the specific part is listed.  If you buy "stew meat" and other generic sounding bits it is usually from the round and other undesirable cuts they are hard pressed to sell otherwise.  

So, for instance, when buying hamburger get ground chuck and not just "hamburger" which will probably be the round (ground sirloin works too but ground chuck is more usual).

----

Understand how different cuts cook.  A NY Strip is great for grilling.  A brisket needs a long, slow cook. Bigger cuts may need to be braised.  The more connective tissue and what not the longer you need to cook it.

----

Cheaper cuts are not necessarily "worse".  The tenderloin is probably the most expensive cut but it has little flavor (very lean...it is prized for being tender...the chef needs to add flavor).  A brisket is a cheaper cut but can be freaking awesome when cooked properly.

Again, just stay away from the round (in most cases). ;)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 14:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be an age thing.  I recognized all of it.  Thing is you rarely see a chateaubriand or even a t-bone on a menu anymore (restaurants figured there is more money in selling a filet and a NY Strip than a t-bone I think).

It was only a couple weeks ago at a specialized butcher that I saw the first tomahawk cut in ages...I was a kid last time I saw that in the meat case.

Hangar steak is indeed making a comeback.  Had not seen it in ages and am now seeing more of it very recently.  I think that is because beef prices are way up and it is a relatively cheap cut so they can offer a steak on the menu and retain a profit margin and not scare customers.

Ribeyes and the rest have been around forever.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Tasted BBQ Sauce Made By IBM's Watson, And Loved It: If the future of food is designed by robots, that's fine by me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 19:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran billionaire executed over $2.6B bank fraud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 15:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The FT Isn't Just Saying Piketty Made A Mistake  They're Saying Piketty Manipulated His Data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 21:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Upgrading to a SSD: Migrate or new install? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 16:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought a Samsung 840 Pro 512GB SSD.  My current system has two drives running in Raid-0 for a total of 250GB (I know but it has served me very well for years).

My question is when I install the new SSD should I leave the current drives in and migrate or unplug the old drives, setup the new drive and do a fresh install of windows and all that?

Either is doable.  Of course migrating would be simpler overall.  I do not know if there are issues getting trim to run via this method though.

Opinions?  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LIVE: Tom Wheelers Net Neutrality Proposal at the FCC - Digits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 17:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comcast plans data caps for all customers in 5 years, could be 500GB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 22:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hero Cat Saves Young Boy from Dog Attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 18:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Timothy Geithner Calls Those Seeking Wall Street Accountability Terrorists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 22:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Randall Munroe: Comics that ask "what if?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 20:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Hampshire Court Upholds COPSLIE Vanity Plate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 20:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nigeria President Criticized as Calls to Rescue Girls Rise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 18:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Justices Votes, Free Speech Often Means Speech I Agree With </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 19:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dark Wallet Is About to Make Bitcoin Money Laundering Easier Than Ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 20:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For Tennessee Lawmakers, Punishing Pregnant Women Is More Important Than Protecting Fetal Life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 17:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tennessee Enacts Law To Incarcerate Pregnant Women Who Use Drugs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 23:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Co-Founder Of Reddit Is Raising Money To Place A Net Neutrality Billboard 'In The FCC's Backyard' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 21:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SEC Commissioner Issues Scathing Dissent From Ruling, Elizabeth Warren Echoes Concern </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 13:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nerd alert: Kansas one of geekiest states in America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 22:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No one's here? Really? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 16:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is everyone?  I figured the Wrigleyville area to be a hotbed of Reddit activity!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC Establishes New Inbox for Open Internet Comments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 20:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Court limits damages to victims of child porn, throws out $3.4 million award </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 18:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chelsea Clinton's pregnancy gives birth to new conspiracies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 20:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Stevenss Solution for Giant Step in Wrong Direction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 20:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> France Drops 'Hate Speech' Case Against Bob Dylan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 22:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5-Year-Old Accidentally Shoots 2 Children At S.C. Birthday Party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 23:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Banksy Is Believed To Be Behind Eavesdropping Mural Near British Spy HQ : The Two-Way : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 19:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Bush's paintings: this is the art of Forrest Gump: The former US president's portraits show all the insight of a brain-damaged farm boy in a southern gothic novel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 20:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cracks in Googles Bid to Trademark Glass - Law Blog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 21:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Court Strikes Down Another Limit on Money in Politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 16:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Voucher programs in more than a dozen states draw on the public treasury to help students pay for private schools. Typically, 70 percent or more of participating schools are religious... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 21:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Europe doesnt need Americas fracked natural gas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 20:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio coal-price case could leave consumers out of luck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 19:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is there a big fuss over Kanye West and Kim Kardashian appearing on the cover of Vogue this past week? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 15:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can see a description of the recent uproar [here](https://tv.yahoo.com/news/kim-kardashian-kanye-west-vogue-cover-backlash-anna-193400697.html).

While I, personally, am no fan of West or Kardashian and view them both as symbols of what is (at least partly) wrong with this country I am not understanding why there is an uproar over their appearance on the cover of Vogue.

It is my understanding Vogue is a fashion magazine.  West and Kardashian are certainly fashionable and attractive (physically).  Since when is Vogue meant to be socially minded or politically active?  Even if readers think they should be how can these two be so controversial *especially* considering their success?  I thought the sorts of people who read Vogue are the sorts of people who are [Keeping up with the Kardashians](http://www.eonline.com/shows/kardashians).

I do not get it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon and Google Could Fix Everything Wrong With Game Consoles | Wired Business </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 18:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keystone XL hearing turns into squabble over U.S. Chamber's take on climate science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 20:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deeper Ukraine Invasion Lurks in Putin's Warnings, 'Provocations,' Clashes in East </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 15:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin Deports Executives for Speeding as Sanctions Loom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 15:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does EA charge tax when other online retailers do not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 03:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC Plans to Issue New 'Net Neutrality' Rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 23:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Truce Declared in Ukraine in Wake of Deadly Violence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 22:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine President Yanukovych sacks army chief amid crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 19:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Vampire Squid Strikes Again: The Mega Banks' Most Devious Scam Yet | Politics News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 17:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Armstrong: Two 'distressed babies' figured in 401(k) roll-back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 21:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Renowned cryptographer believes his 'Blackphone' can stop the NSA | The Verge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 15:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israeli media reports death of Ariel Sharon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 14:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the NSA nearly destroyed the internet (Wired UK) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 22:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US judge rules warrantless gadget searches at the border aren't unconstitutional </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 00:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Brooks' paean to presidential power is year's worst op-ed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 21:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> N.S.A. Phone Surveillance Is Lawful, Federal Judge Rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 18:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Coder Hates Valleywag So Much He Made A Chrome Extension That Lets You Read It Without Clicking On It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 16:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S., EU Mull Sanctions After Ukraine Protest Crackdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 18:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advocacy group asks NFL for language penalty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 00:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BOOM: HARRY REID OFFICIALLY 'GOES NUCLEAR' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 18:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In A Landmark Legal Decision, Google Wins The Right To Scan Pretty Much Every Book Ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 17:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Silly Joke On Jimmy Kimmel's Show Has Turned Into A Matter Of Geopolitical Importance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 18:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal court blocks ruling that would have ended stop-and-frisk | The Verge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 22:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why To Get More Than 1 Newspaper, iPad Edition - James Fallows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 19:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Krugman calls Greenspan the worst ex-central banker in the world - Capitol Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 16:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Bush Official: We Went Into Iraq Because 'We Were Looking For Somebody's Ass To Kick': Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 15:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Blows Everyone Else Out Of The Water In 1 Key Way (making rich people) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-19 01:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Dakota pipeline spews more than 20,000 barrels of oil : Energy News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 19:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bosses in NYC Can Sexually Harass Unpaid Interns -- Daily Intelligencer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 19:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Denying a 16-Year-Old Judicial Bypass, Nebraska Supreme Court Creates Ban on Abortions for Minors in State Custody </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 18:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big Oil loses it: ExxonMobil claims it owns the letter X! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 21:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: Closed-Door GOP Meeting With Cruz Turned Into 'Lynch Mob' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 14:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Second woman in 800 years elected mayor of City of London </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 20:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft: stand the Xbox One any way you like, as long as it's flat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 13:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: All aircraft carriers in history (save two) have their bridges on the starboard side due to a near universal tendency of pilots to veer left in an emergency. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 03:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox Host Todd Starnes Outraged That Indian-American Nina Davuluri Won Miss America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-16 23:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any reason to *not* buy a HDTV from overseas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 18:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been looking to buy a [Sony KDL-55W900A](http://www.amazon.com/Sony-KDL-55W900A-55-Inch-240Hz-Internet/dp/B00AWKBZ0M/ref=sr_1_1?s=electronics ie=UTF8 qid=1377791638 sr=1-1 keywords=kdl-55w900a).  Unfortunately it really is a bit big for the space I want it in.  Doable but would rather have a 46" set.

Unfortunately Sony does not sell the same model in the US in a 46" version.  Their 46" one is a step down in terms of the technology inside.

I was surprised to find that Sony does actually make a 46" version of that set and sell it in [Asia](http://www.sony-asia.com/product/kdl-46w900a) and [Australia](http://www.sony.com.au/product/kdl-46w900a). 

I would MUCH rather have the 46" set and am puzzled why Sony would not sell it in the US but that seems to be the case.

So my question to those here is are there any reasons to *not* buy the TV from overseas and have it shipped?  Things like the menus are in a foreign language and can't be changed (not really a problem from Australia though) or the TV has some kind of regional locking or stuff like NTSC vs PAL from the old days or anything else?

Or do HDTVs work the same everywhere?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wall Street crook Raj Rajaratnam has cushy cell, manservant at prison, insider says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 22:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feeding the Homeless Appears to Be Illegal in Raleigh, NC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 20:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Middle East, explained in one (sort of terrifying) chart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 19:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Illinois - Chicago] My GF keeps finding these in her bathroom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 17:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA paid millions to Internet companies to cover surveillance program costs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 17:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate Represents The Wealthy First: Study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-21 16:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hosni Mubarak Free? Ousted Egyptian President To Be Released From Prison This Week, Sources Say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 15:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Square Enix stops fan from selling 3D-printed 'Final Fantasy VII' figures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 15:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abu Ghraib Torture Victims Sued by Their Torturers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 20:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House insists James Clapper will not lead NSA surveillance review | World news </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 04:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gun Violence Study Uses Math To Compare Policies For Curbing Firearm Deaths </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 15:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samsung Rigged The Galaxy S4 To Seem Faster Than It Actually Is </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 19:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's Who To Blame For America's Lousy Economy... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 16:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If You're Wondering What's Wrong With America, Look At These Four Charts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 18:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Foc.us headset hits the FCC, ready to shock gamers' noggins into shape </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 15:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WWII -- Were the allies aware the holocaust was occurring all along or were they surprised when the first concentration camps were liberated? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-27 14:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Follow-up:  If the allies were aware the holocaust was happening why did they keep it a secret? (At least I cannot recall seeing any propaganda by the allies about it and the soldiers, at least, certainly seemed surprised when they liberated the first camps.)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The case of zombie voters in South Carolina </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 19:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edward Snowden Poll: Traitor, Should Be Charged </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 15:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marte Deborah Dalelv, Alleged Norwegian Rape Victim, Pardoned After Being Sentenced To Jail For Sex Outside Marriage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 13:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joe Biden Is on Edward Snowden's Case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 00:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Truthiness Is Out There </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-28 19:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How The NSA Is Still Harvesting Your Online Data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 18:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Head Of 'American Family Association' Says It's Now Inevitable That You Will Have Sex With Your Horse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-26 17:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Court Sends Texas Affirmative Action Case To Lower Court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-24 16:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DEBUNKING The Bush and Obama Administrations Justification for Mass Surveillance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 17:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Court documents reveal secret rules allowing NSA to use US data without a warrant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 14:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> COLUMN - Snowden versus the dragons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-19 19:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HTC confirms Android 4.2 is still coming to the One, despite rumors to the contrary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 02:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lewis Black pokes at the Kinect on The Daily Show | Joystiq </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-17 05:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PRISM scandal: The problem with "nothing to hide" and surveillance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 20:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Graphic Designer Took The Leaked PRISM Slides And Made Them Look Much Better </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 16:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edward Snowden: the whistleblower behind revelations of NSA surveillance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 20:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Borderlands 2 DLC costs $110? Really? Someone help me parse this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 04:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So...looking to revisit Borderlands 2 and maybe get some DLC Steam tells me there is [$110 dollars](http://i.imgur.com/LSpGzoc.png) worth to be had.  Pretty sure there is overlap here and seems kinda shitty Steam would lay out a $110 pricetag but maybe I am wrong.

So...what is the deal with this? (see linked pic above) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama orders US to draw up overseas target list for cyber-attacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 22:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Contact Lens Computer: Like Google Glass, without the Glasses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 16:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Madoff: Dont let Wall Street scam you, like I did </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-06 18:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House Defends NSA Collection Of Phone Records </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-06 16:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Endlessly shared on social media and replicated as a cartoon on posters and stickers, the image of the woman in red has become the leitmotif for female protesters during demonstrations in Istanbul. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 19:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Turkey is Rebelling by Sebnem Kalemli-Ozcan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 18:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HTC One Android 4.2.2 update reportedly coming mid-June, we go hands-on with leaked version | MobileSyrup.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 12:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Corporations Hijacked the First Amendment to Evade Regulation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-03 22:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Scalia Writes A Scathing Dissent Opposing Forced DNA Collection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-03 18:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TOM BROKAW: It's 'Tough To See' How Eric Holder Keeps His Job Amid Justice Department Scandals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-03 16:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hit her, I dare you [media campaign in Saudi Arabia to stop violence against women] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 21:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Digital Foundry examines Xbox One cloud computation claims | Joystiq </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 02:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is rape legitimate if she dresses provocatively? One author argues yes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 21:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To Catch Up, HTC One Needs Galaxy Lessons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 20:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the government helping speculators manipulate grain futures? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 18:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: No fee to play used Xbox One games, Skype powers voice chat | Joystiq </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-25 04:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its not all bad news: HTC One sales hit 5 million so far </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 14:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
