<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5448</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 00:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Todd I guessed it! I cried so hard when I actually heard it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 23:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wanted to do a story, but I never end up actually doing it. I'll have to try that soon!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 22:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I feel like I'm never able to do exactly what I want. Most lucid dreams I have are random and unexpected </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite thing to do when Lucid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 19:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Lucid Dreamers! My question for you is what is your favorite activity to do when Lucid? If you have not been Lucid what is the first thing on your to do list in a Lucid Dream? Flying is still my favorite! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 21:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figured out every time I watch tv or listen to music before I go to bed really messes with my dream recall. It's best for me to just go to sleep in a quiet environment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 21:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like he's seen so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 21:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a T.A.R.D.I.S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 19:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The WILD technique is where you go to bed wake up after 4-6 hours of sleep, stay awake for like 10 min to an hour (I think an hour is way too long) then get back in your bed, make sure your body is all relaxed. The trick to this is you want to trick your body into falling asleep and your brain remain active. Unfortunately during this technique you might run into sleep paralysis, but you just have to take that with a grain of salt. Once your body is asleep you will start seeing thing, shapes, colors, soon you'll start seeing faces then full on scenes. Don't focus too much on any of that because you will lose all you're trying to achieve. You may even hear some things.One big thing is that you cannot get too excited. You will ruin all of it. There are some good apps/ youtube videos on taking you through the process of relaxing your body and the steps after that. Sorry I wrote this pretty fast, if you have any questions or want other tips just let me know! Happy Lucid Dreaming! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-25 18:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow! That was FANTASTIC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
