<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6818</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Barak Hussein Obama passed a bill during 9/11 in support of same sex vaccinations. The bill, called prop 420, showed that vaccinations could in fact prevent jet fuel from melting steel beams. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 23:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Blart. Upvote this so that way when people Google search Paul Blart, this picture of Paul Blart shows up instead. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 22:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL during the filming of an episode of King of Queens, Kevin James was saved from a robbery. Who was the man to save him? None other than Paul Blart (world renowned mall cop) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 16:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> === number of blacks Paul Blart has not wrongly shot. Body cam footage in comments. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 16:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you are really what you eat, would that make cannibalism socially acceptable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 10:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Don't riots like Ferguson and Baltimore perpetuate stereotypes and racism from violence and fear caused by rioters? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 10:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DID YOU PRESS LE ORANGE BUTTON? XD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If this gets 3000 upblarts, I will force the mods to change the sub to a Paul Blart theme. Ayyyy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What is America's interest in the Russian-Ukrainian conflict? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 11:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by watching Paul Blart: Mall Cop without lotion or tissues. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 11:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Paul Blart: Mall Cop was actually a documentary based on incredible events of a man who believed in serving up justice. That man's name? Gabe Newell. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 11:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> === amount of weight Paul Blart's segway can hold </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 10:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that scientists of Reddit have found a new element that is responsible for overgrowth of hair on the neck. That elements symbol? [Le]. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 03:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL before Reddit, [DELETED] WAS JUST [DETED]. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 02:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AMA Request] Floyd "Money" Mayweather </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 04:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. How is training for a fight with Manny Pacquiao shown to be different then your other fights?

2.  Do you *honestly* plan on retiring at 49-0? Any chance for 50-0?

3.  Who was your toughest opponent to date? 

4. Was there ever a time where you were actually afraid that your opponent may be to much to handle? 

5. Do you think Paquiao lost to Bradley in their first fight? 

Twitter- https://mobile.twitter.com/floydmayweather

Facebook -  https://m.facebook.com/floydmayweather?_rdr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Deleted] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 01:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Circlejerk backward is krejelcric, which is German for Fuck the Mods which was actually used by the Nazi party during 9/11. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 00:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL fuck the mods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 23:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL fuck valve </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 23:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL fuck steam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 23:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the Kardashians added another annoying female to their shitty reality show. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 23:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attendees of UCSC... What is one thing you anticipated college being like but we're disappointed in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 04:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> \_O_(   )_O_/ Lenny has been taking vaccines to make huge gains. Help him increase his gains by pressing the orange arrow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 21:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (_).    '\\=(   )=//''    (_) OH NO! Lenny has entered the matrix again. Help him unplug by pressing the orange arrow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 20:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (_) (   )___ OH NO!!! The NSA are trying to kill lenny while he's walking Comcast! Press the updong so Lenny can leak NSA info! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 18:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dinner with the most interesting man. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 08:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NBA top 10 dunks: Kings got two of them!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 19:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What stereotypes do you feel are true? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 19:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *twiddles thumbs* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is going to beat Garcia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 10:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many karma points did it/will it take you to feel satisfied? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 12:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you are a transfer or freshman, when do you get to apply for housing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 02:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What should all bars have in them to make them optimal for entertainment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 08:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have won the same amount of Oscars as Leonardo Dicaprio. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 20:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This morning.. I woke up dead. What do I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 09:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drew Carey in the Marines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 08:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Definition of genius. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 22:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do the US and Russia have such bad relations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 21:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In history,  they never had direct contact to my knowledge. They fought together in the World Wars.  Why did our relationships go sour?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1ST SUB TO BURN! /r/Occasionallyoccupied </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 06:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by losing my patience while driving. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 00:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This actually happened last year and I can't forget it. I was driving my car to get some food when I hit a stop sign right by the place I wanted to eat. Crossing the street was a man in his mid 20s. He was moving rather slow but he was already to far in front of my car for me to beat him. As he got in front of my car,  he stopped and started looking around slightly but has his head down like he was looking for something. I was patient for about a minute when I came to the conclusion that he must be messing with me. Wrong conclusion.  I decided to honk my horn which startled the man terribly.  The look on his face is burned into my memory.  It was at this moment I realized that this man was mentally handicapped. He was absolutely terrified and ran away!  I felt horrible. I feel horrible.  To this day I remember this story anytime I get frustrated on the road. 


Be patient on the road. It's not worth hurting yourself or others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by having no friends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 18:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I purchased Battleship.  You need two people...  Story of my life.




Edit: lol the PM are ridiculous.  You guys are a friendly community!  I kinda meant that no friends available to play...  Hahaha it just hit me that many of you thought I meant absolutely no friends!!  Hah but you guys are super awesome!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After my wife left me, I was told there was a ton of other fish in the sea. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 23:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It made sense.  Now I'm a ichthyophile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What is the difference between ISIS, Hezzbollah, Al-Shabaab, Hamas, Boko Haram, Al-queda and why aren't they allies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 07:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is there no pacman-mayweather 24/7? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 02:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In our understanding of intelligence, are we bound with the upper and lower levels of our intelligence at birth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 23:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have read alot of books in reference to Buddhism and Dharma but what are the original texts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 20:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the texts I should be studying and knowing that will increase my knowledge and help on my path.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Thomas still off the bench? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 06:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long shot... But what about Kaminsky? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 05:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alot of players fall in the draft and still end up being great players others may have gotten.  He is a tall shooter with Dirk potential. His defense isn't horrendous and may spread the floor for Cousins. Being 6'11 and a PF can't hurt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, how was your day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 02:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does your username mean? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 21:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who remembers this guy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 05:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In this article, Arco Arena was ranked 14th out of all the arenas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 05:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Always make the smarter choice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 01:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was with this girl for about 2 1/2 years.  Hot girl and really good natured.  VERY TRUSTWORTHY.  I was the flirt.  I was this I was that.  She was just a church girl.  University comes along and girl starts acting different.  I notice she was socializing with some of her coworkers. Told her I wasn't comfortable with it and she said I was over-reacting. I decided 30 different girls is better than 1 girl who is going to play you.  I broke it off, played around and landed a smoking hot girl. 

As for her?  She has been seeing the guy she was "talking"  to for a little while now. Make the right choice.  Not the beta choice.  No pussy is worth losing your cool over...  Ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by not accepting that I don't know short cuts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 07:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my Gf and I decided to take a spring break trip to go hiking in California about 2 hrs from where I live. We carefully plan the trip as we will leave at 10ish and be there about 12. 
 
So we are driving up to the forest when she tells she wants to check out this small town she used to go to. (check out trinkets and such I guess idk...) I agree and I Google map it.  About 40 min away..  But then I see a couple small roads that look like they cut angles and time off.  And obviously Google maps has no idea WTF it's talking about Ima do *my* shortcut.  Well...  It took us 20 min in and was a dead end... Drive back and go original way.  Gf rolls her eyes pretty hard. 

We leave her trinket town and leave to the forest.  Once again we map it and I see another "brilliant" short cut. She does her half assed attempt to convince me other wise but I was sure it was better. We ended up lost for and hour and a half to only end up 25 min from where we took my shortcut. We proceed with the original plan.. 

The last one was while in the forest. We were a good hour into the trail when we deviated off the trail to see some site seeing. Well to get back we decided to go a different way then our original...  It is a loop.  Wrong...  We ended up wasting and hour and a ton of energy/sunlight. We went the original way and just arrived home.  She is pretty pissed off and asked if she can keep her jewelry where I am supposed to keep my brain... 

TL;DR Went on hike.  Got lost driving.  Got lost again.  Got lost during hike.  Gf thinks I'm an idiot.  I think I'm an idiot. 

On mobile. Sorry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any relation in Buddhism with Vinshu, Krishna, or Ganesha? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 05:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen a lot of references to these names and would like some accurate info to the relevance of them in Buddhism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kendrick Lamar let's kid on stage to perform his song and kid steals the show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 09:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favorite drinking games that aren't well known or that you made? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 22:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that a single vaccine has been proven to fight against Comcastinoma, a type of aggressive cancer that is literally Hitler, in over 420 trials. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 23:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top of the morning to ya! I am Shamus the Reddit Leprechaun. I have a neckbeard and fedora and I have come for le gold! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 18:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So Will Ferrell played for the Kings in an NBA owned celebrity league? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 08:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This guy made front page on reddit. This is a video I found on his page. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 07:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any good Buddhist/meditation places? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 01:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is Philosophy at SC? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 01:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is the overall department?  Professors?  Are there preferable professors or avoidable prof? 


Are there philosophy meet ups?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the best all star game roster ever? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 06:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I accepted my admission... How do I proceed with housing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 03:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the Peace Symbol was actually a logo for a British Nuclear Disarmament campaign. It was later popularized by Picasso and adopted by the hippies for peace. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 00:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think I scratch the frontal lobe on my third eye... Forgot to wax my tentacles before rubbing my eye. Now it is hard to think. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 21:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am having an identity crisis!!! I went back in time and impregnated myself and gave birth to a carbon copy of myself... Which is the real me!? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 19:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2327 ad,  male insemination became possible and 2329 ad,  rebirth in of self became possible...  We didn't think of the ramifications!!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your cringiest interaction with someone of the opposite sex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 18:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I see your Ali brag and raise you Tyson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 23:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm God and I just realized I'm an atheist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 22:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the transfer village worth the money? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 17:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems pretty steep. About 1400 is alot more a month then I pay now for rent,  car and insurance...  Alot more.  Is it better if I rent a room off campus?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SOLVE THIS ANAGRAM: oCmcast si iLterally iHtler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 07:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some words that you are able to rearrange every combination of letters into words? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 05:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something you regret doing that seems so small to others but you just can't forgive yourself for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 09:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL fuck you guys.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 11:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by losing my Mom's gold necklace that she got for her anniversary. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 22:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Well this is unfortunate to say the least.. It all happened when my mom asked me if I could take her necklace to the jewelers to have it cleaned. First of all,  I didn't know you could clean gold so I laughed.  She explained that they do and how important her necklace is. I guess my father bought it for her years ago before he passed away.  It was a gold necklace with a beautiful gem in the front.  
She wore it a lot and explained it needed some TLC. Fast forward to the drive to the jewelry shop. I decided to stop for some food.  Got my McDonald's and threw the trash in the bag and threw the bag away.  I arrive at the store and that's when I realize I can't find the necklace.  I search everywhere in the car but I can't find it. It occurs to me that it may have fallen into the McDonald's bag when I threw it away.  I drive back to the McDonald's to find the bag right next to the trash bin. Empty.  I lost my mom's necklace that she loved dearly...  I can't see her heart break again or it will destroy me.. So I have decided to make her a new necklace just like the last one.  I have the mold for the necklace and even the gem...  NOW ALL I NEEDS IS SOME GOLD!?!?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Growing my first Neck beard... Where should I grow it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 02:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I see alot of art with Buddha having a bindi looking forehead decoration.. Is that an accurate Buddhist depiction? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 08:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If so what is its significance and why does Buddha have it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where did Charlie Leduff go? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 07:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favorite survival tips that you think everyone should know? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 10:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:        .... never mind I just finished. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 23:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why aren't we affected in America by mosquito's like they are South of the equator? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 22:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why isn't malaria a huge issue in America like it is in other continents?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Future generations will look back at how many people died from cancer like we do at those who died from pneumonia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 09:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>    This dank donger is high. Press the up arrow to make him higher. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 05:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> \_o_(   )_o_/ This little guys has been lifting to make gains to hold up these other posts above him. Press the up arrow to feed him dank meme for strength. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 07:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was wondering why Katie Farrington wasn't at the winter X games.. So sad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 00:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Caught myself rooting for this girl in Sochi.. Still pretty incredible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 21:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who would be on the Mount Rushmore of music? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 07:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on ability,  style,  cultural impact/influence, sales,  hits,  longevity etc.  

Who is the greatest of great? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study on probability shows your SSN is the best group of numbers to use for the lottery. What are your numbers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 05:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that twins can have different skin pigmentation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 05:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These two girls are twins... Though they have different skin pigmentation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 05:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Kobe retires what number will be eventually retired..? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 03:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8, 24 or perhaps both...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doctors find a new way to build finger strength. Click the orange arrow to figure out how! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 05:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit Donations is over and the winning charity is... THIS POST! Donate orange arrows to the left please </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 02:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit announces fifth world charity winner! It is this post! Please make sure to donate 1 orange arrow to the left. WE DID IT REDDIT! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 00:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm literally the last person on earth... And there was just a knock on my door! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 19:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mormon Taylor Swift parody... (X-post /r/videos) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 08:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Had sex with myself for the first time and just found out I'm pregnant but I don't know who the father is... HELP! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 07:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We can't figure it out?!?! Is it black or white??? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 07:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this dress blue or white? Bill Clinton is freaking out right now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 06:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ruby's 48 point game.. Best 2 man combo last night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 19:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who are the most overrated and worst musicians out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 16:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MODS ARE ASLEEP, POST PICTURES OF COCKS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 09:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SHOWERTHOUGHT: Wouldn't Circlejerk really be a circlejerk if we posted actual productive posts? Am gril BTW :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 08:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the plural version of goose pronounced Geese... Why isn't plural moose called Meese? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 04:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Reddit spelled backwards is tidder which is Polish for m'lady </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 23:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I asked a wise man about the secrets to success.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 10:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He explained "There are two things in the world that you need to know to be successful.  The first is never tell anyone everything you know"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> REDDIT IS ACTUALLY TRENDING! I CAN BELIEVE THIS!!! WE DANKED IT REDDIT!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 09:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IF I GET 3000 UPSHREKZ, THEN I WILL STOP SUBMITTING SHITTY CONTENT TO THIS THREAD! I NEEDS THIS YOU GUYS! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 09:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [M] 23 Looking for some good tips or websites/YouTube channels. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 02:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a guitarist looking to get better at my vocals.  I'm improving but still far away from where I should be.  Is there any site or tube channel worth watching? 

What are good tips to drastically improve my voice?  I greatly appreciate your tips!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unoriginal Idiots. If you vote this up it will show up on Google images when people search Unoriginal Idiots or shitty websites. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 01:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (   ) ___ @" Don't mind me just taking Gary for a walk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 01:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Father has three daughters.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 11:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daughter 1: Dad,  why did you name me Rose? 

Dad: Because sweetie,  a Rose petal fell on your head when you were born. 

Daughter 2: Dad,  why did you name me Lily? 

Dad: Because sweetie,  a Lily petal fell on your head when you were born. 

Daughter 3: hghghdnbgh!!? dnbgh!??!  nfhriirb!!? Jfjebdjhcb!!??! 

Dad: SHUT THE FUCK UP CINDERBLOCK!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I use the Internet to boost my confidence.. AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 20:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With all the D-league signings and 10 day contracts... It bothers me we let Heslip go. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 20:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know why we didn't give him a chance but we gave so many other a chance...  It's hard for me to accept he is worse than Nik.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL before Reddit, Hitler was just Hitr [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 19:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SESSIONS IS GONE UPVOTE PARTY!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 18:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unbelievable crystal sculptures, 2014 (X-post upliftingnews) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 08:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Each tree in this row is a different color </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 03:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE say good riddance to Dragic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 22:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a Kings fan and we are in talks of possibly acquiring Goran.. This upsets me especially with how he is handling your team.  He is upset his brother isn't getting minutes? Upset they signed Thomas? Wants a max deal?  All of this is absurd for a good (not great) player...  


They only got Thomas as insurance and 6th man potential but sounds like he took that personally.  Now your team is going to piss off Thomas by trying to shovel him off in delusional hopes of keeping Dragic... I say trade him and focus on the future.  Good luck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we have a Kings trade rumor thread stickied </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 21:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Made this video in 10 minutes just cause. If I get 2000 up Shrek's for this video the I will personally kill Hitler. [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 21:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://youtu.be/A1a5QQoHh60 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL before Shrekkit, ISIS decided that Shrek is love and life. Butt sex = caliphate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 20:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They should make a lock button on phones so when you show a picture you can't swipe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 05:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cousins responds to Charles Barkley's comments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 01:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by thinking /r/circlejerk was a a porn thread... 10/10 would cum again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 10:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today may be the day something happens which changes the course of my life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 21:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by buying cookies from a 7 story girl scout from the Paleozoic era... She wanted 3.50 but I only had 4.20. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 08:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now that it is semi-official... We need to be realistic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 19:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> @========8 number of STD's I have contracted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 07:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just found the stupidest redditor (not sure if repost) [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 19:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Look at this dipshit](/u/train_subject6818)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a liberal I'm a liberal I'm a liberal I'm a liberal I'm a liberal I'm a liberal I'm a liberal I'm a liberal I'm a liberal I'm a liberal I'm a liberal I'm a liberal I'm a liberal I'm a liberal I'm a liberal I'm a liberal I'm a liberal I'm a liberal I'm a liberal I'm a liberal I'm a liberal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 10:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If boy scouts sold circle jerky, I'd buy that. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 17:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every year I buy a Kings autographed Jersey for charity... Three years looking I finally landed the one I wanted for CHEAP! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 07:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is Cousins I bought last year](http://m.imgur.com/IQfAmih) 

[This is my new one...  Of IT22!](http://imgur.com/63VQyLw) 

Been a long time collector of autographs and this one's my favorite yet!  (MJ is by default but let's pretend)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why didn't we sign Marshawn Brooks after this summer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 04:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought he played well and can definitely help play 2 3 stretch.  Fastbreak player with multiple facets on offense...  Does anybody know? 

Edited: *Marshon* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a redditor falls in the forest, does he tip his fedora? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 10:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> M'lady  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>      </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 05:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am having a hard time understanding this... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 04:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wrap my head around the fact that Cousins agent doesn't like Karl so we can't get him..?  Thank makes no sense to me.  Beef about Karl's son is just ridiculous. Cousins isn't going to come out looking good if we can't close this because his agent isn't gonna get the publicity...  Cousins will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did reality shows like Honey boo-boo catch on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 01:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did these shows come from?  How come honey boo-boo doesn't get shut down with the filth it portrays?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by having Intercourse with my dog. \_()_/ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 01:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (   ) ____(   ) ____ Don't mind me. Just taking every post today for a walk. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 00:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] [NSFW] How much nip does a M'LADY flip when a dapper neckbeard tips his shit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 23:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [DELETED]  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chili's is set to allow servers to wear fedoras starting in March. In the event a customer does not leave a tip, the fedora will tip itself. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 21:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> M'lady </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit should be Readit since half the posts are reposts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 08:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL if your rearrange the letters in ISIS it spells Comcast. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 06:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does you So's family do that you just find odd? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 05:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study shows that Circlejerk loves reverse Psychology. Study shows that when exposed to this, they down vote. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 04:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
