<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8834</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 01:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe not the best, but my favorite. Frostfire - SOCOM 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 22:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  NSFW - fap material

It is called NSFW for that specific reason. Perhaps you should create a new tag called SFF (Safe for Fapping)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 22:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might be off topic, but sometimes it is what someone doesn't say that hurts the most. For example, when someone that you care about a lot (and has told you that the feelings are mutual) hurts you in a way that you would not expect from them, a lot of times a simple recognition of the fact that they fucked up would be enough for closure. The lack of this can lead you to question everything leading up to this point, and whether they ever cared about to at all (or enough to avoid hurting your feelings). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 22:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am on reddit at work for the same reason that you are on reddit at school/home/etc: if I have time to browse the internet, I am going to go to whatever sites I want to, provided they are appropriate (hence NSFW tags).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 21:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people need to realize that NSFW doesn't mean things that can't be shown on cable TV. Many companies do not mind if there employees browse the web from time to time, but they do not want them looking at camel toe and side boob.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 02:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Half-Life 3 confirmed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Can't Print! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 00:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a lady come in today complaining that she was unable to print to the network printer down the hall from her office, so I went down to her office to see what the problem was. When I asked her to try again with myself present, she began spamming the "Paste" button over and over again saying, "See? Nothings happening!". Once I moved her mouse over to File - Print (effectively showing her how to print) she then proceeded to print out the same one page 40 times due to the fact that the kept hitting the paste button instead of print.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 21:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad you're not Catholic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 21:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The entire game is set in a post-apocalyptic world that has been taken over by machines. Also, the ending.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 17:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enslaved: Odyssey to the West. More people need to play this game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 16:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for reminding me of how awesome this game was. Easily the best RPG of the DC/PS2/GC era.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-01 15:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mean Dredd? Props if you do; that movie is fucking awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 21:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1.) Aside from your more well known movies, what is one film that you thought should have gotten more attention, or didn't do as well in the box office as it should have?

2.) Tupac or Biggie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-26 16:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shipping is ridiculous. Shirt.woot.com is having the same deal with free shipping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-21 20:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend was driving coming home from wedding reception. Lost control of truck around bend, clipped a telephone pole (went right through the side of it) and smacked into a tree doing roughly 50-60 MPH. I did not have a seatbelt on and all I can remember thinking was, "Please don't die." 

Ended up smashing my face off of the windshield and messing up my arm but overall made it through relatively unharmed. Helped put a lot of things in perspective.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 20:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't be the only person that thought you were a dude in the first picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-13 18:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> saving </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-09 01:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I was supposed to be enjoying the pictures, but I couldn't take my eyes off of that soul patch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-04 18:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have ran quite a few times, mostly for harmless stuff, but the best was when hid under a fake Christmas tree in my friends basement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-21 21:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black Ops. Even though I still play MW3 to this day, I can't get past the shitty matchmaking and continual lag comp issues. If this isn't fixed for BO2, I will probably wright off the CoD franchise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If They Only Knew... (Reviews for Unbreakable) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-11 03:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-10 23:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if it's Rockband. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-09 18:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Klein is small if I am not mistaken </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-03 05:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it boils down to the fact that whether or not it disappoints you, **there is** a lack of endgame content to keep some people playing. Now for some people, this is not a problem as they will make new characters and enjoy exploring the world. For others, who like to continue to progress their character after they hit the level cap (whether through new rewards or just more content) GW2 will likely grow stale for them shortly after reaching max level. 

Speaking for myself, I will most likely play a little PvP and WvW until I get bored and then stop. While GW2 doesn't have mechanics in the game that keep myself and many others coming back for more, I still had a lot of fun playing the game and think it was worth the $60 I spent. 

If I could pick one thing that ANet should do in order to retain players, I think it would be to release new content or update zones based on player level ranges in an attempt to keep things fresh for people who have finished the game. Maybe have a few NPCs that will dole out weekly quests that are basically events that continue to fill out the world, while not necessarily putting a carrot on a stick. I don't think it would be that much to ask to reskin a few baddies, and put together 3-quest dynamic event or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-27 21:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I can say is...wow. That is basically impossible to get, unless you spend a shit ton of money on gems and gold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 20:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strike that last comment then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-12 20:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lag compensation. After putting a lot of my time into MW and MW2, MW3 was unplayable for the first 6 months I owned the game. I just recently started playing again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-12 04:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But relationships like that do exist in nature. The pilot fish and shark is one example, and the Goby fish and shrimp is another. Also, I think you underestimate the relationship between humans and animals, considering in most cases we do feed them and provide shelter.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-12 04:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand what you are trying to say, but there are already quite a few examples of animals in the wild that rely on other species for survival. What makes dogs evolution any different than that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-12 01:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just send invite if you want to play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone up for some MW3? (XBOX 360) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-11 23:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone willing to hop on and play some CoD with someone who doesn't have any map packs? Used to play all the time during MW/MW2 but haven't gotten the itch until recently. 

GT: CenTz01 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-30 17:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Normally I would say to boost score since it's Kill Confirmed, but it looks like he doesn't have any points either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-28 20:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Spoiler](#s "Especially that episode about the Doctor's Daugher....wait. ") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 19:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't help but think the reason there is a crate at Tali's feet is because the artist could not draw her lower legs properly. 
 
Edit: I understand this isn't the reason. Just saying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 18:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get what you pay for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 17:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. I don't think enough people will notice to care. To me, they look pretty stylish for being video game themed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-26 15:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may be a cheap-ass but am I the only one who thinks $18 + SH is a tad too much for a coffee mug? Don't get me wrong because I would use the shit out of this if I had one, but that's just too damn much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-25 15:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the first time I have thought of it like this. If it plays out either way you described, I'll be one very happy reader.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-23 06:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just put my thoughts into a coherent statement. Actually, after watching this movie, it made me appreciate Batman Begins and The Dark Knight more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-21 03:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few things that I will admit to doing:

* Putting innards of broken 360 into new 360 and returning to *******.
* Amazon Prime Student for free. Graduated from college 3 years ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-20 17:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let Me In was actually a pretty damn good movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-20 17:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched Grey's Anatomy. More than once.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-20 15:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1900 x 1200? Please? Pretty please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-20 15:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have they fixed the netcode yet? Just curious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-19 17:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just figured I'd put this up here as most of the members of this sub-reddit are fans of Sean Bean. Was pleasantly surprised by how much I liked this movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
