<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6084</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Army researchers develop pocket-sized aerial surveillance device. It can, for example, give Soldiers the ability to see around the corner or into the next room during combat missions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 21:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 19:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The used Burger Shot bag ties it all together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 23:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Love is a Holy War!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in the 1980s the Naval Investigative Service undertook a massive and futile search for a woman named "Dorothy" in the Chicago area, after hearing gay men refer to themselves as "friends of Dorothy". They believed she was at the center of a ring of gay military personnel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 21:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 20:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to see the movie about this one day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dark matter could be detected by looking for time glitches in the existing network of GPS satellites. One researcher is already mining 15 years' worth of GPS timing data for its signature. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 20:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 19:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Destruction magic's fine, just don't go burning down any buildings." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 19:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Better still, hire a submarine.](http://d1jqu7g1y74ds1.cloudfront.net/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/halley-newspaper-clip-475x580.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 18:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I look forward to an "obesity mod" where you see a beer gut instead and can't run more than a few seconds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 22:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *South Korea. Best Korea has a 100% voter turnout every time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 22:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Mapping the unconscious maintenance of a lost first language.](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2014/11/12/1409411111) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first language that a baby hears leaves a pattern in the unconscious brain that remains even if the child completely stops using the language, such as in cases of international adoption, a brain imaging study shows. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 22:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 13:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there anything said or shown in the video that gives an indication of when it was filmed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wikipedia page views can predict disease outbreaks nearly a month before official health advice, a team of US scientists says. Their technique allowed them to predict emerging flu, dengue fever and TB outbreaks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 19:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 21:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Canusa Street.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Canusa_Street)

CAN USA. Cute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists Make Hilarious Proofreading Error. "Should we cite the crappy Gabor paper here?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 20:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mosquitos evolved to specialize on human prey. They show a stronger affinity for human scents than their "forest" ancestors, due to changes in 14 genes and one olfactory receptor in particular. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 19:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 19:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, getting home from the night shift and coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 18:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the curious, this makes it the film with the most fucks ever. [There's a wiki page about this.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_films_that_most_frequently_use_the_word_%22fuck%22)

 A documentary called "Fuck" from 2005 about the word itself contains it 857 times, but I don't think that really counts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 18:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've got [Programming Languange Inventor or Serial Killler?](http://www.malevole.com/mv/misc/killerquiz/), someone needs to make a "Hipster or Jihadi?" website stat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Health and Retirement study indicates people wildly underestimate how long they will live. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 18:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secret to a long life is still a mystery: a search for genes associated with longevity in people over 110 years of age has drawn a blank. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 21:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 22:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same thing with Australia if you replace the US border with the ocean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 18:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everybody wins when this happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bald Uakari </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 17:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 23:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Newspaper article from the time:](http://news.google.com/newspapers?nid=2206 dat=19831124 id=ybslAAAAIBAJ sjid=IfMFAAAAIBAJ pg=2235,2463975)

 A nude, screaming dancer found trapped under a man's crushed body on a trick piano pinned against a nightclub ceiling was too drunk to remember how she got there, police said.

...

 The dead man's body provided 2 or 3 inches of cushion that kept the woman from being crushed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 22:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's right, it was a happy place. They had flowery meadows and rainbow skies, and rivers made of chocolate, where the children danced and laughed and played with gumdrop smiles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 22:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They thought about it once but nothing came of it: [Project Orion.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Project_Orion_%28nuclear_propulsion%29) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 22:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh. This *had* to be from Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the plastic chair is known as a "monobloc", and was invented in 1967. Since they cost only about $3 to produce they are ubiquitous around the world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 21:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seven Italian scientists who were found guilty of manslaughter after failing to warn of an earthquake have had their convictions overturned on appeal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 19:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why scientists think completely unclassifiable and undiscovered life forms exist. There may be a fourth domain of life on Earth undetectable by current techniques. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 16:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HIV: Genetic mutation leads to two men being 'spontaneously cured' of virus. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 18:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 22:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something I noticed: there's a little dig at the then Soviets:

 We don't hide our space program. We don't keep secrets and cover things up. We do it all up front and in public. That's the way freedom is, and we wouldn't change it for a minute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 20:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No matter what you think of Reagan, [the whole speech](http://www.historyplace.com/speeches/reagan-challenger.htm) is really something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that there is a massive "undergound river", or aquifer that runs about 4 kilometers below the Amazon river for 6000 kilometers, following roughly the Amazon river's flow. It eventually empties in the Atlantic Ocean deep below the surface. It was only discovered in 2011. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 05:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 18:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Metagenomics is going to increasingly turn up surprises such as this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scratching makes itches worse. It initally relieves itching by creating a minor pain, but the brain responds by releasing serotonin, which influences nerve cells and increases itchiness. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 18:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 16:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Thanks for this, though, Buzz!](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TZ0axpAwRso) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Projet Montreal is seeking your input on bus 105 overcrowding. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 20:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists grow miniature stomachs from stem cells, which could patch up ulcers one day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 19:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hagel orders quarantine for troops returning from West Africa. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 18:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DNA molecules can carry electric current, a team of researchers has demonstrated. This could lead to the development of DNA-based electronic circuits. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 17:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why you should always make important decisions on an empty stomach: Hungry people perform better on a psychological test based on gambling that is supposed to simulate real-life decision making </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 01:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 18:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The folks at /r/conspiracy discuss this [here.](http://www.reddit.com/r/conspiracy/comments/1y3frt/til_neos_passport_expired_on_091101_the_matrix/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 17:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You could at least change some of the words.](http://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/1s4lbr/til_that_there_is_a_biker_gang_from_arizona_who/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A virus once thought to only infect algea has been found in the human throat cavity. It also appears to affect the cognitive abilities of individuals carrying its DNA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 17:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that a self-filling water bottle is being developed that draws moisture from the air - up to three liters every hour. It works by mimicking the way a beetle survives in the African desert. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 16:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 05:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also had [a romantic relationship with a pigeon](http://claudiears.wordpress.com/2011/10/01/nikola-tesla-and-the-pigeon-love-story/), so, there's that. I assume the pigeon was fit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 03:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally agree but [this comes a close second.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rMMX8dkbXEU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that a study of film-goers heart rates shows that the "Here's Johnny!" scene from The Shining is the scariest moment in film. Over entire movies, "The Exorcist" is the scariest, sending pulses up by 25.9% on average. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 20:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 19:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [No it isn't.](http://www.reddit.com/r/reddit.com/comments/eozhj/til_slang_is_short_for_shortened_language/c19sfbp)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 255 Terabits/s: Researchers demonstrate record data transmission over new type of fiber. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 16:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 23:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of Brazilians are going to be **really** pissed off about this. Search the words "luto" or "vergonha" on twitter. I'm sure there will be another catchphrase of the night.

Edit: yes, there is a new hashtag, that was quick: #RIPBrasil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 21:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I want to apologize for inconveniencing you while trying to protect the lives of millions.

Very true. What this quarantine is doing is protecting the political lives of Governors Christie and Cuomo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 20:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would be right if this quarantine *was* "protecting people from a seriously lethal threat". It isn't. Ebola isn't transmissable until an infected person is gravely ill. We knew that before, and we know that now. The *only* two cases transmitted in the US were nurses who treated patient zero Duncan near death spewing infected fluid everywhere, while wearing ineffective PPE.

It was the pathetic initial response by the CDC in providing the Dallas hospital with adequate protection that was a "seriously lethal threat" to these nurses. Thankfully they have recovered. What's happening now is a fearful over-reaction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Touching receipts after using hand sanitizers can increase the absorption of BPA into the body by a factor of 100 or more. BPA has been linked to a number of health concerns. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 22:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 19:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The study being referenced is [here.](http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s00442-014-2995-6/fulltext.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plants can tell when theyre being eaten: Arabidopsis plants sense the vibrations of caterpillars as they eat their leaves, and in response secrete mustard oils to deter the predator. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 19:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 17:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it remains the single greatest movie about snakes on a plane in film history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Oz-endorsed diet pill study was bogus, researchers admit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 17:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 18:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps the Dallas Cowboys should switch to black for Ebola Awareness Month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Maine teacher who had recently visited Dallas to attend a conference has been placed on paid leave due to Ebola concerns raised by parents. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 21:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 18:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is comparable to the Dallas Cowboys' value of about $3.2 billion, and the Yankees' value of about $2.5 billion. Basketball and hockey teams are nowhere near as rich.

[The business of football](http://www.forbes.com/nfl-valuations/)

[The business of baseball](http://www.forbes.com/mlb-valuations/) etc...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Early career scientists trapped in 'perpetual adolescence'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 18:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 20:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It gets worse: [Second ebola nurse traveled on plane with low-grade fever.](http://www.wfaa.com/story/news/health/2014/10/15/second-dallas-hospital-worker-diagnosed-ebola/17290677/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 19:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what they should have done with Duncan when he was diagnosed. The Dallas hospital was *not* prepared for ebola - two infected nurses demonstrate that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Glass user treated for internet addiction. The patient appeared to suffer withdrawal symptoms when prevented from using Google Glass and dreamed he was wearing it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 18:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 23:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This article](http://jezebel.com/5899815/how-does-ovulation-affect-a-strippers-income-it-doesnt) explains how the study behind this "fact" may be flawed. The sample size was way too small:

 Two researchers at UNM in Albuquerque studied dancers for two months. They studied 18 dancers. In one club, in one city. For two cycles.

Evidently, a **lot** more field research needs to be done on this phenomenon, before it can be confirmed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astronomers have mapped the weather on a planet outside of the Solar System. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 23:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 20:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "TIFU by joining ISIS and getting knocked up by a Jihadi." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 20:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd take this story with a grain of salt. Here is the questionable source:

[Central European News](http://www.cen.at/)

Having said that, these stupid girls really *are* missing, and probably in ISIS land.

[Interpol link 1](http://www.interpol.int/notice/search/missing/2014-22367)

[Interpol link 2](http://www.interpol.int/notice/search/missing/2014-22373)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ebola Patient Needs $500,000 to Cover Medical Bills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 19:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Captive orcas who live with dolphins can imitate dolphin sounds. Orcas therefore join the list of species capable of vocal learning, which includes humans, birds, elephants, bats, seals and dolphins. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 18:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 18:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not an expert by any means, but I'm pretty sure that's not a shark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 21:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are links to the [two](http://www.sciencemag.org/content/346/6206/251.full) [papers](http://www.sciencemag.org/content/346/6206/256.full) published in Science today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists find lung cancer can lie hidden for 20 years. During this time, tumors will have developed down multiple evolutionary pathways, making it extremely hard for any one targeted medicine to have an effect. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 21:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
