<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9503</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Do Bosses Want Their Employees Salaries to Be Secret? | Ultimately, the big winner in this game of secrecy is the boss, who profits directly from the ignorance and pliability of workers who dont grasp their own economic situation. So theres a gap between whats fair and whats legal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 17:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heeere's Johnny: 'Access' and 'Ingratiation' in the McCutcheon Decision | Why did Chief Justice John Roberts not insert any smiley faces in his opinion in the case of McCutcheon v. Federal Election Commission. The friendly gloss he bestowed on bribery would have been enhanced by a smiley face. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 17:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Because America Needs an Electoral Left: Why Bernie Sanders Should Enter the Presidential Primaries | If Sanders runs, Americas left will move beyond the mere consolation of its philosophy and, at least for a time, become an actual, self-conscious part of electoral politics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 18:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sniffing the Ethical Rot in Wall Street's Culture | Jamie Dimon, boss of JPMorgan Chase had a really terrible year in 2013, forcing his shareholders to shell out some $22 billion in penalties. But that didn't stop Jamie from taking a 74 percent hike in bonus money this year -- a cool $18.5 million. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 20:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Generation of Med Students Wants a Truly Just Healthcare System for All | We have a dysfunctional health care system built around restricting access to care, rather than providing it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 20:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to be interesting - and why the best bits of life are more than 'interesting' | Even in the world of academia, most people aren't motivated by the truth. What they want, above all, is not to be bored. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 03:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought Money Could Buy an American Election? You Ain't Seen Nothin' Yet | There are lots of areas of American society that could do with more money: preschools, infrastructure, mental health clinics, homeless shelters. The one place it's not needed is in politics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 17:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Serious reading takes a hit from online scanning and skimming, researchers say | There are advantages to both ways of reading. There is potential for a bi-literate brain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 18:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oliver Sacks: The Mental Life of Plants and Worms, Among Others | It is fascinating to think of Darwin, Romanes, and other biologists of their time searching for mind, mental processes, intelligence, even consciousness in primitive animals like jellyfish, and even in protozoa. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 23:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Studies Confirm the Dehumanization of Black Children and the Preschool-to-Prison Pipeline | African-Americans have the deck stacked against them starting in early childhood through adulthood. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 19:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McCutcheon, and the Vicious Cycle of Concentrated Wealth and Political Power | By taking Citizens United one step further and effectively eviscerating campaign finance laws, the Court has issued an invitation to oligarchy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 19:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 04:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why stop at 3.5 million?  What if someone wants to give 35 million to a joint fundraising committee?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Supreme Courts Ideology: More Money, Less Voting | A country that expands the rights of the powerful to dominate the political process but does not protect fundament rights for all citizens doesnt sound much like a functioning democracy to me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 21:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 23:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Socialism does not require secret police.  Please get beyond the labels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can Liberals and Conservatives Come Together to Support Families? | Any time you win a great victory after years of bitter struggle, there is the temptation to pillage the lands of the conquered enemy. This is always a mistake.America isn't going to be healthy unless conservative America is healthy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 23:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 18:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ###Submission Statement
This is an amazing account of the lengths to which a repressive regime will go, recording events that the participants had forgotten. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the secret police tracked my childhood | There are records of dreams we recounted to each other in the mornings. The transcriber knew us so well, he or she was able to note our moods. It's like having had a one-sided relationship with these invisible broadcasters of our tormented souls. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 18:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So You Think You're Smarter Than A CIA Agent | How is it possible that a group of average citizens doing Google searches in their suburban town homes can outpredict members of the United States intelligence community with access to classified information? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 18:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Think They Can | Some of the states where the Moral Monday movement is rising are mighty steep political hills for progressives to climb, but success begins with someone saying, I think I can. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 17:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2-Year-Olds Convert Binary To Hexadecimals In Game Experiment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 17:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you smarter than a 2-year-old?  Check out this game -- [Flippy Bit](http://www.flippybitandtheattackofthehexadecimalsfrombase16.com/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2-Year-Olds Convert Binary To Hexadecimals In Game Experiment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 17:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Surprisingly Large Cost of Telling Small Lies | Telling lies is the No. 1 reason entrepreneurs fail. Not because telling lies makes you a bad person but because the act of lying plucks you from the present, preventing you from facing what is really going on in your world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 17:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 19:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Four Arguments That Scream "Save Public Education!" | 1. Equal Opportunity is an American Mandate. 2. Michelle Rhee Is Wrong. 3. The Classroom is Not a Warehouse. 4. Starve the Beast, Starve Society. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 19:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 02:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> George Soros became a naturalized US citizen in 1961, so billionaire, yes, but not foreign.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big data: are we making a big mistake? | Big data has arrived, but big insights have not. The challenge now is to solve new problems and gain new answers -- without making the same old statistical mistakes on a grander scale than ever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 02:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Shame of American Politics | It is increasingly difficult to exclude foreign money from US political donations. We not only come to be ruled by the billionaires, but even by foreign billionaires with foreign rather than American interests at heart. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 17:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> War Fever in the Air | In Ukraine and Crimea we are now seeing the results of overly aggressive Western geopolitics. Russia was woefully underestimated. A crisis between nuclear-armed powers should never have been allowed to occur. Its sheer madness. Like nuclear-armed children fighting over a toy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 17:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 06:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ###Submission Statement
This is a fascinating account of a man who is both arrogant and acutely aware of his limitations, who was late in becoming a surgeon and thought much of surgery was boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Life and death at his fingertips: watching a brain surgeon at work | Henry Marsh is one of UK's top neurosurgeons and a pioneer of neurosurgical advances in Ukraine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 06:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When the Government Outsources to Private Companies, Inequality Gets Worse | The benefits of this kind of private-public partnership largely accrue to contractors, while communities bears the costs of insufficient oversight and limited public control over the use taxpayer resources. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 17:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 18:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is my preference for saying 'for my wife and me' in contrast to the now near-universal 'for my wife and I' just a personal bugbear? And does wishing others would return to the older usage make me unbearably pompous? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 18:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  where no split infinitive has gone **to**

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Envy and Jealousy? Gag Me With a Silver Spoon | Problem is, the deeply rich talk about building the economy but do almost nothing about it. Theres a lot of take and a lot of keep, but not much giving back. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 17:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 22:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an eloquent and moving account of cognitive decline.  Her husband's response has its own wisdom: A table, a meat pie, a glass of wine, a hand to hold: What else does a man need to be happy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Dementia | A teacher describes losing her mind to dementia, as her mother did before her. One small miracle: Her ability to write stays with her. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 22:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Do We Let 80,000 Americans Suffer a 'Slow-Motion Torture of Burying Alive'? | Solitary confinements psychological effects are obvious enough. But you have to hear it from the prisoners to be truly horrified. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 19:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the NRA Is Blocking Obamas Surgeon General Nominee | What the NRA fears is having someone with a bully pulpit who has solid information and is giving people the facts. The NRA fears information. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 18:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 21:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many students in your
 4 bedroom 4 bathroom apartment 
?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starving College Students and the Shredded Social Contract | College students, of course, have long been broke, and plenty members of todays professional class nurture nostalgic memories of their ramen years. What were looking at here, though, isnt picturesque slumming-its serious poverty. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 18:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remembering Tony Benn and His Five Little Questions | If one meets a powerful person ask them five questions: What power have you got? Where did you get it from? In whose interests do you exercise it? To whom are you accountable? And how can we get rid of you?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 16:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Automatic Corporation | Corporations can be thought of as information-processing feedback loops. They propose products, bring them to market, learn from results, and adjust, while trying to maximize profit. So why cant corporations be completely automated -- replaced by algorithms? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 23:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mainstream US Media Is Lost in Ukraine | The real story of Ukraine is far more complex than the black-and-white caricature that the New York Times, the Washington Post and others are presenting. It is in the truthful grays that responsible policies are shaped and bloody miscalculations are avoided. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 18:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Untaxed Americans: The Speculators, Hustlers, and Freeloaders of Wall Street | The most dangerous product out there -- derivatives -- has a ZERO sales tax on it. The trading of high-frequency securities and derivatives and commodities is a quadrillion dollar industry without a sales tax. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 18:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Life as a Retail Worker: Nasty, Brutish, and Poor | After veteran reporter Joseph Williams lost his job, he found employment in a sporting-goods store. In a personal essay, he recalls his struggles with challenges millions of Americans return to day after day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 03:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-13 05:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hard to believe all the grief over not remembering or using the same strange word.  Just put the question and freshly generated answer (such as axv8o8V7X3Dh) in your password manager.  And if you don't use a password manager, then all bets are off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-13 03:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you RTFA?  Nothing in it supports Marxist policy.  Granted, the premise is a stretch -- by their criteria, we might as well say we're all Jewish Republican Christian Democrats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You are a Marxist - but don't worry | At this point in history, we should all be Marxists in the sense of agreeing with his diagnosis of our troubles. But we need to go out and find the cures that will really work. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 21:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wall Street Bonuses vs. the Minimum Wage | If the $26.7 billion Wall Streeters pulled in on their bonuses last year had instead gone to minimum wage workers, our economy would be expected to grow by about $32.3 billion - more than triple the $10.4 billion boost expected from the Wall Street bonuses. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 21:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The McCutcheon Decision Hangs in the Balance. So Does Our Democracy | McCutcheon is a play by the very wealthy to increase their influence, because they dont think Citizens United tipped the scales in their favor enough. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 19:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Society Is More Unequal Than Ever | A growing body of research shows that inequality damages the social fabric of the whole society. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-09 23:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to save the US | The solution to Americas problems is obvious - it should model itself on its military... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-08 06:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Great American Working Class U-Turn | Why didnt we share the gains from globalization and technological advances more broadly? Why didnt we invest them in superb schools, higher skills, a world-class infrastructure? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 17:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 18:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An inspiring story of the persistence of a man who lost his wife, mother and village, then regained them and more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How our 1,000-year-old math curriculum cheats America's kids | By hiding math's great masterpieces from students' view, we deny them the beauty of the subject. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 17:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5-Year-Olds Can Learn Calculu | Mathematics is fundamentally about patterns and structures, rather than little manipulations of numbers. Its akin to budding filmmakers learning first about costumes, lighting and other technical aspects, rather than about crafting meaningful stories. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 17:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seven Numbers that Add Up to a Death Tax for Retirement | It's not the tiny amount paid on multi-million dollar estates. Instead, it's the slow death of millions of baby boomers, the victims of 35 years of deregulated greed at the very top of our nation's mountain of wealth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 17:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suffering? Well, You Deserve It | There is not a free market solution to a peaceful decline. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 17:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Real Job Killers | Progress requires creating more jobs that pay well, are safe, sustain the environment, and provide a modicum of security. The real job killers in America are lousy jobs at lousy wages. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 04:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Release of Fed Transcripts Show Fed Scary Ignorant in 2008 | These transcripts should make readers furious that the FOMC were getting big paychecks for their work and will enjoy fat pensions in retirement. Unlike workers in Detroit and Chicago, they did mess up on their job, big-time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 19:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Myth Behind Public School Failure | The formula: Underfund schools. Overcrowd classrooms. Mandate standardized tests sold by private-sector firms that prove these schools are failures. Blame teachers and their unions for awful test scores. Push nonunion, profit-oriented charter schools. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 19:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inequality, Productivity, and WhatsApp | Unless we figure out how to bring productivity, corporate profits, jobs and wages back into line--or spread the gains more widelyour economy can't generate enough demand to sustain itself, and our society can't maintain enough cohesion to keep us together. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 18:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> True Free Market Proponents Should Support Private-Public Competition | If the private financial industry is more efficient than the government, then why do we have to force people to use it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 21:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 85 Billionaires and the Better Half | The world's richest 85 individuals do not have the same amount of accumulated wealth as the world's poorest 50 percent. They have vastly more. The multitude on the lower rungs--even taken as a totalithave next to nothing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 20:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There Is No Demand for Higher Education | The demand isnt for education, per se, its for what we believe education can provide: a secure, stable life...The social capital earned has greater influence on the lives that graduates will ultimately lead than the credential itself. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 05:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Privatization Perverts Education | 1. Charter Schools Have Not Improved Education. 2. The Profit Motive Perverts the Goals of Education. 3. Advanced Profit-Making: Higher Education. 4. Lower-Performing Children Left Behind. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 20:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When It Comes to Public Services, Government Knows Best | One city shifting 180 bus shelters back into public hands is a minor development with a one-day news life. But it reflects a much larger story, the growing reevaluation by governments of the efficacy of privatizing public services. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 20:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asphyxiating Education | An educational system that fails to revere children and honor their potential - that turns schools into 3R boot camps, demanding the regurgitation of specified data on command, but shrugs off the importance of simply learning to think for oneself - is insane at its core. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 19:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its 2.13: On Valentines Eve, Give Tipped Workers Some Love | $2.13 is the base wage at which tipped employees must be paid, implemented in 1991. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 19:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whose Distressed Baby Is It? | A grown man on a corporate conference call whining about the burden of other peoples babies is simultaneously the most un-American and distinctly American scene one can imagine. What are we risking as a country when we price a child that way? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 20:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Bill To Return Power To The People | In order to receive matching funds, politicians would have to spend more time trying to solicit donations from constituents, and less time courting the few wealthy donors that would invariably make demands of them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 18:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reinventing explanation | "I will focus on media to explain a single scientific idea, a result from statistics known as Simpson's paradox. If you've never heard of Simpson's paradox before, you're in for a treat." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 20:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Following Latest GCHQ Revelations, Who are the Real Criminals? | When we look at what Western governments are doing  snooping on our emails, infecting our computers, intercepting our phone communications -- we have to ask ourselves: who are the real criminals here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 19:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Media Blacks Out New Snowden Interview The Government Doesnt Want You To See | I gave all my information to the American public. If they see that as treason, I think people really need to consider who they think theyre working for. The public is supposed to be their boss, not their enemy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 06:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Dangerous Charade of Billionaire Victims | It is a cancerous corruption of markets, achieved by equally cancerous capture of political and regulatory systems. It is so brazen and uncontested its become normal. Perkins literally believes it is admirable. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 18:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> School ditches rules and loses bullies | "The great paradox of cotton-woolling children is it's more dangerous in the long-run." Society's obsession with protecting children ignores the benefits of risk-taking. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 22:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 19:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article:
 When we have politicians explaining a failure to make basic emergency preparations by saying they didnt want to be accused of harming commerce, the austerity mindset has taken hold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do believers believe THOSE silly things? | So the reason why (or if you prefer a pluralist approach, a major reason why) religions have these silly beliefs is that they serve to honestly signal identity. But this doesnt explain why they have _these_ silly beliefs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 21:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Populist Imperative | The deficit obsession that has exerted such a destructive effect on policy these past few years isnt really driven by worries about the federal debt. It is, instead, mainly an effort to use debt fears to scare and bully the nation into slashing social programs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 06:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three Myths on the World's Poor | Bill and Melinda Gates call foreign aid a phenomenal investment that's transforming the world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 16:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> America Is Still a Deeply Racist Country | The laws on the books claim otherwise, but in Hunts Point (and similar neighborhoods across the country), those laws seem like far away idyllic words that clash with the daily reality: everything is stacked against those who are born black or brown. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 16:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To Save a Generation from Despair, Its Not Enough to Hassle Them into Low-Paying Jobs | The most important political battles are fought on the territory of the imagination. Young and unemployed people need to know: you are more than your inability to find a job. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 18:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Biggest Myths in Economics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 05:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA Insiders Reveal What Went Wrong | By withholding information and exploiting secrecy, NSAs leaders past and present have pulled off an unparalleled coup in concealing the sad reality that NSA could have prevented 9/11 and didnt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 23:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Rise and Rise of Television Torture | Everywhere you see this prevalence of torture it promotes the lie that torture works. It does this very effectively. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 07:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Last Gasp of American Democracy | The moment a popular movement arisesand one will arise--that truly confronts our corporate masters, our venal system of total surveillance will be thrust into overdrive. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 18:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Retirement Theft in Four Despicable Steps | Federal Tax Avoidance is the Biggest Threat to Social Security. State Tax Avoidance Defunds Pensions. Corporations Play One Underfunded State Against Another. Banks Take a Big Chunk of Our Retirement Accounts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 18:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Millennials and Boomers Are On the Same Side of the Retirement Fight | The generational war is a hoax. In this global economy the fight for retirement security should unite us across barriers of age and race. A common agenda: for job creation, stronger Social Security, and economic equality. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 18:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could 2014 Be Year One of the Pay Ratio Era? | In the year ahead, nurses and college students just might jump-start the struggle against Americas chronic -- and growing  income inequality. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 17:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Year of the Great Redistribution | America has been redistributing upward for some time - after all, trickle-down economics turned out to be trickle up - but we outdid ourselves in 2013. At a time of record inequality and decreasing mobility, America conducted a Great Redistribution upward. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 17:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redistribute wealth? No, redistribute respect. | I want to move back toward a society where the hard work of an unskilled laborer is considered worthwhile in social interactions, regardless of how many dollars it brings home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-01 07:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders: 2014: Seize the Moment | It is simply not acceptable that the top 1 percent owns 38 percent of the financial wealth of the nation, while the bottom 60 percent owns all of 2.3 percent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 18:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We Pretend to Teach, They Pretend to Learn | The idea that students can obtain a serious education even with their disengaged, credentialist attitudes is a delusion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 22:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Corporate Free Speech Racket | In the past decade, both the U.S. Supreme Court and lower federal courts have begun, with increasing frequency, to strike down rules and sometimes entire laws, on the grounds that they infringe on companies First Amendment rights to free speech and expression. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 20:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We Are Two Nations | Congress refused to vote to extend unemployment benefits for 1.3 million Americans whose benefits will soon expire. There were some promises about getting something done in January, but these were idly tossed out the windows of the town cars making tracks for the airport. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 18:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 18:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some lights in my area turn green for just 3 or 4 seconds, and they're on main roads, even highways.  Isn't there a minimum? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former BP Geologist: Peak Oil Is Here and It Will 'Break Economies' | "We're like a cage of lab rats that have eaten all the cornflakes and discovered that you can eat the cardboard packets too." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 21:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Affluenza As Liars Paradox | It turns out this false belief is true. But obviously having a true belief is not going to keep you out of prison. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 06:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JPMorgan Chase   Penance   Fines | There is not a criminal anywhere in the world who would not happily accept a public recital of the crimes committed instead of entering a formal plea of guilty with the attendant risk of going to jail. A bit of embarrassment beats a bit of time in jail every time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 18:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yes, Making the Rich Poorer Would Make Everyone Else Richer | When corporate earnings are better distributed, it does improve things for workers down the income ladder. When huge fortunes at the top are more heavily taxed, it does pay for public goods. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 18:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Meaning of Decent Society | How can the economy be back on track when 95 percent of the economic gains since the recovery began in 2009 have gone to the richest 1 percent? The underlying issue is a moral one: What do we owe one another as members of the same society? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 18:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sexism and Tech and Love | I have watched my coworkers slave away for days on a project, to have someone in the marketing department say oh, its like magic! when theyre done. Its not magic. Its time, and devotion, a little chunk of their soul, and a very particular kind of love. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 20:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 20:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [AP Survey: US Income Gap Is Holding Back Economy](http://bigstory.ap.org/article/ap-survey-us-income-gap-holding-back-economy-0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Economists Agree: US Inequality Is Killing the Economy | 'The economic populists are right' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 18:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 05:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your responses seem to concentrate on technicalities whereas what speaks to me is the overwhelming race and class bias in the story. But then I'm no lawyer or paralegal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 00:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That didn't come out at all the way I meant and I'm really sorry about that.  I took your post and split it into 8 paragraphs, as I should have done first, and read it carefully.

What a moving account!  And the way you arranged your give-away at your wedding was brilliant and a gift to both men, yourself and all the guests.

And no way was your post too long.  Thank you for every word.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-15 01:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please learn to use paragraphs.  It will make what you say much more available.  A wall of text is so hard to read some of us are put off reading it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The American Way of Hiring Is Making Long-Term Unemployment Worse | The likelihood of an employer inviting a job seeker for an interview is much higher for an applicant with no relevant industry experience than for a job seeker who has relevant experience but is unemployed longer than 6 months. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 19:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The American Way of Hiring Is Making Long-Term Unemployment Worse | The likelihood of an employer inviting a job seeker for an interview is much higher for an applicant with no relevant industry experience than for a job seeker who has relevant experience but is unemployed longer than 6 months. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 18:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its Simple: Fewer Guns, Fewer Suicides | In a typical year, suicides outnumber homicides by 3 to 1 and a majority of suicides are by firearm. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 04:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 05:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sensitive account by a physician 'helping' a patient die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Art of Dying | Seven out of ten Americans wish to die at home, die the Good, the Valid, Death. Seven out of ten Americans die in institutions, intubated, infiltrated, invalidated. To want the dying to be over is not the same as wanting someone dead. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 05:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Raw Deal | The budget deal fails extend unemployment benefits for 1.3 million jobless. It contributes to the nations savage inequality. It contains no short-term stimulus, and does nothing about the long-term deficit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 18:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Moyers: The Great American Class War | We are this close -- this close! -- to losing our democracy to the mercenary class. So close its as if were leaning way over the rim of the Grand Canyon waiting for a swift kick in the pants. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 18:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scan of an old slide: Cherry blossom time in Kyoto [OC] [1443 x 970] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 23:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why it's Time to Occupy the State | Many Occupy protesters who took to the squares and streets now see electoral politics as the road to real change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 18:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 things the poor do every day | The bottom 20% of earners pay TWICE as much in taxes (as a share of their income) as do the top 1%. (Source: Institute on Taxation   Economic Policy, January 2013) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 05:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 20:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2013/12/experiments-to-do-with-your-baby/280592/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 18:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [](http://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2013/12/experiments-to-do-with-your-baby/280592/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Experiments to Do With Your Baby | Recreate real scientific scenarios. Stimulate two minds. The little ones are fascinating. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 18:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What You Need to Know About the International Test Scores | The myth persists that once our nation led the world on international tests, but we have fallen from that exalted position in recent years. Wrong. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 19:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Die, selfish gene, die | The selfish gene is one of the most successful science metaphors ever invented. Unfortunately, its wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 20:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Gove defends Scandinavian-inspired education reforms | The thing I saw in Shanghai and in Singapore was the quality of teacher development was so good. This is all basic stuff that happens in a lot of private sector companies. Its about treating teachers like high-class professionals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 20:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seeing the Toll, Schools Revise Zero Tolerance | Faced with mounting evidence that get-tough policies in schools are leading to arrest records, low academic achievement and high dropout rates that especially affect minority students... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 18:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats Good for Bill Gates Turns Out To Be Bad For Public Schools | Every current and former Microsoft employee I interviewed--every onecited stack ranking as the most destructive process inside of Microsoft, something that drove out untold numbers of employees. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-30 17:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Were Not Broke - Weve Been Robbed | One of the biggest common misunderstandings is that governments are like households, which need to tighten their spending when times are tough. Actually, governments and households work in opposite ways. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 17:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis Understands Economics Better Than Most Politicians | Inequality is the biggest economic issue of our time. It's only surprising it took so long for a globally prominent figure to say it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 16:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New York Times Uncovers Conservative Attacks and Then Prints One; Both Are on the Front Page | When progressives naively use conservatively reframed words, they help the conservative cause by strengthening the conservative value system in the brains of the public. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 19:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Empire Strikes Back: How Wall Street Has Turned Housing Into a Dangerous Get-Rich-Quick Scheme -- Again | Depending on whom you ask, the idea of bundling rental payments and selling them off to investors is either a natural evolution of the finance industry or a fire-breathing chimera. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 17:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scared to Death in the USA | Dont call this America a police state, not given what that came to mean in the previous century, nor a totalitarian state, given what that meant back then. The truth is that we have no appropriate name, label, or descriptive term for ourselves. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 19:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 20:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An obsessive eccentric's work contributes to an archive that has still unanticipated uses.  We might do well to cherish some kooky people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Incredible Story Of Marion Stokes, Who Single-Handedly Taped 35 Years of TV News | From 1977 To 2012, she recorded 140,000 VHS tapes worth of history. Now the Internet Archive has a plan to make them public and searchable. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 20:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Republican Tempest Over the Affordable Care Act Diverts Attention from Three Large Truths | The other day I heard a young man say why should I pay for the sick and the old? The answer is he has a responsibility to do so, as a member the same society they inhabit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 18:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why There Are No Women on Twitters Board, and So Few in Technology | The research shows that the fields that women avoid tend to be the most mathematically and spatially demanding and the fields they are attracted to tend to be the most people-oriented. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 18:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elizabeth Warren Comes Out for Expanding Social Security | I hold deep values, and I look at basic facts. We dont start the debate by deciding who gets kicked to the curb. We are Americans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 17:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nov. 18, 1872: Susan B. Anthony arrested for voting | She was tried and convicted seven months later in the Ontario County courthouse in Canandaigua. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 18:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nov. 18, 1872: Susan B. Anthony arrested for voting | She was tried and convicted seven months later in the Ontario County courthouse in Canandaigua. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 18:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Obamacare Disaster and the Poison of Party Loyalty | Obamacare is a mess largely because it builds a revamped healthcare system around the retrenched and extended power of insurance companies-setting back prospects for real healthcare reform for a decade or more. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 17:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Nutt's new drug mimics alcohol  minus the health risks and hangovers | And since it acts directly, it can also be immediately reversed by taking an antidote. Users could potentially be sober in a matter of minutes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 18:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 17:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Though these lessons are from a Ghanaian, I expect similar characterizations are available in many other small countries, especially in the global south. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Thought the US was the Land of Gold. Now I See It as Rude and Disrespectful | American foreign policy limits interactions with countries like Ghana. This leads to arrogant interactions and generalizations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 17:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American oubliette | Life without parole is an outrageous sentence for non-violent criminals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-16 20:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wall Street Isnt Worth It | A political strategy based on cutting the financial sector down to size has more promise for the Left than any alternative approach now on offer, and is a necessary precondition for a broader attempt to make the distribution of wealth and power more equal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-16 19:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "End Times for Obama": A Dangerous Conservative Myth | Everyone going their own way and doing their own thing, judging the value of any policy by the immediate fulfillment it gives individuals, has often been a winning narrative in American political life. Apparently it still is today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-16 18:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nadezhda Tolokonnikova of Pussy Riot's Prison Letters to Slavoj iek | Pussy Riot's Nadezhda Tolokonnikova is currently in a prison hospital in Siberia; here she and Slovenian philosopher Slavoj iek meet in an extraordinary exchange of letters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-16 17:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fight Like You're Right, Listen Like You're Wrong and Other Keys to Great Management | When you become successful is when you should be especially wary you're going to turn into an idiot. There's a lot of evidence to support that. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-16 05:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eternal Austerity Makes Complete Sense - If You're Rich | For David Cameron, cutting spending in a highly unequal society works because it doesn't affect those who matter to him. This used to be called class politics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 23:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Sleepwalking to Extinction': Capitalism and the Destruction of Life and Earth | Capitalism is, overwhelmingly, the main driver of planetary ecological collapse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 23:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obamacare's Problems Run Deeper Than Glitchy Website, Cancellation Notices | Its a health insurance industry that profits from complexity and confusion, and providers of medical devices and services who benefit excessively from the very weak cost controls inherent in our fragmented system. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 23:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
