<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1317</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 08:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NOS!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 08:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was the new Lifetime movie 'A Deadly Adoption' I guess the joke was that Ferrell   Wiig wanted to make a legit Lifetime movie and that it was supposed to be horrible on purpose. Welp. Mission Accomplished Dubya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yacht Rock just turned 10 years old and Rolling Stone did this great piece on it. Sail Away: The Oral History of 'Yacht Rock' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 23:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Week in America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 18:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 07:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have the same problem on my 2000 Tahoe (GMT400). Will look into the resistor. Was told to replace the entire control panel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 07:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Making Dennis his bitch on Always Sunny https://youtu.be/9Gnxf0_br44 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 18:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct. It appears that the historical significance of that day is one of the reasons the shooter picked that night and that church. I heard news mention the revolt being tied to that church and looked it up and found the date they stopped the revolt. After they foiled the plan, they hung Desey and a total of 33 conspirators. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 07:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luckily this YouTuber made a video and cleared up those muddy lyrics while he was at it: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oO6wPWFMrCA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: On June 17, 1822 All AME Churches in Charleston were burned to the ground to foil Denmark Vesey's Slave Revolt. Nearly 40 years before the Emancipation Proclamation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 07:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Country Classic Cars in Staunton, IL. Off I-55 North of St. Louis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
