<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4034</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A visualization of the more than 2800 beliefs submitted to the atheism ten commandment contest, along with the winning submissions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 20:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 16:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mediocre </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I present to you the perfect gift for a child to his/her parents. You're welcome. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 21:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have an extra tickets for Conor Oberst's Holiday Cheer concert in NYC tomorrow night. PM me if you're interested. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 23:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have two extra tickets for Conor Oberst's Holiday Cheer concert in NYC tomorrow night. PM me if you're interested. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 18:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 21:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Copyrighting so hard right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does South Park have to pay a fine every time they swear on the show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 18:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I listened to every episode of Serial this week, and then someone sent me this. I probably shouldn't laugh but it is BRILLIANT. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 23:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 19:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actual chills </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Mashable created a TL;DW (too long didn't watch) YouTube channel that profiles movie trilogies including Iron Man, The Matrix   Star Wars in two minutes or less. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 22:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $10,000 ReThink Prize Announced to Crowdsource Secular Alternatives to the Ten Commandments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 20:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 23:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fella with the beard is at work and asked me to respond. As a bit of back story, we all initially began our training with beards- it was kind of a gimmick for charity. He was admirably the only one who kept his throughout, and we actually shaved it off together about an hour after this picture was taken. But here's his response:  

"it definitely kept me warm on a relatively cold day. Disclaimer- Not advisable for use with summer training regimen in NYC and is generally incompatible with most models of girlfriend."

Anyway, thanks for the kudos!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 23:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! Who is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 22:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I think I'm still smiling now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 15:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The entire thing was memorable. Even the people who were miserable were smiling because of the crowds. The three of us ran the entire race together so we had a lot of support throughout, and we did about as well as we thought we would. If I had to pick one moment, it was coming off the Queensboro Bridge into Manhattan. The crowds, which were already massive in Brooklyn and Queens, were ENORMOUS in Manhattan. It was such a cool experience. Thanks for asking!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friends and I just ran our first marathon. Here's our before and after pics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 15:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm at an event at The New America Foundation called 'Will Amazon Lead to the Golden Age of Books?' What do you think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 00:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 20:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR, My twin brother added "I want to come on your hard tits" to my final paper in an AP history class. Teacher was a feminist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 20:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of my favorites:

Ill Bambino,
Sanfords,
Queen's Comfort,
Junkos,
Bartelino's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Obama's inner circle as loyal to Obama as Putin's is to Putin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 20:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been in Astoria for 2 years, looking for any restaurants I haven't tried yet. Blow my mind. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 17:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a new Cold War brewing over the energy market? Interesting video explains why. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 22:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 16:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two time reader here. The first reading wasn't so much difficult as it was disgusting. I've read some dark stuff, but this one got to me. It wasn't until the second read that I realized how amazingly intricate and beautiful the prose was. I actually sympathized with HH and thought of the book as some great story of love and loss. Every time I mention this I get weird looks, but it has become a favorite of mine. Keep at it. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
