<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9585</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patricks Westport Grill apologizes for receipt: FOX 2 received a photo from viewers angry about a receipt from Patricks Westport Grill where the customers are referred to as Black Couple. Management goes on to explain that the employee has been terminated. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: Despite making up roughly 1 in 12 Americans, blacks accounted for half of all homicides. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another backwards left-wing idiot reactionary afraid of change, efficiency, and competition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gawker and their whole network are garbage, especially Jezebel. Only Jalopnik, which is part of the Gawker network, is the exception to that rule. I automatically assume that anyone from my facebook friends list that likes Gawker's or Jezebel's facebook page or links to an article of theirs is an automatic left-wing idiot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to see you understand how every publication can be biased. Do you also apply such logic to Gawker, Jezebel, The Guardian and MSNBC or do you let them slide because their biases are also your biases.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 03:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This very true. What is interesting about this study is that nearly every SJW would fit this type of pattern of behavior as many of them are losers in life and often lash out as a result because someone that they don't like or are prejudiced against is getting ahead of them in life. Many women I have observed that exhibit this type of aggressive behavior also turned out to be losers in life. This study won't just apply to men. I think the more likely explanation is the crabs in a bucket explanation. Losers tend to want to pull other people down especially if the person happens to be different than them or if they are prejudiced against that group.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
