<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7720</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think something is off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 02:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 13:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgive my grammar first off. If rob zombie wanted to make a movie where the victim is the story he should have made it a spin off of his own universe. Instead he decided to take an established continuity and shit all over it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 22:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> home room, very underrated classic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PS+ question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 17:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do we know what the free games for march are? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the hate for Micky knuckles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 23:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i was reading Youtube comments and there was alot of hate for, can any of you give me the reason? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 22:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i wouldn't call her ugly,  she is one of the most beautiful people i have had the privilege to watch.  in a world so defined by outward appearance its refreshing to see someone with such an amazing personality  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 22:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> id say Halloween 5 after, Michael Myers gets shot to shit and such and falls into the river and the old guy finds him and nurses him back to health </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minecraft Roller Coaster - Doctor Who 50th Anniversary Tribute - made by Traffic187 from [Cubecraft] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 09:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> wannabe voice actor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 16:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really wanting to break into that line of work,  Dont need to get paid.  just a way to the project.  sorry if i posted wrong i, wasn't sure how to make this kind of post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> m4f really bored </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 06:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi im really bored, since i am in a terrible town in Idaho, and it is very cold outside, some company would be awesome,  im a bigger guy so there's the disclaimer, anyway interested pm me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 04:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> echo mage clearly looks like the gay lawyer on spin city michael boatman http://www.imdb.com/name/nm0090225/?ref_=tt_cl_t2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> million mask march, anonymous protest officially begins (here's a live stream from james from the internet) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 16:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
