<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7806</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 20:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Built a Jhonny 5 before actually so I'll build on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 20:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the assistance! I don't have tens of thousands and if I do, I'd spend it for sure :D UK robots are pretty lame, I'll go for the Japanese ones and will update here once I built it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone knows how to build this robot with Arduino? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 18:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 13:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Works fine now I guess, can you try on your side? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a brand new Pebble Time for sale! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 17:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 12:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea because Arduino.org is still manufacturing in Italy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 12:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea but Arduino.org is still made in Italy, one of them will kill the other eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any update on the Arduino lawsuit? It's frustrating to see arduino.cc out of stock on all Arduino products. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 19:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 13:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of the room actually! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I built a smart flusher for the toilet where i flush with a voice command using Arduino and 1Sheeld. When I showed it to my roommate he kicked me out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 19:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 18:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sharing, I use Codebender.cc, it's an online IDE for all Arduino a-like platforms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally! Smartphone and Arduino on a Drone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 04:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 04:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree, thanks for your feedback and i will pass it to them for sure :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 01:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right some stuff about the campaign look fishy, i do know them personally though and they graduated from an accelerator called Buildit in Estonia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A HW startup is building (World's Fastest Charger on a Keychain) they are crowdfunding on Indiegogo, anyone knows how to get PR to give them a push? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 20:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm building an iOS App to control Arduino over BLE shield, but the data rate is about 1 Kbps which won't be enough for getting the Gyroscope sensor data efficiently, can someone help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 13:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is not the sensors but the data rate with BLE, in other Bluetooth modules the rate is 115 Kbps.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 20:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  robosapien 

That's a toy guys, is it even hack-able!!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
