<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1598</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 16:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (thanks to the person who noted my original title got East and West wrong ... oops) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Piracy has moved from Africa's East Coast to its West Coast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 16:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British universities are an ocean ahead of their American cousins on explaining role of animals in research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 16:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British universities come out on top on providing clear information on their animal research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 16:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help finding to somewhere to go for two weeks from 8th December </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 22:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Where I am now**
London (any airport)

**Dates**
Around 8th - 21st December, will adjust dates for cheaper flights if necessary

**Interests**
Cities and culture. I am going along so I am looking for somewhere that an English speaking Western traveller can easily meet up with people to travel bits of the journey with. Needs to be safe enough to travel alone, I have travelled before, but always with friends previously. Need to be able to go to several cities or places over a couple of weeks. I intend to backpack the journey (so hostels over hotels).

**Weather**
Hot (18 - 30C)

**Budget**
1500 for two weeks including flights

**Visa**
I'm a UK resident, and I need somewhere I can either get a visa at short notice, or don't need a visa.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Northern Ireland used 18,638 animals for research in 2013 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 17:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 11:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'd have preferred "Jolly good show" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Number of animals used in research falls by 10% in Netherlands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 18:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 11:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just watch a summary of current world news </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 11:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Washing up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hotel charges customers 100 if they leave a bad online review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 13:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 18:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When 9/11 happened, some people chose to burn to death, but around 200 people chose to jump - knowing they would die. 

People who choose euthanasia make a similar choice - a quick death vs a long slow painful death from disease.

I understand why people chose to jump in 9/11, I understand why people choose to die with dignity in a hospital - I think euthanasia should be legalised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 18:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to the press </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 10:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're individually asking 173 countries if they'll accept you on principle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 17:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, technically true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK has most powerful passport in the world in 2014 (alongside Sweden and Finland) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 17:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top 10 Most Powerful Passports In The World 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 17:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Passport Second most Powerful in the World in 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 17:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 19:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given that approximately 40% of the world population has internet access, I would be a lot more careful about making guarantees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dangerous Brinkmanship - Report on escalation between Russia and the West </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 12:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 18:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Anyone know what we did to change from 1929

We  had the Great Depression and lots and lots of people went bankrupt....

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top 0.1%'s wealth about to overtake bottom 90% for first time since 1929 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 00:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 16:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between a 15" Zildjian A Custom Fast Crash, and 20" K Dark Ride </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 12:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a competition my cousin is in - so if you can "like" it - she and I would be very happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 11:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and no services? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 19:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the article - we're not there yet.

Dr Rob Buckle, head of regenerative medicine at the MRC, said: 

"This research is an exciting *early* step towards that goal, and a convincing demonstration of the potential power of direct reprogramming technology, by which once cell type is converted to another. However, much more work will be needed before this process can be reproduced in the lab environment, and in a safe and tightly controlled way suitable for use in humans." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 19:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, we have the first stage of growing organs - there will be a lot of animal research before that gets anywhere near a person. They still need to get over transplant rejection, getting organs to proper size (among other issues). Your suggestion that we were already at a stage where this was a usable technology was nonsense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 00:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What planet are you on?!

"We can now grow new organs with stem cells"
No, no we can't!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 17:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why doesn't the future require liver or kidney damage studies? Are people who suffer organ failure worth less in your opinion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 16:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depend which minorities. If you look at those who arrived recently - such as Romanians, Bulgarians etc, then yes, they are doing worse - there is a lot of prejudice in our system.

The Indians, the Poles, the Chinese, are all doing pretty well in our system these days. 

The group that tends to come closest to the bottom is white working class British - draw what conclusions you want from that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 16:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the LD50 is rarely used - it's not a particularly useful test - I mean any dosage that kills half a group of mice is clearly too high (when weight adjusted) for humans. 

There is a lot more to animal research than toxicology - most of it is about understanding the processes going on. So, for the macular degenration I expect there were a lot of studies working out which stem cells were key to the formation of the eye, and what effect they have when implanted into an adult eye etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 11:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stem cell treatments are developed using animal studies. So the recent stem cell treatment for age related macular degeneration was only possible because of knowledge derived from mouse and primate tests. 
http://www.theguardian.com/science/2014/oct/15/stem-cell-success-in-treating-macular-degeneration </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 17:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Move to Britain. For the weather. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 17:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reposted without spelling error in title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Israeli academics beg Prime Minister to protect animal research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 17:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 17:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reposted without spelling error in title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Israeli academics beg Prime Minister to protect animal research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 17:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 16:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three blinks will be an error code by the manufacturer to say what precisely is wrong, but I can't find the blink-error list for that model of TV. For example, are you sure it's the power board? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secret message from Computer Engineer Barbie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 14:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Firefox address bar stopped working </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 10:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putting url's or search terms in the address bar doesn't do anything. I am having the use the Google Search bar on the right to search for websites. 

Reinstalling Firefox did not solve the issue.

Windows 7. 64-bit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 10:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you explain more - where is that, how do I fix it? Is that what three blinks means? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Power LED flashing 3 times on Panasonic TX-P50G10B - TV not turning on </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 22:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Panasonic TX-P50G10B, the red power light is blinking 3 times intermittently and the TV will not turn on
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 17:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Houston, I'm going to detonate..... farewell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 03:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tip my hat, and you tip your wallet. The deal is done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 23:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *tips hat before turning around and walking mysteriously into the night* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 22:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I graduated from Oxford Uni seven years ago. A few thoughts.

First off. There are great minds everywhere, from the top uni to the bottom, and many great minds that never went at all. That said, you are likely to find that Harvard/Oxford(etc) have a high proportion of very clever people than at lower ranked universities. 

You will find great tutors at all universities. I will go one step further and say that Harvard/Oxford does not necessarily have the best tutors/lecturers. Whereas as a small American liberal arts college may hire a professor for their teaching abilities, top universities tend to hire great academics (those who excel in their field), and top academics do not necessarily make great tutors and lecturers. In my time at Oxford I had great and terrible lecturers. Of my two best tutors, one was a DPhil student (the other was Prof Mayhew). 

Comparing my experience with friends, the major differences between my university and some "lower ranked" universities was:

- Workload: I was expected to read up for, and write, two x 2000 word essays per week. The reading list would be 8-20 books/papers for each. In fact, learning to read quickly and effectively is the single biggest skill I took away from Oxford. One consequence is people cover a lot of ground very fast. One third of my first year was economics, yet I covered more economic theory in my first year than some friends at other universities did in their first year.

- Connections: I met a lot of very driven people, many of whom are on the path to becoming very successful. The contacts I made at Oxford will last a lifetime. The "Oxford" name obviously helps - many employers, rightly or wrongly, would prefer to hire an Oxbridge graduate over (probably equally able) other people.

- Great minds: The tutorial system at Oxford - whereby two people are grilled by each other and a professor each week for an hour - sharpens your mind. It makes you able to vocalise your thoughts concisely and confidently. You are constantly challenged by people who are as smart or smarter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Utilitarian ethics and animal research - A discussion with Jeffrey Kahn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 15:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 14:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's contagious... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 13:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia and America are very different places. 

Russia is much more autocratic (see democracy index), has lower standards of living (about half the GDP/Person (PPP), is more corrupt (US ranked 19th best, Russia ranked 127th).

Much less media freedom, more repressive laws (consider that in Russia promoting a gay agenda is a crime) .... there are many differences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 13:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's going to be a faff if we need to use 5 digits, maybe we can reset every 10,000 years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What rats and dogs have taught us about treating paralysis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 14:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A paralyzed man learns to walk and the basic science that led us there </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 14:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 12:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was in science communication. Became a maths/economics teacher for 3 years. Returned to science communication after.

No regrets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 12:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone clarify. Are the nasal ensheathing cells a form of stem cell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new line of stealth cars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 12:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paralysed man walks again after olfactory cell transplant - look at the studies on rats and dogs that made it possible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 11:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 11:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great to see the background studies that made this possible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> University of Wisconsin responds point-by-point to dishonest petition attacking psychiatric research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 14:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 14:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a better or worse training programme, it's a different approach. What it does do, is get people who may not have considered teaching, into the profession, a proportion of whom stay on for years. 

Remember that "traditional" routes into teaching have similar high drop out rates over the first 3 years of teaching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 14:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most first year teachers don't know how to manage behaviour - TFA or otherwise. My experience in the UK suggests to me that after the first year (where PGCE students have done some teaching and learning, and Teach First (UK version of TFA) have done a year teaching on their own) the Teach First'ers were a lot better equipped to deal with behaviour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 13:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While some of the UK academies have failed, they have generally outperformed non-academies, and certainly turned round many under performing schools. There are issues with academies, but I wouldn't call the whole programme a failure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need a subwoofer suggestion for a 5.1 system </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 17:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Current set up:

Sherwood RD-6106R 5.1 amp
2 x Eltax Symphony 6.2 speakers
2 x Eltax HT-2 Bipolar Rear Speakers
Eltax Symphony Centre Center

Picked up everything second hand. So want to know what type of "stats" i need out of a sub - I know nothing about this.

Budget - up to 60 second hand. (I've picked up everything else for about 150 altogether)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 00:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Set up:

    Sherwood RD-6106R 5.1 amp
    2 x Eltax Symphony 6.2 speakers
    2 x Eltax HT-2 Bipolar Rear Speakers
    Eltax Symphony Centre Center

Picked up everything second hand. So want to know what type of "stats" i need out of a sub - I know nothing about this.

Budget - up to 60 second hand. (I've picked up everything else for about 150 altogether) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need sub to complete 5.1 system [Advice needed] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 00:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 16:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm torn by this too. Also considering the Nexus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 11:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The book is "The Organization Man" - but I haven't read it (yet).

The books are only be stacked temporarily. Half of them have already been put up on the first bookshelf now. I think it'll be ok on the spines provided you don't put large heavy books on small light ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 15:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would this technique be applicable to pets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fly genes hold clue to human illness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 11:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fly genes hold clue to human illness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 11:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 17:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the UK over 98% of animals used are mice, rats, birds and fish (mostly mice). Across the EU this figure is closer to 93%.

Estimates for the US around 95% are probably about right
http://speakingofresearch.com/facts/statistics/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Animal researcher explains how she used to hide what she did from friends and relatives </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 16:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 16:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Has anything you've done made your life better?"

American History X </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 16:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a teacher I once asked this of identical twins, and then spent the next month paranoid that they were switching places </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 16:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...I said the **red** wire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 16:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We do see you as having an accent, but we also see people in different areas of the UK as having an accent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 16:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The talkpage of the Pitcairn Islands has a discussion on whether it would be easier to individually name everyone who lives there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 14:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh dear lord, this is going to get messy..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Love drug' key to sexual behaviour (mouse study) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 12:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 11:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then Steam isn't recognising all the files in the new folder and is downloading them all over again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 00:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't add a folder which is not empty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 20:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All my games ARE on a separate hard drive. But they all get installed initially to the SSD and then moved off to a second drive using steamtool. 

FFXIII was different because the installation appears to require about 80GB (even though the game is only 60GB), which is more than I have spare on the SSD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steam not recognising FFXIII is installed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 20:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have FFXIII on the G:\ with a SteamTool link pointing at it from my C:\ steamapps\common game directory (as with all my games).

Normally If I then "installed" a game that was there it would find the game and not feel the need to reinstall, but instead it's trying to redownload the entire 50GB game. 

I know the game is working as I can play it by using the launcher in its current location, but Steam library thinks it is uninstalled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Problems downloading FFXIII relating to disk space </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 20:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have enough disk space to download FFXIII (with about 10GB to spare - it's a small SSD).

When I finish, I plan to use SteamTool to move it to another drive where all my other games are:

BUT

Steam is creating a 20GB "downloading" folder in addition to the 43GB it's downloaded so far (of 49.4GB of the game). Which is taking me over my available space. 

Help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The role of infant primate studies in child health </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 18:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nobel Prizewinner John OKeefe warns of threat to science from overly restrictive animal research and immigration rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 12:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 12:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great to see a British scientist win the Nobel Prize! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 17:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what the hell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection  Spies, Lies and Inspection Reports </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 16:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BUAV  Spies, Lies and Inspection Reports - How the truth came out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 16:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sweden to recognise Palestinian state </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 16:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 13:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Informtaion on each story is available here: http://www.understandinganimalresearch.org.uk/news/2014/10/the-week-in-animal-research-w-e-3rd-october/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Week of Animal Research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 13:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Week in Animal Research 3rd October 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 13:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 14:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, refuse to buy him one. It's sex or the beard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 14:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20th century = 1900s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To those born after 2,000 - what do you imagine the 20th Century was like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 14:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 14:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Statistically...? Rich parents! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 13:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think my mother has ever cooked anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 12:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A fair question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 12:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good decisions come from experience
Experience comes from bad decisions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
