<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1805</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 13:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at the base of his thumb and you see bad bruising, add the bandage down the arm and would say he has an injury so pointless taking him to America when he wont play so let him stay at home and work on fitness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cole vs Antonio Valencia though wasn't for some reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Individual awards like team of the year are a load of shite, David Luiz got in world team of the year. He is brilliant though and will be remembered as one the greatest England has ever produced  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was good old dithering Dave thinking he wasn't strong enough for the league in the end

Can you also show me where he said it was a done deal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 00:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ronaldo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 23:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me schweinsteiger is absolutely amazing and I genuinely still can't believe it but think it will be bigger than him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 23:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We will go for one massive thing which if it comes off would be huge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 23:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean wasn't going to be on the books this year? As in if we hadn't got him we wouldn't have spent the money, correct but we did so us now not spending the money is us saving it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahahahahaha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahahahahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stopping us wasting money as you put it is still saving money as it is expenditure we aren't now using, before falcao came we lost vida, Ferdinand and evra who probably earned that amount so his wage was just money we had spent anyway so all in all yeh we are saving money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work at Manchester royal hospital and we generally use purple and clear bags for bloods, but the guy could literally have just grabbed a bag and used it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeh because he's saved us another 250 grand a week wages you weird bell, so he was shit it happens but with him, RVP and Nani gone that about 600 grand a week saved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 21:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add falcaos wages to that as well... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 20:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article is a load of shit, apparently he told all this to a Milan fan who met him at Wimbledon who remembered everything fergie said perfectly and then told tuttosport </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 15:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We would not take a 20 million hit after one season, not a chance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read a lot of shit in my life, but this right here is the fucking biggest steaming pile I've ever had the displeasure of letting my eyes witness. Day can only get better I suppose </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 05:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a midfield 3  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
