<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5096</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 06:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I corrected the I;m to I'm  so now everyone should be be on the same page :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 05:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fessed up when I went in for cigs today and she said "no beer tonight?" in hindsight I should have stocked up on more booze so it wasn't suspicious. she acted like she was cool with it, but I could tell she was hurt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I cheated on my bitch last night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 04:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it was after midnight and i was more than a few beers deep but didn't have any more in the house. so i went to the only store open, I'm sorry. i didn't mean to cheat on you but you were closed. i still love you and value our relationship. i made a mistake and hate myself for it, but lets just move on ok honey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 04:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> congrats man. i'm saving up for a dualsport because i'm right at where you were on my fourth steel reserve tallboy right now. I need one so I don't drink so much and feel better about myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 05:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm playing a lot of hearthstone now. my account is Dionysus#1697 in the Americas if anyone else plays hearthstone add me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 18:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> obviously never played slime-grenade wars, put firecrackers on slugs and throw them at each other </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 15:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> widespread panic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 15:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah add me if im not too late ! Dionysus#1697

anybody add me and we'll play eventually whenever i'm on, just ask </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Light] At the movie theater I chose to sit far away from a black couple because I thought they might talk a lot during the movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 23:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At the movie theater, I chose to sit far away from a black couple because I was worried they would talk a lot during the movie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 04:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 07:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't drink a couple days ago for the whole day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 07:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fried cheese. just place on a pan until crispy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 20:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nobody has ever said that about anyone who has dependents or children. and nobody has ever said that about opiates </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 10:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you, that actually helps a lot. but whats the difference between decks used for tournaments and normal decks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 08:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know you could right click them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> where can I see deck lists that really good people use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 10:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 00:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jesus Christ that's disgusting, just use tissues like a normal person </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 22:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shamalongadingdong

also, cheez-its are the shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 07:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in highschool I had to do a two page presentation on if I was for against the death penalty, my whole presentation was about batman. batman doesn't kill people and he's my role model so I think death penalty is wrong, for my research I listed comic books </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 10:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew someone here could help me out. thanks man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 09:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no i didn't intend for that to happen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 07:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> alright, thanks man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I accidentally drank out the bottle I put my cigarettes out in yesterday, and now everything tastes sour and shitty and I cant get the taste out my mouth no matter how many times I've brushed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 06:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 08:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> will you marry me? I can be gay  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 21:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sounds like someone has a case of the Republicans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 12:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why do other countries have such a fascination with America? we're a country too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: use crushed ice when you want a drink to get cold fast and cubed ice when you want a drink to stay cold for awhile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 09:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because surface area and shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 01:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how did you get the paperwork? and how much was it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 09:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lucky there's video to back him up, could have seriously fucked his life up if those passengers were "witnesses" against him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 01:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get how someone can claim to be poor but then it comes out that they have 15 family members... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 02:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I put weed in my soda cup when a cop stopped me one time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 13:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> go for it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 23:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he looks like a down syndrome kid that got recalled to the manufacturer and came back normal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 13:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> too late motherfucker I got my answers. better luck next time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 04:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so about 6 feet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 04:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant how high would the building have to be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 04:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> widespread panic! unfortunately, youtube is lacking in album recordings. but they are one of the best concert bands so its ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 14:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love their fries. but everything else they serve is nasty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 14:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahahahahahahahaha that makes me feel a little better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 13:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what does it mean when poo is green? lack of protein or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what's the worst thing you've tasted? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 13:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 11:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 11:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awesome!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> looking for someone chill to play with! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 11:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my game name is Dionysus#1697 in the Americas

I've never played against a friend before and i really want to. don't worry, i disenchanted all my priest, shaman, and druid cards so i could make a pirate deck.. i mean a deck that has 5 pirates in it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 11:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey i'm looking for someone to play with. except i don't know how to do that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 11:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what does miracle mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 11:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey man let's play a game! i'm definitely casual because i disenchanted all my priest, druid, and shaman cards so i could make a pirate deck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 11:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also want to know this because i disenchanted all my priest, shaman, and druid cards so i could do a pirate deck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 11:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I interviewed for a dishwashing job at whole foods. I made the mistake of cracking a couple jokes during the group interview. got a call saying I didn't get the job because I didn't take it seriously enough. I responded by apologizing profusely and promised I take washing dishes very seriously, they changed their mind and offered me the job. I refused </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 09:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when he stressed equal weight of butter and flour, does volume vs weight really make that much of a difference?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 09:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh cool, thanks. I heard something like 64,000 peopleattended </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 09:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's really fucking cool. goodwill is on olive st right? i'll have to check that out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 09:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did Dempsey or that other sounders defender play in the game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 02:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry about your balls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 12:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm sorry that people downvoted this. some people don't care for it much, that's cool idk people be hating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 11:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when I needed money I sold my car and bought a motorcycle. I should learn about food stamps, I'm sure I qualify. its pretty ridiculous that someone with two cars can get food stamps, she learned how to abuse the system and wrote an article about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 22:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha thanks buddy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 22:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah it has a carb. and i'm using a glass screen. i just stuck a stem down the stem and thats working ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 22:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> using a glass screen, doesnt help. but thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 08:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> friend's house got broken into and his xbox was stolen. the police told him they had a suspect in mind and that this suspect had a record. friend knew i had a criminal record (marijuana) so he calls my house phone and accused me of stealing his xbox. my dad beat me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 20:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe you spilt booze on it and there's a heating vent under your dresser? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 04:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she forgot her purse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> in anticipation of Godzilla, i had to watch Monsters again. what are some other good movies that not many people know about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 20:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> monster or apocolypse movies would be great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 23:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my buddy has a wifi stealer. it's like an antennae that steals wifi from like a mile away. he takes it when he goes on road trips too. its a little expensive but its a 1 time cost and lasts for life. i'm thinking about getting one when i get my motorcycle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 22:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't really get how some alchies can have such interested lives. i buy bulk liquor and cheap beer and drink at home while i swear at my playstation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> looking for a dogfighting anime. or any anime about the frontlines of war (hopefully realistic warfare) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 22:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> really really want a realistic dogfighting anime (not mecha)

edit: first my post gets removed because it didn't have a body, then my post was almost removed because i forgot flair. why does this subreddit have to be so difficult? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 11:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> please don't let me keep you up because of me. really, i'm sorry if i'm keeping you awake. if you want to, tell me your highlights. anything that stick out in your memory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 10:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and you say you can't get easy pussy... lol. just figure out a good segway like say your still in the music business and tell these stories. you will get aids and die a happy man lol;. 

i have a lot of questions but they might by after you met the bands:
1. i heard that Spoonman was still somewhat homeless after his fame with soundgarden, do you know what they paid him?
2. do you know why layne staley left alice in chains to go to mad season? granted mad season would have been huge if they made more than one album </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 10:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're so lucky. i really want to know more about him but don't want to waste your time, so my second question is why you punched curt cobain did you really knock him out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 10:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn sounds like you had an awesome experience. please don't let me keep you awake or refresh reddit- but my first question is about layne staley- what was he like? what point in his career did you meet him? what do you know about his downward spiral? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 10:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just got an idea while i was pissing- do your AMA in r/seattle  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 10:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you have to do an AMA right fucking now! i have so many questions but there may be things i forget to ask that other people with think of. please. maybe a CA AMA if you dont want to get flooded with messages?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
