<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9553</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican-Controlled House Passes Bill To Cut $242 Million From Amtrak's Budget </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Oliver's anti-FIFA ad on Trinidad TV was like a bonus 'Last Week Tonight' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin Says US Imperial Footprint Unmatched: 'Draw a Map and See': Despite US military dominance, Obama accuses Russian leader of attempting to 'recreate Soviet empire' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Government Wants Names of Online Commenters Who Trashed the Silk Road Judge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an anomaly. It still hasn't happened en masse among bankers since 1929. 

Face it, in 2015 bankers don't commit suicide, they're one of the leading causes of suicide.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 02:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That hasn't happened in a long time. 

As a matter of fact, the term "golden parachute" is actually a reference to the bankers who lost it all and jumped out of windows after the Great Crash of 1929. 

The golden parachute figuratively provides an equally safe and luxurious landing for bankers, bailed out by the federal government.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iceland put bankers in jail rather than bailing them out  and it worked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Andrew Cuomo's Pot Problem: In New York, one of the most liberal states in the country, why is the governor doing everything in his power to water down sensible marijuana reform? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 19:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sri Lankas President Bans Glyphosate Nationwide to Protect the Health of the People </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 18:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> War Propaganda and Dirty Lies support the Dirty War on Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 14:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cool crab steals a lit cigar, refuses to give it back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 14:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secret Sheldon Adelson Summit Raises up to $50M for Strident Anti-BDS Push </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 14:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 14:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was an excellent episode of the Corbett Report.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress Didn't Notice the FBI Creating a 'Small Air Force' for Surveillance: Excessive executive branch secrecy and the legislatures oversight failures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legislators Strip Funding For Warrantless Use Of Stingrays By FBI, Take Money From The DEA To Buy Bodycams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers Apologize for Gaming Reddit with Fake Accounts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legislators Strip Funding For Warrantless Use Of Stingrays By FBI, Take Money From The DEA To Buy Bodycams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers Apologize for Gaming Reddit with Fake Accounts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA Won't Say if it Automatically Transcribes American Phone Calls in Bulk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 19:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The totalitarian reign of Sheldon Adelson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 15:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Politicians Attempt to Sabotage BDS Anti-Occupation Campaign against Israel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 15:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 17:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed, rule 10.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 17:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed, rule 10.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 17:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed, rule 10 of the sub, continued violations will result in a ban from /r/conspiracy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 17:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed, violation of rule 10.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 23:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea but I think that the British have been by far the worst. The scope of colonial suffrage caused by the British remains to be matched. 

Also the fact that the British Empire is chiefly responsible for the creation of the 3rd world and the developing world. 

Before the British conquered India, much of Africa and the Middle East, the poor arpund the world enjoyed similar living standards. 

After England created their colonial empire, the poor and middle class in England had much higher living standards than British colonial subjects. Effectively creating a 3rd world in India, Africa and the Middle East. 

To understand the modern world, you have to know the history of the British Empire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 20:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you ever read *Late Victorian Holocausts* by Mike Davis it details how the British were responsible for several famines in India over the course of a century and a half. 

The British pretty much shipped the vast majority of India's grain and wheat to be inserted into European markets, it was a manufactured shortage. 

Just look at the Bengal Famine in 1943, 7 million Bengalis died of starvation, during that same period the majority of Bengali crops were being used to help fight the British war effort in World War II. 

Google *Late Victorian Holocausts*, its one of the best books I've ever read. 

Our history of the British Empire has been completely whitewashed. All of the famines and atrocities that occurred during British rule, especially in India, have been effectively swept under the rug and we are left with a rosy, Downtown Abbey-like view of the British Empire. 

The British Empire was a horrible, exploitative, militant, racist, murderous society. We shouldn't forget the many atrocities committed by the Empire, in its quest for global domination.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> County sheriff warrantlessly used stingray 500+ times, claims to have no records: Sacramento Co. Sheriff says it has no policies for a spy device it acquired in 2005. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 17:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> County sheriff warrantlessly used stingray 500+ times, claims to have no records: Sacramento Co. Sheriff says it has no policies for a spy device it acquired in 2005. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 17:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaza, Drones and the Booming Business of War in Israel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 17:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TTIP and EU-India Secret Trade Talks: Big Business Setting Policy behind Closed Doors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 14:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 14:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, [there's this recent article about how the Red Cross raised nearly half a billion dollars for the victims of the Haitian earthquake in 2010 and only built 6 homes with it.](https://www.propublica.org/article/how-the-red-cross-raised-half-a-billion-dollars-for-haiti-and-built-6-homes)

That Propublica article is what got me to take a look at the American Red Cross and their scandal-plagued history. They seem to do something like this in the aftermath of every major natural disaster or social upheaval.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the American Red Cross raised more than $564 million for victims of 9/11 but only actually distributed $154 million to the victims. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 14:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Very Mention of Snowden's Name Makes Prosecutors Tremble </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 14:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Boston, Media Again Trash a Police Shooting Victim by Uncritically "Reporting" Police Accusations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 14:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want News on Big Money in Politics? Don't Look to Major Media Networks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 13:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What an NYPD Spy Copter Reveals About the FBI's Spy Planes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 13:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Red Cross Raised Half a Billion Dollars for Haiti and Built Six Homes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 13:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Very Mention of Snowden's Name Makes Prosecutors Tremble </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 13:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Political deleted-tweet archive shuttered by Twitter over privacy expectation: Politwoop's API access revoked without warning; had archived posts, deletion times. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 13:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uber Wants to Hire a Million More Drivers Then Replace Them All With Robots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 20:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 14:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never alter the titles of my submissions, I always go with the title of the person who wrote the content. 

Adding my own spin or narrative to the title of the article only confuses and disappoints people after they click on the link for the article I submitted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Podemos Phenomenon: Spains Best Hope for Democracy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 14:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Imgur Is Cracking Down on NSFW Content Because it Wants to Be Instagram </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 14:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are the propagandists: The real story about how The New York Times and the White House has turned truth in the Ukraine on its head </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 13:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> USA Freedom Act: A fig leaf for illegal spying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 13:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress Slyly Changed Campaign Finance Rules. Now the GOP Is Cleaning Up. The Democrats? Not so much. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 13:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Senate approves extension of NSA spying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 14:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Senate approves extension of NSA spying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 14:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One Small Step for NSA Reform, One Giant Leap for Congress </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 13:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV is Losing Ground to the Internet Where It Really Counts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 13:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Iron-Man" Suit Lives on in Dreams of Special Operations Commanders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 19:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Supreme Court Just Made it Harder to Report Online Abuse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 19:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elizabeth Warren Has Had It With The SEC's Aid To Wall Street Lawbreakers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 17:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Underestimate the National-Security State: The sunset of Patriot Act provisions is a symbolic victory, but an inadequate response to post-9/11 surveillance policy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Private Contractors Have Created a Shadow NSA: A new cybersecurity elite moves between government and private practice, taking state secrets with them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 13:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed. Violation of rule #1 of the sub, continued violations will result in a ban from /r/conspiracy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Worry, The NSA Can Probably Still Spy On You. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 20:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Worry, The NSA Can Probably Still Spy On You. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 20:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goldman lawyer becomes SEC chief of staff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 17:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goldman lawyer becomes SEC chief of staff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 17:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goldman lawyer becomes SEC chief of staff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 17:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul: My opponents 'secretly want there to be an attack on the United States so they can blame it on me' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 17:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the First Time Since 9/11, Congress Checks the Security State </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 16:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Solar-Powered Plane Forced to Land Due to Cloudy Skies on Round-the-World Trip </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 16:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 16:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm happy he appears to be doing okay mentally. I was worried he was going to have some sort of permanent brain damage. 

I've followed his whole career since he played Brian Fellows on SNL to the Tracy Jordan days on 30 Rock. I also saw him do stand up in Philly a few years ago, he killed. 

You can tell this accident, like most near-death instances, has profoundly changed Tracy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the First Time in 14 Years, the NSA Cant Get Your Phone Records </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 15:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the First Time in 14 Years, the NSA Cant Get Your Phone Records </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 15:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 15:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This speech gave me a freedom boner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul just sacrificed his presidential campaign for his libertarian principles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 15:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Rand Paul Speaks Out Against the PATRIOT Act - May 31, 2015 (5 min.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 15:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israel wants $4.5 billion and more from US. Every year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 15:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul: My Opponents Secretly Want Attack on U.S. So They Can Blame It on Me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 14:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Al Qaeda Syria Boss Says That His "So-Called Khorasan Group Doesn't Exist" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 19:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US seizes on FIFA corruption to pursue campaign against Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 16:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Real Anti-Poverty Movement Cant Be Led By Millionaires: Those of us who spend our lives worrying about making rent and buying our kids new crayons need better representation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 15:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bomb Threat Temporarily Halts FIFA Congress, Israel Vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 15:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 14:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This shit couldn't possibly be more rigged. 

I don't know what Sepp Blatter did to anger those in power, but it looks increasingly like his days as the head of FIFA are going to end today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arrests Overshadow Palestinians Bid to Oust Israel From FIFA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 14:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Monsanto Is About to Get a Lot Bigger and More Powerful: We should be very concerned about the future of the world's food supply. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 14:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress should sunset part of Patriot Act to prevent domestic spying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 13:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corporate Media Accused of Parroting Fear-Mongering over Patriot Act: Privacy advocates say outlets like New York Times spread 'government propaganda' by publishing uncritical White House quotes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 13:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let Patriot Act Provisions Expire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 13:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A New Report Shows How the NYPD Hassles Minorities for Petty BS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 19:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: US to Give Israel Massive Increase in Military Aid for Iran Deal: 'Compensation' Pact Will Allow Israel to Keep Publicly Complaining </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 19:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: US to Give Israel Massive Increase in Military Aid for Iran Deal: 'Compensation' Pact Will Allow Israel to Keep Publicly Complaining </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 19:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FIFA corruption scandal may prove fortuitous for Israel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 17:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lockheed Martin in Vermont: Senator Bernie Sanders Corporate Conundrum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 14:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Gigabit Fiber Startup Will Compete With Comcast in Detroit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 13:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TSA Body Scanner Lobbyist Takes Congressional Job Overseeing Spending on TSA Security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 13:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anonymous Fear-Mongering About the Patriot Act from the White House and NYT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 13:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israel Wants 50% Increase in US Provided Military Aid. U.S. Tax Payers Fund Netanyahus Killing Machine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 20:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israel Wants 50% Increase in US Provided Military Aid. U.S. Tax Payers Fund Netanyahus Killing Machine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 20:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israel Thanks Obama for Sabotaging Nuclear Nonproliferation Deal: US officials blocked deal last week, sparking concern and criticism around the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 17:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israel Thanks Obama for Sabotaging Nuclear Nonproliferation Deal: US officials blocked deal last week, sparking concern and criticism around the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 17:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Christie attacks Rand Paul for 'siding with' Edward Snowden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 17:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Media Censorship of Critical Coverage of Californias Bill to Mandate Vaccines for School Children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 17:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chicago Police Put Antlers on Black Man and Posed for Pictures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 15:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want to end mass incarceration? Stop blindly reelecting your local prosecutor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 15:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside Amy Schumer - Court of Public Opinion: The Trial of Bill Cosby </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 15:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Corbett on 9/11, Israel   geopolitics, beginning at the 22:44 mark. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 13:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hold bankers accountable for their crimes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 13:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huge Pipeline Company Kinder Morgan Hired Off-Duty Cops to "Deter Protesters" in Pennsylvania </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 13:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Telecom Giants Are Merging to Stop the Nascent Broadband Revolution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 13:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mitch McConnell Will Do Just About Anything Not To Vindicate Edward Snowden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 20:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's time we have a holiday to honor those who try to stop wars too </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 13:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 22:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, see how easy that was ? 

You can make your statement without taking a shot at the sub in its entirety.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 22:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed. Violation of rule #10 of the sub. Continued violations will result in a ban from /r/conspiracy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California Is Giving Free Solar Panels to the Poor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 20:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California Is Giving Free Solar Panels to the Poor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 20:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 18:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed. Rule #6 of the sub. No Caps Lock.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Major Monsanto Lawsuit Completely Blacked out by Media </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 17:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton Endorses GMOs. White House Meals are Organic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 16:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 16:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "*The Gang Goes to Vegas*" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crow going crazy trying to get into my house. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 16:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The military is buying patriotism: A Memorial Day nightmare about Pentagon budgets  and veterans used as a sideshow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 15:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 15:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed, violation of rule #1 of the sub. Continued violations will result in a ban from /r/conspiracy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pro-Israel bias: BBC admits editorial breach in interview with Israeli defense chief </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 15:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corporate Media Doublethink and the Bush-PNAC-9/11-Iraq Connection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 15:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the last of the JFK files could embarrass the CIA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 13:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> County sheriff has used stingray over 300 times with no warrant: San Bernardino Sheriff's Department doesn't tell judges it's using spy device. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 13:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes sense. Schaub is a great wrestler, but Cain's gas tank is unmatched for heavyweights, and you need a gas tank to wrestle. 

Cain was also a NCAA Division 1 wrestler and he's got a black belt in BJJ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The GOP Is Dying Off. Literally. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 15:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Key   Peele - I Said Bitch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 15:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pentagon says no one should be held accountable for $34 million debacle: Defense officials say decision to construct lavish facility in Afghanistan was prudent, even though it was never used </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 14:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joe Rogan and Brendan Schaub thug life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 14:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Audit: Pentagon credit card holders spent $3 million at casinos, strip clubs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 13:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Brooks Tries To Rewrite History Of The Iraq War </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 13:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Brooks Tries To Rewrite History Of The Iraq War </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 13:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bush Says His Brother Was Misled Into War By Faulty Intelligence. That's Not What Happened. He and other Republican presidential contenders have a new and bogus spin on how the Iraq war began. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 17:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sued: Class Action Lawsuit Will Help Break Monsanto for Making False Claims: Glyphosate is harmful to humans and animals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 17:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The CIA and the Myths of the Bin Laden Raid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 17:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The CIA and the Myths of the Bin Laden Raid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 17:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress must debate dangerous consequences of pro-Israel amendment to TPA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 14:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress must debate dangerous consequences of pro-Israel amendment to TPA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 14:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Evidence of Israels Dirty Role in the Syrian Proxy War </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 14:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nevada Solar Power Users Could Face New Fees This Summer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 13:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nevada Solar Power Users Could Face New Fees This Summer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 13:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ive Read Obamas Secret Trade Deal. Elizabeth Warren Is Right to Be Concerned. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 13:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 13:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed comment, you violated rule #10 of the sub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 13:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed, rule 10.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 13:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed. Rule #10 of the sub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 13:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed. Rule #10 of the sub, continued violations will result in a ban from /r/conspiracy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 13:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed. Rule #6 of the sub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch this dad learn a hard lesson about bouncing too high on a trampoline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 14:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Verizon Swallows Net-Neutrality Champion Huffington Post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 13:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 13:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed. Rule 1 of the sub. Continued violations will result in a ban from /r/conspiracy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the US planning a Gulf of Tonkin incident in the South China Sea? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 13:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No, the GOP Has Not Lost Its Lust for War </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 13:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4 U.S. Companies Getting Rich Off Gulf Arab Conflict With Iran </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 16:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Politico Gives CIA's Worst WMD Liar a Platform to Slam Seymour Hersh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 17:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Paddle in Seattle' Protesters Welcome Shell Drilling Rig with Two Words: Go Away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 17:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shut Up Shitheads: Will Reddit's New Anti-Harassment Policy Work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 17:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New NSA Reform Bill Would Give the Government Even More Power to Spy on Your Smartphone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 15:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New NSA Reform Bill Would Give the Government Even More Power to Spy on Your Smartphone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 15:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Are We Paying the NFL to Help the Pentagon Recruit Troops? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 15:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 14:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed, rule #1.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Are We Paying the NFL to Help the Pentagon Recruit Troops? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 14:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Rules Committee Thwarts Effort to Add Privacy Protections to NSA "Reform" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 13:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 21:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, fair enough. In the future if someone posts PI in their submission unintentionally, could you just PM them about it ? Instead of putting their name in a comment, visible to everyone ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 20:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders Troubling History of Supporting US Military Violence Abroad: Why aren't we talking about Sanders' foreign policy more? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 19:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nestl CEO wishes he could bottle even more water in drought-stricken California </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 18:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey Officials Confirm Pact With Saudi Arabia To Help Rebels Fighting Syria's Assad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 17:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trade Beef Between Elizabeth Warren and Barack Obama, Explained: Obama is eager to broker the Trans-Pacific Partnership, but progressive critics like Warren see it as NAFTA on steroids </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 17:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the new acting DEA chief might disappoint drug policy reformers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 17:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Fake' Reform: Little to Celebrate as USA Freedom Act Passes House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 17:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arizona towns new license plate readers aim to reduce already-rare burglaries: Burglaries in Paradise Valley, Arizona, fell from 195 in 2011 to 55 in 2014. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Lobbying by Obama, Senate Agrees to Vote on Trade Bill After All </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 14:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Companies Are Throwing a Fit Because They're Losing Control Over the Internet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 14:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 13:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed. Violation of Reddiquette, continued violations will result in a ban from /r/conspiracy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greatest Threat to Free Speech Comes Not From Terrorism, But From Those Claiming to Fight it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 20:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The bin Laden assassination and the lies of the war on terror </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 20:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 19:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as I live I will never be able to understand why people find this man funny. 

I consider his, to be the bottom rung of comedy, just below the Scary Movie/parody film brand. 

He's just awful in everything he does. 

*Jack   Jill*, gimme a fucking break.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Hicks  BANNED Last Appearance on the Late Night David Letterman Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 17:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 17:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've said it here before and I'll say it again, James Corbett is the antidote to Alex Jones. 

Furthermore, IMHO he was our best AMA guest, the man recorded video responses to questions, *video responses*. 

He's an indispensable source of information and what I would consider to be the best alternative news source ever. He provides citations and always maintains a certain professorial presence, even when discussing atrocities. 

I really can't say enough good things about James Corbett. If you like his work, you should see his documentary, its called *Century of Enslavement: The Federal Reserve*. 

[Here's a link to the documentary on his website.](https://www.corbettreport.com/federalreserve/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Student troubled by New York Times reporter's Jewish litmus test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 17:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Osama bin Laden killing: Pakistan officials 'out' spy who gave away al-Qaeda leader's location: Report from Pakistan that Brigadier Usman Khalid went to the US seeking a $25m reward adds credence to Seymour Hersh expos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 16:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Navy SEAL who says he killed bin Laden refutes Hersh account (Yeah, I bet he does, his entire status as a conservative pseudo-celebrity depends upon Hersh's story being false) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 16:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, I cringed when Slate compared Alex Jones to Sy Hersh. 

This is what I'm talking about when I say that Alex Jones has done more damage to the "conspiracy theorist" image, for lack of a better phrase, than anyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
