<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7938</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Reddit! I was building a background for a forums and I was wondering which one looked better. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 19:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 07:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/unexpected </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 07:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fresh Tires or New Shoes. I don't know why </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 07:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> new tires </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favorite childhood memory? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 07:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite childhood memory? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 07:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "We are not responsible for the damage to your nostalgia or save files" pops up when you try to revert to the old minecraft versions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 07:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i kept putting a "peace sign" onto my lips not knowing what it meant. i did that to a girl.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 04:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVINGSAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE DRIVING SAFE  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If this post gets 2000 upvotes, this subreddit will turn into a NSFW sub. [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 06:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 03:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not knowing if it is your password or username that is incorrect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mods are asleep. Post pictures of eggroles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 03:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You are not a true fan if you don't watch a series entirely. You are not a true fan if you do watch a series entirely. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 01:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are only a true fan if you are powered by electricity, have multiple blades, and spin fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 22:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got in a car crash with my family in Colorado when I was 4. I was sitting a police car when a cop came down the hill, slid and hit the car I was sitting in with the door open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 22:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When people make cross posting a huge deal.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 21:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/thebutton2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 21:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aunt Jemima.. 

For some reason I read it as Aunt Jemina  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every letter is a bubble letter, so is every number. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 21:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NSFW] ayy don't click [NSFL] [GORE] [DEATH] lmao [WTF] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Realistic Giant Spiders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Click the post, and press "A" to change /r/circlejerk's theme to (   ) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 03:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little leg problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 03:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to wake up a baby 101 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 03:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The word "hot" caught on fire in this hotel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 03:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 23:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me SO uncomfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rabbit runs across an avalanche </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 23:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> XD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 23:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 21:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ketchup and Mayo. Makes perfect fish dipping sauce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grey's Anatomy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Helen Adams Keller was an American author, political activist, and lecturer. She was the first deafblind person to earn a bachelor of arts degree. " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our clan needs to do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 03:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh.. Sorry it's been a while since I was townhall six. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 03:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would just do 105.21 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
