<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3590</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 06:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd advise you to goto one of the folk-music seminars/camps like the Plovdiv seminar, Ross Daily's thing,  Macedonian pearl seminar,  Amala School, etc... Without connections or language skills you'll have  a very difficult time arranging things on your own in only 10 days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 07:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In america speaking 3 languages is the equivalent of a PhD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 07:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DOWNVOTED. Here's why
User "Kristinchen" only shares links from this website.
The Article says: 
 ITS NO LONGER ABOUT PORTRAYING AN IMAGE THROUGH EXCESS AND LOGOS. MODERN DAY LUXURY IS ALL ABOUT INTEGRITY.

Well then why is Absolut's 'handcrafted hard to find luxury Elyx brand mentioned at every turn? 
THIS IS AN AD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 05:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read this. Everyone has slightly different needs but this article is pretty good. http://michaelkammes.com/audio/prepping-and-exporting-for-post-audio-in-final-cut-pro/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 16:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in NYC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 22:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your help! It's a doc so there isn't really much subby material so I think I'm probably fine in that dept unless I'm overlooking something? Theater speakers are full range and the LFE is literally for LFE(?) Is there crossover that I'm overlooking and need to account for?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 21:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Room isn't treated but I have a pretty good understanding of its deficiencies. Mixing LCR so 5.1 minus 2.1...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mixing for theater in small room </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 16:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Folks,

I'm mixing a film that got picked up for a festival. My small room is loosely calibrated to -79dB on my nearfields. When I print the stems I want to make sure this thing is going to translate decently to the theater. Are there any steps I can take from my room to make absolutely sure there aren't any surprises when it gets to the theater?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 05:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've rarely had a problem with my big guerrini which I know fits perfectly in the overhead of a large transatlantic flight. That said I know professionals who will actually take the instrument apart into its two halves and have separate cases for each.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 22:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chalga. Love it? hate it?... or love it after 2 drinks?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 05:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fish sauce and shallots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 05:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> np- still learning the basics myself. 
If you can't find kafir lime, you can dilute normal lime juice with a little mayer lemon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 01:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You want the little fresh or pickled "bird's eye" peppers used in Thai and Indian food for CHILLI PASTE.

 However what you are making is CURRY paste, which is different. For that you're best bet is **dried** puya peppers. You mash them up in a mortar and pestle with all the other stuff. Some trouble-shooting tips for 'ya are: 

* When making your curry, first sautee the paste alone in oil for a bit until fragrant to cook all the raw shallots/garlic/other stuff. 

* You are correct to add sugar. Best bet is to dilute **palm sugar** (not white granulated cane sugar) in a mixture or lime juice and fish sauce. Then add that to the pot to incorporate it into the paste.  Add coconut milk after. 

* The boxed coconut milk is better than the canned. 
* finish it all off with some unsweetened coconut cream once your protein is cooked (not cream of coconut or creamed coconut). 
*I've never used it since my city has access to thai stuff, but you could try http://www.templeofthai.com/ for ingredients. I'm guessing you may have also been missing galangal and lime leaves too which makes a world of difference.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What The Hell Do Sound Mixers Do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 06:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 19:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do it all the time for live theater, and have never had a problem with hair noise. I usually use 2 toupee clips, hiding the cable under a part of hair, securing a loop of cable to the back of the neck with skinprep+transpore. The mic sits centrally right at the hairline, best situation are bangs to hide it. You can match the cable color to the hair with shoe paint, just be sure to cover the element with a little e-tape first so you don't mess it up. You can color the element itself with a paint marker.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 19:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mic + pot of hot oil + something frying in it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Accordion Clap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 05:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 21:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a bunch of video on youtube of how to do it. I just seasoned mine yesterday and it worked fine:

 Basically, scrubbed the waxy stuff out of it with warm water, detergent, and a scouring pad. Then I heated it up on my range  REALLY HOT. Next rubbed oil all around in it. Then burned that in occasionally rotating it around to hit as much of the surface as I could- you're going for a smooth burnt black finish on the inside. 

 I've heard of an alternate method using salt to get the same effect but I don't know much about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 17:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could it be some kind of metadata or a copyright marking trick? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 21:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually paying far under the stabilized rate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> stabilized lease renewal legal question? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 02:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to NYC housing code my landlord is legally obligated to renew my lease after it expires. He also never disclosed that the apt. is rent stabilized and I found it out later (illegal although I don't really care). Should I continue to bug him to formally renew it, or in the eyes of the law am I safe and still covered. (see below) 

The catch: My lease has a clause that it's good for a year (which has passed) and "thereafter it shall become a month-to-month tenancy."

Later it says, "TERMINATION: After expiration of the leasing period, this agreement is automatically renewed from month to month, but may be terminated by either party giving the other a 30-day written notice of intention to terminate. Where laws require "just cause," such just cause shall be so stated on said notice..."  

Am I safe from sudden eviction or is he legally permitted to kick me out after a months notice? (a bad situation to be be in) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 21:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CHEESE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
