<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4281</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 16:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this advice could go for most anything anyone video tapes "for the memories"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jobs should let you choose your compensation package/work schedule like a D D character sheet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like zero points in health insurance and 401k matching in exchange for a 4 day work week and the ability to work from home two of those days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A really good dream is just a delayed nightmare, because you wake up devastated when you realize it's not real </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 16:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dreamed I inherited $300 million last night. The emotions were so real and then I woke up a pleb again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about owning a personal space shuttle and launchpad not buying a chartered flight  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: in an economy of extreme wealth gap... many middle class and very few rich, would the price of exotic cars drop? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In countries with extreme wealth gaps, the only vehicles on the roads are Bentleys and bicycles. If one of their poor came here, they would have unreasonable expectations for what you drove. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDY to take a picture of the gaudiest car you can find </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 14:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know the type, autozoned out, plywood spoiler etc.

It must be trying to look cool despite its condition. functional fixes (no matter how ugly) don't count. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 12:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah that's just his wife </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 06:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should get some kind of Jesus resurrection flair.

That being said if dude is awol completely can we petition reddit to take it over? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 06:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was taking a shit actually when I typed it. Had I not had fried chicken for lunch the course of history and perhaps a few arrests could have been prevented </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this your horse and is it amazing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it wasn't for my showerthought, this person would still have their eyebrow  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LF insured detailer near west michigan thst uses 2 bucket wash and could wax my car </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 19:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there an insured shop in the west michigan area that uses the 2 bucket method I could hire to wax my car? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 19:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDY to revive this sub </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 19:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There should be a sub where people can submit random challenges (to attempt in real life) and people reply with picture proof </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 18:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 04:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://clyp.it/w5u0mcqw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This tree grew over a tombstone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 18:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He let his wife have the better grave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 17:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 11:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frugal and cares about the environment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 10:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus OP tag that as NSFW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 10:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figured as much. I don't see the same country that let all those American prisoners go randomly executing people for falling asleep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 03:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of stock. They had a Comcast day sale a few weeks ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
