<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2450</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Federal Election Commission, a bipartisan agency charged with enforcing and administering the nations campaign laws, will next month zoom past a fairly preposterous milestone given its mission: two years without anyone leading its nonpartisan legal office </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jihadist group Ansar Dine on Tuesday claimed responsibility for two weekend attacks in Mali near the borders with Mauritania and Ivory Coast, and threatened to strike both countries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syria, once one of the world's top exporters of pistachios, said on Tuesday that production of the nuts has plunged 50 percent over the past year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Ten Commandments monument on the Oklahoma Capitol grounds is a religious symbol and must be removed because it violates the state's constitutional ban on using public property to benefit a religion, the Oklahoma Supreme Court ruled on Tuesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rowan County Clerk Kim Davis, the newly elected clerk in Morehead, Kentucky, turned away a local lesbian couple who walked in and asked for a marriage license </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rowan County Clerk Kim Davis, the newly elected clerk in Morehead, Kentucky, turned away a local lesbian couple who walked in and asked for a marriage license </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Palestinian protesters whitewashed a rainbow flag of gay rights that was painted by a Palestinian artist on six slabs of the West Bank separation barrier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slow-motion tragedy for American workers: Lung-damaging silica, other toxic substances kill and sicken tens of thousands each year as regulation falters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 04:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slow-motion tragedy for American workers: Lung-damaging silica, other toxic substances kill and sicken tens of thousands each year as regulation falters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 04:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slow-motion tragedy for American workers: Lung-damaging silica, other toxic substances kill and sicken tens of thousands each year as regulation falters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 04:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police say a fight over gumbo spices ended with the fatal stabbing of a Florida restaurant worker and former Florida State mascot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 03:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Immigration authorities will consider housing transgender detainees based on the gender they identify with in the wake of criticism about detention conditions for the population, officials said on Monday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Immigration authorities will consider housing transgender detainees based on the gender they identify with in the wake of criticism about detention conditions for the population, officials said on Monday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The former dean of the University of Iowa law school didn't commit illegal political discrimination when she passed over a conservative lawyer for teaching jobs, a jury ruled Monday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost a third of China's Great Wall has disappeared: Natural erosion, damage from tourists and people stealing bricks to build houses mean estimates of the walls length now vary from 9,00021,000 km </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost a third of China's Great Wall has disappeared: Natural erosion, damage from tourists and people stealing bricks to build houses mean estimates of the walls length now vary from 9,00021,000 km </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mozambique scraps anti-gay law; Old Portuguese colonial laws removed in victory for gay rights campaigners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Death Penalty Abolitionists Optimistic After SCOTUS Ruling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA wiretapped two French finance ministers: Wikileaks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The US State Department says it is resuming aid to the military in Bahrain, which has been withheld since Bahrain cracked down on demonstrations in 2011 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The misdemeanor trial for five white Cleveland police supervisors accused of failing to control a high-speed car chase that led to two unarmed black people being killed in a 137-shot barrage of police gunfire will be held in a predominantly black suburb, not in county court, prosecutors said Monday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 13 states sue over rule giving feds authority on state water </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 13 states sue over rule giving feds authority on state water </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The federal personnel agency whose records were plundered by hackers linked to China announced on Monday the temporary shutdown of a massive database used to update and store background investigation records after newly discovering a flaw that left the system vulnerable to additional breaches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Incomes rise for bottom 99 pct.; US inequality still worsens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are leaving science in the hands of religious zealots. How so 15th century. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study reveals a common beat in global music </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study reveals a common beat in global music </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Congress Moves to Block Human Embryo Editing: The House of Representatives fiscal year 2016 spending bill also would require religious experts to review recommendations for the new reproductive technique </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Congress Moves to Block Human Embryo Editing: The House of Representatives fiscal year 2016 spending bill also would require religious experts to review recommendations for the new reproductive technique </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Belated Apology to Mozart and Modular Arithmetic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Qatar conceded Monday that "much more needs to be done" on the controversial issue of labour reform following fresh criticism of the 2022 World Cup hosts over the pace of change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US says system reached to give UN access to suspect Iran sites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> France's top administrative court said Monday that border controls on migrants at the Italian frontier were legal and did not violate the Schengen agreement that created Europe's passport-free zone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Obama administration is making it easier for some Indian tribes to obtain federal recognition, addressing a longstanding grievance of many Native Americans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 19:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Obama administration is making it easier for some Indian tribes to obtain federal recognition, addressing a longstanding grievance of many Native Americans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 19:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The African Union stood down its election observers in Burundi on Sunday, saying Monday's parliamentary election would be neither free nor fair, as the speaker of parliament said he had fled after being threatened and heavy gunfire echoed across the capital </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Petty legal filings. Diversionary ballot measures. Counting abstentions as no votes. These are just some of the tactics U.S. oil companies used this spring to quash efforts by investors to win the right to nominate climate experts for board seats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Petty legal filings. Diversionary ballot measures. Counting abstentions as no votes. These are just some of the tactics U.S. oil companies used this spring to quash efforts by investors to win the right to nominate climate experts for board seats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A top Cabinet minister on Sunday urged Colombia's courts to legalize same-sex marriage and support the right of such couples to adopt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas' conservative Republican Attorney General Ken Paxton called the Supreme Court decision giving same-sex couples the right to marry a "lawless ruling" and said state workers can cite their religious objections in denying marriage licenses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 05:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas' conservative Republican Attorney General Ken Paxton called the Supreme Court decision giving same-sex couples the right to marry a "lawless ruling" and said state workers can cite their religious objections in denying marriage licenses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 05:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 17:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't like the festival stay home but keep your insipid comments to yourself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While Bostonians are hesitant to host the Olympics, Americans across the country overwhelmingly support the idea of the games on home turf, according to a new Associated Press-GfK poll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 17:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 16:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is official:

All stages are open today, although Gazebo will open late at 3 PM. 

Please be careful of the park, especially where yellow caution tape is marking off areas of fragile turf.

Thanks to our great audience for a peaceful and considerate closing last night. Now let's get this party started! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders doesn't follow the money: The Vermont senator has an unorthodox strategy for raising campaign cash -- Don't do it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 16:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany's oldest remaining nuclear reactor has been shut down, part of a move initiated four years ago to switch off all its nuclear plants by the end of 2022 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 16:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ecuador has released 201 tortoises on Santa Fe Island in the Galapagos archipelago, where a similar subspecies went extinct more than 150 years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 15:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ecuador has released 201 tortoises on Santa Fe Island in the Galapagos archipelago, where a similar subspecies went extinct more than 150 years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 15:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ecuador has released 201 tortoises on Santa Fe Island in the Galapagos archipelago, where a similar subspecies went extinct more than 150 years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 15:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A cultural row in Iran over concerts being cancelled was reignited Sunday when the country's judiciary chief appeared to criticise President Hassan Rouhani's liberal remarks on the subject </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 15:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greece said it may impose capital controls and keep its banks shut on Monday after creditors refused to extend the country's bailout and savers queued to withdraw cash, taking Athens' standoff with the European Union and the International Monetary Fund to a dangerous new level </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 15:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greece said it may impose capital controls and keep its banks shut on Monday after creditors refused to extend the country's bailout and savers queued to withdraw cash, taking Athens' standoff with the European Union and the International Monetary Fund to a dangerous new level </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 15:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Cruz: Today Is Some Of The Darkest 24 Hours In Our Nations History </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 07:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Cruz: Today Is Some Of The Darkest 24 Hours In Our Nations History </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 07:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gun control won't prevent another Charleston-style shooting, says Jeb Bush: Ahead of South Carolina visit, Republican presidential candidate says it is better to identify potentially violent people before they commit crimes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 04:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Argentine judge ordered the seizure of assets of oil drilling companies operating in the disputed Falklands Islands on Saturday, as rhetoric heats up before October elections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 22 Photos Of Happy Couples Who Got Married Right After The Supreme Court's Decision </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even After Supreme Court Ruling, These States Are Still Resisting Same-Sex Marriage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disney: Selfie sticks will be banned starting next week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Palestinian prisoner held in an Israeli jail and on hunger strike for 53 days is in a critical condition and could die "at any moment", his lawyer said Saturday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The president of Armenia has suspended hikes in household electricity rates in an effort to end the protests that have blocked the capital's main avenue for six straight days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 18:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attack on African Union base in Somalia claimed by al Shabab:There have been condemnations of the attack on the African Union base in Somalia which left dozens of troops dead. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 17:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Christie launches 2016 campaign website before announcing run: With just days to go before the New Jersey Republican officially enters the race, ChrisChristie.com is live with a message: Telling it like it is </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 16:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anthony Kennedy: how one man's evolution legalized marriage for millions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 16:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Fate of Greece May Come Down to a Debate Over the Price of Milk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 16:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of angry, torch-bearing Hondurans marched on Friday to call for the resignation of President Juan Hernandez and demand an independent probe into one of the worst corruption scandals in the country's history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 16:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 73-year-old man has taken his 12,000th ride on his favorite roller coaster at King's Island amusement park in Ohio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 16:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ISIS: An Organizationand an Idea. One jihadist theoreticians vision of leaderless resistance may help explain Islamic State strategy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 15:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lions will return to Rwanda for the first time in more than two decades, wildlife officials have said, after the endangered animal was wiped out following the country's 1994 genocide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 15:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lions will return to Rwanda for the first time in more than two decades, wildlife officials have said, after the endangered animal was wiped out following the country's 1994 genocide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 15:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police in China's financial hub Shanghai took away at least three busloads of environmental protesters outside the municipal government Saturday, preventing the latest rally that started with a rumor that a petrochemical plant could move into the area </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 14:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police in China's financial hub Shanghai took away at least three busloads of environmental protesters outside the municipal government Saturday, preventing the latest rally that started with a rumor that a petrochemical plant could move into the area </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 14:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Heroin Deaths Anticipated Due to High Supply from Afghanistan: A U.N. office warned on Friday that record poppy output in Afghanistan will translate into a spike in heroin-induced deaths, with death rates already rising in Britain and the U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 04:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Heroin Deaths Anticipated Due to High Supply from Afghanistan: A U.N. office warned on Friday that record poppy output in Afghanistan will translate into a spike in heroin-induced deaths, with death rates already rising in Britain and the U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 04:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ConocoPhillips Is the Leakiest Gas Company: Efforts to curb waste are growing but have a long way to go </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 04:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A district court panel in Kansas declared Friday that key parts of a new state law for funding public schools violate the state constitution and ordered an immediate increase in aid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 04:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A district court panel in Kansas declared Friday that key parts of a new state law for funding public schools violate the state constitution and ordered an immediate increase in aid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 04:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Supreme Court on Friday struck down part of a federal law intended keep people convicted of repeated violent crimes in prison longer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that the type of reaction segregationists had to the Civil Rights laws of the 60s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Huckabee: I Will Not Accept Gay Marriage Ruling By Imperial Court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Huckabee: I Will Not Accept Gay Marriage Ruling By Imperial Court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to know if his parents are human and not ATMs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are Republicans going to say now that they have lost the same sex marriage case? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Court says same-sex couples have right to marry in all 50 states </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A prisoner at the U.S. base in Guantanamo Bay, Cuba, who has been on a nine-year hunger strike has been approved for release from the detention center </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Presidential hopeful Donald Trump has refused to release his long-form birth certificate and passport records, despite demanding the same from Barack Obama during the 2012 election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Presidential hopeful Donald Trump has refused to release his long-form birth certificate and passport records, despite demanding the same from Barack Obama during the 2012 election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Infuriated by a U.S. Supreme Court ruling that kept President Barack Obamas healthcare program intact, conservative activists and Republican presidential candidates vowed on Thursday to make the role of the high court a central issue in the 2016 presidential election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Infuriated by a U.S. Supreme Court ruling that kept President Barack Obamas healthcare program intact, conservative activists and Republican presidential candidates vowed on Thursday to make the role of the high court a central issue in the 2016 presidential election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vatican signs historic accord with Palestine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 14:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Python dies after eating giant porcupine in S.Africa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 14:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Python dies after eating giant porcupine in S.Africa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 14:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Somali al Shabaab militants fought a gunbattle with African Union troops after ramming a car laden with explosives into their base south of the capital Mogadishu early on Friday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 06:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Antonin Scalia strongly objected to Thursday's Supreme Court decision upholding the Affordable Care Act, so it was amusing to see Chief Justice John Roberts use Scalia's own dissent in the last major Obamacare case against him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 06:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Crypto' Parasite Outbreaks Increasing in Pools Across US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 04:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if students got free college tuition? Study examines Kalamazoo Promise. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 03:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Dutch court has ordered the government to cut greenhouse emissions by 25 percent by 2020. Large swaths of the Netherlands sit below sea level, leaving citizens vulnerable to rising waters blamed on climate change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 00:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Dutch court has ordered the government to cut greenhouse emissions by 25 percent by 2020. Large swaths of the Netherlands sit below sea level, leaving citizens vulnerable to rising waters blamed on climate change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 00:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a journalist is navigating the dangers of reporting in Egypt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 00:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An international group of academic leaders, journal editors and funding-agency representatives and disciplinary leaders has announced guidelines to further strengthen transparency and reproducibility practices in science research reporting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 00:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chile's students were back on the streets on Thursday, four years after their massive protests won wide public support, this time taking on a left-leaning president whose promise of university reform has fallen short of their demands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 00:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A New Jersey group that claimed it could cure gay people and make them straight has been ordered to pay $72,400 in damages to its former clients, after being found by a jury to have broken the states consumer fraud protection law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 23:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over the objections of safety advocates, the Senate Appropriations Committee on Thursday approved a trucking industry bid to allow longer tandem trucks on the nation's highways </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 22:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service says American white pelicans are nesting at a central North Dakota refuge in near-record numbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 22:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A once-homeless Ohio man whose smooth radio voice made him an Internet sensation says he's running for president as an independent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 22:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As U.S. Probes $12.7 Trillion Treasury Market, Trader Talk Is a Good Place to Start </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 21:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Consumer Financial Protection Bureau released thousands of complaints Thursday from disgruntled customers of banks, credit card companies and other providers of financial services </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 20:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Authorities at Grand Canyon National Park have identified a man from Japan who died during a hike last week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 20:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cruz: Any Candidate Unwilling To Repeal Obamacare 'Should Step Aside' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 20:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cruz: Any Candidate Unwilling To Repeal Obamacare 'Should Step Aside' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 20:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rape on the Night Shift: Under cover of darkness, female janitors face rape and assault </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 19:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Votes To Weaken And Delay The EPA's Climate Rule </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 19:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Votes To Weaken And Delay The EPA's Climate Rule </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 19:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio lawmakers' budget plan includes a small-business tax cut, an increase on cigarettes, new restrictions on abortion clinics, later bar hours for the Republican Convention, block journalists' access to some gun records, and remove a proposed tax on Social Security benefits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 19:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Bank of Canada, frustrated by unilateral U.S. moves which regulate Canadian banks with U.S. subsidiaries, called on Thursday for the possible adoption of a bilateral agreement to clarify responsibilities in winding up failed banks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The judge who blocked a new Kansas abortion law says the state's constitution protects a woman's right to have an abortion separately from the U.S. Constitution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unchecked pollution befouling majestic Lake Titicaca, Bolivia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Court upholds a key tool fighting discrimination in the housing market </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 17:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Court upholds a key tool fighting discrimination in the housing market </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 17:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A state appellate court on Thursday struck down a law designed to make it easier for organizations like the National Rifle Association to challenge local firearms ordinances in court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 17:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cambodia's prime minister has established a special commission to investigate the long-unsolved killings of three labor leaders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 17:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aboriginal prisoners are overrepresented in Canada's federal prisons and waiting longer for parole, according to new numbers from the Public Safety Ministry, which is responsible for corrections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 16:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aboriginal prisoners are overrepresented in Canada's federal prisons and waiting longer for parole, according to new numbers from the Public Safety Ministry, which is responsible for corrections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 16:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With Native American Youth Suicide On The Rise, Tribal Leaders Ask Congress For Sustained Funding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 15:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An international team of researchers have discovered a key missing link in the evolutionary history of turtles. The new extinct species of reptile, Pappochelys, was unearthed in an area that was an ancient lake in southern Germany about 240 million years ago during the Middle Triassic Period </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican presidential contenders face a dilemma when talking about racial issues after last week's racially motivated murders at a South Carolina church, as a new poll shows many Republican primary voters are less likely to see the topic as important </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican presidential contenders face a dilemma when talking about racial issues after last week's racially motivated murders at a South Carolina church, as a new poll shows many Republican primary voters are less likely to see the topic as important </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of Burundi's vice presidents has fled the country and sought refuge in Belgium after urging the president to step down, days ahead of key elections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The European Central Bank should not provide stop-gap financing to Greece even if the debt-wracked country does reach a deal with its creditors, one of its governing council members, Jens Weidmann, said on Thursday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The European Central Bank should not provide stop-gap financing to Greece even if the debt-wracked country does reach a deal with its creditors, one of its governing council members, Jens Weidmann, said on Thursday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US consumers ramp up May spending; largest gain since 2009 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Myanmar's parliament voted against several constitutional amendments Thursday, ensuring that the military's veto power remains intact and that opposition leader Aung San Suu Kyi cannot become president in an election this year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Africa says it will consider withdrawing from the International Criminal Court as a "last resort" following a dispute over Sudanese President Omar al-Bashir, who visited South Africa this month despite an international order for his arrest for alleged war crimes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A UN panel that advises the security council has called for internet and social media companies to respond to the exploitation of their services by al-Qaida and other extremist groups who use the web to recruit fighters and spout increasingly horrific propaganda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 07:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disgruntled Chinese military veterans converged on Beijing to protest for what they say is the government's failure to make good on promised pensions, medical insurance and other benefits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 07:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A police officer was killed and two others seriously wounded Wednesday during a shootout in an Albanian village known as a "cannabis kingdom" for its industrial-scale production of the drug </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 05:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Physicists observe magnetic 'devil's staircase' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 04:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vancouver becomes first Canadian city to regulate growing marijuana market </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 02:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The owners of a coal-fired power plant on the Navajo Nation reached a settlement Wednesday with federal agencies over complaints they flouted rules for permits and violated the Clean Air Act, leading to expanded pollution control upgrades that will cost millions of dollars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 00:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The owners of a coal-fired power plant on the Navajo Nation reached a settlement Wednesday with federal agencies over complaints they flouted rules for permits and violated the Clean Air Act, leading to expanded pollution control upgrades that will cost millions of dollars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 00:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The owners of a coal-fired power plant on the Navajo Nation reached a settlement Wednesday with federal agencies over complaints they flouted rules for permits and violated the Clean Air Act, leading to expanded pollution control upgrades that will cost millions of dollars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 00:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Human Rights Watch accused some of Colombia's top generals Wednesday of links to the "generalized and systematic" execution of civilians, who were then presented as felled FARC guerrillas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 00:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French MPs on Wednesday approved a landmark deal with the United States in which France agreed to pay $60 million in overall compensation to foreign nationals deported to Nazi death camps on French trains in World War II </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 00:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White nationalists condemn church killings, identify with shooter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 21:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Republicans are moving forward with a plan to block a key element of President Barack Obama's strategy for fighting climate change, defying a veto threat from the president </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 21:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Republicans are moving forward with a plan to block a key element of President Barack Obama's strategy for fighting climate change, defying a veto threat from the president </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 21:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker Reveals Extreme Views On Equal Pay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 21:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An abortion rights group is asking a Kansas judge to block the state's first-in-the-nation ban on what it says is the most common method for terminating second-trimester pregnancies, contending that the new law would force women to either accept higher medical risks or forgo abortions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 21:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An inmate convicted of killing three teenage girls and a Bible studies teacher in Ohio in 2000 and a fellow prisoner in 2012 has been found dead of an apparent suicide in his cell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 21:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baku, with infrastructure and personnel in place thanks to the ongoing European Games, are now in a position to launch a serious bid to host the Olympics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China, US in new bid to protect the world's oceans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China, US in new bid to protect the world's oceans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Louisiana's attorney general is showing no signs of backing off his effort to retry the last imprisoned member of the "Angola Three" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gov. Scott Walker is defending the timing of a ceremony to sign two bills loosening Wisconsin's gun laws, saying they were scheduled before nine people were shot and killed last week in a South Carolina church </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gov. Scott Walker is defending the timing of a ceremony to sign two bills loosening Wisconsin's gun laws, saying they were scheduled before nine people were shot and killed last week in a South Carolina church </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whole Foods supermarkets have been routinely overcharging customers by overstating the weight of prepackaged meat, dairy and baked goods, New York City's consumer chief said Wednesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A confidential document obtained by The Associated Press shows that the U.S. and others negotiating a nuclear deal with Iran are ready to offer high-tech reactors and other equipment to Tehran if it crimps programs that can make atomic arms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 09:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brazil Auditors May Reject Government's Accounts For the First Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prominent U.S. flag makers said on Tuesday they will stop manufacturing and selling Confederate battle flags after last week's attack on worshippers at a black church in Charleston, South Carolina </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A U.S. appeals court ruled on Tuesday a decades-old pollution case over nuclear weapons production in Colorado should be sent back to the district court which in 2006 ordered companies that ran the facility to pay damages of $353 million </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 03:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A U.S. appeals court ruled on Tuesday a decades-old pollution case over nuclear weapons production in Colorado should be sent back to the district court which in 2006 ordered companies that ran the facility to pay damages of $353 million </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 03:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The man who was jailed for 22 years  on the fantasy evidence of a single hair: Kirk Odom spent 31 years in prison and on parole after pseudoscientific analysis that has finally been discredited. Now the FBI admits it was wrong  in Odoms case, and many thousands like it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 03:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The House on Tuesday approved a bipartisan bill that would update regulation of harmful chemicals for the first time in nearly 40 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 03:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio is again cracking down on exotic animals, telling owners who don't yet have permits for their tigers, snakes and other wild creatures to put them under quarantine until the state can decide whether they should be removed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 02:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost 18 months into Colorados experiment with legal recreational marijuana, the counter price of an eighth of an ounce is down as much as 40 percent, researchers from New York brokerage firm Convergex reported Monday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 22:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The mysterious Russian agency that hires people to write pro-Kremlin propaganda on the web stepped into the public spotlight for the first time Tuesday as a former employee took it to court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 22:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cosmic Turbulence May Spawn Monster Magnetic Fields: Galactic collisions replicated in the lab help researchers investigate the origins of vastly amplified magnetic fields in the universe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 21:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Netherlands is discussing with its allies an international tribunal to prosecute those suspected of downing a Malaysian airliner over rebel-held eastern Ukraine last year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 21:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doctors are joining the fight against pollution from coal power, adding a significant new dimension to the effort to rein in global warming. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 04:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China Margin Trades Buckle Leaving $364 Billion at Risk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 04:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wal-Mart removing Confederate flag items from stores, online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 04:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wal-Mart removing Confederate flag items from stores, online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 04:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Sotomayor Hides Good News For Abortion Clinics In An Obscure Case About Hotels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 04:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Sotomayor Hides Good News For Abortion Clinics In An Obscure Case About Hotels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 04:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate change may wipe out the last 50 years' gains in global health by ramping up heatwaves, flood, drought, hunger and disease, an expert panel said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 03:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate change may wipe out the last 50 years' gains in global health by ramping up heatwaves, flood, drought, hunger and disease, an expert panel said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 03:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The mighty lion, reclusive cave crabs and the world's rarest sea lion are among nearly 23,000 species at risk of dying out, a top conservation body warned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 03:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The mighty lion, reclusive cave crabs and the world's rarest sea lion are among nearly 23,000 species at risk of dying out, a top conservation body warned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 03:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The mighty lion, reclusive cave crabs and the world's rarest sea lion are among nearly 23,000 species at risk of dying out, a top conservation body warned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 03:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican presidential candidates, GOP lawmakers and the lone black Republican in the House are returning donations from the leader of a white supremacist group cited by Charleston church murder suspect Dylann Roof or giving the money to charity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 00:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican presidential candidates, GOP lawmakers and the lone black Republican in the House are returning donations from the leader of a white supremacist group cited by Charleston church murder suspect Dylann Roof or giving the money to charity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 00:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Early Europeans interbred with Neanderthals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 21:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Early Europeans interbred with Neanderthals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 21:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some 4,000 Armenians took to the streets of the ex-Soviet republic's capital on Monday to protest against the government's decision to hike electricity prices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nun who vandalized uranium bunker likely to remain free: An 85-year-old nun and two fellow Catholic peace activists are likely to remain free because the government said Monday that it will not seek to have a sabotage charge reconsidered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nun who vandalized uranium bunker likely to remain free: An 85-year-old nun and two fellow Catholic peace activists are likely to remain free because the government said Monday that it will not seek to have a sabotage charge reconsidered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
