<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3431</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 18:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just shooting in the dark here, you a psych major? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 18:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He deleted it! What was it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone take governing environments before? Was it a fun and difficult subject? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twinkle twinkle little star has the same melody as the ABC song. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:Why are there no third world countries with white people being the majority of the population? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 14:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Downloading this game now, whats the population? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 14:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is COMP10001 Foundations of Computing full? It says that there are no classes that are on today or in the future for you to register. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 12:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 02:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was young, silly and had some problems. I couldn't stand to hear more than 10 minutes of a Beethoven symphony and would just want to run outside the concert hall. I think it might have been because of my youthful impatience and naivety. I did however, one day stumble across my grandfather's huge collection of classical music and played 
some Schubert on the record player which made me feel emotions I never knew existed in me. Needless to say, after that moment my entire perspective was changed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 17:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love how "The Nation" implies we're all American.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 12:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming the camera was super advanced and could take clear images of our streets even. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If there's a satellite with a camera pointing exactly at Earth around 1000 million lightyears away that could take a picture of Earth and send it back in less than a second, would we be seeing the past if we looked at the images? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 12:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 12:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm assuming that if it could, the minute would be different than here on Earth. Thus are we viewing history? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 10:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found a dusty collection of Karajan conducting the 4th on my grandfather's shelf and am going to play the recoding tonight. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 09:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you soo much for your detailed post! I've just heard the piano quartet and the third Symphony that you suggested and it is absolutely remarkable! Your comments on him really opened my mind to his music and i'm currently trying to appreciate him more. Thank you once again.

Schumann really is a unique gem! 

I'm currently listening to his "Gesnge der Frhe" and it is to say the least, intriguing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 09:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know! The final passages of the third movement just strike home for me!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 09:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who hated classical music with a passion a long time ago, learning to appreciate it made me realise that it is the things that we find boring and incomprehensible that often holds remarkable beauty and wonder. To extend on that, I once hated Mozart and Bach but over the years have come to love them! With Schumann, I feel the same and simply wish to love and understand him more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 09:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's just... incomprehensible to me. The way he writes his music and structures it is just.. foreign...

I think this work really sums up what I mean. It's gorgeous! But at the same time, I don't understand anything!

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pcmO4AKmeDc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worried student here, what exactly are my career options? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 05:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everyone! I'm currently a student studying Geomatics Engineering (accredited) with geology and CS on the side as minors and am worried about my career options. Most posts i've read here say that GIS is mainly a desk job, no field work, etc. and quite a few posts expressed disdain in their jobs. While I still enjoy doing GIS related projects in class, if all else fails, do I have any other options?

Just for clarification, some things covered in education include:

- Engineering Computation (Basically programming with Matlab)
- Engineering math, calculus I,II,III, linear algebra
- Engineering risk analysis
- Database Systems (Programming with SQL)
- Python, C++ and Java
- GIS, GIS and more GIS
- Some remote sensing 
- A handful of geology courses 

I apologise for any inconvenience I may cause but thank you in advance for offering your insight! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 05:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a student who's doing a GIS focused degree (Geomatics Engineering) with geology and CS on the side, i'm worried.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 05:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Update please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone help, I just can't appreciate Schumann! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 04:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been listening to him my whole life and have played a few of his works including his Kinderzsenen, Kriesleriana, Piano Sonata no.1 and Symphonic Etudes. However, I cannot for love of god appreciate and love him as much as I do for other composers like Schubert, Liszt, Beethoven, etc.

Any advice? He's an amazing composer that I know but what am I missing here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's basically a field that focuses on spatial analysis and visualisation and uses stuff from GIS to remote sensing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Planning to get the "ASUS UX501JW-DS71T Touch" for College/Gaming, is it good enough? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 13:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna do an engineering degree with a fair bit of CAD, ArcGIS and programming work like Matlab. I'm also an avid gamer and would love to be able to play demanding games like Deus Ex Human Revolution, Far Cry 4, GTA 5, maybe even Fallout 4 when the time comes? Just wondering whether the specs of this laptop would fit the bill. Thank you for your time! 

- 15.6-inch 10-point touchscreen IPS 4K UHD display
- Core i7 processor and NVIDIA GTX 960M
- ZENBOOK aluminum uni-body design
- 512GB PCIe x4 SSD and Thunderbolt connectivity
- Premium sound design with Bang   Olufsen ICEpower </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 08:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh! It was on my flair! It's called Geomatics/Spatial Engineering! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I call myself an engineer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 07:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean my engineering course isn't really the standard like EE, CE, SE, etc. and while I do graduate with a few engineering accreditations, is my field really an "engineering engineering" field? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
