<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject800</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 14:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Test audiences. Heh. It's the most anti-artistic concept I can think of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 09:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Errr... What mask? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 09:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [So that's the fucker who has been singing this song for four days in my head!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=srEDcmbrmZA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 09:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit never ceases to amaze me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 09:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I looked about this in youtube but found nothing. Do you have any video somewhere? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 09:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So she was like your 3D printer... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 09:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to point out that you are reposting some of your photos. Maybe you should be more careful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 09:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine explaining your grandpa comments like "and my axe" or "rekt". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 09:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, like in that Mtv show. That would be interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 08:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then I'm soulless since many years ago. I got it removed when I was twenty something and I still get my heart broken by girls and feel moved by art works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brian Peppers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im sure this thread got lots of shit and off topic posts. They just edited it out of the picture because it's irrelevant. Of course nowadays you'll get tons more of shitposting, because /b/ is more populated, but you still can do threads like this whenever you want. It's just that the people with imagination are not interested in /b/ anymore because the cancer killed it years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 20:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you believe I almost cry everytime I watch this commercial? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 20:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's obvious. Even so, he was creative enough to make such an awesome thread. Years ago there were lots of people samefagging and doing very original threads like this one. You don't find that kind of stuff nowadays in /b/. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 17:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damned was quite better. I love everything hell and heaven related. But Pygmy was like Palahniuk was parodying his own style and thematic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 16:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2009. Back when /b/ still had epic threads like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 15:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time you didn't look, you were missing thousands of dollars in CGI effects and costume design. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 15:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that artist is Thomas Ott. At least it looks like his style. I think he draws white over a black background. He has some great and eerie comic books like Cinema Panopticum, Greetings from Hellville or The Number 73304-23-4153-6-96-8. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 14:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would recommend Haunted next. And maybe Choke and Rant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 14:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pygmy is sadly the worst thing I have read by Palahniuk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 14:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is one of his best books, because it has the creativity, originality and passion of that young age when he started writing it. It has many unanswered questions maybe because it's more about mistery, poetry and atmosphere than about a definite plot. But every following book gets more and more conventional. The world of this setting and the story of the characters get better explained with more and more details with every book. The last books were almost insuferable for me regarding writing style but I can't deny it's a very very funny and imaginative saga. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 14:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would sell the most valuable books, get some money and donate the rest of the collection to a public library. You would be doing something  great for your community and will feel great. If the collection is as big as you say the library could put it in a special section and put it your friend's dad name in his honor. That would be a great way to remember him. I work in a public library and we have a special collection named after a guy that made a huge donation of old books.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 11:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We all float down here" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 03:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bob </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 03:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I watched that moment twice and I still didn't get what I was looking at. Due to the angle of that shot, it seemed like there really was a tiny woman swimming in milk right there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 11:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. You are damn good. In fact I think I've seen some of your work before in tumblr. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 01:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have some illustrations online that we can see?
Not necessarily sleep related. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 15:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe it was... A ghost! *gasp* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 12:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have experienced it lots of times for years, even several times in the same night. But it still scares me. I panic, but, well, I can't do anything, because you can't move, you can only breathe. So I've learned to just relax and wait until my body reacts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 12:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, that took forever. But, yeah, cool video indeed. I like all I see by Adult Swim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 12:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you have three different accounts? Couldn't you just unsuscribe from the subs you didn't like and subscribe to new ones? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 01:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you'll like White Suns. Their last album, Totem, is from 2014.

http://whitesuns.bandcamp.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liars -- Plaster casts of everything [Rock] (2007) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 01:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 01:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of the best things I've seen in Youtube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 01:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And how would you say Reddit was before? I'm quite new here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 22:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D-d-do you wanna go out with me on a date? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 20:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So,it's made of [vantablack](http://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/blackest-is-the-new-black-scientists-have-developed-a-material-so-dark-that-you-cant-see-it-9602504.html)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 20:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a very cool old drawer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 20:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I checked the Nightvale wiki: http://nightvale.wikia.com/wiki/Fey

Fey was merely a piece of self-aware software trapped in a heavily-defended metal box

And I guess the following can't be considered canon, since it's from the Thrilling Adventure Hour   Welcome to Night Vale Crossover:

Pemily Stallwark (played by Molly Quinn) is erased from existence. Before returning to existence moments later, she finds herself facing an endless stream of numbers and is forced to read them out loud, briefly breaking into "Roar" by Katy Perry at one point. This was a reference to both characters being voiced by Quinn. A "techno-theological debate" from earlier in the episode over whether or not robots (and presumably computers) have souls may hint that Stallwark is Fey's future reincarnation.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't subestimate human kind. It's capable of the most strange acts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A computer program? I thought she was a real person, like those people reading numbers and talking in the "number stations". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you mean Casper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 17:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an amazing story. I think Im gonna translate it into spanish and post it in one of my blogs, where sometimes I talk about weird and cool things that happen in videogames and virtual worlds.

Thanks for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 17:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chronenberg-esque! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 17:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apruebo esto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 12:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "If this thing had happened, then this other thing would have happened."
"What other thing?".
"I don't know".

Anyway, I admit my comments are useless. The world is not gonna change thanks to them. And I know I'm not gonna convince you that you made a thread that makes no sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 12:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you made a useless thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 11:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A happening like what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 09:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, thanks to smart phones and access to google translate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 00:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you invite your friend to come to Reddit and elaborate on this? It's quite interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 23:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> French sounds great but I like even more the sound of portuguese. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 23:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a european citizen like me, this is a very interesting aproach to the life of an american teenager in the 00's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 23:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I normally don't use them. I know where to get the album in mp3 for free, like Soulseek, torrents or Mega. What's more, if I have the record it's probably because I already listened to it on mp3 and liked so much I decided to buy it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 23:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. When you sneeze you expel saliva, and saliva uses to smell bad, because of lots of bacteria. At least, my saliva smells bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 23:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Journalists and professional photographers will continue using real cameras. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 23:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Is a video good too?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UA4sifQ3ymk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 23:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm following "Louie" but this 5th season had only 8 episodes and the last one was recently released.

I can recommend you some of my favorite shows: The Wire, The Sopranos, Rick and Morty, South Park, Twin Peaks, Lost, Friends, Adventure Time... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 23:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You weat matter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 22:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, he definitely looks like a frog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, let me see if I got this right... They were black? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comic is quite old and have been posted here several times before. And I don't care.

Also recomending "Fuan no tane/seeds of anxiety". Most fucking terrifiying manga I've ever read. I read it alone at home at night and really felt uneasy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a true ancient 4chan meme. I hadn't seen in for years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 18:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, my sweet summer child... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 18:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He will love to talk with you about ancient memes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 17:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Thank you for the debate. It's been exciting. I even learned a pair of things about my own history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 17:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course nowadays there are a lot of people against muslims in Spain, not only because of terrorism, but because millions of moroccan people started migrating here, and, you know, people are always afraid of immigrants, specially if they have a different religion and skin colour.

And yeah, while the Al Andalus era there was a real war between christians and muslims, the reconquest, and our hate for muslims comes from that long. 

But I can assure you we don't hide or reject our muslim past. Is taught in the school. I am from Murcia, which was a muslim territory and we still have a strong legacy from them. We have moorish monuments, historical personalities like [Ibn Arabi](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ibn_Arabi), streets designed by moorish and archeological remains. We even have a festivity called "Moros y Cristianos" (moors and christians) were people dress like medieval muslims and christians knights and courtiers, they make parades an emulate fights and battles. But I must admit I'm not proud of this festivity. It looks like a cheap cultural parody with those cheap ridiculous disguises.

Being that said, I'm not gonna lie to you: a lot of people now in Spain are racists and islamophobics who think that muslims are terrorists that should go back to Morocco.

But Al Andalus, yeah, that is cool for us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 14:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll see if the number comes to me in my dreams tonight. If it doesn't, I'll try to elaborate some kind of occultist and symbolic ritual, probably summoning the spirit of Alan Turing and using a random numbers generator or something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 14:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll post this here since I think it can be of general interest.

There is a debate going with the OP questioning if the term "pre-spanish" is appropiate. He affirms spanish era started after Al Andalus (moorish occupation in the south of the Iberian Peninsula for 8 centuries). Some of us affirm Spain was Spain before Al Andalus, being called Hispania even before the year 27 b.C. and that there were Spanish people living in the peninsula, people from different civilizations and origins, like romans and visigoths.

So, I asked a friend of mine. He is not a historian but has a degree in classic languages as latin and greek, so he knows one or two things about Spanish history. Here are some interesting points he gave me:

1. As OP affirms, modern Spain was in a great degree stablished after Al Andalus, after the "reconquest" when the Catholic Kings expeled the muslims from the peninsula. The feudal system, the main regions, the catholic religion were stablished then. So, Spain doesn't equal Hispania.

2. It's not so simple. You can't say Spain started being Spain after Al Andalus. Before Al Andalus there were the visigoths, and before them the hispanoromans living there. So Spain would be an equation consisting in: Hispanoromans + Visigoths + Moors / Reconquest.

3. There are books wrote by experts still debating about when did Spain started being Spain, so it's an open debate.

4. There is the idiomatic question. We didn't started talking arabic after Al Andalus, but kept using the same language we used before they came. Spanish comes from latin, not from arabic. It's a corruption of latin, so to say. So, linguistically, we have a "hispanic" identity, although we adopted a lot of words from arabic, like "almohada", "algibe" (just to put two examples) and the name for a lot of rivers like "Guadalquivir".

5. Indeed, you can't deny the Al Andalus era. Nobody is trying to do that. But you can't say Spain as a concept or territory didn't exist before them. It's more complex than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
