<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9154</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shadow Temple or Spirit Temple first? Zelda: OoT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm playing it again right now and am conflicted which I should do first. Would it help me more to do the Shadow first to complete the Spirit or vice versa? I did Forest-Fire-Water, got Boggoron's Sword and fire arrows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't. I've tried. Website doesn't work I've been trying for a few weeks now at least once a day. I'm not interesting in reading about people talking shit and saying things they wouldn't say in person. It just doesn't do anything for me.
And if I want porn i just go to xnxx.com or /r/riskyclicks, or some other porn subreddit. But I don't have a need to talk shit about fat people, LGBT, or anything else. It just isn't something that I care to do even though I know I'm anonymous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do smoke pot for my Crohn's. High in CBD is best. 

I don't care what the entire thread was about you commented on free speech being denied because reddit banned some fucking subreddit that hates on fat people (so fucking what...get over it)- it's not. It's like you haven't even read the 1st amendment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I hardly eat- I have Crohn's Disease incredibly hard to gain weight with all the blood and shit that comes out of my ass. Reddit banning a subreddit shaming fat people does not deny you free speech. 

Free speech only means congress will not make a law denying you the ability to say what you want. Free speech doesn't mean Reddit, a website, can't ban a subreddit if it wants to- if the guy who made it or whoever runs it wants to do it- they can. It's not much different than a mod banning someone for saying shit either. 

The only guarantee you have with free speech (with the exception of libel) is that you won't be prosecuted for what you say- it doesn't mean you won't get fired from a job, have a website ban you...etc 

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No sorry it's my fault I meant to reply to /u/AllRubyx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ? What law did congress make that denied you free speech?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're allowed to do whatever you want. I'm just curious why it would be better than reddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was the best part of the movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your free speech isn't lost. Free speech only means the government won't make a law limiting what you say (with the exception of libel, or words that present clear danger). So...you can still say whatever you want- but that doesn't mean it won't get you banned on a website for it. 

Why should I care if Reddit bans a subreddit about hating fat people? My freedom isn't being taken away. That doesn't bother me. Good for them. This is there website- they made it- they can do whatever they fuck they want with it. 

If you don't like that- why don't you just make your own the way you want it? That seems like a good solution. You can find ANYTHING on the internet. My freedom of speech isn't being limited. It never have. Just because this person disagrees with you doesn't make them ignorant nor myself and it doesn't make me shortsighted. 

You are foreseeing a trickle down where "banning subreddits against fat people...well shit...next i won't be allowed to 'fag' or 'fuck' on this website and anywhere on the internet...my life is doomed!!" 

I think you're overreacting a bit and foreseeing a future that will not happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why would it be better than reddit?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> doesn't work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Spock. Spock vaporizes Rock.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but, in a live action movie it would be pretty cool I think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Person Jedi: How cool would this be in an actual Star Wars movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't know what brown is. He can't conceptualize brown if he's colorblind (greyscale)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 19:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 425,218 

Bucky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 18:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You don't say much do you?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5UH2raPtbw4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 18:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he probably thought it meant something like voluptuous  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 18:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah lots ofshows still have insulting humor like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 16:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's not my first time. just its been a decade lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 15:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I figured out my confusion. I was freaking out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Song of Storms from Ocarina of Time sounds a little like Game of Thrones title theme music. (At about the 7 second mark) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 15:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 15:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm an idiot. I figured it out. thanks. It's been about 10 yrs since I've played and I really am trying to do everything this time. 

Side note: Does Song of Storms sound like Game of Thrones theme? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ocarina of Time question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 15:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I am in the forest temple, I got the two keys in the beginning, killed the Stalfos for the map. I went into the door you have to use the song of time on and had two keys total at this point. I know I was supposed to use the hookshot to make the water in the well go down well i accidentally fell off the cliff and exited the door to try again but the door now has bars over it. How do i get rid of those bars?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DO ME DO ME DO ME DO ME </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 06:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mmm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 06:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I do. Doesnt bother me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 06:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nah i thought it was awful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No that's not enough they could become resistant strains of spider. Here's what we have to do. 

1. Immediately set fire to the gloves using a blow torch. 

2. Spiderlings may have escaped, burn down the house/garage with napalm...lots and lots of...napalm (thank you Dan Akroyd)

3. Leave the country.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AHHHHH
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harry.....*tugs at shirt*....H-H-H-Haar rrryyy!! 

"WHAT RON!?!?!?!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet so. I just thought Wilder was terrible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting considering Dahl disliked Wilder's version considerably. So much so he refused to sign over rights for the sequel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm I thought his acting was great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. I read it as, "The thing that put me off ... I like Johnny Depp, I like him, as an actor I like him very much ... but when I saw little pieces in the promotion of what he was doing, I said I don't want to see the film, because I don't want to be disappointed in him" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i liked alice in wonderland.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked Depp's version better lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> downvotes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 22:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. Don't agree at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 22:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well this match wasn't particularly as close as 6-4, 6-4. A lot of tennis players have the skill to beat Serena- but they don't. It's not just beating her- it's consistently beating her. I don't think anyone but Venus can say that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 22:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't disagree Graf had amazing skills, but not any better than Serena's skill. Yes she won 22 slams before she turned 30, but did she win any when she was over 30? No. I think that's impressive when you consider at what age most women retire in tennis. It's even more impressive when you consider her dominance at her age. It's not like she just won one or two close ones after she turned 30, she pretty much revamped her career.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 22:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you are. There wasn't anyone like Serena in the past. She is unique.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 22:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Court has 24 grand slams, but pro's weren't allowed to play in grand slams for a time- so i don't think you can consider hers as the number to reach. 22 is the number.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strings? She's in the conversation of being the greatest collection of loops we've ever abstractly looped.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ESPN isn't exactly the greatest place for good sports news. 

Edit: So you think ESPN is awesome?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They call me Mr. Glass  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read this as A E the cable television channel for some reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blastoise headbutt attack fails against Meowth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 14:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shutup do gooder. Go do good things on your own. We're fucking rebels, if we wanna not replace blinds and find a way to not pay for it- we fucking will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 14:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [eerily familiar](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PKffm2uI4dk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 14:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So your doodles are pretty much just taken from those [sad cat](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PKffm2uI4dk) commercials with the morgan freemanesque voice. So is it his ridiculous personality or ar eyou just projecting the personality you see from cat advertisements?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vat 69...mmm  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no sex in the champagne room </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> synonym cinnamon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 12:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 422,383 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Dog Mediator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 12:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 12:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 422,379 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 12:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 422,376 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 11:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pls OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 11:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So did you take a pic of the room as it looks now with a lamp/light on?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 11:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mmmm reflective paint </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Citronella Candles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 11:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are citronella candles safe to use indoors for just a small amount of time like an hour or two?  

Side unrelated question: Anyone know where I can buy online a scented candle that burn for a really long time like 100+ hours?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stevenology* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 19:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Oh good you're awake- thought you were dead. I love you!! Now pet me human. I need pets since you're awake. I peed on stuff, saw you were awake. Sorry"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it's not the same religion though- I know it appears to be because they have the same book, but denominations are vastly different from one another. They interpret things differently- making them, to me, same God but different religion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 421,696 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 421,694 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 421,691 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw this on my friend's facebook trying to get people to buy it. Probably NSFW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 421,689 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I was raised Lutheran. We obviously came from different Lutherans lol because the Lutherans I was around were not humble, or take care of people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 421,683 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 13:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This is far more fucking important.

Unless drunken behavior leads to rape and murder (because that's never happened). Also, there was no murder in Naples, FL on July 9th 2015.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 12:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She needs fucking pets human. Pet her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 12:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  for basically no reason at all

You mean for disorderly intoxication? He pulled a fire alarm. That's why the officer's arrived at the scene, his wife was too drunk to be left alone so they took her until she sobered up and could care for herself. I live in SWFL and all they did was put him in the drunk tank until he was sober which is just 8 hours. He wasn't charged. They took him for disorderly intoxication- that's pretty normal down here in SWFL since we get so many tourists. There's nothing wrong with that. Had they not pulled the fire alarm for no reason the cops wouldn't have came at all. By the way, you can get in trouble for pulling a false alarm too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police: Drunk man asks officers to tickle him - Naples, Florida </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 12:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 12:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  BUT I WANT TO BE A REAL BOY PAPA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Live Animals Sold As Keychains in China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 12:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 11:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wanna meet this girl. She sounds fun as fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 11:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably too much grillin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 11:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've .... I've used reddit in jokes with real people and I'm ostracized for it :(.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 10:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I do have a metal arm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Foot Song </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 09:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 09:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can be shit buddies. I shit a river of blood and you shit Hawaiian Lava hills of fresh stink. 

I once created a rap song. A couple years ago (mind you I can't keep a beat and I certainly can't write). I had this ex girlfriend who had OCD of her feet being touched. Whenever someone touched it, she had the touch the other foot exactly the same then clean them off as they were 'dirty'. For example, if you splashed on foot with water she had to splash the other. So my friend (a drummer) made a beat and I wrote some weird lyrics and we made a weird music video for it. 

This is for your viewing pleasure sir. [The Foot Song 2013](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=geB2HNTHm4Q) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 08:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure you don't have Ulcerative Colitis or Crohn's Disease? I have UC, and I can tell you I give birth to death- daily.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 07:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOU WILLLL TRYYYYY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your post seems to be deleted. Please stop harassing me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 15:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MYSTERION! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 12:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 421,234 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 09:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, this is Patrick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 07:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ing shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 04:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 421,213 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 15:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My voice isn't super manny manny man, but it's certainly lower than Mike Tyson. I am reasonably tall, kind of, at 6.3 and I am avg weight and I have a bushy beard- no mustache- would give me raper face. Sinewy arms are a yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 421,008 

originally i was going to go for the assist but you said go for the GET lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 421,006 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 421,004

i only sniped once. I won't do it again. But if I've been counting or trying to count the last 1-200 i dont consider it sniping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 421,001

wasn't a snipe! I was counting the last 150 or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> congrats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 421,000

2nd time that's happened to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,969 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,967 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,965 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,963 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,952 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,950 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,938 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,924 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,922 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,920 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,918 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,891 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,889 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,887 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,885 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,883 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,881 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,879 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,877 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,875 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,873 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,871 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,865 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,863 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,861 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,849

lemme get some music hold up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,847

yOU WANNA RUN IT? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,845 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,843 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,841 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420,840 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 11:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am OP. And no I wasn't saying that. The 'Stairway' is a firework- he uses fireworks to make it work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 11:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/peoplesdaily/article-3126861/Chinese-artist-creates-stunning-1-650ft-ladder-sky-FIREWORKS.html

"The ladder, which was made of metal wire and aluminum, was filled with gunpowder and attached to the bottom of a hot air balloon.
The balloon, which was made with special material, was launched from a boat off the shore of nearby Huiyu Island." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 11:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it's not. 

"The ladder, which was made of metal wire and aluminum, was filled with gunpowder and attached to the bottom of a hot air balloon. 

The balloon, which was made with special material, was launched from a boat off the shore of nearby Huiyu Island."

It most certainly is not [fake.](http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/peoplesdaily/article-3126861/Chinese-artist-creates-stunning-1-650ft-ladder-sky-FIREWORKS.html)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 11:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please stop harassing me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
