<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4510</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 06:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turn the vibrate on your watch, join 50 group chat's, apply watch to your girl #shakeitlikeasaltshaker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 06:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe I can read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 05:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANK YOU!!!!!!!!! WHEN THIS SHIT HITS 2.32 I'M GOING TO SAMS CLUB AND BUYING SOME FUCKING INDUSTRIAL SIZED BOXES OF CEREAL AND FUCKING PIZZA ROLLS #YOUonlyOWNamdONCE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 04:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *slaps* Don't be such a pussy. I'm still in, stay strong!!! We're going to be rich!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 04:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I didn't know that until about a week ago. You know who told me about Garmins dope smart watches? My grandmother. #YOLODOLO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 23:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stupid fucking 3 days settling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 22:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. I just could never understand GoPro. It's a camera company with a one trick pony. I think the people that would use one, have it. I think 5Y down the road it will look a lot like Garmin does now. With that said, I know you're not investing for 5y down the road, hope you make bank. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 22:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't trust it. Don't like it. Won't play with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 21:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know a Soros or a Buffett? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 19:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off, thank you. Second. I went ahead and for shits and giggles repurchased around .30 (only $500 worth) but I was curious if this was going to go all willy wonka after-hours and in the morning and I'm fine with losing $500.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 16:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 05:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have prophets, fuck, where do you buy those?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 03:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Riding this money train with you brother. Are we taking out my yacht or yours? I've got $2,000 at 2.30 = GONNA BE A THOUSANDAIRE TOMORROW !!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 02:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw about 60 million people running off the bridge jumping for a full day and I couldn't see exactly where they were jumping but I could hear them going WEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE, so at the very end of the day I decided to jump. It was a really fun ride but I went back up and there was 62 million people jumping today but the bridge just felt different so I decided to ask whats down there this time. But once again... I decided fuck it and jumped. I pray you hear me yelling Weeeeeee in the morning. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 00:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After Hours is looking positive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 21:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 21:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second question, I know nobody truly knows with a stock this volatile but what should people be looking at to help indicate the direction of this stock?

Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PTBI - Where the hell are we headed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 20:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh great leaders where the hell is this one headed? I've jumped out and jumped back in. Debating keeping it overnight, I figured I would see what great advice I could receive to continue to YOLO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 17:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got $2,000 just sitting around on AMD for the last week or so at $2.30.

*high five* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 21:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope so. I showed up late to the party and ended up losing money. I bought back in at $5.95. Hoping to recoup my losses and maybe a little in the morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 21:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does today end? I'm tempted to jump in right before the day closes out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 16:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do I get in on this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 04:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I hesitantly gave him the card and stood over his shoulder watching him. I wish I had a cooler story but basically he explained the law and I acted nonchalant while also googling the law on my phone and realized we probably weren't being robbed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 03:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know nothing John Snow!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 22:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was passing through New Jersey with my girlfriend and we stopped to get gas. I legitimately thought the guy was trying to steal my girlfriends credit card. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 21:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Garett Richards.. It was a great day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LG 47LX9500 Pricing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 20:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was the closest thing I could find to an appropriate place to post this:

How much do you think I should sell my LG 47LX9500. It's hardly been used, I really mean that. Probably turned on once every 3 months. I could use it but if I could sell it for a decent amount, I don't watch enough TV to really care and would just buy something cheaper. 

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 19:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sure as hell hope it doesn't because I've purchased ~~a lot of it's stock today~~, well a lot for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 19:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You killed it today with AVEO  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 19:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I only spent $500 so I just don't really care and I'm riding it down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 18:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bought in at 7.25 and it just keeps dropping, should I take my losses? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
