<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9175</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 11:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It bothers me that it doesn't bother me more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 11:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be sure to remember that the next time someone tells me I should raped by a pack of niggers.

Here's a little more light reading.

http://gawker.com/5582644/all-the-terrible-things-mel-gibson-has-said-on-the-record </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 11:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It means nothing that a celebrated actor is racist, homophobic, anti-semtic and violent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 11:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He pled no contest to misdemeanour battery. So there's at least one person he hurt.

Polanski is scumbag and deserves prison.

Broderick was in a car accident 30 years ago. The family of the victim forgave him. Hardly the same thing.

I agree that Gibson was great to watch but he has ruined his own career. It is no one's fault but him.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 11:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /s ?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 11:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repeating the things that actually happened and are on the official court records? 

Events that there are audio recordings of? 

The Gibson freely admits happened?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 10:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pictures of well dressed tall/fat/skinny/short/hunchback/neckless guys and why they look good.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 08:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Portal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 05:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They forgave the first half-dozen fuck ups. But even Hollywod has limits. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 05:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mel Gibson has show extraordinary hate and vitriol towards everyone from African-Americans to the gay community.
He threatened his wife and pled no contest to a  battery charge. He's an alcoholic, self-destructive, megalomaniac shit of a man. 

But sure, blame the Jews.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 04:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In smaller communities, the scammers need to go undetected and run scams in which the victim is unaware they have been taken for a ride.

One of the criteria that con artists seek out is situations in which their victims are compelled to trust them. For example, older people are scammed more often than younger people not because they are gullible but, as you age and become more separated from your community, you need to trust others more.

A canny con man could very easily take advantage of the levels of trust that are necessarily built up in small communities. 

For example, if there is only one butcher in town, you're less likely to question the quality and source of his meat. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 03:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-l_rMkXZfl8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 02:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Micheal Bay has never shared anything still in his life.

Here's a better representation...

http://i.imgur.com/6jIlLjw.gifv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 01:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally got a good base suit. Now what? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 00:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After years of wearing shitty suits that don't fit I've got a nice suit that works with my body shape and complexion. 

Any suggestions for ties, pocket squares and shirts?

EDIT: I'm a speaker on the subject of con artists, scams and deception. I'm happy to look a little eccentric.

http://imgur.com/EGXeZ0H

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 00:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, looks great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 00:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My vote is for yellow. Love it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 06:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have very specific kinks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 05:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Because he's the Joker Gotham deserves, but not the one it needs right now. So we'll hurl abuse at him on the internet. 

Because he can take it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 04:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote an article a few years for a magazine about the Spanish prisoner and how it has evolved as technology has evolved. 

The earliest versions of the scam, which dates back 500 years, was much the same as today. The con man needs to rescue a spanish prisoner held prisoner with her vast fortune in a foreign land. If you'll pay for the rescue mission, the money and the girl are yours.

Check out this short story from 100 years ago.

http://www.hidden-knowledge.com/funstuff/spanishprisoner/spanishprisoner1.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 04:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck yes.

The night racing looks great.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 04:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it but could never carry it off myself.

You need skinny legs and/or jeans to make that work, otherwise you'll end up looking like you're in a cacoon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 04:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out windsor smith in Preston for cheaper brown boots. 

I'm pretty rough on my shoes and I find WS are a good halfway in terms of price vs. quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 04:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just spent two hours at Doncaster trying to find a jumper. 

FCUK has a nice navy one with horiztonial ribbing. I'm too fat to carry it off but I like it. 

http://www.frenchconnection.com.au/knitwear/ribbed-cotton-crew-neck-knit/w2/i7920653_2405753/

I ended up getting this sweater from country road.
http://www.countryroad.com.au/shop/man/clothing/sweats/60178003/Printed-Sweat.html

Do you have a big head or broad shoulders? If so, you can stretch out jumpers real quick. 




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 04:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it. The colour is great and it looks well constructed. It does look a little like a handbag in the photo.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 03:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could fit at least three Jared Letos into your average Juggalo.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 01:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the full raptor episode

http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x2cyrqo_archer-archersaurus-unaired-pilot-episode-season-1-episode-0_fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm an author, entertainer and collector of scams. What interests you most about scams? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 01:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm recreating my websites and bringing the content up to date and would love to know what you find most interesting about con artists and scams.

The history of famous swindles?
The psychology scams?
The latest scams doing the rounds?
Movies about con artists and scams?
 
scams.wikispaces.com.au
www.conman.com.au </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 16:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to be clear, we're talking about the twin raping his brother's wife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 10:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thread was actually about a weird anime where the actors were told to say whatever the hell they wanted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditor watches Raptor episode first and thinks that's what the show is like every week and gives up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 06:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 05:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you kick a guy with gun?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 14:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free Willy
http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/b/b5/Free_willy.jpg

Rocky 4
http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTg3ODk5ODE0NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNDkzODM1NA@@._V1_SX640_SY720_.jpg

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 10:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I found the pic, not the pudding pie. It's an old image.

Sad thing is, if I had them, I would have eaten them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 03:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have to ask... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 01:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "Warning - Item Baby chicks ground alive might contain content that is not suitable for all ages."

Nope. Nope. Nope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone recommend a good tailor in the north? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 15:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 02:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think about it this way, you were the pioneer, you beat the tracks and built the roads of bad behaviour that your 14 year old brother is now the recipient of.

Every fight you had with your parents, every time they panicked because they had no one what they were doing, it was making your siblings life a little easier.

Don't be angry, be pleased you could make your parent and brother's live's easier in the future. 

You're the Johnny Appleseed of families.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 14:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're fantastic films but none are ground breaking. 
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 04:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All great films! But none of those films are ground-breaking or exciting though.

Sixth sense is a classic premise done really well, Toy Story 2 is sequel and green mile is shawshank redemption with magic. 

Good solid films in a dull year.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 01:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1999.

We had Fight Club, American Beauty and The Matrix but, while fantastic, none of those films are particularly ground breaking. 

The year was also packed full of films by filmmakers who had done better. Phantom Menace, Eyes Wide Shut, The Spy Who Shagged Me, Tarzan, The World Is Not Enough, Notting Hill....

1999 was a year for playing it safe, limping to end of the lackluster nineties.

Also, Wild Wild West.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 14:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too late! 

:( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 22:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hitler himself.

http://www.imdb.com/name/nm0386944/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five star review for Jonestown - Guinea Pigs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 02:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 02:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank you to all the redditors who came out to support Jonestown on Saturday and Tuesday night. Here's the first review from those shows. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 00:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know where I can see Llamas in Melbourne? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 06:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my wedding anniversary tomorrow. Thought I'd take my wife to see llamas. 

Chicks dig llamas. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 05:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They flowered a little last spring hence my interest in them. Only a few flowers.

A few bulbs snapped off so I'm trying my luck in the garden with the rest of my winter bulbs. (I'm in Australia and it's autumn) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 04:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! We found a half dozen of them when we moved into our new house. They've been sitting down the back of the garden for two years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 03:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're dead right down to the roots. I can cut off the dead leaves but then I'm left with dead stalks right down low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have any tips about what I should do about the dead parts of this orchid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 02:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free double pass to geeky comedy festival show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 01:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm performing in Guinea Pigs at Melbourne International Comedy Festival. 

We've had great crowds and great reviews (Here's one: http://www.melbartsfash.com/109918) until now but, on Tuesday night we've got the Herald Sun coming in.

For some reason, people actually read the Herald Sun reviews so we'd like to stack the deck with our kind of crowd. 

Check out the description below and, if it tickles you, hit me up in my inbox for a free double pass.

http://www.comedyfestival.com.au/2014/season/search?q=Jonestown submit=

EDIT: We had over fifty responses and all the tickets are gone! Thanks! However, please feel free to send me a message anyway in case we need to paper the room on any other nights. If you'd like to come on Tuesday night anyway, it is tight arse Tuesday and tickets are already super cheap.

EDIT 2: Thank you so much to everyone who came. We had a full house in the end which was fantastic. We even had two guide dogs in the front row. https://www.facebook.com/GuideDogZeke?fref=ts
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 06:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, not great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 00:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I like to keep in short because it grows so fast. When it gets just a little longer, I look really bald. Like here.

http://joy.org.au/backseat/2015/03/31/micf-guinea-pigs-take-over-jonestown/ 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 23:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of great stuff on the IMDB triva page.

http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0088930/trivia?ref_=tt_trv_trv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 23:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carrie Fisher was the original Miss Scarlet but was replaced at the last minute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 04:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, that's just what my head looks like :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying To Stand Up (a short documentary) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 13:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone suggest the quickest way to Cheltenham from Preston round 8 in the morning? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 08:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got to drive to Cheltenham tomorrow morning. I assume Punt going South is just as bad as Hoddle in the morning? 

Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 07:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BWOOOOONNGGG
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G2jUhnCU9iA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 13:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've used them a couple of times. They're great for sick kids as you don't wait long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 00:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can recommend this guy. He's very funny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 10:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly what I thought.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is "per centage" correct? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 08:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that both percent or per cent are correct but what about 'per centage'?

The in-house style guide insists on per cent.

Should I also use per centage? 

EDIT: Just to provide more context, this is in a piece of dialogue in a second novel. In the first book, the publisher used per cent. The word percentage did not occur.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 01:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phew! I find going to the movies and seeing non-white people very uncomfortable. 

;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think of the decision to change the ethnicity of the Attack On Titan characters from European to Japanese? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 00:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i41ZKisDeoE

The original story is set in Europe and draws from European history, politics, landscape and architecture.

The titans stride through cobblestone streets between Georgian houses and buildings, smashing churches. By making the characters Japanese, a lot of what made the series unique gets lost.

Do you think the film could suffer in the same way The Last Airbender suffered?




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 11:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was tonight!

But we're doing another one Sunday at 4:30 on Northcote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 05:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting your joke is the first time I've used my English major in years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free comedy festival test show tomorrow night. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 01:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're free tomorrow night (Thursday) and love comedy that is half-baked and under-rehearsed, we'd love you to be in the audience for the test show of our sketch comedy show.

It is at 6:30 in Collingwood. 

Send me a message if you're keen!

Not cost at all, just your honest opinion.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 22:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downvoted for getting safety dance stuck in my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 12:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeremy is misunderstood. I've worked with him for years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying To Stand Up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 12:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 03:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fairfax, for the past few years, has been outsourcing a lot of their vital services overseas. http://www.crikey.com.au/2014/05/07/more-photographers-subeditors-to-go-in-new-fairfax-restructure/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying To Stand Up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 06:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 04:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, but viewership doesn't mean successful in the same way for Netflix as it does on network TV.

An original show offers Netflix prestige, publicity and air of quality that 20 year old repeats won't. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ratings Advice with Jonestown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 02:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 23:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got to Northside as well. I'm straight and have had nothing but great experiences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 12:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit. Why don't I read the comments before I watch these trailers?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 10:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll probably be disturbed by the whole show then... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made an interactive twitter adventure called The Guinea Pig Room. Hope you enjoy it! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 03:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 01:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have and continue to do so.

But I'm referring to a rapist who has managed to escape justice and who regrets his actions. 

If a person is truly remorseful, I would imagine they would want to make up for what they did. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 12:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original AMA...

http://www.reddit.com/r/melbourne/comments/2xn6ma/i_used_to_work_at_revolver_ama/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 23:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I enjoy a pilot or first couple of episodes of a new series I'll often wait until the send of the season before I get hooked and binge watch it all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 12:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is also an Australian version of Wilfred if you're interested in seeing what else we've got. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 21:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's me being a killjoy...

http://expertvagabond.com/elephants-in-thailand/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 02:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a pretty good send off I guess.

But Aubrey Plaza's send off for him was much better.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0ZQQfkJ7hZY

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 23:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'BROAD CITY!' he shouted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 23:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a web series but check out The Katering Show on YouTube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 23:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brooklyn 99 is getting better. It's progression reminds me a lot of Parks and Rec in the first two seasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 23:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it first came out, a lot of reviewers missed the satire and thought it was a serious film. 

It is only in hindsight that people see the film for what it is.

He has similar problems with Robocop and Showgirls.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 06:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's only one Scott Walker.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jMUk1R_fKEA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's just stop for a moment to consider the fact that Alabama has gay marriage and Australia does not. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 05:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 01:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I'll give it a go. 

Does @rpgshowla still work?

I'm following the instructions used to create this:

https://twitter.com/wnd_go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 01:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consider me educated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 01:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you're giving those woman or men enough credit. 

They're geeky but not hideous. Their stupid pillows are as creepy as all fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 22:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm a frenchman living in Texas. I stopped a cafe and ordered a coffee"

http://data.whicdn.com/images/26000176/tumblr_m1r9nv5zRU1qjsveoo1_500_large.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for old twitter accounts for a Choose Your Own Adventure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 01:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm building a Choose Your Own Adventure on twitter.

I've been told, if I set up new accounts that don't have a lot of followers and tweets straight away, I can run the risk of being deleted as spam.

I'm searching for some old accounts I can steal. Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 22:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe you. 

You tried to take him down with a lollipop back in '04. 

http://www.mtv.com/news/1488580/lollypalooza-lollipop-in-the-eye-stops-bowie-show/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 12:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My daughter's name is Beatrix. We told everyone it was after my grandmother, Beatrice.

I look forward to tell her the truth when she's older.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 11:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOW DARE YOU! YOU LEAVE DAVID BOWIE ALONE!


oh, you meant the knife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 10:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in Australia and Starbucks failed here.

Our population is made up of a lot of european migrants who insisted on good coffee when they came here in the 50s and 60s. 

I have to admit I struggled to find coffee the way I like it in the US. I think Americans drink their coffee weaker than other countries, but drink more of it. 

I loved the jugs of drip coffee at the gas stations with the racks of syrups and creamers (I still don't know what that stuff is). 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were forced to take a life, how would you do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 10:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 10:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 10:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Titantic is too manipulative to make me cry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 10:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Life Is Beautiful fucking devastated me. Not in a way the pulled on my heartstrings either.

It left be ruined for weeks.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 10:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you do like about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 10:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not popular? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Starbucks popular? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 09:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Qantas Face Swap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 00:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 00:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is anyone else getting a cool hollow face illusion effect?

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hollow-Face_illusion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 10:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Team Reddit sees physical exercise for the first time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 13:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 10:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just put a pillow on my grandmother's face and tip toe away. 100% success rate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 09:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think the horrors of Apartheid have been undone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 01:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> " after he kicked your ass in video games he probably had sex with your mom" - AmericanPsychout </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 00:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's great about his performance in Episodes is that while he is a prick, it's still a nuanced and interesting character. You end up feeling sorry for him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 22:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the Worlds before Monkey,
Primal chaos reigned, Heaven sought order.
But the Phoenix can fly only when its feathers are grown.
The four worlds formed again and yet again,
As endless aeons wheeled and passed.
Time and the pure essences of Heaven,
The moistures of the Earth,
And the powers of the Sun and the Moon
All worked upon a certain rock - old as Creation,
And it magically became fertile.
That first egg was named Thought,
Tathagata Buddha, the Father Buddha,
Said, 'With our thoughts we make the world.'
Elemantal forces caused the egg to hatch,
from it then came a stone Monkey.
The nature of Monkey was irrepressable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 22:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking forward to him in Community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 09:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pears. Oh god, the pears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 05:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen Bosom Buddies. That looks amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best TV series opening credit monologue? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 04:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favourite has to be Renegade:

*He was a cop, and good at his job. But he committed the ultimate sinand testified against other cops gone bad. Cops that tried to kill him, but got the woman he loved instead. Framed for murder, now he prowls the badlands...an outlaw hunting outlaws...a bounty hunter...a RENEGADE.*

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E0kkPK_WSck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 21:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the time, Charlie Hebdo reprinted a lot of the Danish cartoons. Their offices were firebombed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 13:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The people delivering packages are all contractors now. It's easier to just leave the card and not knock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 22:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That gingers have no souls? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 11:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great film but probably not quite what I was after.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 11:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just checked out the trailer. Looks harrowing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 11:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ooh! Nice one. I realised the other day that Nolan's films, with a few exceptions, are actually getting worse as he goes on but I never noticed because he set the bar so high at the start of his career. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some films in which the protagonist wakes up in the room, unsure how they got there? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 11:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far, I can think of Cube, Saw, Oldboy, Exam, Captivity, Killing Room and Unknown.

Most in the genre are pretty terrible low budget efforts but I'm sure there is some gold out there like Cube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 10:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno. You're pretty far away from me and I find you REALLY annoying. 

Same goes for phones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
