<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6584</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary speaking fee: $300,000 with the university discount. Bernie's fee: $1,867.42 for three appearances, "a grand sum that is chump change in presidential politicking but enough for the senator to respectably donate the money to charity." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 18:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 17:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Bernie 1941; Biden 1942; Clinton 1947. They're all old. So what?
2. Too soon to say, given his surge.  Don't nip it in the bud - let this movement blossom across the nation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 05:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, mine them for resources and develop them with condos and strip malls.  I saw that Wisconsin wanted to sell park names.  How about BP Wilderness Park? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 05:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really bad.  They want to hide, those sneaky bastards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 23:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was an example of how the media can use one tiny incident to shape/control the hive mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 23:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. How did it happen? Maybe there is a connection to Wisconsin's high rate of alcohol consumption and the continuing elections of Scott Walker.  Alcoholism = poor judgment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 23:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 16:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Defining Russia Musically; p.470; Richard Taruskin; 1997; Princeton University Press.
Refers to Musorgsky's "aristocratic companion and probable lover, Count Arseniy Golenishchev-Kutuzov."   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did this guy graduate from high school? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All good points that you've made.  Don't forget that he's short, ugly, cross-eyed, buck-toothed and chinless.  Americans don't elect short, ugly Presidents.  Oh, I forgot stupid and morally bankrupt.  The Kochs like him because he's empty and stupid - easy to control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I favor harsh and severe consequences for drunk drivers.  Too many innocent people have been killed by drunk drivers.  Caught driving drunk?  Lose your license.  Caught again?  Prison.  I know this is an unpopular position. Too bad, drunk drivers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bach was only 22 when he wrote this gorgeous cantata Gottes Zeit ist die allerbeste Zeit (Actus Tragicus) BWV106. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 23:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
