<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8959</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What presently popular tool, technology or past time will distant future generations likely label monumentally stupid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 07:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wonder Woman vs. Saruman the White </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 20:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cage match to the death </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A medical company offers you 1 billion dollars to receive an injection that will kill you in exactly 15 years. Would you accept? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 11:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Incredible Hulk vs. Voldemort </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 09:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Faith No More's Mike Patton Once Defecated in Axl Roses Orange Juice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 20:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Tagteam Deathmatch] Gandalf and Saruman vs. Batman and Wolverine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 04:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arena match to the death with six hour prep, fighters must tag in or must enter if team mate dies. Book, film and assumed abilities in play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bruce Wayne with a wooden baseball bat vs. 1,500 bloodlusted pit bulls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 06:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Open field, Bruce is taking his favorite bat for a morning stroll as the rich are wont to do. All of a sudden he hears the howls and growling of an army of pissed off dogs as they run at him from all directions. He is surrounded and knows he has to fight. Will he live? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Instead of going through the hassle of waiting for your grandparents to die to collect inheritance, sue them and claim they sexually molested you then settle out of court! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 23:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 00:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear many people say this as they continue shopping there... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Ask your partner "Are you cheating on me" every single day when you first see them and every single night before bed. If they EVER get agitated with your question, they are cheating on you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Danny Devito in his prime with a baseball bat vs. Haley Joel Osment now with a hammer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 04:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> City street fight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 04:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super Grover would put up a fight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Muppet Deathmatch) Grover vs. Animal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 22:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cage match to the death </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Joker vs. Skeletor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 16:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cage match </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: When a girl tells you she just wants to be friends, she's really hoping you propose to her in an incredibly public way, in front of a large crowd. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 03:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 03:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gonna second this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sterling Archer, James Bond and Jason Bourne are sent to Gotham, instructed to assassinate the terrorist known as the Bat Man. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 17:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Collaborating, could they pull it off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Radiohead's Thom Yorke records song thats 18 DAYS long for Sydney art exhibition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 07:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 21:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I blame the goddamn Jews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 20:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought he was muslin? He sounds confused. Is he a linen or the follower of Muhammad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 17:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Write it in gold ink. For some reason they really focus on gold ink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 16:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They built a temple of shit and they're shocked that it stinks. This story is the perfect summary of the Republican party as a whole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 16:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your neighbor is a linen? Do you live on a clothes line?In a dryer, perhaps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If rappers can make it rain, why don't they fix the California drought? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 18:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 17:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> idioteque </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 17:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is no more or less restrictive than stores, hospitals, restaurants or offices I've worked in throughout my life. It's called a uniform. If you disagree with it, don't work there for christs sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bruce Wayne drugged with a hallucinogen vs. Captain America drugged with a horse tranquilizer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 21:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bruce is unarmed. Fighting in the woods at night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If the line at the airport is too long, start shouting "Allah give me courage!" repeatedly and as loudly as possible. Security will recognize your religious devotion and move you to a special VIP line. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 20:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Completely unarmed Jason Bourne vs. Completely unarmed Bruce Wayne </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 19:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> City street fight to the death </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jack Nicholsons Joker vs. Heath Ledgers Joker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 06:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both Jokers and their respective gangs are teleported into Gotham with only one Joker surviving the battle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why isn't menstruation on the periodic table? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 05:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do sperm know what an egg looks like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 07:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Vampire Lestat vs. Wonder Woman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 15:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Book version of Lestat takes on Wonder Woman in a city street fight at sun down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 20:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kurzweils "The Singularity is Near" is looking less and less fantastic to me as time progresses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Future potential of brain chip is limitless after man controls robot arm with his thoughts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 20:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You can select one superpower to grant yourself. Everyone you have ever hurt, offended or dumped gains the same power and joins together and plots to kill you. Could you survive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 20:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 20:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Oil is a helluva drug" 
-Rick "Halliburton" James </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: All IPhones come with a built in cancer screening test as a hidden feature. Urinate directly on the phone and the results are almost instant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 19:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend works for Apple and said they couldn't make it public because they're still testing this feature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 15:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds like a wasted opportunity to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Magneto teams up with with Darth Vader, Goku and The Hulk. Can they defeat Superman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 01:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 00:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just proved that reddit users with the name nobody25864 can't not post in this thread.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 00:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting thing about HAARP I read recently,  Russian scientists hpothesized that HAARP could [invoke a chain reaction](http://www.wired.com/2008/01/russian-journal/) in the ionosphere that could trigger precession.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 22:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's MISS Amazon. I'm sure Amazon could be...a ...lovely name for a woman... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Bond is ordered to assassinate Jason Bourne. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who survives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As an atheist, what's the fastest way for me to prove to everyone that God isn't real? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't have said it better. I typically don't actively read lyrics, I just listen until I know them but dammit he can be challenging! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 15:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still have no idea what Thom Yorke is saying in "Airbag". If I wore head phones and sang out loud to it people would think I had some form of severe mental handicap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Videos capture strange trumpet sounds coming from the sky Experts cant say exactly what it is </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 15:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What song lyric did you get wrong for years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 15:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Incredible Hulk vs. Darth Sidious </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 04:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mountaintop fight to the death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If you're feeling incredibly depressed and no one in your life seems to care about you at all, all you have to do is die. All of your bad feelings immediately end plus everyone will realize how they neglected you and will be haunted by guilt for the rest of their lives! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 01:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 07:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 06:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to call the police and report the person holding a gun to your head, forcing you to surf Reddit submissions that hurt your feelings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 06:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Close your fucking browser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 06:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you repeat "Pulitzer prize winning"? What does that accomplish, exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 03:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US isn't remotely close to this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Disagree with an opinion on Reddit? Post a lengthy response devoid of reason while filled with rage and insults. Everyone who reads it will respect your passion and realize that your way of seeing the issue is clearly the correct way! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 16:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Chinese Emperor Jiajing died from an overdose of mercury, believing it to be an elixir that would grant immortality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 16:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There should be higher taxes on sugar and fat than nicotine and alcohol. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 08:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 08:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carl Sagan actually believed in similar lines of thought. Personally, I view any answer regarding post life that isn't "I do not know" as uneducated warbling. Chest thumping and pissing contests aside, no one knows what happens when we die. They know what might happen, what they want to happen or what they're afraid will happen. That's it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 08:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is she saying it to be "ironic" or is she genuinely a horrible person? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 06:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An anonymous source in Pakistan told me bin Laden was female. So now it's a fact. That's how it works, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 04:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've wasted my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: There is a near 100 percent chance that after you die, not one single person will remember anything you said or did in life, so stop stressing about stupid shit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 02:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bushs terrible, horrible, no good, very bad week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 18:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bullshit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 04:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd even add to this and have a few random items that you can toss on the desk or table as trophies of past conquests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 00:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are an embarrassment to us all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If you are black and can't find a job, bleach your skin until it whitens. Not only will you get any job you apply for, police will teach you the secret hand signal that prevents you from ever being arrested! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 15:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't doctors just take all the transgendered men and all the transgendered women and switch their brains? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 07:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 19:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Just because your roast beef got ruined you don't need to ruin mine" or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My wife was raped two days ago coming home from work and won't get out of bed. How long should I wait before reminding her that dinners don't cook themselves? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 16:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I broke my mail order bride and the company said the warranty on it expired. What should I do with it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 18:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 12:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually addressed this, sorry if it was unclear - California is a coastal state. Moisture should be inherent, I would think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why isn't cloud seeding technology used in California? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 04:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Admit to limited knowledge of technologically feasible weather manipulation techniques, but as California is coastal, isn't there a way to seed clouds carrying ocean moisture to assist drought areas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 21:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound upset, internet friend. Talk about it while I take you seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 20:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The question isn't whether or not it's a penis issue. We KNOW it's a penis issue. The question is whether or not YOU knew it. Education is key. Think of the children etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 20:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Now that you're dickless, I'm into it..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 17:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loudly make fun of gay people at every opportunity. It establishes alpha male dominance, large genitals and a totally not gay fixation on gay people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daimler's self-drive trucks are going to be tested in Nevada </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 16:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If you have a small penis, modify the exhaust system on your car to be REALLY loud. It makes everyone who hears you driving think your penis is huge! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 16:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Deathmatch] Han Solo and a Bloodlusted Chewbacca vs. Rocket Raccoon and a Fairly Annoyed Groot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 10:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cage match. No guns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ladies, if you have a child with autism, tell everyone you know it was because of vaccines. That way no one will know you smoked meth when you were pregnant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 06:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 03:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How exactly is social security reduction a bipartisan goal? Id like to see some sources if possible, because I was always under the impression it was a Republican target for looting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carly Fiorina: Drug addiction shouldnt be criminalized. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 20:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 20:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not startling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 20:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can understand this to an extent, but then I get confused as to how it is viewed as justified to deliver judgement, as I thought judgement to be a responsibility reserved for the God in question.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] From a religious perspective, what is the rationale behind a pro life, pro death penalty position? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 17:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now that homosexuality has become much more acceptable in society, I am bored without any injustices to protest. How can I turn back into a straight person? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 04:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Cruz 'reached out to the Pentagon' about martial law conspiracy theory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 02:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why does the United States tolerate human rights violations and terrorism links in Saudi Arabia but not in Syria? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 19:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every character Nintendo has ever created teams up and attacks the X-Men. Who wins? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 06:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Nintendo army strikes Xaviers School for Gifted Youngsters in the middle of the night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 20:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title was literally copied directly from the article.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report Says American Psychological Association Collaborated on Torture Justification </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 16:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 03:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, of course he is "not concerned". He is filling his XXXL underwear with fudge right now. The word 'concerned' isn't even close to what he is feeling deep, deep, deep in the distant depths of his gut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 101 Baltimore Protesters Go Free as Arrest Paperwork Backs Up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 02:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 23:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, he's an extreme left that will leave the independent vote untouched. So far, I'm putting my money on O'Malley. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neo (Matrix) enters the Marvel universe while retaining his powers. Who can take him? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 17:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could the rising levels of obesity around the world be the cause of the increase in earthquake activity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 08:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh Dae-Su (Oldboy) believes The Bride (Kill Bill) is responsible for his imprisonment. Can he get his revenge? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 04:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 04:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to give him too much credit here, but Marilyn Manson did this fifteen years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do people in Baltimore hate The Police? Did Sting insult them somehow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 03:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Waters on "Free Speech" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every time I encounter an African American I hug them while apologizing for slavery and congratulating them on Obama. Is there anything else I can do to earn their respect? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 18:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 05:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a problem at all. The only people who would say "nuts" or scoff are people who actively ridicule others for asking questions, and they don't matter much in the scheme of things. Thanks again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 04:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very strange, thanks for sharing that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 04:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you respond? Did you have time to actually watch this, was it a fleeting glimpse, night or day? Never heard of anything like this, sounds interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] To Redditors who believe they have seen a UFO of possible extraterrestrial origin, what about the experience makes you believe what you saw cannot be explained by modern science/aviation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 04:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 04:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried Youtube and it didn't work. I spent hours doing a .5 second by .5 second frame analysis of the Star Wars E7 (That's Episode 7 for the neanderthals reading this) trailer specifically to prove to people that the red lightsaber handguard is an absolutely redundant and stupid creation, but I'm pretty sure I used language that is too intelligent because no one watched my video, which obviously means they can't keep up with me. So the short version, Youtube users are just not on my level. I will certainly try the beard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 01:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell your dad not to pull his penis out next time, live as conjoined twins forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 19:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next up, a study proving that after years of speculation, water appears to be wet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wear a fedora all the time, I have put on 45 pounds and condescendingly preach to sheeple that I and I alone understand how ridiculous religion truly is, but somehow I still do not feel enlightened. What am I doing wrong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 18:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 18:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You know what I really hate? Fried chicken." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hail Satan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 17:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What caused humans to develop a sense of humor and what purpose does it serve? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 17:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 23:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote Satan in hail. I thought it was hailarious. Apparently the downvoters are thinking "hail no" but I just can't hailp myself. Hail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 22:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Kudos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every superhero or villain who's character name ends with -man, -boy, -woman or girl from all fictional universes enter a dance competition against one another. Who wins? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 22:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Contest is judged by a panel of three judges aided by public voting ala American Idol. Judges are: Jaimee Foxx, Amy Schumer and an incredibly intoxicated Sterling Archer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
