<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9974</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 19:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Que? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 19:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/Trollabot doctechnical </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 19:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/Trollabot train_subject9974 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think AR 670-1 defines the IPFU's unserviceability.

 
DA Pam 710-2-2, Supply Support Activity Supply System: Manual Procedures, 30 Sep 98, Glossary, pp. 268-276 defines unservicability as **More inclusive term than damage or destruction. It indicates, in military usage, that the article to which the term is applied is no longer useful for the intended purpose. Damage or destruction may not be involved. The term also indicates property that has deteriorated through use; however, it may include property no longer usable for its original purpose, despite the reason for its condition.**



Technically your pt's aren't unservicable, since they serve their original purpose but they are unpresentable (presentability can be determined by your CO). Unless your NCO argues that the reflective Army logo was a safety thing, in which case rubbing it off would make the shorts unservicable since they don't perform the original purpose.




Bottom line, your NCO/SNCO is gonna fucking win this war. Buy new PT's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Groupon's comments on their "banana bunker" were comedy gold. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 14:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drunk guy is at a bar pounding drinks and he notices a well dressed young man at the other end of the bar. Every time a female walks by the young man he whispers something in their ear, sometimes they look at him shocked until he says something to soothe them, but the drunk notices that several times the women accompany the young man to a private room in the back of the tavern. The drunk has observed the young man score several times today. Thd drunk thinks to himself, "what line is this man using to get all these girls? It has a pretty high success rate." and stumbles across the room and asks the young man "Shayy, what line are you ushing to get all theshe pretty women". The young man politely explains "whenever a pretty woman walks near me I whisper in her ear, 'Tickle your ass with a feather?' If she agrees, we go to the back and get kinky, on the other hand if she is offended I repeat myself 'typical nasty weather' and she thinks she just misheard me."


The drunk agrees that this is a fine line, and decides to try it before he forgets it. He stumbles out of the bar, summons a cab to drive him home, stumbles into his house where his wife is resting on the couch and propositions her "Shayy honey, can I shtick a feather in your ass?" She looks at him and replies "What did you say you drunk sonofabitch?" To which he replies "Fucking rain".






Not super dirty, but I like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 13:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A comment about how shitty 9gag is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 13:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some shower shoes. Gotta love those feet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 04:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People spend a lot of time arguing about just and unjust wars. The way I see it, if you are murdering women, children, and noncombatants or committing war crimes you are fighting an unjust war. 


If you are fighting bad guys (The Taliban, Al-Qaida, ISIS, fill-in-the-blank) it may not always be a *wise* war, but that does not mean there is no justice in it. 



Its up to the politicians to decide whether we go to war, it is up to the soldiers to fight those wars honorably. We voice our opinions about the wisdom of proposed wars through the ballot box as private citizens, we actively influence the way in which our nation wages war by behaving honorably in our AO's whenever we are sent to war.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 04:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is service inherently honorable?No. If you do shitty and immoral things while in uniform they are no less shitty and immoral. Can service be honorable? Absolutely. Dedicating yourself to making the world a better place and, most importantly, living for the guy to your left and right are totally honorable in my sight.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 04:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Mentee" is a legit word. Protege is also correct. Both are acceptable.




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 04:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yes, he was a fine fellow.


I don't think it was his lie at all, if I remember correctly Ben Franklin puffed up Von Stueben's credentials to persuade Washington to hire him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 04:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "Baron" who was not actually a Baron at all, haha!


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Serious Is The Army About Fostering A Mentoring Culture Within The Ranks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 02:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 19:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On fucking point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 03:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the same thing SGM said when I charged my cell phone on a SIPR computer... What am I missing here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 03:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope this is a troll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The Military Has Overkilled Alcohol With Big Collateral Damage"... Thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 02:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 00:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, the media is gonna elect him "official representative for the Army" and blast his opinions. That is how it usually works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Experiences coming into the Guard from Active duty? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 00:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am an active duty E-5 considering moving to the Alabama National Guard. I have heard a lot of negative things, but I was just curious what y'alls experiences have been? I am trying to score a job with the railroad in B-ham or maybe something in trucking, and stay in the Guard for a while? Has anyone had a similar experience? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 21:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to remove Govt from the picture. As with anything, involving the government with private matters fucks them all up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 21:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't waste my time thinking about the sexual preferences of other men. I honestly don't give a shit what any other dude likes in thd bedroom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 21:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always think /u/slothfactsbot is funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favorite Reddit bots? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 21:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all know there are several floating around, which ones are your favorites to run into? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 21:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always think /u/slothfactsbot is funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 20:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I hate drum. Been here 3 years. I am stuck here right now trying to come down on orders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 20:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Outlaw Country.


Because I am country and identify with the themes of hard work, self sufficiency, traditional southern values, and getting drunk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 20:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am at Drum too. Just moved to the CAB from 3rd Brigade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 18:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what you are referring to here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favorite Reddit bots? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 14:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all know there are several floating around, which ones are your favorites to run into? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 14:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another OP who thinks random=original. 


Speaking of random, I summon /u/slothfactsbot to bring us some facts about sloths. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 06:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loxley, AL.


I don't have to deal with city people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 04:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I meant no legal penalty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 04:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did your hadji commander tell you to post this here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 03:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of what we think is funny hinges on the element surprise. Jokes are all about tricking your brain by ending the story different than you expect (aka delivering the punchline).


What we percieve as cleverness is someone else stimulating our brains by inserting a common reference/relatable shared knowledge in a surprising way (for example when they make a pop culture reference at a time we did not expect a pop culture reference).


It all boils down to brain stimulation through surprise. Of course it is more complex than this,  but that is the eli5 answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 01:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take ju-jitsu. Fighting is not an overnight skill, it takes practice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 00:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Afghanistan. I learned about brotherhood, that life is most memorable when shittiest, that the problema we face over here are petty and not worth crying over, and that I don't need half as much stuff as I think I do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 23:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do support the existence of unions. I said that in my first post. I am all for folks *voluntarily* joining together to bargain for healthcare or anything else. I just do not support using the state to achieve those goals. I also stated I would not join a union because as of yet there are none who want to further my goals.


I oppose abortion because I believe it to be a violation of the nonaggression principle, and therefore the lawful domain of state intervention. I believe the state should punish/prevent acts of aggression, since I believe a fetus to be a human entitled to full human rights, extinguishing their life is an act of aggression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 23:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right, my bad. Corrected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 23:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My goals are

1. Deregulation of the markets. Unions advocate for *more* market regulation. I do not support welfare, federal organizations like OSHA, or any other federal market legislation.

2. Total freedom of association. If a business owner does not want to serve or hire someone based on race, religion, or bias, he has that right. Although it is apalling, I believe each individual owns the products of their labor, and can refuse to give those products to anyone for any reason.

3. Many unions support abortion coverage in an employment contract. I do not believe abortions are moral and therefore oppose this.

4. I oppose the state forcing employers to provide healthcare for their employees. While it is moral, and good business practice, the details of an employment contract are for the employee and employer to decide through bargaining the state has no place in the matter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 22:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unions are fine, but should remain voluntary. Individuals must be free to join and leave a union at will. Forced unionization is an infrigement on the right of voluntary association. There should be no penalty for refusal to join a union. 


I would not join a union because there are none whose goals match my own, but if others want to join one it does not bother me.


One important distinction. Progressives and Liberals (in the modern sense) tendto view the world collectively. We view the world through an individualists perspective. My class, race, and cuture do not represent me and I do not represent them. I am my own person, distinct from my class, race, and cultural heritage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 22:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot access the republican sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 22:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We aren't emotionally charged bleeding hearts who spend every spare moment on deployment opening up about our feelings and political persuasions..


-Soldier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sergeant Major Daniel Daly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 21:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was one of only 19 men to win the MOH twice, one of only 2 to win them in separate conflicts. He was an amateur boxer, Marine, fought in the Boxer Rebellion, Banana Wars, and WW1.
During the Battle of Belleau Wood in WW1, he is purported to have yelled to the men of his company, Come on, you sons of bitches, do you want to live forever? in order to motivate them to charge the Germans. He was offered the chance to commission as an officer twice, declining both times because he would rather be an outstanding sergeant than just another officer."
[This is him rocking both of his MOH's](http://i.imgur.com/aQiOytq.jpg) Seems like one salty-ass motherf*cker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was reading about Sergeant Major Daniel Daly today... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 21:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparantly he was one of only 19 men to receive the MOH twice, one of only 2 to receive them in separate conflicts. He was an amateur boxer, Marine, fought in the Boxer Rebellion, Banana Wars, and WW1. 


During the Battle of Belleau Wood in WW1, he is purported to have yelled to the men of his company, Come on, you sons of bitches, do you want to live forever? in order to motivate them to charge the Germans. He was offered the chance to commission as an officer twice, declining both times because he would rather be an outstanding sergeant than just another officer."

[This is him rocking both of his MOH's](http://imgur.com/aQiOytq) Seems like one salty-ass motherf*cker.


Edit; changed "win" to "receive" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 21:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please add me to the Republicans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 16:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is ending drug prohibition unrealistic? Drug decriminalization and even legalization has been accomplished in many developed nations. If the US is such a haven for liberty and freedom, why can't we do it too?



My end goal would be total legalization. Your body is your own and you alone get to choose what substances your body uses. Realistically I would like to see significant reduction in drug penalties, lower sentences, turn drug crimes into misdemeanors. I would like to cut all funding to national agencies' operations against drugs, especially the DEA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 13:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no such thing as stress cards, and never has been. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 03:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would not necessarily be repealing all aspects of the ACA, just the mandate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 02:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. MEPs is basically just a very long set of examinations, physical, mental, bloodwork, xrays, etc. Once deemed fit it is also where you sign your contract. Basic is tough but simple. It is stressful, drill sergeants will scream at you and get in your face, but as long as you follow basic i structions you will be fine.

2. The cutoff age is 42 for enlistment.

3. Being in the Reserves or National Guard means you go to drill one weekend a month, and two weeks out of the year. Sometimes they deploy and you get active duty pay. Active duty soldiers are on cal 24/7, usually work Mon thru Fri depending on your job.

4. goarmy.com has a list of all possible jobs. Not all of these will be available though. Depending on your ASVAB score and the dates school seats are open.

5. n/a

6. They don't *have* to move with you. If you want to live away from them. You typically stay at one duty station between 3-5 years at a time. As long as you are in the Army you have to move where they tell you to when they tell you to. They will pay for your family to come along and provide accomodations, but if you choose to leave your family behind it is your choice.

7. Yes. When a leader tells you to respond, you respond. No matter how minute or pointless the thing they tell you to do is, you will do it because they own your ass. If you have a temper and a tendency to snap off/talk back to authorith, the drill sergeants in basic willl resolve that issue quickly.



The Army is not for everyone. If you are just looking for benefits, you will be disappointed. There is piles and piles of BS that falls on you the minute you join. At the same time it is rewardinf, enabling, and something you will never forget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 01:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A libertarian supporting government intervention in the markets? Embarrassing.


I am also a Libertarian-Republican. I would offer extreme immigration reform, marriage equality, ending the drug war, stopping NSA spying, and cuts in defense.


In return I would ask for support auditing the Federal Reserve, repealing the Patriot act, a systematic removal of gun control, cutting the IRS drastically, and the repeal of the healthcare mandate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 17:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should try him, he is perspective broadening and important to the genre. You may not like him, but there is value to his work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 17:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Faulkner. 


I am a huge Southern Gothic and Southern Lit fan, but I have read nearly everything Faulkner has written and not liked it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 10:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are still deployments, some of them combat, some of them more humanitarian. Most folks end up doing overseas tours of some kind whether it is Africa, Afghanistan, or chilling in Guam. There is no way to predict accurately whether you will see combat. 



If you are not deployed you will be training to deploy. In and out of the field, big field exercises, going to the range to become more accurate on your weapon etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 00:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Long legged guitar pickin man](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=0_59br5LAU0) by Johnny Cash and June Carter.



This is how we talk to each other, and we are huge Johnny and June fans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 23:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah.... No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 23:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in the NG from the stories I have heard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 18:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lexington Steele. 


Obvious Reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 18:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are just talking about American city folks.



I eat Sheep, Venison, Turkey, Rabbit, Quail, Dove, Pheasent and many others on a very regular basis. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 15:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because you can put a bunch of random words together does not mean you are funny. More folks need to figure this out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 15:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adolph.


Something about not preheating his oven properly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 03:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Free" and "taxpayer funded" are two very different things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 02:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "That dress *did* make your butt look fat!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 02:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are probably ashamed about it, and probably are using it in an unhealthy way to deal with some other issue or insecurity.  I would try to get them to get help for the core issues/insecurities that cause them to drink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 02:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red-what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 02:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lock box to lock your cell phone in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 02:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously the Portal Gun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 02:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adolf Hitler and Adam Sandler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 02:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't really thing of anything. I have a pretty calloused stomach, worn rough by my experiences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 02:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being politically incorrect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 02:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Army;

They are kids. Kids act like kids. Everyone needs to calm the fuck down. Hypernationalism usually comes from folks who don't have a clue what real sacrifice is all about. 



The parent needs to teach their kids about respect, and respecting things other people find valuable. I would say letting your kids run wild on an object others find solemn probably indicates you haven't taught them about respect well enough. 


But no, I am not offended.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 23:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freckles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 14:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love steak in the mornings. Steak and Eggs is my birthday breakfast every year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 03:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it will always be [this](http://youtu.be/dQw4w9WgXcQ)


I will never see a more accurate personification of Satan himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How working men's sheds reflect their beer, powertool and fast car-loving owners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 02:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 01:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came from a trailer park in South Alabama. I have now achieved a comfortable lifestyle through the military, and look forward to a very comfortable life after I retire (in 16 years) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 01:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't remember. It has been too long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 01:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loyalty. Sticking by you when everyone else ditches you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 01:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reasons I become friends with girls has no corollation to the reasons the males mentioned in your OP became friends with you. The only way you are going to find out the answer to this question is to be direct and ask them.


I become friends with females for the same reasons I become friends with males; I share some common interest or perspective with them and benefit from their presence. 


If I want more than friendship with a girl I will be very clear and direct about my desires/intentions. 


My perspective is not indicative of the whole male gender though. The males you mention could share my outlook, or they could think totally different. The only way you will find out is to ask.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 22:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a laser range finder/long range recon system.


Read about it [here](https://www.strategypage.com/military_photos/long_range.aspx) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 19:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I have not deified anything. The Word is not a divine entity, but is the true Word of the only God. It should be worshipped as the one true revelation of God.



The Holy Spirit has many roles. He reveals the scriptures to those whom he will, he works upon the hearts of men to prepare them to recieve the Word, he impressed the Word upon the hearts/minds of the writers of the Holy Scriptures, etc.


Are you asking if the Holy Spirit can reveal God outside of Scriptures? If so, yes he *can*, it is physically possible, but he does not. God has ordained that his word would be the final and closed revelation of himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 17:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super right wing evangelical conservative. Runs with the like of Glenn Beck. Not someone I would associate with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 17:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The direct Word of God. The complete and closed revelation of Himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 17:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Libertarianism advocates a free and voluntary society wherein each individual has the liberty to behave and act any way they wish as long as they do not aggress against another individual's life, liberty, or property. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 02:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Murder their family and leave a note written in blood on their wall that says "you're next". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 00:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bit. Not every girl can rock every hairstyle. i am not a fan of short hair, and I freakin love neon dyed hair.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 00:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same bar of Lava soap I use on my body. Shampoo is overrated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 23:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure. A lot of folks have done so it the past. As far as I know it is not against sub rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 13:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had/have no endgame. They just want to drag this war out until it no longer makes politicians money. That is my opinion. Just like Vietnam and Korea. No endgame, no good planning, just something that made the politicians look good at the time.


We should have gone in there with the sole purpose of retaliation for their attacks. Shock and awe, obliterate them and their hold, then leave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 05:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody owes you anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 05:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at Forward Operating Base Shank in Eastern Afghanistan.


I think originally the war in Afghanistan was justified, but politicians put their stupid heads into it. It does not take 13 years to win a war. We should have been done a long time ago, it is not our job to build a nation. Iraq was never justified. Saddam was a bad guy, but ISIS is a helluva lot worse. I don't trust politicians, and I don't think they have our best interests in mind. They don't give a shit how many young kids die overseas as long as they can make it look like they died for something. Since Korea we have been doing the same shit, and young American kids have been paying for the politicians records.



That being said, i fought and lived for my brothers. We were not fighting good or decent people, they deserved every bit of firepower we used against them. I don't regret it, I would do it again. I just wish people cared still. I wish folks cared about the guys who died. I wish people would learn that war is costly and should always be a last resort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 05:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Move home to Alabama, buy a few acres and raise sheep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 05:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because western society is pretty self centered and narcissistic. Folks are taught from a young age that the world revolves around their feelings/emotions, and all that matters is that they are happy all the time. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 05:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lazy motherfuckers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 05:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever it is fitting. I cry when friends die, huge emotional events, etc.



There is nothing wrong with men crying. There is something wrong with anyone crying over petty shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 02:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be a Navy thing, I don't know. We have MWR sponsored boating and sailing for enlisted and officers alike </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 00:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he is trying to "hook up on the meat market" he needs to grow the fuck up and stop looking for one night stands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 00:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha its a little trailer trash town without a whole lot to see, but I love the place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 23:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am from Loxley, but we had our party in Dothan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 23:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a weird cultural image that a lot of folks have that says a woman who approaches a man is too forward/brash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 23:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't add value to my life. I personally feel like they would be a waste of my time. I have hobbies already (gardening, hunting, fishing etc) and I am a voracious reader. There is nothing about video games that appeals to me. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 23:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soldier. 



The effects of White Phosphorus on a human being. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 23:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At my bachelor party (in Alabama) we smoked cigars, had whiskey tasting, and had some fine steaks. 



P. S. Stay away from strip clubs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 23:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His generals were brutal and heartless bastards, he waged war in a brutal way. He was a politically skillfull person. I don't buy the "honest Abe with a big ole heart" persona. He was an imperialist with little respect for the idea of decentralization. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 23:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you fulfill your responsibilities and live for more than self gratification. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 23:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, I have yet to get into videogames. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 23:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first time mortars fell from the sky in Afghanistan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 23:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they don't just accept the most qualified parents. It is pretty easy to become a foster parent. As with most large programs, it is really easy to cheat the system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 22:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be interesting and well rounded. I am in the military too. 

Take advantage of every opportunity for adventure, read good books, and be kind to everyone. If you have interesting experiences and connect with many folks you would be surprised at how many opportunities for female companionship will present themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 22:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any sort of compliment, especially from ladies. Deapite what men say, we love when women compliment us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 21:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your service sir. I am a veteran of the Afghanistan war myself. I was curious, what advice would you have for young veterans like myself? Is there anything you would like to say to young veterans?



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 06:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A 12 mile ruck march. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 06:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a good forum to practice social interaction. Sure, some people just come here to be dicks but some of us actually enjoy interacting with folks from different backgrounds and with different perspectives. Reddit can be a good place to learn how to politely disagree with somone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 06:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Character I would like to resemble/identify with;  **Atticus Finch**


Character I actually identify with; **Forrest Gump** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 05:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That I would only make a Reddit account to *lurk every now and then*... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 02:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tattoos are a strong part of the military tradition. I agree with that. Most military folks (including myself) have several tattoos. That being said, there have to be standards. The Army has no problem if you have tattoos, they just have to follow certain guidelines. The Army will change as the culture changes though. 



No, our recruit pool will not grow slim. We are kicking good soldiers out as it is to meet force realignment. For every kid who doesn't meet the minimum enlistment requirements, there are a dozen other who do meet the standards. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 02:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are going to have to face this phobia at some point. Getting your blood drawn isn't an Army thing, it is a life thing. Why not go ahead and face this fear with the resources the Army has to offer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 02:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't necessarily agree with the tat regulations (especially regarding sleeves) but the military is not the place to accept every individual and make everyone feel good. It is not s problem, it is a lifestyle. It is not about being free to be the individual you are, that is antithetical to the military lifestyle.



We have polypro's. They are not practical for year round wear, too hot many kids would pass the fuck out. Plus, at least in the Army, your arms are already always covered by your blouse. You don't need an extra layer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 02:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you would like a high level of discipline, hard work ethic, the ability to totally broaden your horizons and encounter the world in a first person way; this is the job for you.


I am a soldier. Been all over the world, saw a lot of shit, grew up a lot really quick, I am responsible for millions of dollars and the lives of my friends every day. I can retire at 39 and get a pension and healthcare, with plenty of time (and a phenomenal resume) to embark on another career. Oh, and sometimes I get to blow shit up and drive big trucks. And I can say the work fuck in every sentence without getting in trouble with my boss. I fuckin' love my job.


Advice for folks who wanna come into my career field;

1. Don't smoke weed.

2. Don't get in trouble with the law.

3. Don't be a lazy fuck.

That pretty much covers all the bases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 01:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. What huge problem with tattoos? 


2. We already have something similar. Of course you would never wear it under rolled up sleeves because that would look even more unprofessional than some think tattoos look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 22:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put it in a Roth IRA for retirement. You will be set when you are older. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 20:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 13:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bath and Body Works Sensual Amber. Always has been my favorite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 01:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is warmer than Fort Drum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 21:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be a mother fucker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 03:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you never stepped foot in the South? We drink gallons of sweet tea a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 01:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huge. It is larger than my palm. That green notebook it is sitting on is around the size of a waitress pad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 23:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will likely never stop having income. I come from a breed of folks who always have a job until they die. Also, since I intend to continue my military career for the full 20 years, so I will get a retirement pension from them.

Nonetheless, I will withdraw the money when I officially retire from fulltime work. By the time I officially pull my money out it will likely be in the millions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favorite challenge coin in my collection. Given to me by a CW5 at FOB Shank, Afghanistan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 23:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 21:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Remember the days when you actually had to choose your own meals? The hassle of choosing the cuts of meat, the sauces, the vegetables. Now, thanks to the almighty state of Ultron, your hassles are gone! You simply have to walk down to your local meal dispensary, ensuring you arrive between the hours of 0900 and 0925 and recieve your daily ration of whale blubber and three saltine crackers. Choose Ultron for the hassle free life!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 21:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am dying to be stationed in Europe just so I could sample these places for myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 21:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are beef hula hoops? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 21:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shepherds pie is one of my favorite comfort foods. 

I feel like UK pubs are so much classier than ours. If I asked my local bar for roast dinner they would laugh me right out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 21:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't those like potato chips in the US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
