<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2585</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 10:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well then... in terrified at four in the morning shouldn't... shouldn't have read that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 20:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the electric fence turned him into some sort of zombie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 20:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the other condo was showing you many ways you could die. For instance you said that you could barely afford your condo, so what if you get a loan from that guy and he kills you. And if you date that black haired lady she might kill you as well, so what if you killed yourself the first time you looked through the window because you couldn't handle the images anymore. So maybe you shouldn't look through the window anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 18:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yu know what would be funny? If the child was really some evil monster that looked like a human and if he wanted revenge, because you prevented him from eating more human flesh. Yep, very funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the race begins... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe death saved you as a baby and be wanted to check on you? I don't know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 12:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretend to join them, then nuke all. No mercy, avoid the mind reader device and just bomb them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 03:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably the homeless guy living underneath my bed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 02:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you did there, and I'm kinda shocked about it too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 08:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well now my childhood is officially ruined, thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 08:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I think the ending was not surprising because this is nosleep  and I've read similar stories like this, sadly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 08:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting interesting, I need to read more of the story for entertainmen- err I mean research... yep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 17:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no! We got a normal person! Normal person alert! Kill it, kill it with fire! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 02:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I am everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 19:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kinda guessed it because the guy couldn't hear him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
