<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5015</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 02:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you could become butt buddies with a dev and get him to delete you from the database, or you could do it yourself but i'm guessing that's not an option if you're posting here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 00:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah.... I know; apparently reddit dosen't know the spoiler tag though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 22:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JET FUEL DOSEN'T MELT STEEL BEAMS!111!1!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 22:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "An estimeed PhD cyber-psychologist"........ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 22:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 22 years of service and now hes a tour guide... */s* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 22:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much cynicism on videos like this... sure he could have been a paid dancer but at the same time he could have just been a security guard that could dance having some fun. No need to act like a smartass about it, as if you have some inside info. Even if it was a plant, why are they trying to get the video viral? There's not even a product placement and the video isn't even on the colleges youtube - even if I wanted to buy a ticket to see him I have no idea where he is/who he works for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 15:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Said a lot better here:https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s9Ke2bMYBFs#t=88 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 22:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Now* you're thinking like AAA game devs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 22:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never thought my fetish would show up on reddit...! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 17:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10/10 british impression </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 07:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Urgh people wanting more money for producing free entertainment. What a drag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 07:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure saying totes unironically is cringeworthy too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 07:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do they know if she's right..? I'd guess they have someone typing the numbers as she says them or? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 04:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had good experiences with NordVPN, and i've heard Feral is a good seedbox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 21:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some say she's still looking for Terry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 21:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the problem with the entirety of reddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 02:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean you're not wrong, probably should have included those details, but IMO it's still better than PTN because it dosent make my eyes hurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 21:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frasier: You know the expression, "Living well is the best revenge"?

Niles: It's a wonderful expression. I just don't know how true it is. You don't see it turning up in a lot of opera plots. "Ludwig, maddened by the poisoning of his entire family, wreaks vengeance on Gunther in the third act by living well."

Frasier: All right, Niles.

Niles: "Whereupon Woton, upon discovering his deception, wreaks vengeance on Gunther in the third act again by living even better than the Duke."

Frasier: Oh, all right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 12:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better off without them IMO. If you're looking for a good ratioless movie tracker try out BeyondHD. It's really only 'semi' private but they have all the new releases and some good internal encoders (famestor,legion). On PTN, their site design is so astoundingly bad it boggles the mind how people can use it on a daily basis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 20:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waffles is probably a good first stop, they have a lot of recruitment threads all over the place, and the requirements are never too high. Of course Waffles is still #2 to What.cd, so you could invest the time to learn the interview for WCD, which is the largest music tracker (https://www.whatinterviewprep.com/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 11:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait - it checks if for AV and if it's in a virtual machine? Dosen't a malware only do that if it's looking bypass/hide from one of them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The first and final step to failure..." - Anonymous [1882x2136] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 04:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 11:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its from the bottom of the dudes shoe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 10:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 09:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's talking about BAN, never heard of it? Good, that's they way they like. (*/s*) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 02:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love both and you are completely right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 00:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what does the private key do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 23:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can someone explain what the private key passphrase does? i assume it lets anyone simulate the cert or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 20:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 19:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain this and the implications in laymens terms? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 18:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean it sort of is. Although i've never had anyone tell me this i'd just say its worth it if you like to torrent enough, pretty simple really, being able to download so much content easily outweights the 'work'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 00:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
The newer versions of utorrent are filled with ads..maybe it was doing you a service.

http://filehippo.com/download_utorrent/9859/

Download this, it's the most reccomended older version of utorrent. If you still get a warning then theres a virus on your computer that's changing the download links. Switch to ESET Nod32 (Norton is a POS) and run a full scan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 00:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah most to all isps will do this. just change providers or ask reallly nicely saying you wont do it again... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 02:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not asking for an invite, that's asking for where they recruit from. You're not allowed to ask for invites, you are allowed to ask where x tracker recruits from. As per https://www.reddit.com/r/trackers/wiki/rules </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 01:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The subreddit is empty. Read the message on the gate. Sounds like your experience has been jaded somehow, and I apologise on behalf of whoever did that. I sincerely hope you decide to try and get back in, as its a rewarding experience with good communities, whose requirements aren't nearly as bad as you make them out to be... i'm nearly 5 months in and i'm in pretty much every private tracker I want to be (music,games,movies,tv) Greetings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 17:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have no idea what you're talking about. GazelleGames is in comparison with something like PtP or BTN is extremely easy to get into. They even have a recruiting thread on bB (/r/baconbits) where you just need to be a member for 1 month and have a ratio of 1.05, which essentially means just being a member for a month. No waiting for a year like you said.

The reason most private trackers don't open for registration (I think) is because they want to control the number of users, but the large majority of them have invite threads on 'gateway' trackers that require nothing more than power user (again, trivial to get). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 00:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little anecdote, i've never seen something so aggressively marketed, saw it all over public transport over here in the UK. Usually just see one or two posters, even for games like Assassin creed. This was actually plastered everywhere, it was so out of the ordinary for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 19:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GazelleGames seems to have a nice collection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 19:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Common knowledge they only have one policeman in Japan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 01:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, they're in there because they're British, but they win because your game is the best British game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 01:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you go: https://www.reddit.com/r/Eve/comments/2vihry/eve_online_nominated_for_persistent_game_bafta/coi47wy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 01:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/Eve/comments/2vihry/eve_online_nominated_for_persistent_game_bafta/coi47wy

Their defenition of persistent is...wildly different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 01:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at this comment: https://www.reddit.com/r/Eve/comments/2vihry/eve_online_nominated_for_persistent_game_bafta/coi47wy

...

I have no words for how stupid this is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 01:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why but his voice sounds a lot better in this video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 01:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT'S SO FUNNY? WHATS SO FUCKING FUNNY!?!!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 00:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/humblebrag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 21:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they emptied their clip on me before that I say fuck them and just shoot them. I'm not kniving only when its convienient for them lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 21:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people think you say it regardless, others only if it was a good game (e.g. I would not consider 5v1 a good game). There's quite a few in both camps of thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 21:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best reply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 19:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly the former I think. Coupled with them probably not having enough people submit their games for awards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 19:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Shitty"... this is the most prestigious gaming award (if you take it in the context of the 'main' BAFTA's). It's the only gaming award show to be broadcasted on TV ,BBC3. One of the most popular channels. Although I agree if by shitty you mean the fact that LoL and Destiny are in the same catagory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 08:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.ebuyer.com/174033-steelseries-s-s-mouse-pad-63001


http://www.amazon.com/gp/offer-listing/B000ANEQFM/ref=dp_olp_new_mbc?ie=UTF8 condition=new

? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steelseries Kinzu v2/Rival for big hands? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 08:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

Looking for a new mouse, my lachesis just died on me after a few years (Razer). Is there anyone here that has the Kinzu/Rival and has big hands? I've gotten used to the lachesis which is pretty big.

Cheers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 08:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any idea if any of those are ratio-less? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mouse like Lachesis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 08:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey,

After many years my lachesis finally gave up. Anyone that used the same mouse that knows of a good replacement? Preferably claw, needs to accomadate large hands.

Cheers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 08:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can eat some bacon raw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 08:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 08:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's such a fucking weird pick for that catagory. All of my wat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 08:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also for Persistent World along with League of Legends...i'm so confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 08:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good question. One i'm most confused about is League of Legends..... Dosen't the world 'reset' with every game played? They must be using a really broad defenition I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 07:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With all the hype i could unfortunately see Destiny taking this, but i'll be cheering for EvE on the day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EvE Online nominated for 'Persistent Game' BAFTA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 07:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 18:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the plate is 30 degrees below zero. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ice cream being made from scratch in minutes using a machine 30 degrees below zero. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 03:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ice cream being made from scratch using a machine 30 degrees below zero. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 03:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 00:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only there was some way to turn down the sound.... hmmm... Let me get back to you on this, I think i'm onto something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 00:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Astoundingly adorable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 00:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're asking the wrong question. What kind of cop dosen't stop every right minded person *from* buying a meerkat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 23:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ComicBT recruits from bB. The requirements aren't that high either. /r/baconbits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 15:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aaand its down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 16:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except he dosen't play EvE anymore, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 17:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how that one CT is so confused looking for it.. "It must be around here somewhere!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 16:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except he only talks about it in ts, while his friends say something through in-game VOIP once or twice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 16:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try watching the whole 45 minute game, or try to hear footsteps while that's playing. The kid also talked way too much. Plus they barely said anything rude to him, only on TS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 16:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should watch the whole game, it dosen't stop lol. And they never yell at him, only once does one of them say something negative about it in game and not in ts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 15:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an uninformed opinion, but i'm guessing if a projectile can be fired from 10x the distance it can now it gives them a much larger engagement range, allowing them to be safter when attacking, or defend from farther away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 01:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Script supervisor sounds like a cool job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 01:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 01:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's the antichrist. [S]atan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 00:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My god have they ever heard of makeup? That dude looks like he hasn't slept in way too long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 00:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shoutout to /r/irlsmurfing ! Awesome sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 23:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually saw a guy holding a water gun in one of the other epsiodes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 16:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/user/Lomak1581/videos This guys channel is a justiceporn goldmine. Highly reccomend checking out the rest of the videos. 

Smoking in some public places is illegal in Russia, they have dedicated smoking areas to stop passer bys breathing in second hand smoke. See: http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-21571418 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Public movement stops people smoking in a public place (Illegal in russia) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 16:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 16:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are both HDA and AHD ratio based? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 23:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You almost qualify for a bB interview: /r/baconbits read the message. From there you only have to get elite for an invite to WCD, or you could get into Waffles by being power user (takes pretty much no effort) which is #2 to WCD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 15:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit this is hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 01:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.imgur.com/OoX8nAf.png probably still not a fitting picture though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 00:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool idea but the indifferent being on a different line fucked it up for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 00:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ignore the dicks OP. It was readable but maybe a better font choice (sans serif?) and a white outline would have done it some justice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 22:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually thought that was aaron rodgers for half the video. God damnit OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 19:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He who is cruel to animals becomes hard also in his dealings with men. We can judge the heart of a man by his treatment of animals.

 Immanuel Kant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 15:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/csgolounge/status/561629987850452992 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 13:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Person running their twitter is mentally impaired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 09:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or take the DoS route: "Ohhh yeah, start up that slow loris you dirty slut. Oh god those packets feel so good!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 09:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recipient allah@god.com, gotta make sure he gets those virgins bro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 08:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Parts of this seemed fake as fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 04:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 00:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a whole series of them. This is awesome. Part 2: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O6EtRWdsdbI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 00:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was just a blog post about this: http://blog.counter-strike.net/index.php/2015/01/11288/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 23:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit this picture is so trippy. It almost looks like a mirror or a printed out photo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 01:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TS as in TorrentShack? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 23:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use symbolic links to cross seed. Simply install this: http://schinagl.priv.at/nt/hardlinkshellext/linkshellextension.html#contact and create a symbolic link of the file/folder, then use that for the other tracker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 20:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't Aura the one on that soundcloud recording acting like a complete dickhead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 01:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.imgur.com/PHUyL6A.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 07:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> then he should have never applied sorry (why even apply if you live in a completely different timezone, with even a remote possability of your schedule changing? what a waste.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 05:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speak for yourself, not me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 20:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait how did they find out? Did you make the pastbin public? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 16:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do so many people leave the battle report out of the description T_T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 16:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You only need this one if you're in the CFC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 16:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear these TLD's are getting out of hand.ninja </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 16:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious, not sure if you've stated anywhere else, is GGn being DDoS'd (I assume by IPT) or is it something else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 22:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its fine just close your eyes - the emu's are onto something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 05:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uusally i'd agree, but this guy is shooting a portrait in portrait mode. I think that was what it was made for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 23:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah and make sure you persevere through learning the basics of the game (controls, navigation, etc.) that was the biggest learning curve for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 22:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just out of curiosity, what's your average upload speed on a torrent (assuming just you seeding)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 15:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been down for like a week now, must be revamping that whole thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 03:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe she was just mentally ill? Or didn't mind taking responsibility for her actions? Or there were cops off camera and running would have made no sense? You're making a lot of assumptions for someone that knows almost nothing about the situation or the person. A true reddit detective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 03:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's be real, we all did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 22:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made me laugh for the first time today. Thank you OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 17:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> P...Poitot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
