<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7851</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 07:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SD card was taken from Grizzly shit. OP is the park ranger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 07:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically Souvlakistan lost total autonomy and are now Europe's prison bitch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 07:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah,  another 80+ billion gone that we will NEVER get back and Souvlakistan can burn a bit longer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might want to take a course in comprehensive reading, because I have been quite clear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not up to you to decide they opinions are reprehensible. Who made you a god? It may be your opinion that their beliefs are reprehensible, but that doesn't automatically make it so.

Stop thinking the world revolves around you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not up to me to decide if her statement is fine, neither is it for me to give judgement on her saying it. Do I agree with her? I don't think so, but that goes into a deeper conviction that marriage is an old fashioned concept regardless of gender. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh obviously it would bother me, however I would still defend her right to say so.

However if she was actively firing up the oven, that quite a different story.

Voltaire had something nice to say on this

 I do not agree with what you have to say, but I'll defend to the death your right to say it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! You have a great day as well, friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We tip the paperboy at Xmas. Usually about 20-50 euros. Depends a bit on how the service was. This year so far he's getting the 50 euro tip. I got a morning paper,  and without fail,  it's there before I wake up, which is pretty early.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No no. It might be your opinion that she is for lack of better words, a prejudiced asshole. Doesn't automatically make her one because her believe are not in line with yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good on you mate! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Whoohoo I won another argument on the internet.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Godwin%27s_law) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree in the sense that I believe marriage is an outdated system that should be made completely equal to a civil union (same rights and plights). It's just a word that is causing a ton of crap. Let whoever wants to call it a marriage call it a marriage and whoever wants to call it a civil union a civil union. Most issues solved, Christians happy, homos happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great "counter" there, buddy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a fan of whiskey and cigars. But I'm sure my Gin and hooker  budget exceeds yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, no I wouldn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Social Justice Warriors are a cancer that will ruin all progress made in the past 100 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who says it's the right thing to do? It's a matter of opinion. In her believe system it is not the right thing to do. Perhaps you should respect her beliefs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say the say the same as I am a proponent of free speech. Merkel could say the moon was made of cheese. It would make her look like an idiot, but she could say it none the less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure it will last you. However I have a nice looking kitchen and want a nice looking trashcan in it. I spend 20K euros on remodeling my kitchen,  do you think I would even hesitate at spending some cash on a nice bin instead of having some shitty disposable bin?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely right. If you think Merkel is a bigot,  feel free to express it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fine. Whatever consequences follow from expressing your opinion are your own to deal with. You're still free to express your opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's all not vote CDU,  wanna bet we van vote for who is Chancellor ;)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's your right to say it. Whatever consequences follow from saying that are your own responsibilities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Merkel doesn't?  I guess being the single most powerful woman on this planet is not a powerful and influential political position.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's your right to disagree. Doesn't mean you are right though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that is their prerogative. Luckily Germany is a democratic country and they can tell her next election.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Society will judge them. They are still free to say it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm voting for her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. It would make me think less of them,  but I'll be the last to care what they say. Society as a whole will judge them accordingly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite the opposite,  but also not a fascist telling people what they can and cannot say.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Najib pretty much told me to shove it when I missed a deal. Either I got unlucky,  or you got lucky.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's a human being entitled to her opinion whichever that opinion is. If the German people don't like it she'll be a goner by the next election. 

My guess: we do not care.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember,  up and down votes on reddit mean nothing. Just voice your opinion in a polite way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're pretty sick of having our benefits being reduced year over year while we have to keep bailing out a corrupt and lying nation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost 15% now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fortunately your opinion doesn't really matter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still ridiculous pricing. Got a 90 Oz tub of certified organic coconut oil for 18$ here. Restaurant supply store.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because you don't agree with it doesn't mean she is wrong or cannot say it. Two sides of a coin remember.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not too fizzed about it. She said this on her personal conviction. There is nothing wrong with someone saying they believe that a marriage is between a man and a woman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 19:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maynard James Keenan. After dropping LSD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 19:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No Walmart in Germany. I live in Germany. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 19:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snagged a XB One 500gb + extra controller. + Halo: Master chief edition + headset for 299 (330$) on amazon.de. It sold out in less than 30 seconds. It's about a 100 discount over the cheapest I could find online.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 22:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't he threaten to out his reptilian masters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 21:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nigger is just as bad as cracker. Case closed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
