<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8250</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 11:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but I've been meaning to try it out. I've heard it's a really good time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 01:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never imagined that this happened in other places. 

Here is the newspaper archive from the day the lot collapsed : 

http://newspaperarchives.vassar.edu/cgi-bin/vassar?a=d d=miscellany20070223-01.2.4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 00:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try and post some things that I happen to come in contact with while living here. Like you said, I never see anything from the area! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 23:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SERIOUSLY. I realize now that I probably should have at least stepped outside of my vehicle and took a picture before posting it on reddit with such shit quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 23:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It gets worse and worse every year, yet everyone still parks there (including myself). Its actually one of the busiest parking lots at the galleria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 23:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping someone would recognize it, I honestly didn't think anyone would. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 23:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I could understand that. Unfortunately, as I stated, it has already caved in once. It gets worse and worse over the years. Yet people, like myself, still park on the roof.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 23:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for the quality, it's supposed to be the degradation of the parking lot on top of a parking garage. The entire lot has multiple points where it is sinking  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 23:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahah me too! That and Fun Central that used to be down Route 9, I used to get free tokens all the time. It was great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bahahahaha you mean that spot in the food court which literally every store that has been there has ceased to exist? Maybe they are bitter assholes because they lost their business! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
