<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1473</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poverty can be eliminated by killing the poor or just letting them starve. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 07:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adolf Hitler depicted by the United States Secret Service in 1944 to show how he might disguise himself to escape capture. [1323  694] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 05:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was extremely dissapointed when I found out that SJW stood for "social justice warrior" instead of sexy Jewish woman. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 04:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 04:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. I remember hearing Metro Station's [Shake It](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_wjFahULCK8), which was released in 2008 about seven years before its release, multiple times. I even told other people who agreed that they could remember hearing it years before 2008. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Challenge: Make China repeal it's one-child policy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 04:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Besides the Amish and many isolated tribes, what are some communities that seem to live like it's still the past? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 18:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 14:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has the jaw, forehead, and lips of a man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 05:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serbian war crimes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If only they made it so you could enter the church. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 04:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since a late model Mercedes S-Class has so many more safety and driver assistance features than one from the 90s, is it possible that Princess Diana would have survived the crash that killed her if it had happened today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 03:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FWI: The shortage of women in China causes the sex industry in China to boom. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 02:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China, with its millions and millions of lonely men will develop a huge sex industry if the situation doesn't change anytime soon. Porn will be rampant and have a huge market. Many women will take advantage of the situation by becoming prostitutes, strippers, porn stars, and escorts. Men will take advantage by being pimps, opening up strip clubs, distributing pornography, acting in porn, or even crossdressing to prostitute themselves as women. Some of those who profit off the situation may become very wealthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shemale - Hitler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 02:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have three kids and no money. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 21:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FWI: A diplomat commits a mass shooting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 20:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 11:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I have been reading a little too much /r/futurology lately and a lot of the commenters predict a bleak future for driving, but I'm not sure if that's because they think that's what will happen or what they want to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the unpopular opinion that you stand by no matter how much it has gotten you downvoted and flamed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 05:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would a society where being a sociopath is the norm look like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 04:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FWI: A European country adopts American-style gun laws. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 03:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I tell this girl in my class that I think she might really be a guy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 03:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 02:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jaguar F-Type </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dylann Roof went full retard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 00:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Still blacker than Rachel Dolezal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 00:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The seller is DREAMING! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 04:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 69 - Hitler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 03:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FWI: Facebook goes the way of MySpace by 2025. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 03:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 06:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Affluenza </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 05:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/glitch_in_the_matrix </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Foot Fetishism - Hitler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 03:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you rather do for a billion dollars? Kill someone or get AIDS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 03:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 03:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taxes are lowered for the rich, increased for everybody else. This decreases the number of corporations leaving the U.S. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FWI: It is proven that the Universe is really a simulation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 01:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read this and also look up simulation theory, 
http://www.nytimes.com/2014/02/16/opinion/sunday/is-the-universe-a-simulation.html?_r=0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 Ford Torino GT is most likely a myth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 22:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nigerian news report about a man cutting off his penis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 05:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 08:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sex and violence will be way more acceptable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 08:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.timesofisrael.com/unfortunately-named-chevy-ss-wont-storm-israel/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FWI: A transsexual woman receives a uterus transplant and is able to become pregnant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 07:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 06:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see something like this in Portland, San Francisco, Austin, or Minneapolis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whoever farts in church sits in his own pew. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 05:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 05:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as I am disgusted by smoking, I can still tell that banning tobacco would be a step in the wrong direction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 05:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice to see that there are other young people and other redditors out there who like 70s American cars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 04:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, do they sell it in Germany or Austria?

I've always thought the same thing about "SS" cars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 04:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something will happen if the Republican Party doesn't get any younger and ages out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any credible statistics on how many Sovereign Citizens there are? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 04:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google - Hitler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 04:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 03:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, this turned into a circlejerk real quickly. No pun intended. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 03:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toyota Land Cruiser. Starts at 80k and looks like a bigger, blander version of the Sequoia. Not a bad truck until you realize that the Range Rover Sport and Cadillac Escalade start at about the same price and actually look like what you pay for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE think that it takes away from someone's point if they disparage someone else because they disagree with them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 02:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was the Jaguar E-Type designed to look like a big dick on purpose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 02:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9a/1963_Jaguar_XK-E_Roadster.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 01:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America will no longer have a two-party system. The Libertarian, Green, and Independent parties will grow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I was in kindergarten I wanted to color myself with brown magic marker to become Black. Rachel Dolezal has been living 5-year old me's dream. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 23:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 20:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes sense now that you say it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 20:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found a render of what a coupe version of the current gen CTS could look like,

http://tripedali.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/Cadillac-2015-CTS-V-Coupe.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 18:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't think Iv'e ever seen one in person, I imagined it being bigger than a CTS coupe though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jenna the Sovereign Citizen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 18:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rachel Dolezal - Hitler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 18:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE feel like you can easily imagine what an older person looked like when they were younger, but can't usually imagine what a young person will look like when they get older? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 18:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 17:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~[Cadillac ELR](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cadillac_ELR)~~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 16:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Morgan makes modern cars that look like they are from the 1920s-30s.

- The Bentley Arnage and Chrysler 300 are big and boxy like 80s cars.

- The 2000-09 Jaguar XJ has the same basic shape as the 1968 XJ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FWI: A group of sovereign citizens buy a large parcel of land in a remote location of either the Western United States or Alaska where they live together and attempt to isolate themselves from the government. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 14:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see this potentially resulting in a Waco or Ruby Ridge style siege if the government finds out and feels that enough illegal activity is occurring there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the longest amount of time an imposter has been able to successfully impersonate someone else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 07:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These two </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 05:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE feel that Reddit has made you better at arguing or debating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 04:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FWI: Japan and Russia go to war with each other over the Kuril Islands. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 04:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FWI: 20-50 years from now, politics and views that are now considered to be on the fringe will be considered mainstream. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 03:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 02:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He probably did, if you consider that this happened, https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Nyou_eKlr0U </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Euro coins have been counterfeited,
http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2886170/Chinese-criminal-gangs-master-ability-create-perfect-euro-2-coins-investigators-reveal-shipments-forgeries-arriving-Italy.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FWI: 3D printing is a boon for crime. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 07:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3D printing will increase crime by making it easier to make homemade guns, knockoff goods, copies of keys, fake credit cards, fake IDs, and counterfeit coins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FWI: The average height for women becomes taller than the average height for men. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 07:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 05:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think quickly, honk, and do whatever you can. Move over, brake, or speed up depending on the situation. I've nearly been nudged twice by drivers changing lanes without looking at 30-45 mph. In your case it sounds like the other car got in front of you and was on your front bumper. I'm imagining that I would have to brake to make room for them and try to notice early. Being in New York I'm pretty used to assholes not signaling and cutting other cars off. Having a dashcam would probably also be beneficial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 04:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The wheels might be big though, 19-20 inch rims are optional on the S Class. Also, Acura has a similar looking lighting system on some of their cars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 03:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he doesn't understand that the CLS is a high tech luxury car. My mom says she used to be able to wash the interior of her bare bones 1970 Chevy Nova with a garden hose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Idiot ruins a CLS. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 02:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 22:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me it looks like an $80-$110k car, but I could see it being priced lower since Lincoln has generally priced its cars lower than the European counterparts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Lincoln Continental concept is the best thing to come out of Lincoln in years. If it goes into production what position do you think it hold in the market? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 20:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will it be a Livery cab/Uber/rental car like the Town Car, a near-luxury sedan like the Chrysler 300, or an actual competitor with cars such as the Lexus LS and Mercedes S550?

http://m.caranddriver.com/news/lincoln-continental-concept-revealed-news </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 20:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds a lot like Ancient Rome or Greece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ellen Pao - Hitler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 19:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japanese musicians </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 08:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interview with a Crab </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 07:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 05:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, I instantly thought Mitsubishi Mirage as the answer to the question. Then I look at the article and see a picture of the Mirage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some technologies that a lot of people thought we would have in the future but never got? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 04:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 04:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if he is right?

Ha what? Google, Audi, Mercedes, freightliner and who knows what other companies have already driven a combined million+ miles, and crossed the US driverlessly. Technology companies like apple, uber, Delphi, Cisco systems, and nvidia are all competing to release driverless car technology. 

That doesn't mean that the technology will become mainstream or be perfected.

There are already mass produced cars on the road today that have lane departure warnings, emergency braking, self parking, and adaptive cruise control features.

Electronic driver assist features and self driving cars are not the same thing.

The government is making rules mandating technology that will allow vehicles to communicate with each other, which is pretty much the biggest barrier to autonomous vehicle technology working on a large scale. 

This is still very early in development and may be used either in autonomous or human driven cars.

And pretty much every single car manufacturer in existence will readily admit that autonomous cars are an inevitability. Your prediction is wrong you fudgetosser. 

If they don't become an inevatibility, that wouldn't be the first time a prediction of the future didn't come true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This dealer has no idea what they are talking about. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 03:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian roulette - Hitler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 02:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why hasn't any major American manufacturer produced a V12 powered luxury car since the 1940's? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 02:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 01:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might be able to get a better "normal" Crown Vic for the same price.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 01:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -70 points and still not hidden and labelled "score below threshold". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 00:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of 80s American cars looked like Rolls Royces, http://i.imgur.com/F6h2JtA.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 22:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boxy style or round style? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually don't see it as ugly. It's not the prettiest, but still a decent, simple, elegant design for what it is, http://www.collectorcarads.com/Picture1/Pontiac1985003.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out of all the cars you've owned, which is the most different from the rest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 15:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if being a Psychopath or Sociopath becomes the norm? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 07:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FWI: We are living in a computer simulation and there are likely few "updates" left to be added to our world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 06:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought of this because every year used to feel different to me, but not anymore. 2013, 2014, and 2015 have all felt the same to me, even though there have been major changes in my life since 2013.

Edit: also watch this: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Chfoo9NBEow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Masturbation - Hitler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 06:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 05:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Morgan, Backdraft, Factory Five, AC, TVR, and Wiesmann are some successful, long lasting, niche sports car manufacturers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At what point do you expect the last Crown Vic Police Interceptor still in service to be retired? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 04:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 02:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The OLdsmobile Diesel engines used in 1977-85 GM cars, such as the Bonneville were terribly unreliable, http://www.autosavant.com/2009/08/11/the-cars-that-killed-gm-the-oldsmobile-diesel/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 02:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever you do, don't touch it if its a diesel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/shittyphotoshop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These three posers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mature means miniaturized, mass produced, cheap, and little room for new improvements. Most current tech is at its height and future technologies such as A.I. are either as far as they will get, will not catch on, or may be banned. It's interesting that you mentioned AI because many experts, such as Steven Hawking and Bill Gates believe that it will end humanity if it becomes too advanced. If enough support their view, certain forms of AI may be banned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sprinter van? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 07:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched some of his videos and can't tell what kind of mental illness he's suffering from. He also wasn't a bad looking guy before getting his face covered in tattoos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 06:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of this annoying teacher I used to have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 06:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not as shitty as GG Allin's tattoos were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 06:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So do I, that's part of why I hate him and am fascinated by him at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 06:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is since there was never a Mercury over there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 05:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its called 5 Seconds of Summer, but there's 4 of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teddy Boy Greg before and after. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 05:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teddy Boy Greg before and after. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 05:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 02:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I linked to that because it is a screenshot from those notorious PSAs, and you spelled "writing" wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What kind of things will become trendy again in 5-10 years when people start becoming nostalgic for the 2000s? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Teddy Boy Greg a GG Allin wannabe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 23:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I guess that doesn't work for green mod comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beer - Hitler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 23:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 23:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The gay is turned up to 11. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fighter plane themed car with working propellor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 23:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 22:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://static1.squarespace.com/static/52e28821e4b07cd558a3e967/t/54f9ece4e4b0251d5319bd83/1425665253965/you-wouldnt-download-a-car-1-728.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 22:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why can't this get labeled "comment score below threshold"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> going nuts and causing a scene at 711 today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 05:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some anachorisms you have noticed in GTA games set in the past? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 00:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realized that Playback FM in GTA San Andreas is called an "old school hip hop" station, yet the songs range in year from 1987-1992. This means that the oldest songs are 5 years old and the newest one is from the year the game takes place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 21:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://static1.squarespace.com/static/52e28821e4b07cd558a3e967/t/54f9ece4e4b0251d5319bd83/1425665253965/you-wouldnt-download-a-car-1-728.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giant centipede </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 19:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should have written "continue to coexist", but I just wrote coexist because they haven't become widespread everywhere yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will electric cars replace fuel powered cars or coexist with each other? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By coexist I mean be chosen by different people with different needs and preferences, kind of like diesel and gasoline has been for decades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else get excited when you're listening to the radio (in real life) and a song from GTA comes on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 15:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 742 Evergreen Terrace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do trolls get upvotes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 06:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does everybody on Reddit have the same voice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 06:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 05:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real people do dumb shit. Who's not going to strap-on a Go-Pro and try car surfing when the car can't crash? Wanna bang in the back seat while Robo-Bob drives? etc... There's going to be some sort of freak accident where some family drowns when the car drives on a correctly mapped road through a flash-flood or something a human driver could have easily avoided.

Thats one of the things that makes me worry about self driving cars. They will bring out people's stupidity because they trust the computer too much. I could also see a trend of dumb kids jumping in front of self driving cars to see if they get hit or not occuring.

The main problem I see with trucks would seem to be that the absence of a human operator combined with accident avoidance software would seem to make such vehicles easy targets for criminals (cargo hijackers).

Couldn't the trucks be manned by guards even if they are self driving? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 05:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that the current concepts are slow and overly cautious, cannot be used in harsh conditions, and don't recognize the color of traffic lights in the sun are some more problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE generally delete a post if it gets no comments, upvotes, or downvotes for several hours? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 04:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What chance do you think there is that self driving cars may never really be a thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 04:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ask this because most of the news regarding them seems to be made of hype and because similar concepts which were said to be the future of transportation such as [Personal Rapid Transit](http://www.tbd.com/blogs/tbd-on-foot/2011/07/metro-history-the-1970s-thrill-surrounding-personal-rapid-transit-prt--11713.html) and flying cars were tested in in the 1950's-80's but were never perfected and never became widely used. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 03:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have wondered if electric will replace fuel or if it will coexist with it like diesel does with gasoline now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 03:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gombe Chimpanzee War  Cannibalism (zoology)  Cannibalism  German mistreatment of Soviet prisoners of war  World War II  Hitler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rick James - Hitler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 03:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RicK James - Cold Blooded [Funk] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 03:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 16:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, there's plenty of family sedans these days that are as fast or faster than any Ferrari built before the 80s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veruca Salt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 14:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 14:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scary thing is that she looks so normal.

Edit: she looks like someone who would post on /r/awwschwitz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 14:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't notice this when I copied and pasted the caption. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 07:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who beat and verbally berated him and the other Jackson kids while they were growing up. He is a psychopath who mainly used his kids as a way to make money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 06:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heavy Metal Trailer Trash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michelle Watson; charged with aggravated assault on a police officer, resisting arrest and drink-driving in Nov 2011. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 05:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charles Manson at his craziest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 05:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 05:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buffalo Bill meets Michael Meyers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 05:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The legs on the girl to the left of her look too thin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 05:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of like how some parts of the U.S. still looked like the 50's back in the late 60s-early 70s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extreme Guido </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 05:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 04:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a scrotum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creepy phone charger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 04:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 03:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like he has yet to grow out of his wannabe gangster phase that started in 8th grade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fred Durst </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 03:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 02:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These jokes are getting old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 02:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice Porsche </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 01:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> miata </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 01:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I did post this on /r/shitty_car_mods a while ago](http://www.reddit.com/r/Shitty_Car_Mods/comments/36ys0w/the_worst_thing_to_put_on_a_german_car/)

and this question would be better suited for /r/carscirclejerk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 00:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He can't go 120 on the highway if he doesn't want to be "that guy". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 00:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he say he ever actually went 120 on the highway? Whether he did or not, this is still a dumb question that should be self-explanatory for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Radovan Karadi - Hitler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 00:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 23:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, but in the case of the Matrix/Vibe and 3000GT/Stealth etc. didnt both companies own shares in each other? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 23:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The iA clearly looks like a Mazda 3, the iM looks more like a Prius or CT. I guess they could be on the same platform, but I never knew that Toyota/Scion owned Mazda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 23:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The iM looks like a rebadged Lexus CT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
