<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1576</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dewey executives cooked books, ex-finance director says at trial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 02:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 02:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/jorgepal02 to r/stopdrinking--At [this link is a post called the Baby Steps](https://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) which is an accurate summary of what I did to stop drinking and get sober.  I still do these things.  Good luck and I hope I see you continue to post and comment as you go along. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lobbyists spend less on lawmakers in wake of McDonnell trial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great, /u/saltwatermonkey -- when you get and stay sober you get your life back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations on 7 years SOBER.  I just put an invite to join us on /r/dinos in your inbox.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Bicycle and the Ride to Modern America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The argument against common-sense gun control crumbles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VA supervisor took $1.2 million in kickbacks; another employee stole at least 150 gravestones, prosecutors said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are absolutists among philosophers of honesty.  For instance leaving a false impression or creating a misimpression is also lying.  We have an affirmative duty in my opinion to correct lies.  Which is my  way of saying that I'm not advocating white lies with this post; I'm saying let us not justify unnecessary cruelty to others under the guise of "brutal honesty."   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is a valid point.  The constant lying about and covering up for my drinking were more than enough to cause all sorts of distortions in my character.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonderful.  What a great sensation that is.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not going to drink TODAY because I am not going to drive drunk with people in my car.  I've done that too, my young children.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In early sobriety I ill-advisably dated (and briefly lived with) a young woman, Audrey, who long timers on /r/stopdrinking have heard me speak of in past posts and comments usually in the context of why it's not a good idea to date in early sobriety.

One of Audrey's most striking characteristics was her tendency to pop off to her "friends" or newcomers in AA in a manner in which she would shrug and say, "'Sorry, I'm brutally honest." Except she wasn't, she was merely brutal.  This week while we talk about Honesty remember that in striving to be more honest, we can not and should not justify our rude and unsupportive behavior as "brutal honesty."  In sobriety we reserve brutal honesty for the man or woman in the mirror.  

When my SO asks if she looks fat in a dress, skirt, slacks--no amount of karma was ever earned by saying "Yes." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brutal Honesty is not Honesty, it's mostly just Brutal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The person who is brutally honest enjoys the brutality quite as much as the honesty. Possibly more.  Richard Needham, (1912-1996) Canadian educator and cartoonist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 22:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're doing it right and becoming a real power of example, /u/Andrew_Tefft.  Please keep doing what you are doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Youll Never Guess This Bad Lawyers Name </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 21:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 21:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/whenisitmyturn2 to /r/stopdrinking -- [at this link is the Baby Steps post](https://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) which describes what I did to stop drinking and to get sober.  I hope something there resonates for you.  Best of luck and welcome aboard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 21:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations, my friend.  An invite to join us on /r/dinos will shortly follow in your inbox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 21:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you, /u/rose_the_wolf -- you can do this and you can post and comment about it as a power of example.  We support you and your reasoning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 21:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the best investments I ever made was in a [Blackburn high pressure pump.](http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00NFX298U/ref=pd_lpo_sbs_dp_ss_3?pf_rd_p=1944687642 pf_rd_s=lpo-top-stripe-1 pf_rd_t=201 pf_rd_i=B005ZGQFDK pf_rd_m=ATVPDKIKX0DER pf_rd_r=1HZ9YKXGRJH8G6KG1HRZ)  Nothing you can do to make yourself go faster and with fewer punctures than to run a max pressure (even slightly higher) on good tires. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man who pimped teen girls, advertised them online as 'Barbie dolls' gets 20 years in prison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 21:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 21:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mano a Mano! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump: Plant? Foil? Something's not right </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Money makes a difference in state judge races </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations, my friend.  I am so happy for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations, you sound like you're doing it right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great news!  Congratulations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump says hell kick El Chapos a--, calls FBI after threat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Commutes Sentences for 46 Drug Offenders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Washington County judge sentenced for stealing drug evidence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 19:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 19:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Which vote?  Field Manual?](http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2015/06/16/2016-gop-torture_n_7597906.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 19:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the same time he said waterboarding was torture and "not what we're about." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 18:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what you're saying is: he doesn't have a buck to his name? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 18:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think you're wrong about Graham's position on torture.  Remember this is McCain's closest Senate ally and my recollection is that the two of them are zealously anti-torture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 17:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the last of my generation, then.  It's a little dated at this point, but I thought it captured some core truths. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 17:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 7th or 8th drink was never my downfall.  It was always the first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 17:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I don't sympathize with Graham's let's-fight-every-war obsession; I don't think it's fair to label him a Chicken Hawk.  Until recently he was a commissioned US Air Force JAG officer--not likely to see action, but still someone in military service. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 17:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may be the last person in recovery to have seen [*28 Days*](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0191754/) with Sandra Bullock, but I really liked her navigation from the bottom-drinker to someone in recovery.  It's ordinary, and as a result I liked it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 17:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck, /u/randoker -- you may have hit upon a strategy that's effective for you.  Not really, for the long term.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 17:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/WMWA to r/stopdrinking--I was able to stop drinking and get sober doing the things I describe at the [Baby Steps post.](https://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/)  Why don't you see if anything there seems helpful to you in your effort--best of luck to you and your GF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 17:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you think that is?  Let's talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 16:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This [is the link to the post from the FAQ; What do drinking dreams mean](https://www.reddit.com/r/stopdrinking/comments/2dit1m/what_do_drinking_dreams_mean/) which I wrote after exchanging emails with dream researchers.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 16:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem; the title was in the original with my insertion of "Louisiana," only for clarification.  It was not my intention to editorialize. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 16:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember this well, a_o, I was at the event earlier in the day and, of course, I have coffee near there every morning.  But more significant to me was that a guy I know in AA was the first responder on the scene.  He opened the door of the drunk driver's car after his fellow first responders attended to the dead and other injured.  He describes recoiling from the smell of alcohol and the driver in a panic asking, "Are they dead?"  

Honesty is accepting that when I drank and drove, it could have been me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sheriff: Man went to Ariz. for 'sex acts' with horse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 16:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As 2016 race starts, will Christie's Jersey-bred mannerisms play in prime time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 16:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme dumbness at Louisianas high court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 15:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 15:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't feel bad for Alabama, this ass-clown was impeached and then the voters re-elected him to the bench. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 15:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL!  Inauthentic dumbass pretends otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Univision Hires Bush Lawyer to Defend Donald Trump Lawsuit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Politicians Keep Using Songs Without Artists' Permission </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Memo to Hillary: 'You're Still the Problem' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alabama Supreme Court Chief Justice Roy Moore told a church crowd on Sunday that the U.S. Supreme Court "destroyed the institution of God" by legalizing same-sex marriage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alabama Supreme Court Chief Justice Roy Moore: Same-sex marriage ruling 'destroyed the institution of God' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scalia/Ginsburg: An affectionate comic opera look at the high court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not going to happen.  Reince Preibus is not a candidate for the Profiles in Courage award. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great comment, I totally agree.  One of the things that I find most offensive is this politician's successful attack on the liberty to contract, and enforce contract rights.  We would not tolerate this ransacking of the Rule of Law in a close foreign ally, but many applaud Walker as the second coming?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Rep. Filemon Vela, D-Brownsville, the Democrats' ranking member on the House Homeland Security Committee Subcommittee on Border and Maritime Security, said Sunday that had the U.S. been able to extradite the reputed warlord, Guzmn's confinement would have been guaranteed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lindsey Graham Says Reince Priebus Should Denounce Donald Trump on Immigration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps trash talk: The 23 people and institutions he slammed in a single speech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote this [post on Drinking Dreams after exchanging emails with leading dream researchers.](https://www.reddit.com/r/stopdrinking/comments/2dit1m/what_do_drinking_dreams_mean/)  There's good news for recovery in this post.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker, Viewed as Authentic, Aims for Smart in the 2016 Race </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 12:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 11:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not drinking TODAY no matter what happens good or bad; honestly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 10:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 10:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, Ha, well-done, KJ!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 10:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not my experience.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In AA I was able to drop the mask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an active AA, within the fellowship just one dishonest predator can devastate a recovery community and drive out newcomers like crazy.  How can you spot this sort of character?  And what might you do to protect yourself?   For one thing, newcomers should be wary of too private a contact.  Solid supportive relationships form in the OPEN.  When someone sounds too good to be true; they probably are.  Remember, in recovery we are all drunks and addicts, so someone presenting as totally together isn't.  Other ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best wishes, /u/comiju on day one!  [At this link is the Baby Steps](https://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) which is a post I wrote about some simple "next" actions to getting and staying sober. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I WAS a liar.  I did not really appreciate it at the time.  I thought I was an honest person.  In reality I lied to achieve and gather to myself that which I valued.  I lied to manage how I was perceived.  Before I got sober and even for sometime after I got sober, I was a reflexive liar.  I have described how in March of 1986 I drunkenly fell down sustaining a quadriceps injury that required that my leg be placed in air cast.  This injury began my long effort to get and stay sober.  Remarkably every time I was asked about how I injured myself I told a different story.  Sometimes two irreconcilable versions to the same person.  During that same period, an administrative hearing officer told me that I had developed the unfortunate reputation for being not a serious or credible person.  That was my rock bottom.  But even after I stopped drinking the struggle to get honest and be honest was a real struggle, but as I learned ESSENTIAL to getting sober.  Ralph Waldop Emerson gave the following advice: "Speak what you think today in hard words and tomorrow speak what tomorrow thinks in hard words again, though it contradict every thing you said today.   I call this getting molecularly honest.  And the person I needed to get honest with most in the world is ME.  Over the years and through my actions, only--I think I have been able to change the way the people who I most care about in the world see me.  I believe that today, I am perceived to be honest and trustworthy.  This has been a long haul, but it is the character asset that is most valuable to me in the world.  It is a gift of sobriety.

The simple step of a courageous individual is not to take part in the lie. One word of truth outweighs the world. --Alexandr Solzenitsyn

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Week on r/stopdrinking | Can we get Honest about Honesty? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I propose that in addition to all of our normal posts, comments, advice, and sobriety (and life)-threatening issues--that we think and talk about HONESTY.  Especially about how getting honest was prerequisite to getting sober and getting to quality sobriety.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I challenge you to raise your hand and "re-introduce" yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 23:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/bagaiste to r/stopdrinking.  This is a great and supportive community.  I like to share the [Baby Steps post with](https://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) the newcomers as a place to look for "next" things to do as you get sober.  If anything resonates there for you, terrific.  Best of luck.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Christie and all those other governors should pay for their own police protection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 23:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LPT: Be yourself, everyone else is taken.  

Source: Oscar Wilde </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you.  Keep doing what you're doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sitting here at my computer sipping my homemade iced tea--happily chatting on SD.  I am not going to drink TODAY. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is said that alcohol is but a symptom or our "disease."  Personally, that was true for me, but amazingly after I undertook to stop drinking (which I did via [the things I describe at the Baby Steps post)](https://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) my underlying mental health issues were much improved.  In other words I was able to ACT MY WAY INTO better mental health.  Bill Wilson, one of the co-founders of AA describes in the book, Alcoholics Anonymous aka the Big Book that he had access to the leading mental health and addiction specialists of the day (1920s-1930s) and that self knowledge did not keep him sober.  So, /u/MenstrualJackson, we are not alone.  

Good luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 19:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can I hate myself and yet be obsessed with how I appear to others?   How can I want to destroy myself but spend a fortune for custom tailored suits and shirts?  I do these things BECAUSE I am not honest.  I am not honest because I am afraid of rejection, pain, and further diminishment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 17:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooooh good one.  So true, too.  

If I am to get sober, and stay sober I need to honestly see the man in the mirror for who I am.  Sometimes I am weak, sometimes strong; often vulnerable and fearful; but, trying one day at a time to be more and more accepting of what is real, rejecting my fantasy thinking and embracing life on life's terms.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 17:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't think of why not.  AA is not a monolithic society.  AA is made up of people like you and me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 110 year-old case that still inspires Supreme Court debates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 17:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 17:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you, and welcome.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 17:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll never give up hope double-D.  You DO have it in you.  Action, my friend.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 16:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then by that standard Hilary and Bill Clinton must be Gods in real life, because Maureen Dowd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 16:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations, u/mossboss.  An invite to /r/dinos will shortly follow in your inbox unless Slip or one of the other DINO mods beat me to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 14:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not on the bestsellers list because its not a bestseller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 14:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for being an important part of the whole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 14:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You obviously don't read the NYT opinion section.  Setting aside the constant stream of conservative free lance contributors and conservative office holders the NYT is where William Safire went after his time as Nixon speech writer; where David Brooks, and Ross Douthat have permanent columns.  You right wing types really need to drop the whole resentment-trope, it's unbecoming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 14:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your comment made a vague and meaningless point that purported to refute the well-reasoned essay of a Southern journalist and historian--your comment was nonsense.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Howell Raines is a journalist from the deep south.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Howell_Raines)  He worked as a journalist at the Birmingham Post, the Atlanta Journal Constitution, and the St. Petersburg Times. He wrote an oral history of the Civil Rights movement and a history of the deep South.  I suspect he might have slightly more insight into the politics and history of the South than your average NYT reporter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forty-two days and depressed?  This in my experience is totally normal, because it takes time to recover from the assault on the body, brain and central nervous system that we were doing with alcohol in the period (years?) before we stopped.  I guarantee that give it some time and you will feel so much better.  If the mood does not lift, please by all means don't drink and see a licensed professional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While you technically are correct about the remaining southern democratic holdouts--[Howell Raines is correct and you don't know what you are talking about.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Southern_strategy) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Cruz 2016: Feuds with the New York Times-and loves it | The Texas senator is making the most of the Gray Ladys refusal to put his book on its bestseller list. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walkers primary strategy: Motorcycles, barbecue and a Winnebago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a brilliant essay by Howell Raines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio GOP payouts in ballot fight nearly $600,000 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Dream World of the Southern Republicans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a powerful post that gets at several core issues that I was speaking to someone about early, early this morning and over the past few days.  In my opinion we struggle with "honesty" or what AA calls the necessary prerequisite to sobriety: rigorous honesty--because, we want to "appear to be" smart, funny, attractive, and powerful when deep down we believe we aren't or we suspect we are fraudulent.  A personality distortion that can result from this struggle is narcissism--which is an obsessive, dishonest stage management of how we are perceived.  It's not uncommon to see people in recovery who are incredibly, even reflexively dishonest, and I suspect this also stems from not being comfortable in being in "their own skin."  I was one of these people, too.  

I had to learn to be vulnerable, honest, what I came to call--molecularly honest.  That extends to EVERYTHING I say on /r/stopdrinking and frankly all the Reddit forums.  If I am to grow up, I need to embrace honestly, who I am.

So while you felt bad, and vulnerable, /u/Englishfella -- I applaud your honesty and I am gilding you as a power of example.  Keep doing what you're doing and the next time you see your friend with the 14 years--go up to him and stick your hand out.  Congratulate him on his 14 years.  I suspect that if you can hang on to what you got, we will be celebrating you and looking to you for more wisdom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 11:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to r/stopdrinking--I'm on my iPhone so I  can't share the babysteps post with you but I will update a little later.  I  wanted to say that you are in the right place to get support for a SOBER journey. 

[The Baby Steps are what I did to stop drinking and get sober.](https://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/)  Good luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 11:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not drinking TODAY no matter what happens good or bad; free time? Someone has free time?!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 11:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, /u/divebarprincess -- I thought I shared the [Baby Steps post with you previously](https://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) but it sounds to me like you really need to talk to a licensed professional and not well-meaning but anonymous redditors.  Please keep us updated on how you're doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! And we reached a place of indifference to alcohol.  It is not in my movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, no kidding.  You look great.  Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 23:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was totally on-topic; relating to both corruption at the highest levels and the impact on local, state and national politics.  The article was by the pre-eminent Virginia political reporter and it further pertained to what "honest services" constitutes in the view of the federal courts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 19:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my SD pals logs on here, periodically to itemize where he's at in terms of booze not consumed and money saved.   At last count he was closing in on a year and the totals are mind-blowing.  Trust me, he saved ten times the amount you poured down the drain last night.  In other words you aren't "down" anything.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 19:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations, /u/saltwatermonkey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not small at all; that's real life and if you don't pick up the next drink you have a chance a whole new and authentic life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 14:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check the pic--all the donors lined up to give "Hedge" a check. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bush Draws on Family Dynasty for Fund-Raising Efforts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 14:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker: Open records changes 'a huge mistake' that 'didn't come from us' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Appeals court panel upholds former Va. Gov. Bob McDonnell's convictions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Rubio has more than once disqualified himself for higher office.  This is one more example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [ethical rules](http://www.americanbar.org/content/dam/aba/migrated/cpr/mrpc/mcpr.authcheckdam.pdf) that apply to all lawyers tell us that all persons deserve competent and professional representation (the rules adopted in most states used to say zealous representation, but that idea justified unacceptable distortions in professional conduct). The rules also remind professionals that just because a matter involves repugnant or controversial allegations, that in and of itself does not justify declining to represent a client.  Remember if a person comes into an emergency room with gunshot wounds received in the commission of a crime, an emergency room provider won't decline medical services, right?  Having undertaken a representation, competent and professional lawyers pursue every defense, challenging everything from jurisdiction (the power to render judgment in a matter), investigation into facts, challenges based on the law applicable to the facts--so as to hold the prosecution to EVERY element of the government's burden of proof beyond a reasonable doubt.  It is not the job of the lawyer to judge a client--the people, the finders of fact and of law will do that.  The lawyer is ultimately just one of the advocates in an imperfect system of justice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perry Consulting for Big Donor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was never one glass for me either.  In fact, when I was drinking I would deliberately avoid just one drink because of how uncomfortable and miserable I would feel.  I was a PIG drinker who once I started would not stop until I was in a stupor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, this is a common issue.  I think it was /u/offtherocks who said, mark-off the first two weeks on your calendar for a bumpy ride. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marco Rubio Calls Abortion Rights Indefensibleand Knocks Down Pro-Abortion Straw Man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rick Perrys $6 million man: Rich donors pour massive sums into 2016 super PACs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not Like Us </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 11:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not drinking TODAY no matter what happens good or bad; I am keeping a beautiful, sunny Saturday in Cleveland SOBER.  

Than you, /u/McLensky for a great week of daily check-ins for SD World.  Service work can be a great step in the SOBER Journey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay, congrats, KJ!  Well-deserved, my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good news!  I am so happy for you.  Naughty kitten! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AA meetings helped me through this sort of quandary about what to do.  Especially when I was in new surroundings.  There I found people who understand me.  Especially other Irish binge drinkers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition to the excellent advice of my pal, /u/juden-shikker -- I found an attitude of ALL-IN made a lot of difference.  Let me add one more observation: persistence, one more day, one more day...and, then the miracle occurred for me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice!  Action not words is the path to sobriety in my experience--and, fitness is action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 01:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/fabiolives to /r/stopdrinking -- let me share the [link to the Baby Steps](https://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) which is my answer to the question: what do I do next?  Obviously, following your doctor's advice is huge and very smart.  Good luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 01:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At supper an hour ago, I said essentially these words to my wife.  In fact add the fact that I am a white guy born in the deep south, you get no argument from me that this flag is an offense to my black brothers and sisters.  As flawed as I am personally, that flag should no longer be officially in the face of black Americans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 01:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What worked for me in terms of stopping drinking wasn't fear of liver failure or wet brain--instead, being sick and tired all the time and hoping, knowing if I stopped that I could turn my life around.  In other words it wasn't death--it was the certainty that there is life.  I stopped drinking and I got sober by doing [the simple things I describe at this link.](https://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/)  Good luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 01:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found all the support I needed and more, in AA meetings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 01:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [least popular advice in early sobriety is dry people, dry places.](https://www.reddit.com/r/stopdrinking/comments/2szkp8/the_least_popular_advice_dry_people_dry_places/?ref=search_posts) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's what I did: [the Baby Steps.](https://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/)  And like you I recognized that my drinking was endangering not only my health but putting my children at risk (mine from driving impaired with them in the back seat of my car.)  I had to take ACTION.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love AA and I avidly work an AA program, but I agree you hear a lot of stupid shit in AA meetings sometimes.  I try not to judge, but I'd like to think that I've reached a point where I developed some discernment between substance and utter bollocks.   Remember even with substantial time sober, these are many of the same drunk clowns who made sitting on a barstool insufferable.  As Slip likes to point out, some are sicker than others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I would be going to /r/alanon meetings to learn some coping strategies with my brother's alcoholism.  A lot of us in recovery are "double winners" so to speak; and it looks like you might be one too.  The other thing is I would have to look long and hard--as you are doing--with what you thought you were doing with the cans of beer.  Remember anger and resentment are the chief offenders for relapse.  Good on you for posting about this; because I've been there and all I needed was one good excuse and I spent 7 years in relapse hell.  Don't go there, it's not worth it.  Most of us don't make it back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pastors Eye A Move From God's House To The Statehouse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 20:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 20:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That lovely young woman was the original Lolita. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attorney in hypnosis case files to resign from law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 20:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 18:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Caught cheating, go figure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Oversight said it sent subpoena to Secret Service chief. It actually didnt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 17:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 17:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the daily conservative hit job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Jonah Goldberg. 

But it is true that when the NYPOST decides to target you there are NO holds barred.  It's unremitting, scurrilous, and defamatory (if you aren't a public figure.)  This is the Fox News machine in tabloid print.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confederate battle flag removed from site in front of S.C. Statehouse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary is still a bad liar despite decades of practice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mitch McConnells Civil Rights Record Sets Him Apart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First electric planes fly over English Channel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really happy for you.  Yeah, my home group, a large commuter AA meeting was laughing with me when I said that I too didn't want to be a member of this AA Cult.  For 22 of the last 29 years the AA sober life boat and path has  been saving my life and giving me a path to discovering my authentic self. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My psychologist called this: The Safe Harbor of Pain.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI, Cuyahoga County Prosecutor's Office ask questions about Beachwood Mayor Merle Gorden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Listen: Alan Jackson, 'Angels And Alcohol' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Turtles Aim to Halt the RIAA's $210 Million Settlement With SiriusXM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Many critics of Army cuts ignored Pentagon warnings, supported sequestration | Army announced staffing cuts Thursday |Congress complaints look ironic given voting records | Pentagon warns more cuts will come </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Many critics of Army cuts ignored Pentagon warnings, supported sequestration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The NC State Bar has filed a new complaint against the death penalty defense attorney previously charged with keeping a water bottle to test for exculpatory DNA. The attorney is now charged with giving an uncertified transcript of an innocence hearing to a reporter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-teacher sentenced after pleading guilty to sex with boys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 14:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 14:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a problem. We might disagree about what's on or offtopic but I never violate the titling rule. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 13:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was EXACTLY the title of the article at the time I posted it.  I do not alter titles.  The website title changed after I linked it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 13:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck today, /u/imaginarylindsay -- and here is my [Baby Steps post](https://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) which is what I did to stop drinking and to get sober.  In my opinion it's a pretty decent place to start stopping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 13:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet dreams, /u/chickenhips! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 13:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hilarious!  

I have a client from Cornwall, the accent!  Is that even English? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martin Sheen lends voice to Don Siegelman documentary 'Killing Atticus Finch' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 13:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clerk who refuses to issue marriage licenses led 2006 protest against gay playwright </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 13:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brownbacks office: Religious freedom order doesnt apply to local government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 13:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wichita attorney convicted of income tax evasion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 13:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Impassioned speech by lawyer opposing Confederate flag rocked South Carolina House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 13:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Columbus Mayor Coleman sent ambassadors letters to help house buyers visa bid | Buyer of HIS house </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 13:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Susan J. Demas: Conservatives mocking fast-food workers losing jobs to robots may find they're next </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 13:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did 11 Republican representatives vote against Scott Walker's budget? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 13:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perry: Let's Pull Federal Funds From "Sanctuary Cities" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 13:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 11:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not drinking TODAY no matter what happens good or bad; TGIF SD world! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Flake: Local GOP should not host Trumps Arizona event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 10:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 10:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good job /u/sarah_never! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is politics in action, in the most dramatic sense.  All politics are local. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alcoholism, or an alcohol disorder, or an alcohol addiction is more than a bad habit, or a bad choice according to medical and mental health professionals.  For many alcoholics if not most it is an intractable disease resulting in misery and premature death--so it is DAMN HARD to quit drinking or to stay stopped on will power alone.  What to do?

I did the things I describe at the [Baby Steps post.](https://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/)  It may sound like semantics, but I never "quit drinking."  Instead I make a daily decision not to drink TODAY, only--no matter what happens good or bad.  I tough out the tough hours.  I doggedly persist for one day.  One Day.  Then I do it again.  Amazingly, it get's easier--after the first tough days, and the first couple of bumpy weeks as long as I don't pick up the next drink.  Key to my success was throwing myself head first into recovery.  All-in.  A real commitment.  

That my friend is my best recommendation for trying again.  Make a decision, go all-in, doggedly persist, repeat.

Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NPR to change lineup of anchors for 'All Things Considered' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Posner admits he's 'brutal to lawyers' but defends his critique of Roberts' gay-marriage dissent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video Shows Same-Sex Ky. Couple Being Told Clerk Refuses to Issue Marriage License </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gov. Nikki Haley to sign bill today, Confederate flag to come down Friday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 21:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Governor to Casey County clerk: Issue marriage licenses or resign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 21:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel bad that you felt that way; and as a long time AA and the OP  of the [Big Book Study Group](https://www.reddit.com/r/stopdrinking/search?q=big+book+study+group restrict_sr=on sort=relevance t=all) you wandered into the reading of the most insane and sexist  chapter in the Big Book, in my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't disagree with this.  I think he's a little nuts having heard him extemporize and call a Ohio State Trooper, a jerk because the officer  pulled him over for speeding.  But he is competent and way-too-sane by GOP standards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe you are correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the famous words of George H.W., that's "the brown one."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George P. Bush calls for de-listing of endangered Texas songbird </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McCain dumps on Donald Trump over anti-immigrant rant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are talking about why the POTUS should have continuous "security" 24/7 versus the Ohio taxpayers paying for security for a governor who ran for a full term fully intending to become a part-timer on the taxpayer's dime when he ran for President.  If that's illogical to you, then you might consider a refresher course on logic, maybe somewhere other than a home school, this time.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 16:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [At this link.](https://www.animallaw.info/statute/tn-good-samaritan-dogs-cars) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 16:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you.  It may well be that AA didn't work for you, because you when you went "you had one foot out the door" so to speak.  For me, being ALL-IN made all the difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 16:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference is that the POTUS travels with redundant offices, communications, and staff to remain in continuous contact with the levers of his office: e.g. Air Force One.  

Name-calling because you disagree is childish.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 16:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kasich is hardly governor 24/7 when he is running around the country running for POTUS.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 16:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's how I would see that based on years sober:  we can not foresee the future.  In recovery, I've seen all sorts of families form, families of affiliation, new families, and recovery families.  But newly sober, and in pain and regret we can't imagine feeling OK again, free, and happy.  I've seen with my own eyes, miracles in recovery.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
