<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8652</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Age of (un)Reason: Blind rule-following too often blocking basic common sense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 01:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Selleck accused of stealing truckloads of water from drought-stricken Southern California </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 01:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why We Shut Down Reddits Ask Me Anything Forum, written by IAMA moderators. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 01:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for OLegendStudios </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 21:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for Pickleberrdpsandwich </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 20:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for Movvo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 20:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 20:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isaac Newton, who was widely regarded as the best scientist ever....  he invented calculus, came up with Newtonian gravity and optics, etc.   You know what he spent a large amount of time doing?    He continually reread the bible while, get this, mapping Hell!    In the literal sense as if was a real place like London or Disney World.  

Individual Scientist often believe some strange shit.  What matters is what the Scientific Community on the whole espouses. And in the case of Climate Change, more than 97% believe it's real.    Of the remaining 3%, what you need to ask is how many are crazy outside their field of expertise and how many are paid to believe something else?     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for BTNInfosystemkol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 12:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for motivationviper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 11:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 10:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/nallen is one of the best mods of Reddit.   He knows how to swing the ban hammer when it comes to people who deny scientific facts.    If you deny climate change, evolution or the the germ theory of disease, the mods of /r/Science will jettison you from their subreddit.   They do it because facts are facts.  If you want to make up your own bullshit, then you don't get to play in their sandbox.   It's a great policy for them to have.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China unveils new measures to halt major stock market slide: China's main market index has declined 30% since early June </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 10:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New Overtime Rules Are a Big Deal. Heres Why. -- The overworked and underpaid American workforce has something to celebrate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 10:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austerity Has Failed: An Open Letter From Thomas Piketty to Angela Merkel -- Five leading economists warn the German chancellor, History will remember you for your actions this week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 09:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for tles4356 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 04:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 00:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And again, the admins took action.   But by default you want to assume everyone, probably including yourself, is secretly involved in a conspiracy.     And if you are confessing to something, then I think you should get to your confession.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do a great job at /r/Help.  Thank you very much.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard he once killed and ate a jogger.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, I don't think they are that well spoken.   And they are covered in drool.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be helpful if the admins read and responded to things in all the various mod and help-based subreddits.  Including /r/Help, /r/Modhelp, /r/Bugs, /r/ideasfortheadmins, /r/modclub, /r/Modtalk, /r/DefaultMods, and /r/ModSupport.   Plus any I am sure I missed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the record, SolInvictus was shadow banned by the admins for breaking the rules of Reddit.  He was removed for being a spammer.   It was clearly not a secret conspiracy or anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should all just thank the Lords of Kobol that the admins used their deep fat frier on him.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oy vey.  Really, anyone who wants to talk about the greatness of  voat, should just leave for that place.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, there is a discrepancy.    Other than an abstract "what's the way it works", you aren't going to get much more. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I understand, same with vote manipulation and brigade detection as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for theherbguy1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for lisazingg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In general, based on my personal observations, down votes don't count after about -15.   And there are cases where down votes count for positive comment karma as well.  The day I got more than -3000 down votes on one comment I net earned about 250 comment karma.  There were no corresponding comments that earned +3000 either.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for CarsAccidents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for TheTitoComplex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for EvolutionScientist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 20:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for 10diggs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 20:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for nahamed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 20:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for chshteiger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 20:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for vlstr </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 06:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for MindDisciples </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 05:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 03:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes, the various witch hunt threads that never even included half the real story.   You link to a bunch of stuff that is wrong about a whole bunch of things and you don't care about basic facts either.   For example, I didn't get kicked out at /r/Technology, [I quit and told the world why I quit](https://np.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/23p696/meet_the_reddit_power_user_who_helped_bring_down/cgz8ecm?context=3)

As to /r/Europe.... [I said this](https://np.reddit.com/r/europe/comments/3c0m0a/why_reurope_went_private/csrbiaw?context=3) a few days ago.   Mod leaks showing I was doing the right thing.   The same thing the remaining mods there are continuing to do currently.  Like that guy I am sure basic facts are outside your purview and I'm not going to waste any more of my time talking to you.   

I like how you see good supporters of you as people who uses usernames with K.K.K. in them.  [Look at what he mods](https://www.reddit.com/r/CoonTown/about/moderators).   Which tells the world everything they need to know about you and your so-called friends.  You don't know anything you are taking about.  If you said the sky was blue I would 100% know it wasn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 01:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to say, I'm very disappointed you joined a gang with Qgyh2.   We might need to evict you from the /r/History gang for that.  :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 01:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on, /u/Creesch.   It's obviously that the cabal is ruining the world.   Who is in the cabal?  I'm not exactly sure.     Nobody really ever seems to know what the secret cabal is up too.  From what I can gather I think it has something to do with controlling the coffee futures market.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit CEO Says Miscommunication Led To Blackout Protest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 01:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for umairshamraiz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 17:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 06:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a very simple way to make sure you never get reddit gold, even by accident.   Don't use Reddit.  If you have an account, you can always [delete](https://www.reddit.com/prefs/delete/) it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 05:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would take credit, but I was only doing what was right.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 04:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All Hail the one true DZNeill!   He died and then was risen for all Reddit sins remembered.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for akdesigner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 04:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for Sokhal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 02:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 00:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dzneill singlehandedly ran the help-based subreddits for years.   Everything in /r/Help, /r/Modhelp, /r/ideasfortheadmins, etc. was answered by him.    He stopped doing it at one point because.... well, basically back in the day he never got attention from the admins when it was needed.      They just ignored all the good work he was doing for them.   I am still very disappointed in how they treated DZ back then.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for myfrancisco </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 20:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 19:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know and have modded with /u/solidwhetstone a bit.  And he isn't the type of person who flexes is e-peen a lot.    He may disagree with fellow mods a lot, but never in a non-productive way.   He has never appeared to be disingenuous to me.  

I would be surprised if he reverses himself on this issue.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 07:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Wehrmacht willing joined in committing war crimes and genocide though.  

See these AH threads:

* https://np.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/1bspmo/how_correct_is_the_notion_of_clean_wehrmacht/
* https://np.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/1bidsr/why_wasnt_the_wehrmacht_represented_at_the_wansee/c96yjjp

They're hands were not clean.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 07:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it's a [standard thing](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DbsMZecRgbI) I am once again forced to link too. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 05:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to suggest that Reddit hire you.   You did a lot of great work for this site back in the day.   I still think they should.   But they aren't that smart.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 05:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, but no.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 05:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the subreddits that went private are public again.  

/r/History, /r/Science, /r/IAMA, /r/AskReddit, /r/Gaming, /r/Art, etc. 

That said, you can check out the list of the subreddits you are subscribed to here:

* https://www.reddit.com/subreddits/mine/

You can remove subreddits that may be private from the list on that page.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for AveForty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 23:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for Jakemorgan34 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 23:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for Titorelliable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 22:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 22:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I removed a shit load of spam.   Things that still need to be removed for being spam.  I do that same thing now at /r/GetMotivated, /r/History, /r/Bestof, /r/Food, etc.   Spam is not a small problem and spam is still spam.    I had done more than 120K spam reports in my time on Reddit.   That's the second most of any mod ever on Reddit.   Only /u/Kylde has done more spam reports.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for technologycasts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 22:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 22:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering I didn't remove the threads in question that you complained about before, that should tell you something right now.  But then, as I already pointed out.... you like to ignore actual facts.   In short, they are still being removed; you just choose to ignore it.  

Good day to you.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 22:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're still cooler than she is.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 22:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not true.   I was the mod who took /r/History private.   /u/Creesch later put it back online a few hours after /u/Nallen made /r/Science public again.   They were made public again because /u/kn0thing made threads in /r/Modtalk and /r/Defaultmods and seems to be addressing the issues.   Getting his direct attention was the goal.    

OF course, the fact that it took several hours to get the attention is still a bit whacked.  

People want to make crap up.   But then, they often like to do that because some people are just crazy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 22:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was removing racist bullshit from here.   Things I continue to remove from other subreddits I mod to this day.   Heck, the thread you guys complained because you thought I remove was **NOT even removed by me**.   It was removed by another mod of /r/Europe who is **still** a mod here.    But I stood by his removal and continue to stand by it.    Removal of that thread was the correct action.  It's still removed at this time.  The current mod team here continues to remove similar threads every day.   Not that you care really, because facts are actually unimportant to you.  

Racism and hate are a major problem on Reddit.  We know this because the Users of /r/Europe have said it was a problem. See these threads from /r/Europe on the storm front problem:

* https://www.reddit.com/r/europe/comments/1w3fnr/seems_we_are_important_enough_for_stormfront_to/
* https://www.reddit.com/r/europe/comments/2y0tbb/headsup_popular_neonazi_site_daily_stormer_is/

And it's a problem faced by all of Reddit.   For example, the definitive /r/History comment statement on the problem.  

* https://www.reddit.com/r/history/comments/2puapu/alfred_hitchcocks_memory_of_the_camps_very_nsfw/cn0a25e?context=3

The history-based subreddits of /r/History, /r/HistoryPorn, /r/AskHistorians, /r/BadHistory, etc. all ban users for racist and hate-filled opinions every day.  Be they racism, holocaust denial, NeoNazis, NeoConfederates, Pro-Slavery or simple history-fact denial.    World War Two happened, denying it will get you banned for that alone.   And no, the mod teams don't care if you agree with how we mod the subreddits.   If you don't like it, then you are free to unsubscribe at your earliest opportunity.  

Back to the issue of subreddits going private, /r/History was taken private after a long discussion among the mod team.  We were the fourth default subreddit to go private.  Only a few minutes after /r/Movies did so.   I was the one who made the setting change to take it private.   

We then made it available again after the Admins had made statements in various backroom mod-only subreddits.   /r/Science had already decided that it was time to come back, and we followed suit because the admins will giving the stated mod-issues the required attention.   

Others links that explain what was happening follow:

* [OutoftheLoop thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/OutOfTheLoop/comments/3bxduw/why_was_riama_along_with_a_number_of_other_large/)
* [Subreddit Drama thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/SubredditDrama/comments/3bwgjf/riama_set_to_private_over_mod_firing/)
* [Bestof Thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/bestof/comments/3bw7ms/top_mod_of_riama_explains_why_its_been_set_to/)

In short, mods doing their jobs are important for Reddit.   Mod tools have not been updated in several years.   Tools like /r/Toolbox which were created by people like /u/Creesch and /u/Agentlame are stop gap measures that they themselves have asked for the admins to copy their work for the benefit of all communities on Reddit.    

I could continue to go on here, but you won't read it and aren't really interested in what I am saying.  But somebody else might be interested in the actual facts, and so I post this answer for them.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brzezinski on Russia: 'We Are Already In a Cold War' -- Former US National Security Advisor Zbigniew Brzezinski believes the West should stand up to Russian President Vladimir Putin in Ukraine. "We should make it more costly for the Russians to use force" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 17:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muzzling the Media: Defying the Kremlin Crackdown on Press Freedom -- Against the backdrop of the bloody conflict in Ukraine, the Kremlin is seeking to harness the Russian media and increasingly clamping down on critical voices. But some journalists are refusing to deliver pro-Putin propaganda. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 17:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Grassroots movement working': Bernie Sanders gains on the Clinton machine -- The Vermont senator is winning over progressive voters and has raised millions in small donations. Could this underdog campaign have a fighting chance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 17:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Grassroots movement working': Bernie Sanders gains on the Clinton machine -- The Vermont senator is winning over progressive voters and has raised millions in small donations. Could this underdog campaign have a fighting chance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 17:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 02:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Several default subreddits have gone private at this time.   [This list](https://www.reddit.com/r/SubredditDrama/comments/3bxjyu/list_of_subreddits_suddenly_going_private/) is being maintained by some people.  

So far /r/AskReddit, /r/IAMA, /r/science, /r/History, /r/Movies, /r/videos, /r/Art, /r/listentothis, and a few others have gone private.   Others links that explain what is happening are here:

* [OutoftheLoop thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/OutOfTheLoop/comments/3bxduw/why_was_riama_along_with_a_number_of_other_large/)
* [Subreddit Drama thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/SubredditDrama/comments/3bwgjf/riama_set_to_private_over_mod_firing/)
* [Bestof Thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/bestof/comments/3bw7ms/top_mod_of_riama_explains_why_its_been_set_to/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 02:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to make a bit of a public statement about /r/History.   

The mod team held a discussion and a super majority of the mod-team was in favor of going private in solidarity with /r/IAMA, /r/Science and the other subreddits.    We are hoping the admins get the message and that this is resolved in a way that we can all live with going forward.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 01:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was madness in any direction, at any hour. If not across the Bay, then up the Golden Gate or down 101 to Los Altos or La Honda. . . . You could strike sparks anywhere. There was a fantastic universal sense that whatever we were doing was right, that we were winning. . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 01:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been around for a long time.   But there is the [Team Page](https://np.reddit.com/about/team/) that lists them all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 23:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True dat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 23:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/IAMA and /r/Science have both gone dark so far.   Both taken there by their mod-teams.  I am not sure what to do myself, but there isn't much else mods can do other than post a "were really upset by this decision" sticky that would get ignored.     Ignored so well that you wouldn't even know if the admins were aware of it or just not reading their PMs.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you going to write your "When I was a Reddit admin" book?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/karmanaut knows that it's been set to private.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/ocrasorm is cool too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just tune those people out.   But yeah, that can be stupid.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 21:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reason I have difficulty believing you here is that you have always had a problem in responding to people.  Mods often ask for input from Reddit, and rarely get it.   And this one is a problem that is going to be spread out across dozens of subreddits.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 21:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know he left /r/games or /r/gaming.    I"m sure it was because he thought he didn't have the time to mod them and wanted to let others have the sidebar display space.   Cause he's an upstanding person.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 21:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please, let's not actually go crazy.   Bad decision is just a bad decision.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 21:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, there are a few others we like.   /u/deimorz and /u/krispykrackers are well liked.    But there are not a lot of admins that regularly talk to users.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 21:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firing may be the wrong word here.   Laid off or let go may be a nicer way to describe it.   I wouldn't want to say she was fired, as that often carries the implication that the person deserved it.   And /u/chooter didn't deserve to be let go.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 20:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't a mod that was fired.  Reddit as a company let an admin  go:  /u/chooter  / Victoria.   She helped set up most of the highly visible AMA threads.   Not just at /r/IAMA but also at /r/Books, /r/Science, /r/Food, etc.   

She was a great admin.   

Edit:  /r/History has gone private in solidarity with /r/IAMA, /r/Science, /r/Movies and other subreddits now.  

Edit2:  /r/AskReddit, /r/Art, /r/Videos, /r/listentothis, and others as well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 20:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Victoria setup several AMA's at /r/Food several times as well.  She was doing a lot of good work for Reddit.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for JustBananasIceCream </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 20:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for allis1898 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 19:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for SociallyUnited </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 19:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for ElephantHuntMassacre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 19:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 19:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vH3-Gt7mgyM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 19:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Invited.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 19:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if anyone wants to volunteer, they should let me know.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Infrared lifts the veil on a golden city: Powerful technology has enabled astronomers to penetrate the dense fog surrounding Liller 1 to reveal an unprecedented ultra-sharp view of this vast stellar city. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 18:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neurones involved in everyday memories identified </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 18:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really, the place could use some moderators.   I would be willing to add some people to keep an eye on it and try and do something with it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was invited there at one point.   I just do mod mail there.   That said, the top-mod there doesn't do much.  I could add some mods there to keep an eye on things.   I could draft you and /u/Quouar if you wish.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for djmoonbooties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 06:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As Donald Trump surges in polls, Democrats cheer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 05:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP presidential candidates are lying about climate change  And this is how theyre getting away with it: Print and broadcast outlets aren't doing enough to counteract Republicans' anti-science claims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 05:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 1 percents most useful idiot: New York Times columnist Frank Bruni says corporations need more power -- The absurdly inept Times columnist proves once and for all that he's a caricature of plutocratic neoliberalism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 05:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Egypt's president vows speedier death penalties after a spike of violence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 05:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peru's big corporations come out in support of gay marriage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 05:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Latest blow to black AME churches in SC: Letters threaten to kill women pastors and their children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 05:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox analyst: Anti-racism activists are cultural brothers and sisters of Charleston shooter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 05:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Allegations of abuse in Indian-administered Kashmir: An Amnesty International report accuses India of "facilitating impunity" in disputed region </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 03:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yemen's children suffer collective trauma: Medics in Yemen barely have tools to tend to physical wounds of Yemeni children, let alone psychological ones. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 03:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for BigRyry00 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 03:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for LuckOnMars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for gregpokriki </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for garygpelow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for Faithvirally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for QuotesforHustlers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for zohaibakhlaq </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for lmclarty31 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for dionflex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for xfriz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for JewelMORE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for StellabelleYT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for ItsJozeyGirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for TheAmazing97 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for KittenOfMine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for ssimdwarka1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for mistysunrise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for davene13 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for sloth2002 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for prity1452 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for Radique72 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for tremdon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 01:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, this is new the definitive reddit-link/work on the subject.   

The only thing I would add is a quote from former Confederate General James Longstreet, responding to a question asking him what he thought the cause of the Civil War was: "If it wasn't about slavery, then I don't know what else it was about".  

But then, Neoconfederate apologists don't care about actual facts.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US, Cuba announce embassy re-openings: The US and Cuba have laid the Cold War to rest. While some see dialogue as a path to reform, Cuban exiles believe the White House has strengthened the Castro regime. Spencer Kimball reports. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 00:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Massive' NSA espionage of top German officials: Wikileaks says its latest release of documents shows the wide reach of economic espionage conducted by the NSA in Germany. Documents released by the whistleblowers suggest an intense interest in the Greek debt crisis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 00:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was indoctrinated to obey the Nazis and did not register daily atrocities, Accountant of Auschwitz testifies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 00:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Burmese fishing slave makes long journey home after 22-year odyssey aboard Thai fishing vessels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 00:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for nohabadr </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 22:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> London gets all-electric double-decker buses: Will the US follow suit? - The environmentally friendly buses will have no emissions, benefiting London air quality and raising the bar for public transit around the world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 21:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Supreme Court win, LGBT activists look beyond same-sex marriage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 20:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greece makes concession but no deal seen before Sunday vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 20:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 20:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wish the mods of /r/IAMA would shut crap like that down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 20:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct.   Some images of Jesse Jackson with Dr. King [here](http://ww3.hdnux.com/photos/01/76/11/516702/5/628x471.jpg) and [here](https://davidmandre.files.wordpress.com/2010/09/martin-luther-king_t3002.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 20:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be great.    I would love to see that happen.   Get rid of /r/Coontown, /r/GreatApes, /r/Holocaust, and other racist-hate filled scumreddits.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 20:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister, who is big into Facebook has never heard of Reddit.   Well, except from when I occasionally mention it while she is going on about how great Facebook is.  The vast majority of Americans just don't care.   That said, there is a semi-important marketing demographic some advertisers like.   Too many Redditors think that makes them important, when in reality it just makes them a target demographic to mine for money.   People still don't really care about them at all.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for yoloswegz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 19:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for thehungryhutch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for madaughe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for Totolingo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for smithsonian9909 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for tablethub2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wouldn't have contradicted me if I had worked in a Battlestar Galactica reference.  :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 06:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genocide Olympics:  The only winning move is not to play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for Forevercaff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 05:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for mwydyn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 05:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. and Cuba to announce agreement to open embassies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 04:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
