<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5008</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 00:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cause I posted this video in the other merc thread yesterday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 00:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's an old thread from ar15.com in which Haley gives the specs of his rifle if you want to build a clone. http://www.ar15.com/forums/t_3_118/408500_.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 20:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [there's a thing for that](https://youtu.be/jlpx4DMGzYI)

expensive though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 18:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is probably the most historically inaccurate thing I've ever read on reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 18:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His importance extends far beyond the midnight ride. He rode from Boston to Philadelphia 18 times as a messenger for pre-revolutionary independence movement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 18:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and then was captured by a british patrol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 15:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, when my son brought my glock to school I NEVER got it back. Fucking straight up theft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 00:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vaJYlk4z5RQ

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P1g-x9ncP8I

Some more videos of the same incident </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 00:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's a SMAW-D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 23:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I certainly hope you can be sterilized as soon as possible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 23:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> giving you an elective procedure whenever you demand isn't their job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 22:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is africa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 21:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mob violence in SA, there are differing accounts of where/why it happened </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 20:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that hard, but getting hits on the first shots is difficult unless you have a very precise range estimate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 20:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T.I.A. NSFW http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=4d1_1428675879 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 06:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hep C </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 04:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I'm curious. I wonder if they are ex Syrian Army. We were always told that the Iraqis were better with mortars than the afghans because they were from Saddam's army. I'm also curious why they are trigger firing...concerns about ammo/tube quality? I dunno, maybe that model doesn't have a drop fire option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 02:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not bad, I wonder how many shots they took to make those hits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 01:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuck, you can still smoke at a certain bar in cambridge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 20:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should sell it at CVS with uniform dosages. No amount of law enforcement, or for that matter, treatment and and counseling is going to keep some people from wanting to get high. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 06:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what about foreigners and students? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 05:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Lots of tech" It seems like it would be a big hassle. Like, are they going to want property records, capital gains, assets held in trust? Can they even compel someone to hand over that kind info over a parking ticket? What about foreign assets?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 05:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this really so much of a problem? This sounds a lot like the liberal version of drug-testing people on welfare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 04:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for real though: Summer, Marissa, or Ms. Cooper? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 21:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks grammerbot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 17:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 89% of the politburo were engineers.....worked out GREAT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 06:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the guy has made millions selling other people what they want to hear "all your failures are on someone else." The guy is actually a great capitalist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 04:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saying "such and such strong" has been around for a while ie the Army since the mid 2000's and Vermont since Irene. Boston doesn't get a monopoly on stupid catchphrases. Sorry, no fucks given. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 22:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 20:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like it's preparing them for the real world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 17:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This video is such a classic, it never really went viral for some reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 15:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's racist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 14:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there has been a TON of this going on over the last few days, i dunno if it's bots or a new upvote whoring thing or what </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 06:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why we need an independent federal agency tasked solely with investigating and prosecuting law enforcement officials for misconduct. They could be recruited from the law schools, accounting programs, and military counter-intelligence. No one who had ever worked as a law enforcement officer would be eligible, and no former agents would ever be allowed to work in law enforcement. They would have jurisdiction over ALL law enforcement agencies and would themselves only be subject to investigation by the FBI. All lethal use of force by law enforcement would be automatically be investigated by this agency. Most agents would be located in regional offices and no agent would be allowed to remain in any office for more than four years. All of their cases would be tried in federal court and a new crime of "lying in the course of law enforcement activities" would carry a mandatory minimum ten year sentence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 04:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP Spc. Dawson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 03:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty confident that that Tsarnaev kid was a bomber </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 03:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do rehabilitate someone that rapes and murders kids?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worcester police officer arrested, accused of assaulting prisoner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 01:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 00:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only there was a government program that paid you to go to school </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 22:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of course, the terrorists truly "won" that day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 22:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Less time, because the dude would have found the kid in his back yard instead of being stuck inside all day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 16:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, they face consequences for their actions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 16:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything's relative </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 15:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 07:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought everyone cowering in their homes because of one kid on the loose was pretty pathetic. It was nice getting the day off work. I went out to brunch and spent the day jogging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 06:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what percentage of american charity is "save johnny from leukemia?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What stereotypes do Europeans have about each other? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 05:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dirty 'murican here. A Swedish friend of mine once said to me, "The Norwegians are a bunch of stuck-up jerks and the Finns are just stupid rednecks." I've heard plenty of American stereotypes about Europeans and plenty of European stereotypes about Americans. What do you guys say about each other? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 05:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is firearms per capita (ie. total firearms divided by number of people) I was reporting over 40% ownership rate (ie people actually own a firearm) The per capita rate in Iowa is likely significantly higher than 1.0. The homicide rate in Iowa was 1.4 in 2013. My point is that it is perfectly possible to live in a largely peaceful society with tons of guns. If you have a large number of assholes it doesn't matter what the rules are. For instance, Lithuania has a very low rate of gun ownership and a higher homicide rate than the US. I prefer to live in a society where my rights are not dictated by the lowest common denominator. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 03:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It also has a lower rate than Belgium and Finland for example. I don't know what rape has to do with this conversion, but Sweden has twice the rape-rate of the US and far more restricted firearms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 02:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hell if you discount black people the US homicide rate comes down to near European levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 02:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meanwhile, Iowa has a lower homicide rate than many European countries, almost no gun laws, and a firearm ownership rate over 40%. Hint...the problem isn't the guns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 00:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bloomberg is a dick for many reasons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 00:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why wasn't he expelled? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 00:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> inferiority complex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 22:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oUltheRpJNw

This is like five years old, but if you haven't seen it, it really is the best of Cage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 19:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'NGLEND! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 06:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, thanks. I wasn't in the truck, I was sleeping a few hundred yards away. Talk about a rude awakening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 05:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Pashto have been like that for a long time, way before the Russians. That said, having spent considerable time in Helmand Province, it is a beautiful place. I always thought we should forget about trying to install a government and just colonize the place. Give soldiers who stay there 1000 acres each and a few wives. It would be Texas in 50 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 05:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of course you would, easy peasy, for example see north america </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 02:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one person I know who went there was also a nutty girl that dropped out after losing her shit. Must be something in the water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 02:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/cxwwQ7c.jpg

That's my buddy sitting in the turret. No one in that truck had a scratch on them.

happened here: https://goo.gl/maps/dq5fX </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 01:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they should pay teens 100 bucks a year to get a implanon, 10K to get a tubal ligation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 01:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's what happens when you don't have a strong NCO corps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 01:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found that guy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 23:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first couple looked pretty bad but I wouldn't assume everyone was killed. MRAPs/MATVs are fucking tough, during my deployment we had something like 100 vehicles hit by IEDs. Not a single death or amputation. Probably some TBIs but nothing that left anyone unable to function. All of our fatalities/amputations were guys on foot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 14:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if they want people to continue lending them money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 02:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cars make suburban cities perfectly viable, it's almost as if certain modes of transportation are suited to certain lifestyles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 02:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe sometimes, I have extremely close access to public transportation and I still drive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 22:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I were you I would live in Worcester. Much cheaper and the commute would be way less horrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 05:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just think, they probably fucked your grandma! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 22:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually a very legitimate tactic. The cop in question was the guy that likely actually made hits on Tamerlin and the department firearms instructor. Probably the most competent guy there. https://youtu.be/x28X4FK8Hkk?t=253 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 22:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "highly trained"

lots of law enforcement firearms training consists of shooting at static targets - good for developing basic marksmanship but not much else, and simunition training. Simunition training is basically paintballs fired by gunpowder. Unfortunately this type of very valuable training often becomes more of a game than anything else. Training with sims  shouldn't be fun. We did a bunch in the Marines and it always sucked. Getting shot wasn't "awe darn you got me," it meant lying facedown in the road for a few yours or your fire-team dragging/carrying your ass a mile or two the the LZ for the medevac. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 03:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you really told 'em! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 21:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's one way to bust the glass ceiling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 20:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *vomits furiously </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 16:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right next to old fezzipoop ale </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 03:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm triggered by your ableist slur, guess they didn't have a debate team in the dumpster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 01:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good thing your opinion doesn't matter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 23:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nope, but if you try to take the trash and put it in a nice recycling facility the dumpster will flip a shit. Wouldn't it be nice if there was a way to keep dumpsters from filling up with garbage? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 23:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Good" -Eugene Sledge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 22:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> idiotic

-typical

except she's already elected, she didn't need to help marry anyone
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 21:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You said convenient and necessary, which clearly it was to get him elected. He lied about his opinion to help him politically, just like Polito. Don't change the subject, besides those efforts you cite happened AFTER he was elected. Im sorry your partisan blinders are so tight that you're upset that a Republican is supporting same sex marriage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 20:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama was against it when he was running for president in 2008 and only 40% of Americans supported it. Be became for it in 2012 when he was running for election and 51% of Americans supported it. Same shit, different party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 17:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is part of the reason stitches cost so much. It's called stealing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 14:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.goarmy.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 23:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow, you're really helping your argument! Maybe I've been wrong all along!! Don't worry, I don't think you should be allowed to own guns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 23:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did a gun touch your pee-pee? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 19:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> depends on who the patient is, the majority of people I see in the ER are being paid for by tax dollars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 15:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like Saddam, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 14:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Five years after the Arab Spring: Middle East engulfed by war" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 14:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So when are they gonna build a homeland for christians in the middle east? Anyone got ideas for locations? Maybe the Syrian coast?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 02:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yea, sure worked out well for Haiti </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 22:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "jamming problem" I'm gonna guess you've never carried an M4 professionally  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 22:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> man, butthurt germans can't admit their gun sucks. Go with the 416 like your SF if you want to buy domestic, it even uses the same gas system. Or could've stuck with the g3, THAT was a nice german piece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 17:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just buy m4's and be done with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 16:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and that's why their great-great-grandchildren will also be living in poverty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 21:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should be a death penalty offense for a police officer to lie on duty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 20:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno, the one liver doner I know said it was much, much more painful than childbirth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 16:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> then get licking, I just trimmed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 15:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well gosh, if justice needs to be done anyone who has lived in the US for decades after coming from a war-torn third world shit-hole really should be investigated. Who cares about the cost. Really any immigrants from Africa, Korea, Vietnam, Eastern Europe, the Caribbean, the Middle East, and South America should be investigated. Or we could pay for things that actually matter in America. No one gave enough of shit to do anything in Rwanda 20 years ago, why should we care now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 05:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it would be pretty funny to watch epic asskicking that would commence if they ever came to blows </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 05:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only 6 or 7 blocks from where those hippies blew themselves up in the 70's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 03:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like justification to cut the DHS budget right there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rocket attack in Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 02:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
