<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8395</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 12:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom Cruise in Collateral (2004) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 19:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Last Of US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game Of Thrones Season 5 Trailer- Cam Footage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 18:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 02:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cafe Kino on Gloucester Road. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 13:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus the companies who they attacked will probably sue them for causing their servers to go offline.....or hire them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 14:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank god someone mentioned this, such a terrific film with a really interesting script and intriguing characters despite most of them not being visible. 
We had the producer come and introduce it to us at uni and told us some fun facts about the film. Apparently the script was wrote between Boxing Day and New Years and was pretty much the final draft. It was also a 5 day shoot that entailed Tom driving around the same intersection with a camera strapped to the bonnet of the car. The other actors spoke to him whilst sat in a hotel reading through their lines.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 15:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope David Batista only speaks literally throughout his challenge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 12:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are great....however I do not want to see his interpretation of The Lion, The Witch and the Wardrobe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 22:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see the Kill Bill saga Tarantino's homage to Asian films. The first one features about 50 direct references to other films that inspired him across his career while Volume 2 is the western influence of these films. It is all shown in this video that shows these references.
https://vimeo.com/19469447
Tarantino has always said he is more of a film lover then a film maker which I respect from him and adds more context to this film as it is often seen as one of his most misunderstood films.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 19:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *"This is a stick-up"* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
