<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7036</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 19:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l7VuGknEfQY) is her full vision from the House of the Undying. 

Edit: That second paragraph might be one of my favorite new theories. Thanks for that! I couldn't think of the parallel's - with her family being up there I mean - and now it makes so much more sense. They did say some heavy clues were laden throughout season 2 for future episodes. Would be huge to see some of this come to fruition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 18:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great point. Last night's really put that into perspective. 

TV spoilers below. 

So many things seem so trivial now but conversely, a lot of the feuds between houses could impact so much in the grand scheme of things. Bolton v Baratheon will determine if we see an entire army aid in the fight against the wights. Dany will most likely learn of what is really going on beyond the wall and focus her attention there. Tyrion will have to be our champion here. Her dragons now hold a huge key to forging weapons to fight the most dangerous threat known to their world. So she better learn to tame those things. And Bran is acting as Frodo did in LOTR. A huge burden to bear, essentially alone. We all probably suspect he and his contingent will be a huge asset to the fight against the Night King and his army. Not to mention so many others. My brain hurts. So many possibilities and all we can do is sit at the mercy of D D/GRRM. 

Edit: grammar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [All TV Spoilers] These visions are looking like realistic possibilities after last night's episode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 16:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 19:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold on guys I gotta charge my pants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 05:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Link is diggin this J, right Link?](http://40.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_l7qutxYUts1qc0m6fo1_500.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cory Henry -- The Revival Project [Jazz/Organ/Gospel] (2015) another level of musicianship and passion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 05:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 01:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy is correct.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 03:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fresh mint 100% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 02:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Update: we dubbed this brew the Chocolate Chip Girl Stout.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 01:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have fun! Definitely intimidating at first but instantly more rewarding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 23:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was at around 63 degrees during primary fermentation. Recipe below. 

http://www.brewersfriend.com/homebrew/recipe/view/13843/chocolate-mint-stout </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 23:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Link below. We turned this into a 5g batch.

http://www.brewersfriend.com/homebrew/recipe/view/13843/chocolate-mint-stout

EDIT: we added an extra 1lb of caramel to this recipe. Was around 18 pounds of grain for a 5g batch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was pumped at the clarity and color of our mint chocolate stout! We hit our numbers and at 9% abv I can hardly wait to pour this brew in a glass. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 17:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 21:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get the kid and they don't come with a manual. No YouTube unboxing for children either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neil's custom drum kit for this R40 tour is reportedly crafted from the wood of a 1,500-year-old Romanian oak tree. That shit is cool. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 20:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 03:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its like having a kid. Not everyone plans on it but if it does happen, its pretty nice - until they shit on you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 03:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "where have you been all of this time?!?!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 22:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice shots! How far back were you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 22:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was 15 at my first Rush show. It was a good year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 14:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We watched Dany go through something similar. We were not as attached to her as a character yet. Watching last nights post Wedding scene for me was almost as shocking as the Red Wedding. I'm rooting for Theon to make moves. Although chances are slim.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 23:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just think so much of Power Windows and Caress of Steel are underrated. I love 'The Necromancer' and 'Fountain of Lamneth' so much not to mention those tracks helped birth '2112'. Geddy's bass parts on Power Windows are amazing. Namely 'The Big Money', 'Grand Designs' and 'Marathon'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 00:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy birthday! What kind of kettle is that? Looks sweet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 23:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jury Duty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 18:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just so everyone knows, these are not actual McDonalds sandwiches.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
