<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9584</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Terra Mystica: Fire   Ice Expansion on sale at CSI - $24.99 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 14:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 06:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Heroes of Normandie** is a phenomenal 2P war game. Tons of replayability, really neat mechanics. And even though it's a serious topic (WWII), it's really really *fun*; has a great epic, cinematic feel to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 22:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you meant...

"I'll take 'Things People Eat' for $500" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 22:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only played Suburbia Inc. It's fantastic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 22:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you really love Suburbia, CoMKL might fall a little flat for you. CoMKL is more of a streamlined, less complicated Suburbia. The master builder mechanic is neat, but works best with 4. CoMKL is definitely not as heavy as Suburbia, so if you're looking for a lighter version of Suburbia, then it's perfect. If you're looking to up your Suburbia action, then go with the expansion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lance McCullers makes his MLB debut in Batman cleats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 18:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 17:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want my $2.99 back, CSI! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 17:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sarah Palin and a microphone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 22:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shipping from Buffalo, NY

**[H]** **Fortune   Glory: The Cliffhanger Game**. The game is in perfect condition. I played it once, just not for me. 

**[W]** Cash/PayPal/Amazon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 22:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the vast majority of boards wouldn't in a shoebox, so you can pretty much throw whatever deck builders   card games you own in there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 18:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have Terra Mystica, you need to get the Fire   Ice expansion. TM is my favorite game of all time and the expansion makes it even better. It's just incredible. 

Also, I'd go KoNY over KoT. It adds a little more depth and strategy. 

From the rest of your games you want, it seems like you're looking at lighter, more social games. I'd check out **Sheriff of Nottingham**, **Small World**, **Forbidden Desert**, **Flash Point: Fire Rescuet**, **Bohnanza**.

/u/r2d8 getinfo


edit: trying to format game names for bot. wrong flashpoint and smallworld typo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 18:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have game nights with 20-30 people?? Where are you??? 

Also, if you have that many people, I wouldn't worry. There's going to be so many games going around, people can do what they want. If you want to bust out a 2P game...go for it. I'd say 2P games would be less played if you have 4-6 people because it's more intimate, it feels slightly weirder to split into 2 groups.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Evolution Game System Kickstarter campaign is lowering stretch goal requirements since they're not allowed to do raffles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 17:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 16:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not local, but you want to check out [Chessex](http://www.chessex.com/index.html). All kinds of custom dice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 21:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dominion: Adventures and Medina </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 17:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even like Settlers but I want this. That is awesome! Love the covers for the different colors. 

Question about the printing...how long does it take to print all that? Are the materials for the printer expensive? Can I have your 3D printer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 17:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn you damn you damn you. $33 is not a sale when you just made me buy $100 of games for free shipping! 


But totally worth it :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 16:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take a gander at the right hand column </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 14:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I'm talking about just rolling with cruise control on for awhile, then a guy passes, merges into my lane and just slows the hell down for no reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 21:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Checks out](http://www.reddit.com/r/casualiama/comments/35vny7/36_year_old_high_school_drop_out_father_of_two/cr89e14) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 20:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't understand why they have then slow down so much once they merge back into my lane. You just passed me. If I was driving too slow, why did you go in front of me to then just drop your speed below mine??  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 19:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Robinson Crusoe**](https://boardgamegeek.com/boardgame/121921/robinson-crusoe-adventure-cursed-island). Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate these drivers. Don't make me brake and change lanes right after you were doing 85 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 19:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 18:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, yep. It's all about playing your opponent. That's what makes it so fun. When you flip the play cards and you have those "HOW DID YOU KNOW I WAS GOING TO RUN THAT PLAY?!" moments. Hilarious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 17:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm...maybe all my nieces and nephews are just dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 16:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**1st   Goal**](https://boardgamegeek.com/boardgame/95105/1st-goal) is a very fun 2P game. Not super strategic, has a good amount of luck, but it's a blast if you want to goof around with your buddy for an hour, not take it too seriously! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. It's pretty much LA or that little Fitness 19 next to Tops.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't imagine an 8 year old having a world of fun with Agricola. Agricola is a heavy, heavy game. There are so many other games that would provide a better experience for a young kid.


edit: saw a comment below and definitely forgot about the easier family variant.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 23:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for him. They have lots of good food in SF.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 23:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Mom, you must've downloaded another virus. I have no idea how all that porn got on there." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 23:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I joined when they first opened and it was incredible. I went after work and there was like 15 people in the entire place. Place is bananas now. Had to quit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 22:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DJ Scratches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 22:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a spider in the car </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 21:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *They're uh...they're flocking this way* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 16:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of me wishes he was so I could see him more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe all the Bruges poo-pooing I'm seeing here. I love this game. Lots of different paths to victories. Good interaction. I love the artwork and components. The amount and variety of cards always offer a unique experience. And I always appreciate a game where you just can't do everything. It really forces you to pick a strategy to focus on, while balancing the other paths to victory a bit as well. Love me some Bruges.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea. I bought this game when it came out. I like the master builder mechanic, but it really falls flat after that. My biggest peeve is that once the game is over, I don't feel like I did a lot. I want my castle to be bigger!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. I own and love this game and I have had a few plays that were just awful because of the group. People would stare at their phones, or just leave the table when it wasn't their turn and just do whatever on their turn. Brutal. You need a group that will get into the theme, the story of the crossroads, etc. And always try to vote someone out. It's hilarious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 14:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is the goal for this set at only $100? That seems fishy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 22:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's just not true. Look through this thread alone for evidence of that. And as a few people have pointed out, Roethlisberger was never even charged with anything. Just accused by a woman he had sex with in a bathroom. Sleevey? Definitely. Rape...maybe? no one will know at all for sure. And Lewis was charged with accessory, meaning he was there, but charges were dropped. Again, obviously not saying deflating footballs is remotely close to anything in the realm of rape/murder/DV. Which is the point. Pictures like these are trying to make the NFL look like they value both the same. And that's just stupid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 22:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not saying he's actually guilty or innocent, but they also happen to be the most falsely reported crime. Especially against famous people. Two sides to that coin for sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 22:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He keeps using that word. I don't think it means what he thinks it means.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 22:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit   horseshoes: where close enough is good enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 22:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't win a suspension appeal unless you're suspended... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 21:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In fact, of the balls that they measured from the Colts, 3/4 were also under-inflated, but for some reason they stopped measuring there.

*Today in, 'Made Up Facts That Sound Real Because They Were Said As Fact.'* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 21:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get your point for sure. I think it was the absolute perfect storm for him. There was a definite quiet boiling of public ire at the NFL for their treatment (or lack thereof) of players with records of domestic violence. Then Ray Rice in the elevator happened, with the added bonus of the smoking gun in the form of a video. That visceral evidence blows it out of the water. Can you imagine if tape surfaced of Mike Vick killing dogs? Or of Greg Hardy beating the hell out of a series of women? They'd have never set foot within a country mile of an NFL city. Ever. They'd have been burned at the stake. People don't forget when they see the evidence. 

The NFL completely underestimated this growing resentment and media interest in the Ray Rice case. They tried to cover up and give a weak pass to protect their brand and keep pretending they're a nice company with nice people. Then the public flipped out and the NFL had to conjure up "new evidence" that led them to suspend Rice indefinitely to appear tough on DV.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 21:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [ya sure?](http://www.nfl.com/news/story/0ap3000000430302/article/adrian-peterson-suspended-without-pay-for-rest-of-14) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 20:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, you're right, thanks for clarifying!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 19:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I guess that's just not as catchy as "murderer" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 19:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is about the 100th time I've seen this. This photo is a disgrace. Lewis: acquitted (make your jokes). Mayweather convicted and served jail time and absolutely everyone agrees he's a piece of shit. Roethlisberger: acquitted (make your jokes). Ray Rice: suspended from NFL indefinitely and still remains out of league. AP suspended last year for remainder of season. 

They all were either acquitted in trial or depositions, or served far worse punishments than anything Brady will get. And no one thinks these are comparable moral actions. Just stop with this crap. 


edit: thank you /u/Ravenman2423 and anonymous gilder for the gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 19:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Cool" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 18:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Who are you quoting?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 23:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if it's because you don't like euro games or heavier games based on your collection, but if you're looking to fill that void, I'd go with a euro. Keyflower and Caverna are fantastic. Terra Mystica is my all time favorite game, especially if you're looking for heavier. For worker placement, I'd look at Manhattan Project, Stone Age, Lords of Waterdeep or Spyrium. The game of the week right now is Bruges and that is immensely fun. Pretty easy to get into and a ton of depth/replayability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 23:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah ok, so would 1 person load the app up and it gives you a code for that specific game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alchemists Question about using the app </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 23:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can each person use their own phone/tablet for the app or do you need to use one to keep track of what it's spitting out for the potions? Not sure how this works, we're planning on playing for the first time tonight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 14:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then he's an asshole. I'm a 3 handicap golfer. My best friend has a handicap somewhere in the high 20's. We play together all the time, often with people on par with him. Good golfers, myself included, generally don't care if you suck as long as you play quick. If you suck and take a ton of practice swings, walk slow, switch clubs, and drag the round down, then we don't want to play with you...same as if you were a good golfer (it just gets exaggerated when you're bad). Keep up the pace, and no one (besides assholes) will mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 23:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You literally just copied a comment from a recent LPT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 23:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not very familiar with Chicago...what is the island in the front right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 23:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #JocWatch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 19:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thanks for that link, I haven't seen that before. Really helpful. And I checked and it looks like we'll be row 1 in 212 or Row 10 in 113. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attending first Nationals game next week, questions about seating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 19:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was offered tickets in either section 212 or 113 (my choice) from a coworker. Any opinions on preferences of sight-lines and viewing from either section? I'd be sitting in the front few rows of either section </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 17:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have a problem taking sound advice from someone that either 1. ignores it themselves or 2. learned from their past mistakes, you're going to have a real hard time in life because you will run into a lot of those people. 


You want to make fun of your mom for not working hard and use that as a reason to not work hard yourself? And you think that's not idiotic? Fast forward twenty years and your kid will be thinking the same exact thing as you are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 21:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Neighbor is gonna be all like](http://wildcraftvita.blogspot.it/2013/01/things-to-do-with-dandelions.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 21:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Fuckin'- What the fuckin'. Fuck. Who the fuck fucked this fucking... How did you two fucking fucks...Fuck!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 18:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "why the hell did you throw this thing on me?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 15:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Craigslist and Artvoice classifieds are probably your best bet for apartments, especially in Elmwood/Allentown area. If you like the downtown loft vibe, [The Buffalo Lofts](http://thebuffalolofts.com/) have several locations around the area. Take a look through North Buffalo as well. If you like Elmwood, Hertel Ave is coming up nicely as well and is likely a bit cheaper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 21:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We drove our tank through the basement door! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 21:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blues should step up with some real loyalty and offer him a 15 year contract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 22:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> strange looking hermit crab </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 22:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you wanted this meme to make any sense, your thought should at least been "if cigarette tax reduces smoking, does income tax reduce earning?" 

To answer your meme...of course income tax reduces your fucking income. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this exact meme yesterday, but that's none of my business </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the playoffs. There are no penalties, silly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Well](http://img.pandawhale.com/139403-excuse-me-gif-Tobias-Funke-Arr-3Gxe.gif). 

Seriously though. That's crazy. I'm willing to bet that's faster than I could do, and I even played hockey as a kid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 19:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who says that was 80mph? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 18:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I don't remember being this fed up with the playoffs before. It's just brutal. Every other major sport has realized that offense is more exciting and sells. NFL, NBA have cracked down on rules to open the game up and MLB is working to speed things up. NHL is going backward and backwards because old school guys wants to keep the game "tough." Meanwhile, the NHL leader in points this year was in the 80's. Derek freaking Roy scored in the 80's for the Sabres a few years ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 17:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he has some disorder where he can't spell anoi a-words correctly, ant we're just eh bunch of insensitive asslohlles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 17:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [No one has ever screwed up spelling "absolutely" as much as you just did. Congrats!](https://www.google.com/search?q=Absoalluly oq=Absoalluly aqs=chrome..69i57j69i61 sourceid=chrome es_sm=93 ie=UTF-8#safe=active q=%22absoalluly%22) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Honest question about the watchability of these playoffs. Are people (outside of fans with teams still in it) enjoying these playoffs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 17:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My issue is with how clogged up the NHL allows playoffs to be. They throw out the rule book and there is grabbing/interference/cross-checks/more interference/holding/hooking/boarding/more interference again than I ever remember seeing. With the rare exceptions every game seems to end 2-1 and every goal seems to be a tip in from the point. It's just not fun to watch. How are other people feeling about this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 22:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully Sansa is less whiny in this movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 18:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. Skinny Jonah creeped everyone out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 19:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *You don't turn your back on witches...even when they do* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 19:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you work at noon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 19:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, nice. I think I'll upvote just because it's so bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 19:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the most incorrect uses of a meme I have ever seen. Bravo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 17:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [OP](http://i.imgur.com/q0QKmzJ.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 17:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A puppy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 17:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if an MMA fighter is speaking out against vaccinations, maybe I should reconsider... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 18:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No and you can't make me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 18:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't at all. Perhaps you just don't like or are not familiar with some forms of contemporary dance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 18:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great video. I liked the part with the cocaine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 18:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea ok. The guy finished 8th in Season 4 of So You Think You Can Dance and the girl finished 3rd in her season on the show. They have continued to dance professionally. They are exceptional, world-class talents.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 18:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [ESPN had a reply on twitter](https://twitter.com/kc_barnett/status/593081949935243264) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Browsing /r/new and seeing so many wonderful opinions on Baltimore... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 18:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 17:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [That's what I'm saying to you](https://youtu.be/mnwyqxdgnEI?t=1m50s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 17:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always one that double replies... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 17:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Where The Red Fern Grows of Dicks

* Where The Wild Things Are of Dicks

* Charlotte's Web of Dicks

* Harold and The Purple Crayon of Dicks

* Charlie and The Chocolate Factory of Dicks

* The Giving Tree of Dicks

* The Lion, The Witch, The Wardrobe of Dicks

* The Secret Garden of Dicks

* Treasure Island of Dicks

* The BFG of Dicks

* Black Beauty of Dicks

* Horton Hears a Who of Dicks

* Cloudy With A Chance of Dicks (I cheated, I know)

* The Lorax of Dicks

* The Giver of Dicks

* Not a Box of Dicks

* The Kissing Hand of Dicks

* Once Upon A Potty of Dicks

* The Cat In The Hat of Dicks

* Paul Blart: Mall Cop 2 of Dicks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 17:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harry Potter and The Sorcerer's Stone of Dicks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 16:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bryce Harper -- the most punchable face in the universe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Wars fans send X-Wing miniature into space in hopes to win 2 tickets to the VIP Force Awkens premier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 22:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, but they really held the stage together, dude.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 22:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every person losing an argument: "dude calm down, why are you taking this so seriously."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 21:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Braves fan...no thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 21:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I move slavs?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 21:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I've seen this movie... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 21:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously this island is a secret Illuminati lair  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 21:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, that's a bizarre clause. Baseball contracts are fully guaranteed. This makes it sound like teams can just say "well you're bad now, we're going to stop paying you." Either this has to have some sort of insanely high threshold of ineptitude or I don't know what.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 19:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, that's not how formal notices of resignation work. You include, in writing, the date and time frame of your departure. Given this exact notice in writing, the employer has rights to accept their resignation effective immediately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 19:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that is incredible. [Some further information on Aogashima](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aogashima). Population estimate of 170.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 18:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because she probably didn't email an imgur link to her boss with the title "my two week notice." No where in the letter does she give notice of two weeks. All she says is "immediately."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 18:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doing the wave: expert level </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Josh Hamilton could be gone from Angels in matter of days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 17:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 16:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/passiveaggressive Hall of Fame - unanimous selection. 


Also, it's not a two week notice when you say "immediately."


Edit: Seriously people on the "what's so hard to understand about the two weeks notice?" Take the title of her post out of the equation and look at the letter. Not a single time does she mention giving notice of two weeks. All she says is "immediately" at the end. As an employer, if I got this letter, I'd be surprised as hell to see this girl show up the next day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 16:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Alternate shitty quality version](http://i.imgur.com/pRuW22h.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 16:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/D6ewEyU.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 16:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People that say "drollery" are always fun.


Edit: /u/whiteskwirl2's previous comment was "weakest cumshot ever." on a porn gif, so clearly this low-content drollery is beneath him.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 19:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya'll get any of them strikes??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 19:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Off to /r/cityporn with you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 19:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *"Why would I want to go anywhere when I'm in the greatest country in the world already??"* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 18:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 18:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "As long as we punch people in the head and crosscheck necks, we'll be alright" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 17:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> their existing contracts... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 17:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Players   coaches don't give a shit about ticket sales.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 22:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't put a TLDR on the most beautiful thing you have ever read. Trust its beauty for people to enjoy in it's full length.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 22:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like "cops are coming, sweep the cocaine away!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 19:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To make this a full socially awesome penguin...you should have sneaked into the car, quickly turned engine on, and floor it. Drive straight home, with proper speed and momentum, making sure they remain on the hood at all times. Bring them inside, tip your fedora, cook them spaghetti, have a three-way. Make success kid meme. Turns out, one of em had herpes. Make a Bad Luck Brian meme.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
