<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3014</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 19:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pressed the button by accident. Lucky 13 I guess... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will the price of an unlocked G3 drop because of the G4 announcement? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 16:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering if I should wait to buy an unlocked G3. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 15:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww man, I just tapped the touch pad on my laptop by accident! I know how you feel pal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 14:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every account on reddit is a bot except you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 23:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! This looks promising. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whitchmarsh | A co-op Platform RPG set in 1920s Massachusetts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 23:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I find the most diverse selection of colored shirts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 18:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This question may be a little odd, but I'm looking for as many different colored shirts as possible. Long sleeve and short sleeve but no button ups. I don't want logos, patterns or pictures, just solid colors. [This] (http://cdnd.lystit.com/photos/2013/05/07/old-navy-dark-green-heather-classic-vneck-tees-product-1-8542319-185125367_large_flex.jpeg) is the type of shirt I'm describing. 

Ideally I'd like the widest selection of hues there can be so I can use them for a special project I'm working on in one of my classes.


Thanks for any help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 19:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/trollabot train_subject3014 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 16:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah, just, no words for this. 12/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 16:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was won in a game of charades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 17:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John! Are you ever going to come visit New England? Maybe for a book signing/nerd fighter meetup? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 20:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought a laptop for $200... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here are 42 quotes from Germans about American soldiers after World War I. It's amazing to see all the varied responses! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 05:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 05:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno why you got downvoted,  I thought it was funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emitt Rhodes - You Take The Dark Out Of The Night [Soft rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 22:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 19:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree.  Can someone confirm the legitimacy of this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 16:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it might be special, oh well... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 15:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The blade says:
 
**STAINLESS**
**PAKISTAN** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is my grandfather's knife, thought you guys might find it interesting! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 15:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 06:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turn my pages bitch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 05:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 55! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help] Should I buy a heavily used Galaxy S3 or a new Galaxy Grand Prime? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 00:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in need of a phone and this will be the first that I ever own. Due to my relatively small budget I don't have many options. I've narrowed my choices down to a used Galaxy S3 from Craigslist, or a brand new Galaxy Grand Prime from Amazon. After reviewing all the specifications for both phones I've found that the Grand Prime has an edge with almost every feature; screen size, battery life, camera resolution, weight...

The S3 does have a few things going for it though. Twice as much ram (2GB vs 1GB) and twice as much internal memory (16GB vs 8 GB). Although the internal memory shouldn't be a problem because I plan to use an SD card to expand it. The S3 also has a few extra sensors that the Grand Prime doesn't, such as a gyroscope.

One major factor that I'm considering is the fact that the S3's screen has many cracks in it, and I really would love the q-hd screen the Grand Prime has.

Thanks for any information!

TL;DR: I think the title sums it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
