<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7762</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 00:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a ddj sx for home use and it's more than capable of serving my needs. 

The only down side is that it requires a laptop and Serato. 

It's time consuming enough to keep your music collection updated and organized in Serato, but you would have to prep your tracks again in rekordbox if you want to use them with cdjs.

If you're set on a controller, I would recommend the xdj rx. It's a standalone unit that doesn't require a laptop. It uses rekordbox so you just have to manage one music collection. It has the stacked wave forms (Which I think is the major advantage of software driven setups).



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 23:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy, asking the important questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 23:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So they can reach go marry their own respective gay lovers. The long con... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 20:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've easily filled up a 750ml wine bottle before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 00:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would probably help I'd you mentioned if it was a male or female vocalist. Who the dj was, that was spinning the set. 

No luck whatsoever trying to pin down your track. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 22:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darude - Sandstorm by Darude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 18:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I either go with Magnum or Blue Steel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 16:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confirmed: op is black. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 16:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You bastard. You made me go back to look at your nipples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 04:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, you don't even look like the same person. Good work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure why people are hating on your nice mattress. 

Your debt shouldn't be that difficult to overcome. Like others have stated, get your spending under control. Plan to "disappear" from the social even for at least 6 months. Find a hobby that costs little money. I'd suggest done self improvement, like working out.

This way when you get home from work, you have your obligation to go work out and you won't be tempted by vices, such as going out.

Budget as much of your income as you can to paying off the credit card. And I mean actually sit down and draft a budget.

In 6 to 8 months you'll have made a significant dent in your debt and you'll be a healthier you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get off reddit and go practice driving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 02:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouch, this cuts deep.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 23:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Justin Bieber. He wasn't even 18 years old and he was with more than $100 million dollars. Tell me you wouldn't have been a bigger douche than him at that age with that money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 22:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> www.investopedia.com

You can register a user name, invest in the real stock market with fake money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 22:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erektified </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 22:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet! Time to cancel the gym membership. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 22:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Checking in from r/keto just to say this will NOT clog your arteries. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 17:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That a penis sits on a vagina kind of how a hotdog fits in a hotdog bun and that's how sex works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might like Allen   Envy, they do a lot of vocals, but I tend to get tired of their bassline after a while.

Try these tracks

Allen   Envy - The Heart That Never Sleeps (Allen Watts remix)

Sneijder - Letting Me Go

Indecent Noise - Glitches (Matt Bowdidge remix)

Dash Berlin - Never Cry Again (Jorn van Deynhoven remix)

Dash Berlin - Waiting (Sean Tyas remix)

Giuseppe Ottaviani - Angel (Vandit Night mix)

Lostly - I Tried (vocal mix)

Aly   Fila - Running

Aly   Fila - We Control the Sunlight

That's all I got off the top of my head right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 03:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're just into vocal trance then you're better off looking for specific tracks, not djs, as they do not always produce vocals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 02:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this sorcery?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 21:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to a lot of butter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 04:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shut up jaden </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 01:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm -active here in the LA underground scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 20:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jorn van Deynhoven

Adam Ellis

Neptune Project

Bryan Kearney

Sean Tyas

Sneijder

James Dymond

Darren Porter

Reorder

John Askew

Greg Downey

Temple One

Ferry Tayle

Driftmoon

Solarstone

Cold Blue



I would suggest you go on Spotify and do some searching yourself. Tons of great uplifting artists out there.


Edit: added more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 07:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this comment make you a snob snob? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 02:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great way to get someone to fart into your mouth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 02:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go search for his high school photo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 21:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to post this but was too lazy to type it out. Glad to find your response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 21:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Samsung Galaxy S6 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 18:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I'd rather look at a red pancake than a blue waffle, but that's just me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 18:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well eventually this happens:

Lobbyist: "If you don't vote for free bacon, we will stop donating."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 17:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was wearing jeans and a grey T-shirt but police say it was likely he had changed his clothing.

Police are on top of things. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 17:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would have to be administered by a high priced hooker. You know, to go along with the expensive bottle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 18:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If there's anything else? I was trying to type never even appears on the suggestion box. I'm not referring to all the time difference between a good idea! I'll take a bit longer be working with a warm and you want yo, the line of the car, so I know what terminal to wait in that I would immediately toss out your whole argument, but I think it's okay to make sure you addressed everything else in the world of pure imagination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 18:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would suggest going to the most expensive body shops you can find.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 17:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rekt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 16:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like the guy from the movie Fury. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 21:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The prize will be airfare and hotel accommodations to Vegas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 06:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

Jesus christ. "Just following orders" is great and all, but there's a very obvious line where that needs to be broken for the sake of not being a fucking idiot.

You're giving them too much credit by assuming there was a single person in this situation that wasn't an idiot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 05:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ALE HOUSE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 22:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's ok. No need to get upset about it. In fact, it's useless to give diet advice to others. I avoid giving advice unless it's solicited of me.

I always post pictures of bacon, steaks, korean bbq, and other "fattening" foods on instagram. When people ask how I stay slim, I tell them it's because I eat bacon all day, everyday. 

They laugh because they think I'm joking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 21:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Things I have done:**

- Graduated college (BA in Business).

- Lost 30 pounds (180lbs to 150lbs, 6ft tall).

- Broke up with gf, got a new gf.

- Got a new job.

- Wrecked my car, got a new car.

- Paid all credit card debt.

- Quit smoking (after 10 years).





**Things I've yet to do:**

- Get my own place.

- Open my own restaurant.

- Take an actual vacation to Europe/Asia.




Insights: thanks for this OP. I was feeling down about myself, but upon reflecting, my life isn't so bad after all. I just need some capital to start my business.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 20:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your assumption is incorrect. Skype and telephone calls both have delays. You can test this out by calling yourself from another phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 18:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baby don't hurt me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 07:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubt she was hot. Looks like she has cankles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 01:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upon closer inspection, you can see the ink is rather of poor quality and detail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 00:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lil nigga tryna get dunked on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 22:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the strangest boner right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they don't. 

On an unrelated note, would someone call an ambulance. Time is somewhat of a factor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's the same person who posted it, but they just went back 2 weeks ago to post it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's very minor damage then you'll be lucky if your insurance company can get his insurance to pay for a new hood and bumper. More than likely, it will be a repaint.

You need to call your insurance company and tell them what happened. 

You should go to at least 3 body shops to get an estimate on repairs. Estimates are free. I would suggest going to the most expensive body shops you can find. A higher estimate is in your favor.

Once fault is determined, your insurance company will offer 2 ways to receive payment: either they cut the check to the body shop that you fix your car at or they issue you a check.

I would choose to take the check personally. Then go to any body shop and have them repair the car.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 17:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 16:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even with oil prices down, gas prices in California have risen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 16:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Climbing into bed at 3am, while your wife is asleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 06:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm longing for WaW zombies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 23:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well how do you think I got so fat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 23:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Number 5 will shock you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 23:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouchi indeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 20:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forshizzle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 20:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everybody at my office thinks was sick for the last 3 days and have been coming by constantly to see if I'm better.

In reality, I woke up on the floor of a hotel room Tuesday because I had been partying with my dj friends for the past weekend until yesterday.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 19:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cunt punt! Cunt punt! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 06:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All for Silas! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 02:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just checked. He's telling the truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 01:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather get my teeth drilled than listen to dubstep. But thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
