<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject138</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tensions on the Supreme Court over America's use of the death penalty boiled over on Wednesday as the justices appeared badly split in a case challenging Oklahoma's lethal injection method as a breach of the Constitution's ban on cruel and unusual punishment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 00:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It All Comes Down to Justice Kennedy - The two most recent of Justice Kennedys LGBT decisions have leaned heavily on a concept of equal dignity and the need for the Court to recognize the harm generated by laws that demean or disrespect gay people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 00:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oil Drilling May Slow Drought Recovery - The study estimates that up to nearly 34 billion cubic meters of water were used for fracking and refracturing in the central U.S. and Canada between 2000 and 2012, enough water to fill more than 1.3 million Olympic-sized swimming pools. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 23:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudi King Salman appointed a nephew as new heir and made his young son second in line to rule on Wednesday, a major shift in power towards two princes who have overseen a more assertive stance at a time of almost unprecedented regional turmoil. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 23:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Senator Rand Paul, a Republican presidential hopeful, on Wednesday introduced a resolution to block new regulations on Internet service providers, saying they would "wrap the Internet in red tape." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 23:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A UN internal report leaked to the Guardian newspaper alleges that French troops deployed as part of a peacekeeping mission in the Central African Republic (CAR) raped boys as young as nine. The abuse is believed to have taken place between December 2013 and June 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 23:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A baby boy has been rescued from the rubble of the Nepal earthquake after being buried under a collapsed building for 22 hours, according to a local newspaper. Images published by Katmandu Today showed the boy covered in dust being pulled to safety by members of the armed forces. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 23:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taking U.S. and Russian missiles off high alert could keep a possible cyberattack from starting a nuclear war, a former commander of U.S. nuclear forces says, but neither country appears willing to increase the lead-time to prepare the weapons for launch. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 23:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Lyndon Johnson Responded To Baltimore's Last Riots - I dont know why were so surprised. When you put your foot on a mans neck and hold him down for three hundred years, and then you let him up, whats he going to do? Hes going to knock your block off. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 01:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iranian patrol boats intercepted a cargo ship in the Strait of Hormuz on Tuesday and forced it into Iranian territorial waters by firing shots across its bow, prompting the U.S. Navy to send a destroyer and reconnaissance plane to monitor the situation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 01:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Senate on Tuesday rejected an effort to require an international nuclear agreement with Iran to be considered a treaty, which would have forced any deal to be approved by two-thirds of the Senate's 100 members before it could take effect. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 01:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Lawyer Defending Discrimination In The Supreme Court May Have Just Talked Himself Out Of Victory - One justice who did not join Alitos dissent was Justice Kennedy. As Bursch started to lay out his view that child-centered marriage is different than adult-centered marriage, Kennedy balked. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 01:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why The NFL Is Voluntarily Giving Up Its Tax-Exempt Status - And as far as tax benefits go, the subsidies its teams get from federal, state, and local governments to build and maintain stadiums remain far more beneficial than the exemption anyway. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 01:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian Cargo Ship Spinning Out of Control in Orbit [Video] - The Russian space agency Roscosmos is scrambling to regain control of a robotic Progress 59 cargo ship that appears to have suffered a serious malfunction shortly after launching into orbit early today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 01:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Barack Obama accused China on Tuesday of "flexing its muscles" to advance its maritime claims against Asian neighbors and assured Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe of the U.S. commitment to defend Japanese territory, including tiny islands in dispute with Beijing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 01:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Barack Obama nominated the U.S. Coast Guard's second-in-command on Tuesday to run the Transportation Security Administration, tasking Vice Adm. Peter Neffenger with keeping passengers safe amid increasingly complex threats from the Middle East and beyond. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 01:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. lawmakers introduced legislation on Tuesday to end spy agencies' bulk collection of Americans' telephone data, setting up a potential showdown over the program, which expires on June 1. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 01:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Cities Funding Woes Are Driving Racial and Economic InjusticeAnd What We Can Do About It - When property tax revenue declined in St. Louis County, fines-and-fees revenue increased in order to maintain revenue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 00:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dispatch From Baltimore: Praying for Peace, Living Another Reality - Those leaders often assume that we're all equally capable of overcoming the long-term effects of police brutality; decades of unanswered questions and unsolved murders; a stubborn, clawing, generational poverty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 00:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Last 3 Bornean Rhinos Are in a Race against Extinction - The clock is ticking. In the past few years we have already lost the western black rhino in Africa and the Javan rhino subspecies in Vietnam. Without immediate help, the Bornean and Sumatran rhinos may not be far behind. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 00:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senator Bernie Sanders of Vermont, the longest-serving independent member of the U.S. Congress, will announce his candidacy for the Democratic presidential nomination on Thursday, Vermont Public Radio reported on Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 00:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Andrew Cockburn, How Assassination Sold Drugs and Promoted Terrorism - Whatever the euphemism -- the Israelis prefer to call it focused prevention -- assassination has clearly been Washingtons favored strategy in the twenty-first century. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 23:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Motivated reasoning is the additional tendency to defensively reject information that contradicts deeply held worldviews and opinions. One example of this is the motivated rejection of science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 23:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iranian forces boarded a Marshall Islands-flagged cargo ship in the Gulf on Tuesday after patrol boats fired warning shots across its bow and ordered it deeper into Iranian waters, the Pentagon said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 23:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every so often, in a bid to sound threatening, a member of Congress has vowed to revoke the NFL's tax-exempt status. Now Commissioner Roger Goodell says the league will give it up voluntarily to "eliminate this distraction." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 23:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 16:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  American politics. There is no more useless animal than an American politician.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 16:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Archer, is that you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Multiple gunshots were fired early Sunday into two buses carrying Grammy-winning rap music star Lil Wayne and his entourage on a Georgia highway following a performance in Atlanta, but no one was hurt, police said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 08:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Supreme Court's arguments on Tuesday over same-sex marriage will cap more than two decades of litigation and a transformation in public attitudes. Based on the court's actions during the past two years, a sense of inevitability is in the air </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 08:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iranian Foreign Minister Mohammad Javad Zarif will meet U.S. Secretary of State John Kerry at the opening of a UN conference on the global anti-nuclear weapons treaty on Monday, as they try to make progress in talks on a long-term atomic deal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 08:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is a growing convergence of concern about new technologies in the life sciences that are raising significant societal, ethical, environmental and security risks. Global public engagement must be a priority for deliberation about these technologies and for developing a set of common red lines. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 07:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 05:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The clown car will just be a little more crowded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 14:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this comment is going to be downvoted to oblivion by the Israel brigadel, but it's as if the Israelis learned population control from Nazi Germany. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ban Ki-moon, the United Nations secretary-general, has appealed to Indonesia to stop the planned executions of nine prisoners within days for drug-related crimes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 08:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least a dozen protesters were arrested in Baltimore on Saturday evening after peaceful demonstrations over the death of Freddie Gray were followed by clashes with police in riot gear and scattered vandalism. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 07:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The White House Correspondents' Association dinner has become a celebrity magnet, this year drawing some big names from television, sports and movies to rub shoulders with members of Congress and to hear the president speak. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 07:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greeks view of the debt crisis: What lies ahead is great, great hardship - It is a sliding scale of drama, of high-octane intensity that Greeks have learned to watch with a mixture of shock, angst, bewilderment and dismay. Today dismay predominates. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 07:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three people were found dead inside a Los Angeles-area business on Saturday in what might have been a fire bomb or Molotov cocktail attack, law enforcement said. One victim was alive but covered in flames when firefighters arrived </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 07:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As contributions fall, House GOP rebels blame party leaders - "Those who don't go along to get along aren't going to get as many PAC checks," Massie said last week, using the acronym for political action committees. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 07:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A bakery that turned away a lesbian couple looking to buy a cake for their wedding will have to pay them an award of possibly $135,000 for emotional damages, a hearings officer said Friday. The sum is recommended by an administrative law judge for the Oregon Bureau of Labor and Industries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 06:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nepal urged countries to send aid to help it cope with the aftermath of a devastating earthquake that killed nearly 1,400 people, a toll predicted to rise as rescuers used their hands to dig for survivors among the rubble on Sunday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 06:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington Governor Jay Inslee on Friday signed a bill that will overhaul the state's medical marijuana market, reconciling the long unregulated system with the voter-approved recreational pot industry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 12:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A shallow earthquake measuring 7.9 magnitude struck west of the ancient Nepali capital of Kathmandu on Saturday, killing more than 100 people, injuring hundreds and leaving a pall over the valley, doctors and witnesses said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 12:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earthquakes Linked To Fracking Activity Are On The Rise, U.S. Government Says - According to the USGS scientists, there are 17 regions within eight states  all of which are located near deep fluid injection wells or other industrial activities capable of inducing earthquakes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 02:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An archaeologist has discovered liquid mercury at the end of a tunnel beneath a Mexican pyramid, a finding that could suggest the existence of a kings tomb or a ritual chamber far below one of the most ancient cities of the Americas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 02:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sabeen Mahmud, a prominent Pakistani social and human rights activist, has been shot dead, shortly after hosting an event on Balochistans "disappeared people", in the southern city of Karachi, officials have told Al Jazeera. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 02:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marc Benioff, the CEO of Salesforce, has launched a companywide program called Womens Surge that aims to eliminate any pay disparities between male and female workers, hire and promote more women, and make sure they are better included in meetings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 02:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Wednesday, about a dozen Native American actors, including the films Native consultant, walked off the set of Adam Sandlers new Western parody, The Ridiculous Six. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 02:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Wednesday, about a dozen Native American actors, including the films Native consultant, walked off the set of Adam Sandlers new Western parody, The Ridiculous Six. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 02:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deep beneath Yellowstone national park, one of the worlds most dynamic volcanic systems, lies an enormous, previously unknown reservoir of hot, partly molten rock big enough to fill up the Grand Canyon 11 times, scientists say. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 02:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The accidental killing of two hostages in a U.S. operation against al-Qaida has put a new spotlight on the Obama administration's reliance on drones in the battle against terrorism - and has also raised pressure on the White House to revise the nation's oft-criticized strategy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 01:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A US activist group that has received funding from energy companies and the foundation controlled by conservative activist Charles Koch is trying to persuade the Vatican that there is no global warming crisis ahead of an environmental statement by Pope Francis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 01:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A US activist group that has received funding from energy companies and the foundation controlled by conservative activist Charles Koch is trying to persuade the Vatican that there is no global warming crisis ahead of an environmental statement by Pope Francis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 01:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poor People Need a Higher Wage, Not a Lesson in Morality - one that might begin with Brooks and others looking in the mirror and asking some basic questions: Do I accept that people working full-time are paid wages that keep them in poverty? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 22:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton defended an alleged rapists: Feminist lawyers are right to represent all clients zealously - As a matter of professional ethics, Clinton did the right thing in accepting a court appointment to represent an indigent charged with a repugnant crime </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 22:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists in China have genetically modified human embryos in a world first that has re-ignited the debate over the ethics and safety of genetic therapies that have the potential to prevent inherited diseases. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 22:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Loretta E. Lynchs long wait to become U.S. attorney general ended Thursday, with the Senate voting to confirm the veteran New York prosecutors nomination five months after President Obama submitted it to Congress. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 22:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A U.S. drone strike in January targeting an al Qaeda compound in Pakistan near the Afghan border inadvertently killed an American and an Italian who had been held hostage for years by the group, U.S. officials said on Thursday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 21:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Senate Energy and Natural Resources Committee held a hearing Wednesday morning to examine possible ways to limit the use and effectiveness of the Land and Water Conservation Fund (LWCF), a 50-year-old program that will expire in September without congressional reauthorization. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 02:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What about Earths Microbiome? - Even today, though we usually think of plants as responsible for photosynthesis, about 50 percent of global photosynthesis is still carried out microbially, primarily in the oceans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 02:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey has recalled its ambassador to Austria in protest over the Austrian parliament's condemnation of the massacre of Armenians by Ottoman Turk forces 100 years ago as "genocide". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 02:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Environmental Protection Agencys proposed Clean Power Plan will add more than a quarter of a million jobs to the U.S. economy by 2040, according to a new economic analysis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 01:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oil May Have Killed Gulf Dolphins - "Put all that evidence together and it supports the hypothesis that the oil spill contributed to the increase in deaths," says veterinarian Stephanie Venn-Watson of the National Marine Mammal Foundation in San Diego. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 01:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Southern Chile's Calbuco volcano has erupted for the first time in more than four decades, sending a thick plume of ash and smoke several kilometres into the sky, local television images showed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 01:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 01:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you believe in god/allah? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Though police retain a fair amount of ability to use routine traffic stops to seek out evidence of other crimes, the thrust of Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburgs opinion in Rodriguez v. United States is that they cannot extend a traffic stop even for a minute without a new justification </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 00:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the first time in US history, a judge has granted two chimpanzees a petition  through human attorneys  to defend their rights against unlawful imprisonment, arguably bestowing the status of legal persons on the primates. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 00:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Saudi-led coalition bombing Yemen for almost a month announced on Tuesday the end to its military operation, but a Saudi spokesman said forces would continue to target the Iran-allied Houthi movement as necessary. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 23:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton Cash, by former Bush speechwriter and Breitbart.com contributor Peter Schweizer, is billed as a game-changer for Clintons candidacy, revealing that the Clinton State Department traded favors for big donations to the Clinton Foundation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 23:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Space geckos show their playful side on zero-gravity mission - When given the opportunity, the Russian experiment found, geckos are happy to spend time batting an object around a tank at zero gravity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 23:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attorney general nominee Loretta Lynch, nominated by President Obama in November, will get a confirmation vote in the coming days under a deal announced Tuesday morning by Senate leaders that ends a weeks-long impasse sparked by partisan divides over immigration and abortion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 22:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A U.S. congressional panel will examine whether federal Drug Enforcement Administration agents divulged secrets at sex parties that Colombian drug lords may have staged to elicit sensitive information. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 22:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A coalition of big insurance companies, consumer groups, and environmental advocates are urging the United States to overhaul its disaster policies in the face of increasingly extreme weather due to human-caused climate change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 22:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After a coalition airstrike in March that left Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi seriously wounded and on the verge of death, the leader of the so-called Islamic State (IS) is no longer in full control of the violent militant group's day-to-day activities, sources have said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 22:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A major study published in one of the worlds leading medical journals has concluded that there is no link between the MMR (measles, mumps and rubella) vaccination and autism in children. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 22:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran's deputy foreign minister said he was optimistic that a ceasefire in Yemen would be announced later on Tuesday, in a sign diplomatic efforts may be underway to stop almost a month of Saudi-led bombing of Yemen's Houthi group. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 22:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Supreme Court said Tuesday that police may not extend an ordinary traffic stop to seek evidence of crimes unrelated to the offense that prompted officers to pull a vehicle over. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 21:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberal leaders are pressuring Hillary Rodham Clinton advocate a national plan for "debt-free college" in her presidential campaign, part of a broader effort to convince the Democratic front-runner to embrace pillars of Sen. Elizabeth Warren's progressive agenda. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 21:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This was easily the hottest March  and hottest January-to-March  on record, according to the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration. NOAAs latest monthly report makes clear Mother Nature is just getting warmed up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 00:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington, D.C.s National Football League team uses a racial slur for its name. Several Native Americans brought a lawsuit to cancel the teams trademarks, and the U.S. Patent and Trademark Offices tribunal determined that the teams marks are indeed likely to disparage native peoples </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 00:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia has said the leader of a North Caucasus al-Qaeda linked armed group has been killed in an operation by special forces, with the rebels confirming his death. Russia's National Anti-Terrorism Committee said on Monday that Aliaskhab Kebekov, also known as Ali Abu Mukhammad, was "neutralised" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 00:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alabama has no money. A lottery might be its last hope. - State lotteries are regressive institutions, amounting to a tax  albeit voluntary  on some of societys neediest. Forty years ago, these losing games of chance were illegal in every state. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 23:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. authorities have charged six Somali-American young men from Minnesota with planning to join Islamic State and fight for the militant group in Syria, the U.S. attorney for Minnesota said on Monday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 23:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Post and Courier newspaper of Charleston, South Carolina, on Monday won the prestigious Pulitzer prize for Public Service for its series on domestic violence against women, "Till Death Do Us Part." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 23:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does The Fight For Body Cams Trump Privacy Concerns? - But what if the Tulsa, Oklahoma police didnt release the footage showing Harris being chased, shot and pinned down by several officers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 22:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astronomers have discovered what they say is the largest known structure in the universe: an incredibly big hole. The supervoid, as it is known, is a spherical blob 1.8 billion light years across that is distinguished by its unusual emptiness. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 22:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Supreme Court on Monday threw out a North Carolina court ruling that upheld Republican-drawn electoral districts for state and congressional lawmakers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 22:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Barack Obama is meeting with Crown Prince Mohammed Bin Zayed Al Nahyan of the United Arab Emirates to discuss top issues for the Gulf region, particularly the Saudi-led air campaign in Yemen, Islamic State militants and negotiations over Iran's nuclear program. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 22:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Navy has sent an aircraft carrier and a guided-missile cruiser into the waters near Yemen to conduct maritime security operations, a Pentagon spokesman said on Monday, but he denied the ships were on a mission to intercept Iranian arms shipments. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 22:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As many as 700 people were feared dead after a fishing boat packed with migrants capsized off the Libyan coast overnight, in what may be one of the worst disasters of the Mediterranean migrant crisis, officials said on Sunday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 16:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 05:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is something a bird can do that a man will never be able to do?  
  
Eat with its pecker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Pat Roberts is urging people to "let it go" after his cellphone filled a somber committee hearing room with the first few bars of a song from Disney's "Frozen." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 04:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oil prices fell in early trading on Friday, ending a run of rallies earlier in the week, after OPEC said that its output surged in March, adding to a global glut. The Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC) said that its March production jumped 810,000 barrels per day (bpd) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 04:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Groups who oppose gay marriage are increasingly fighting a losing battle, but no one is waging war on behalf of penis-vagina couplings more entertainingly than a bunch of gay Mormon men who just asked the Supreme Court to consider the idea that same-sex marriage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 03:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A rush of hormone that helps people bond could explain why humans and dogs have been best friends for thousands of years. The scientists found that dog owners experienced a surge of oxytocin when their pets gazed into their eyes, a dramatic effect that was mirrored in the animals themselves. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 03:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the Gaze from Those Big Puppy Eyes the Look of Your Doggie's Love? - A story emergesand probably one that will make dog lovers cheer: Mutual gaze between dogs and the people who care for them produces a very similar physiological profile to whats observed between mothers and infants. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 03:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the Gaze from Those Big Puppy Eyes the Look of Your Doggie's Love? - By describing it in this context, the researchers postulated that gaze between a dog and human (particularly a known human), will share similar properties to motherinfant relationships. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 03:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mutual funds make air travel more expensive: Institutional investors reduce competition - Indeed, it is possible that managers of corporations dont need to be told explicitly to overcharge passengers because they already know that its in their bosses interest, and hence their own. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 03:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Vladimir Putin accused Washington on Thursday of putting pressure on some world leaders not to attend events in Russia marking the 70th anniversary of the end of World War Two in Europe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 02:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A compromise allowing the U.S. Congress to vote on a nuclear deal with Tehran may prompt Iranian negotiators to drive a harder bargain, but does not drastically weaken President Barack Obama's ability to deliver on a final agreement. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 02:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 03:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was my go to issue. Americans have been scared of socialism since the turn of the 20th century. In fact, any economic ideology that competes with capitalism will be a hard fought battle for any generation. It's the perfect example of entire portions of the population fighting against there own best interests. When taxes are proposed on the wealthy or corporations, the US elites political watch dogs begin screaming that it's a scheme to transfer wealth between social groups and a form of class warfare. Meanwhile, smirking in the background are wealthy individuals, sipping on a nice single-malt scotch, and thinking to themselves what a bunch of ignorant putzes populate the rest of the nation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Public arguments are scheduled to begin Tuesday in the Netherlands, where nearly 900 Dutch citizens have filed a lawsuit against their government for failing to effectively cut greenhouse gas emissions and curb climate change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 00:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Physicists Battle over Meaning of Incontrovertible in Global Warming Fight - Instead, the American Physical Society (APS) now states that climate change is a "critical issue that poses the risk of significant disruption around the globe." It then discusses uncertainties inherent in climate science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 00:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Authorities say a man shot an armadillo, but ended up accidentally wounding his mother-in-law when the bullet ricocheted off the mammals hard shell. Sheriffs deputies told WALB-TV that 54-year-old Larry McElroy fired his 9mm pistol at the armadillo on Sunday night in the southern state of Georgia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 00:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP Senate unanimously confirmed first federal judge - Five senators missed the vote to fill the seat on a Texas district court bench, including presidential candidates Ted Cruz (R-Texas) and Marco Rubio (R-Fla). Cruz, more notably, skipped confirming his own constituent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 23:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA's Spitzer Space Telescope has teamed up with a telescope on the ground to find a remote gas planet about 13,000 light-years away, making it one of the most distant planets known. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 22:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long, sinuous, tendril-like structures seen in the vicinity of Saturn's icy moon Enceladus originate directly from geysers erupting from its surface, according to scientists studying images from NASA's Cassini spacecraft. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 22:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Safety Risk of Shrinking Airline Seats Question by DOT - Fliers are older and heavier. Flight attendants warn about an increase in air rage, and experts question if having rows of seats packed closer together might make it harder for passengers to evacuate after a crash. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 22:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eight former Atlanta public school educators were ordered to serve between one and seven years in prison on Tuesday for their convictions on racketeering charges in one of the nation's largest test-cheating scandals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 21:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 02:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You still only get fifteen minutes, and you're paying full price." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its Not Who Follows Hillary Clinton, It's How She Uses Them - The study, published in December by Daniel Kreiss...found that Twitter is used in political campaigns primarily to influence journalists and an elite core of supporters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 01:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To Win Its War in Yemen, Saudi Arabia May Have to Split the Country in Two - "These old men are nothing to us now," he says, clearly angry. "All they did before is talk. They are not here and they are not fighting. We will get our country back, God willing." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 00:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nestl is making waves across the West Coast this week for its bottled water business. In drought-stricken California, the food and beverage conglomerate is under investigation by the U.S. Forest Service for using expired permits to use water from a national forest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 00:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mystery of Ceres's Bright Spots Grows - Not all of the puzzling bright spots on the dwarf planet Ceres are alike. The closest-yet images of the gleams, taken from 45,000 kilometres away, suggest that at least two of the spots look different from one another when seen in infrared wavelengths. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 00:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pakistani Nobel laureate Malala Yousafzai has criticised Nigerian and world leaders for failing to help free 219 schoolgirls kidnapped a year ago by Boko Haram fighters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 00:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ExxonMobil Explosion That Nobody Is Talking About - It feels as though the people in charge, both the government and the refinery, are looking out more for their PR than anything else, says Jennifer Richards, the director and co-founder of Childrens Montessori School </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 00:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Monday, the John F. Kennedy Library Foundation announced that the former U.S. Congressman for South Carolina had been named the 2015 recipient of the John F. Kennedy Profile in Courage Award for political courage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 00:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robert Charles Bates, the 73 year-old insurance-executive-turned-volunteer-cop who was caught on video fatally shooting an unarmed black suspect was charged with second degree manslaughter on Monday. The charges allege that Bates demonstrated culpable negligence when he shot and killed Eric Harris </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 00:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia paved the way on Monday for missile system deliveries to Iran and started an oil-for-goods swap, signaling that Moscow may have a head-start in the race to benefit from an eventual lifting of sanctions on Tehran. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 23:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton, under pressure from the left wing of her Democratic Party to aggressively campaign against income inequality, voiced concern about the hefty paychecks of some corporate executives in an email to supporters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 23:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 00:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an originalist argument because they used the "clear and present danger" argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Hollywood Tells Us the Future Will Suck - Today's films presume an audience's compliance with an almost nihilistic school of thought. Hollywood hardly needs to explain why things in the future are going to suckthey assume that you, dear viewer, already agree that this is how things will be. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 00:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lt. Col. Dave Grossman repeated those lines to a crowd of hundreds at the National Rifle Associations annual meeting in Nashville on Saturday, telling the gun owners to fear for themselves and their families and that the only solution is to arm all of our citizens. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 00:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 00:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually the justices used the "clear and present danger" excuse to place Japanese Americans in prison camps. That is an originalist argument. If you'd like more information I'm placing a reading list below.  
  
Peter H. Irons. A Peoples History of the Supreme Court. New York: Viking, 1999.  
  
Cliff Sloan, and David McKean. The Great Decision Jefferson, Adams, Marshall, and the Battle for the Supreme Court. New York: PublicAffairs, 2009.  
  
James MacGregor Burns. Packing the Court the Rise of Judicial Power and the Coming Crisis of the Supreme Court. New York: The Penguin Press, 2009.  
  
Mellor, William H (last). The Dirty Dozen How Twelve Supreme Court Cases Radically Expanded Government and Eroded Freedom. New York: Sentinel, 2008.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The gun group held the second annual Womens New Energy Breakfast on Sunday for female-only NRA members and family. And a seminar on methods of concealed carry included a section dedicated to the female body and the best ways to hide a gun on it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 00:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey has recalled its ambassador to the Vatican for consultations in an escalating diplomatic row over Pope Francis' use of the word "genocide" to describe the massacres of Armenians by Ottoman forces during World War I. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 23:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 23:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are plenty of reasons to decry an originalist SCOTUS because the constitution was written for a different country. There was no capitalism or corporations for the original framers to protect against. There were African Americans but how did that go for them? Relying on an origanalist's interpretation of the constitution kept them from freely using their voting rights until 1965. It allowed the military to place Japanese in camps during WWII. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis sparked a diplomatic row on Sunday by calling the massacre of up to 1.5 million Armenians 100 years ago "the first genocide of the 20th century," prompting Turkey to accuse him of inciting hatred. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 23:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 01:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird sex parties that include masks and tons of flabby bellies hiding wrinkly droopy ball sacks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 01:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans want to control the judiciary appointments because it provides the opportunity to enact laws friendly to the party and the financial system that supports the party. Giving corporate-person hood a free-speech argument wouldn't have occurred without the maneuvering of George Bush cronies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 01:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's another article trending in r/politics about judicial vacancies that have been held up for an extremely long time. One of the means to protect business-friendly laws and those who would break them is to control the laws and those who decide the law's legality. By keeping judicial seats vacant or by changing the rules to remove a progressive judge, conservatives control the ideology that bends justice towards those that least deserve it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police body cameras - The difficulty in indicting and convicting police officers illuminates an uncomfortable truth of the criminal justice system: There is an enormous divide in the standards of justice we apply to cops as opposed to all other citizens. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 23:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The head of the UN agency for Palestinian refugees is set to visit Syria to start an "urgent mission" aimed at alleviating the humanitarian crisis in the southern Damascus district of Yarmouk that has been devastated by increased conflict, his organisation has said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 23:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The NBA Players Association said it was concerned about the arrest of two Atlanta Hawks players following an altercation with New York police outside of a nightclub earlier this week that resulted in a season-ending injury for forward Thabo Sefolosha </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 22:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A man shot himself Saturday afternoon on the steps of the US Capitol building in Washington, DC, and a suspicious package was found nearby, prompting police to swiftly lock down the surrounding area. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 22:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Were Lincoln and Nixon gay? The history book that is dividing America - The gay historical timeline tends to go back as far as Oscar Wilde and no further, said Hicklin. There were pioneers before us but no one took the time to write about them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 22:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton Is About to Launch the Most Boring Presidential Campaign in Years - So Clinton's biggest task will be converting her sky-high name recognition and the sense of inevitability around her campaign into the kind of energy that Obama generated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 22:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Second Amendment was front and center at the annual National Rifle Association Meeting on Friday, but another topic was close behind and discussed by the dozen Republican presidential hopefuls nearly as much: Hillary Clinton. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 22:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It is the fastest spaceship ever launched and has been hurtling towards its target at a staggering 36,000mph for the past nine years. But now Nasa engineers are preparing to put their robot craft, New Horizons, on its final course  to the tiny world of Pluto. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 22:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Egyptian court sentenced Mohamed Badie, leader of the outlawed Muslim Brotherhood, and 13 other senior members of the group to death for inciting chaos and violence, and gave a life term to a U.S.-Egyptian citizen for ties to the Brotherhood. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 22:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Workers Sue Walmart - The lawsuit alleges that they were managers in name only because they did not have the managerial duties or authority, but that Walmart purposefully classified them as managers to avoid overtime pay and cut costs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 22:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Pauls claim that Reagans tax cuts produced more revenue and tens of millions of jobs - But the tax cut itself was a money-loser for the governmentand it was not the sole reason for tens of millions of jobs. We cannot quite say Paul committed a Four-Pinocchio violation, but its close. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 22:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wisconsin Agency Bans Talk of Climate Change - Employees are also required to notify the board's three elected commissioners before answering email inquiries about global warming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 22:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M.I.T. Debates Whether to Drop Fossil-Fuel Investments - "Divestment aligns the institute's actions with its values," Gould said, drawing roars from the crowd as he suggested MIT could show up cross-town rival Harvard University </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 22:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. President Barack Obama said Washington is concerned China is using its "sheer size and muscle" to push around smaller nations in the South China Sea, drawing a swift rebuke from Beijing which accused the United States of being the bully. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 21:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smartphones and other personal electronic devices could, in regions where they are in widespread use, function as early warning systems for large earthquakes, according to newly reported research. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 21:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Massachusetts officials on Friday released video footage showing the near-fatal shooting of a Boston police officer last month by a man who was subsequently shot dead by other officers. The decision to release the footage comes amid protests in several major U.S. cities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 21:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The biggest extinction event in planetary history was driven by the rapid acidification of our oceans, a new study concludes. So much carbon was released into the atmosphere, and the oceans absorbed so much of it so quickly, that marine life simply died off, from the bottom of the food chain up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 02:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Florida Family Releases Video of Cop Killing Their Schizophrenic Son - "Get on the fucking ground or you're dead!" Trimino is heard yelling in the police video. "Get on the ground or you're dead. Get on the ground, get on the ground." Trimino then fires four shots, pauses, then fires a fifth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 01:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> About 90 employees at NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory, Pasadena, California, are running 1.2 mile laps through the laboratory grounds today as part of a marathon-length relay to celebrate the first-ever Martian marathon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 01:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A St. Louis resident who was formerly homeless and wants to see the city devote more money to social services and homelessness this week threatened a lawsuit against the city of St. Louis if it moves ahead with a plan to fund a new NFL stadium without giving the public a say in the process. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 00:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rahm Emanuel may have been elected to a second term as Chicago's mayor on Tuesday but now he faces a stark choice: inflict pain on the city's population in the form of unpopular measures such as higher taxes or kick its problems further down the road and risk a fiscal crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 23:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran deal shadows Rand Paul's presidential announcement - But as Paul, 52, tries to strike a chord with nontraditional Republican voters, he is encountering resistance from many within the party who advocate a more aggressive approach in the Middle East. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 23:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Pauls problem with female interviewers just cropped up again - It is not a college lecture class where you talk and other people listen and take notes. It is an active back and forth between the candidate, voters and, yes, the media. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 23:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Islamic State of Iraq and the Levant (ISIL) group has released more than 200 captives - mainly elderly and children belonging to the Yazidi community - held for eight months in captivity in the groups stronghold, Mosul. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 23:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samples from mummies in a Hungarian crypt have revealed that multiple tuberculosis strains derived from a single Roman ancestor that circulated in 18th-century Europe, scientists said Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 22:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Insists that Climate Change Hurts Health, Sharpening Debate - Murthy, confirmed by the Senate in December, said climate change leads to more intense heat waves, more particulates from wildfires clouding the atmosphere, longer allergy seasons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 22:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Rodham Clinton has hired a longtime Google executive to oversee her likely presidential campaign's technology development and build new ways for Clinton to engage with voters, according to Democrats with knowledge of the move. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 22:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dzokhar Tsarnaev was found guilty on Wednesday of killing three people and injuring 264 others in the 2013 Boston Marathon bombing and of fatally shooting a police officer four days later. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 22:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul will not be the next president of the United States. If Im proven wrong about this, Im prepared to get a prominent tattoo of Rand Paul taking his place on Mount Rushmore. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 01:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A white South Carolina police officer will be charged with murder over the shooting death of a black man who appeared to be fleeing from him, local authorities said on Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 01:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United States is speeding up arms supplies and bolstering intelligence sharing with a Saudi-led alliance bombing a militia aligned with Iran in neighboring Yemen, a senior U.S. diplomat said on Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 01:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YouTubes copyright system has taken Rand Pauls presidential announcement offline - But it's hard not to see some humor in the situation. Rand Paul's spirited cry against government intervention has been blocked from view because YouTube lets huge music companies preemptively apply copyright law. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 01:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 00:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry...that was supposed to go into r/news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ralph Naders Unanswered Letters to the President - When you were a candidate, I called you [G. Bush] a corporation running for the presidency masquerading as a human being. In time you turned a metaphor into a reality. As a corporation, you express no remorse, no shame, no compassion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 00:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A North Charleston officer who previously claimed he shot and killed a suspect in self-defense now faces murder charges, as a newly-surfaced video shows 50-year-old Walter Larner Scott running away from Patrolman Michael Thomas Slager. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 00:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers from several institutions are in the Four Corners region of the U.S. Southwest with a suite of airborne and ground-based instruments, aiming to uncover reasons for a mysterious methane "hot spot" detected from space. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 00:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Problems at a Maryland electrical station caused widespread power outages across the nation's capital Tuesday, affecting the White House, the Capitol, museums, train stations and other sites. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 00:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chicagoans headed to the polls on Tuesday in a mayoral runoff election pitting well-funded incumbent Rahm Emanuel against underdog Jesus "Chuy" Garcia in a race to lead a city on the brink of financial crisis and plagued by violent crime. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 00:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How The Oil Industrys Dr. Evil Is Running A Campaign To Sell Off Americas Public Lands - The articles published argued in support of right-wing efforts in Utah and ten other western states to seize control of national forests and national monuments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 00:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA's Mars Reconnaissance Orbiter, at Mars since 2006, made an unplanned switch on Wednesday from one main computer to a redundant one onboard, triggering a hiatus in planned activities. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 22:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Likely Republican presidential contender Jeb Bush, who was popular among Spanish-speaking voters while Florida governor, marked himself as "Hispanic" on a 2009 voter registration application, The New York Times reported on Monday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 22:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker, while currently polling well as a potential Republican presidential candidate, has a problem. He cant deal with dog dander. And if recent coverage by the New York Times is any indication, American voters might be allergic to presidential candidates who do not own dogs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 00:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Kelly Ayotte's state director was caught in a prostitution ring Friday night and resigned the next day, according to the New Hampshire Republican's office. David Wihby, 62, was arrested in Nashua on a misdemeanor charge for solicitation of prostitution and has resigned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 00:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Santorum's inflammatory defence of Indiana law - Appearing on a weekend talk show, former Pennsylvania Senator Rick Santorum used a homophobic word to defend a new religious law in Indiana that some believe gives businesses the right to discriminate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 00:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Milos Zeman has "closed the door" of Prague Castle to the U.S. ambassador following comments perceived as critical of the Czech's decision to attend a World War Two commemoration in Moscow, according to local media reports on Sunday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 00:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese Taxi Drivers Drank Pesticide in a Mass Suicide Attempt at a Protest in Beijing - The Times reported that "at least 10 men" drank pesticide, while the South China Morning Post (SCMP) put the number at "more than 30." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 00:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Principal To Gay Student: Girls Wear Dresses - The Monroe City School Board president said he would discuss the rule with Carroll Highs principal, as he does not believe there is no school policy dictating student dress at prom. You cant just go making up policies, he said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 00:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why scientific truth may hurt - Science is quite the opposite of common sense. Common sense deceives us all the time: the horizon tells me the Earth is flat; people seem to get better after taking homeopathic pills; spiders are dangerous; a cold snap ridicules global warming. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 00:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate Republicans on Sunday pressed their demand that the U.S. Congress be allowed to vote on a nuclear agreement with Iran, but signaled they are willing to wait for last week's interim agreement to be finalized before passing judgment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 23:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cern restarts Large Hadron Collider with mission to make scientific history - High on the wishlist for discoveries are dark matter, the invisible material that appears to hang around galaxies and makes up more than 25% of the universe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 23:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu urged the United States on Sunday to seek a better deal to curb Iran's nuclear program and said he would press American lawmakers not to give Tehran "a free path to the bomb." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 23:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two journalists held by the Nigerian military since March 24 have been released, the network has confirmed. Ahmed Idris and Ali Mustapha were allowed to leave the Maiduguri hotel where they were detained </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 23:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis prayed for an end to the persecution of Christians in his Easter Sunday address, commemorating the students massacred by Islamist militants at Garissa University in Kenya. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 23:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 03:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The funny thing is that McConnell is married to a chinese woman, which was taboo in US society only a century earlier. If the nation allowed prejudices in any form, McConnell would still be single and without his daddy-in-law's money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 02:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference between Cali's drought and the snowy east coast is that the latter is a singular event that occurred this year while the former is a long-term ongoing event. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 02:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jesus was married to mary magdalene, even though it's not mentioned in the bible.  
  
reasoning: when the romans crucified someone, they did it by the book. this was especially true with jesus because his crucifixion was political in nature. one of the romans strictest rules was that only family could visit or collect the body after death. mm's inclusion into the viewing party at the tomb means she must have been married to jesus or the romans wouldn't have let her anywhere near him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 02:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you really believe a group of high-tech headhunters would turn out their pockets for a cash down payment to Ben Asshat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 02:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus, D. Vader doesn't age very well because in all his later fights scenes, he moves at the same speed that old people fuck at. Especially compared to his younger, more agile bad-ass self. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 02:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Blazing Saddles*  
 [the Johnsons load their guns and point them at Bart. Bart then points his own pistol at his head]  
  
Bart: [low voice] Hold it! Next man makes a move, the nigger gets it!  
  
Olson Johnson: Hold it, men. He's not bluffing.  
  
Dr. Sam Johnson: Listen to him, men. He's just crazy enough to do it!  
  
Bart: [low voice] Drop it! Or I swear I'll blow this nigger's head all over this town!  
  
Bart: [high-pitched voice] Oh, lo'dy, lo'd, he's desp'it! Do what he sayyyy, do what he sayyyy!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 02:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved this song as a kid and *Guardians of the Galaxy* reminded me about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 01:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No...it's a Stephen King short story originally titled Rita Hayworth and the Shawshank Redemption. In the book, Red's skin color isn't mentioned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 01:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I preferred the Eastwood cowboy over the J Wayne cowboy, but I'm sad that Eastwood became a right-wing asshole that supported Romney and talked to empty chairs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most destructive extreme weather events in the United States last year caused 65 human fatalities and $19 billion in damage, according to an analysis of federal government and insurance industry data released Thursday by the Center for American Progress. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 00:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Horrifying Blowback in Kenya - At the same time, al-Shabaab began recruiting youths in the slums of heavily Muslim Mombasa and elsewhere along the Kenyan Coast, staging retaliatory attacks which by now total well over 100. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 00:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Franciscos chief of police has moved to dismiss eight officers who allegedly sent and received racially charged and homophobic text messages that included references to lynchings, white power and burning crosses. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 23:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robert De Niro is ready for Hillary. The formidable actor and long-time Democrat has come out swinging in favor of the likely Democratic nominee for president in 2016, Hillary Rodham Clinton. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 23:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police say a New York City teenager has died after falling off the roof of a six-story Bronx building as police officers attempted an arrest. The New York Police Department says 17-year-old Hakeem Kuta succumbed Saturday to injuries from the fall Thursday night. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 23:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A series of anti-Islam rallies have been held across Australia, with police forced to intervene to separate protesters from rival, anti-racism demonstrators in the city of Melbourne. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 22:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
