<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1033</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 00:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is without question the right decision...

... but there is a tiny, Grinchy part of me that hates denying the American Right another chance to utterly humiliate themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 20:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is *explicitly* about US politics.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 20:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A fascinating interview with an expert on the "'Christian Identity' Movement." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Behind Dylann Roofs Race War: The Highly Motivated Secret White Supremacy Movement Working Toward the Battle of Armageddon: A Scholar of "Christian Identity" Militants Warns that Lone Wolf Killings like Charleston are Part of a Larger Plan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 20:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am a manufacturer of Confederate memorabilia, and the Free Market just spoke. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 05:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What am I to do now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 04:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that every time a bald eagle loses a feather, somewhere in America a gay biker ejaculates all over Chuck Norris' beard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 04:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really have to give the political consultants on Jindal's campaign credit for the timing of this announcement.

The victims of last week's church shooting aren't in the ground yet, the Confederate flag has captured the news cycle this week, and tomorrow is likely to see the release of the Supreme Court's rulings on gay marriage and the ACA. 

And, Jindal announces his run *after* the deadline for tonight's evening news.

Jindal's staff is either timing-impaired or *trying* to bury news of his announcement. What's your guess?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Louisiana's Jindal Joins Crowded 2016 Presidential Race </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 03:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 01:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Precisely. Example: the Kochs and prostate cancer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 01:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But anyone time someone says the word democracy around here, someone has to jump up and say "we're not a democracy, we're a republic". I honestly am not sure where that impulse is coming from

Fox News "journalists" and AM radio talk-show hosts have been pounding that talking point for years.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 00:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now we know why it's impossible to reason with TeaBots: they're so detached from reality that they can't be reached. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 00:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and yet he'll still wave the flag of the Plantation Owners that sent his great-great-grandpappy to die to protect their cotton profits.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 00:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like Ron Paul. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like another MONEYBOMB! stunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 22:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What race has the highest percentage of gun violence?

The poor.

Stop insisting on seeing things on race lines, and instead take a look in economic terms. The *poor* are the most likely to die from gun violence.

Follow this thought through and you'll realize who profits from promoting, exploiting, and continuing such divisions among the impoverished  and why they will give their all to perpetuate these divisions.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 22:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White Nationalists/Neo-Confederates/Would-Be Domestic Terrorists: *America is sick of your shit.* Turn back from your rage and hatred before you wind up like these two did.

[The Chilling Anti-Government, Cliven Bundy-Loving Facebook Posts of the Alleged Las Vegas Shooters:
Jerad and Amanda Miller's Facebook and YouTube likes included the NRA, Rand Paul, FreedomWorks, and other right-wing championsand videos justifying the killing of police officers.](http://www.motherjones.com/politics/2014/06/jerad-amanda-miller-las-vegas-shooting-cliven-bundy-anti-government) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 21:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another right-wing vulgarian reveals himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For your edification:

[Homegrown Radicals More Deadly Than Jihadis in U.S.](http://www.nytimes.com/2015/06/25/us/tally-of-attacks-in-us-challenges-perceptions-of-top-terror-threat.html)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why can't they do the right thing, today of all days? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jerry Falwell is spinning in the grave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confederate flag still flies as slain pastor to be honored at S.C. State House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meryl Streep takes crusade for women's rights to Capitol Hill: Actress Meryl Streep has mailed members of Congress a plea to pass the Equal Rights Amendment. Hollywood is helping to resurrect the issue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The G.O.P.s Ties to Extremism Go Beyond the Confederate Flag](http://www.newyorker.com/news/john-cassidy/the-g-o-p-s-extremism-problem-goes-beyond-the-confederate-flag?mbid=rss) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's precisely what the now-disgraced ProGun mods said 2+ years ago when they took over this subreddit and began banning users, content, and articles at personal whim based on their own biases: "This is at the request of the User Community."

Thankfully, that hellish era seems to be coming to an end, though some of the Mods that were hand-picked and installed during that reign of terror and error are still in place.

Forgive us if we are not quick to trust the motives of those who participated in that failed coup of right-wing extremists *against* the actual wishes of the "User Community." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Growing Right-Wing Terror Threat](http://www.nytimes.com/2015/06/16/opinion/the-other-terror-threat.html?ref=opinion _r=0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's getting harder and harder for the American Right to hide who they are and what they support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And thus women.

I really don't know how any woman (Texan or otherwise) can still bring themselves to vote Republican. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only because Texas Republicans care about the lives and health of women so much.

/S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 18:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Translation: "It's just another rule we made up with zero input from the user community." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Growing Right-Wing Terror Threat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 18:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Since Sept. 11, 2001, nearly twice as many people have been killed by white supremacists, antigovernment fanatics and other non-Muslim extremists than by radical Muslims" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 18:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 09:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like solid advice. The only thing I would add is some gold holdings.

Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 09:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet, there are no statues of Hitler in London, Paris, or Stalingrad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 08:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You're going to be very surprised in about a year.

Can you clue us in on what you've got planned?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 07:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similar to how Bob Barr and all the right-wingers ran around in the 1990s renaming everything after Ronald Reagan while they could still get away with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 07:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Britain got over it. The South hasn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 07:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he hated those Holstein race-mixers worst of all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 06:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your thoughts are intriguing.

Do you have any investment advice you'd be willing to share at this time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... to his front yard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, of course.

The complexities of the war get lost in heated internet arguments. I'm as guilty as anyone else. It remains the central event of American history and here we are, 150 years later, still working ourselves into a fury over it. Its shockwaves are still felt today.

Thank you for the brushback. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Murray Rothbard says it's not only ethical but morally justifiable to starve your children to death if you can't be arsed to feed them.

Do you have any inkling of how deep the hole of ***"LIBERTY!!11!!!"***^TM goes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 02:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The South's self-fueled paranoia triggered their own "Lost Cause" secession. It's ridiculous to argue otherwise.

It isn't Lincoln's fault the paranoid, greedy, traitorous, slaving cowards fled the Union at the direction of the Plantation Class and their representatives *months* before Lincoln was even sworn in. 

Confederate revisionists only need look in the mirror to find their source of all their woes, but they don't seem to have either the guts, brains, or humility to do so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 02:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Translation: "No, I cannot adequately rebut him." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 01:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baby steps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 01:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. It's the flag of sedition and treason against the United States. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 01:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, Scott ["I'll Do Whatever the Kochs Tell Me To Do"](http://www.salon.com/2011/02/23/koch_walker_call/) Walker promises "bold leadership." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 01:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, we know. People are fleeing California for the low-tax paradise of Brownback's Kansas. [eye roll]  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 01:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they were also traitors to the United States. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 01:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, you're the ultra-"Free Market" fantasist here. Can you adequate rebut him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 01:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The day that the Neo-Confederates' obsession with this bullshit ends will be the same day a white guy walks into a store and is told, "Fuck off, Whitey. We don't serve your kind here."

That will disabuse all of these "Liberty-Lovin'"^TM Confederate apologists of their "Free Market of Segregation" fantasies, posthaste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 01:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's another Neo-Confederate trying to cover his ass. What else would you expect?

The extremist American Right isn't going to get away with their horseshit anymore. They've been humored and pandered to for decades by Republicans, Right-Libertarians, and Confederate apologists.

No more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 01:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did the South make any effort to repay the federal government for all of the federal property they seized by worthless fiat?  Who violated the NAP?

Put that in your Ron Paul decoder ring.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 23:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is laddy formed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 23:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A profound ignorance of our nation's history is one of the defining characteristics of TeaPublicans and Republitarians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 23:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, pal. That's your monopoly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 23:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Chabanais" is an extremist right-wing troll who was once inexplicably elevated to Moderator on /r/politics by a previous Mod regime who are largely no longer here (though a few Mods from that dark of era of right-wing censorship of /r/politics content remain, and are as vociferous, unreasonable, and authoritarian as ever.)

He can usually be found over or /r/conservative ranting and raving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 23:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Rand's father and mentor Ron Paul certainly doesn't seem to think so.

[Ron Paul's "The South was Right!" speech.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xEC68vTQwP8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 23:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rand, like his father Ron Paul before him, takes great "LIBERTY!"TM with American history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Pauls First Two Books Are Full Of Fake Founding Fathers Quotes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 23:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 08:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Propagating the "Democrats/liberals are coming to take my guns" myth has won groups such as the NRA and its affiliates great fortunes.

*Nobody wants your damn guns. Have as many damn guns as you like. Hell, ask a liberal to the range.*

The more paranoid that the NRA/arms dealers/arms manufacturers can make their audience, the better for their each of their bottom lines. The greater the fear, the greater their profits.

It's astounding how successful they've been all these past decades with their false "CONFISCATION IS IMMINENT!" meme. That myth makes the NRA and Wayne LaPierre a lot of money.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 08:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *This message sponsored by Jeb! 2016* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 03:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dr. Ben Carson just went from *zero* chance of winning the GOP nomination to a *-10,000,000* chance of winning the GOP nomination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 03:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope Gary Johnson does an AMA about this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 03:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "He's not dead yet" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 03:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Germans had to be de-Nazified.

The South was never de-Confederatized. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 02:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could the be the beginning of the end of Richard Nixon's/the GOP's race-baiting ["Southern Strategy"?](http://rationalwiki.org/wiki/Southern_strategy)

It's lasted almost 50 years now and done incalculable damage to our nation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 01:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Koch Brothers' push, more like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 01:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "Free Market" has spoken! 

I'm sure the Republitarians will be thrilled! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 01:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Y'all-Qaeda and other Teahadists will not be pleased.

***GOOD!*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 01:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering that's where a great deal of it comes from, this is a very significant step. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 01:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Salon.com* (along with *Talking Points Memo*) have ***finally*** been released from the /r/politics list of sites that are auto-deleted upon submission as "Rehosted Content."

Conversation has begun as to the validity of the continuing ban on "MediaMatters.com" as "Rehosted Content."

None of these sites should have been blocked in the first place, and some still remain on the Automoderator's kill list from the days in which the "Rehosted Content" fiat was first issued. Still, this can be viewed as an encouraging development in the struggle to keep Reddit's content ***USER***-controlled and ***USER***-curated.

Here's to a more open discussion of Politics in this forum! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Rand Pauls Libertarian Hypocrisy Reveals about the GOPs Giant Race Problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 01:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 22:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean this sincerely: ***THANK YOU*** for the first positive, constructive response I've seen from the Mods in over two years now. 

Neither of those sites should ever have been censored in the first place. Hopefully, this is a sign of things to come.

Now, release MediaMatters too, please! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 21:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You absolutely have the power to remove *Salon.com* from the censorship list that was deliberately programmed into the Automoderator. The same applies to "Talking Points Memo" and "MediaMatters."

What's stopping the current Mods from recognizing right, as well as reality?

*Salon.com* is ***NOT*** "Rehosted Content."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 21:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why, then, is *Salon.com* auto-deleted as "Rehosted Content," when most of their articles are original content?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 21:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it leads to more subjective decisions on our part, which we try and limit as much as possible.

Then how do you explain the continued use of the "Off-Topic," "Not US Politics," and "Rehosted Content" lies which are still employed to censor completely valid content? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Small Govt = Big Business can screw you over and get away with it.

It's the Republitarians' dearest fantasy: "Whoever has the most money wins by default." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "But... but... the 'FREE MARKET!!1!1one!!'^TM " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps you're unfamiliar with the founding principle of Reddit: content is to be user-submitted and user-curated.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Help, help! I'm bein' repressed!](http://media.giphy.com/media/CbezwsaSQNilG/giphy.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "LIBERTY!"^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  if you think that if Rand Paul became president he would somehow make abortion illegal then you are not a rational human being.

if you think that if Rand Paul can be elected president then you are not a rational human being.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So why is a man condemned to parenthood but not the woman?

Are you aware that more women die in childbirth than from legal abortion? That's a fact that the self-dubbed "pro-life" crowd is always happy to ignore.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 19:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  People like him would rather there be no government over site and be able to do whatever they want. Including destroying whatever they see fit, as long as it brings them more money.

And that's what they call "LIBERTY!"^TM
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 19:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder what his passionate partisans in this subreddit think of this.

They'll probably try and find a way to blame it on "the j00s." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 19:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if Rand's good buddy [Jack "the Southern Avenger" Hunter](http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2013/07/09/rand-paul-staffer-southern-avenger/2502637/) helped him write it, as he did Rand's 2011's book *The Tea Party Comes to Washington*?

[Rand Paul Staffer Expressed Support for Lincoln Assassin](http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2013/07/09/rand-paul-staffer-southern-avenger/2502637/)

Or maybe Rand just plagiarized it, [as he's been caught doing before?](http://thecolbertreport.cc.com/videos/yxqllm/rand-paul-s-plagiarism-problem) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 19:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the people who whine about "federal overreach" think Cliven Bundy is a misunderstood hero rather than a bitter old racist crank.

Many of them are still fighting the Civil War in their heads (and worse, preparing as if a 'Second Civil War' were imminent.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 19:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never understood how/why people fall for the Pauls.

A great deal of their support comes from "The South was Right!!1!" fantasists, which certainly explains a lot.

Don't believe me? [Check out Ron Paul's famous "The South was Right" speech here.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xEC68vTQwP8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 08:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the White Nationalist/Neo-Confederate/Gunbertarian Downvote Militia acting out again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 08:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To his other pocket. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 08:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's getting harder and harder for the American Right to deny their foul allegiances and fetid ideologies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 08:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I don't like the Iraq War but I support our troops.

Did you put a yellow ribbon magnet on your SUV?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 08:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Denial is a bigger river than the Mississippi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 07:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That pack of losers gave a country with three times the manpower and industrial capacity a run for their money for four years.

At the cost of 740,000 American lives. That's more than have died in ALL of the military conflicts/wars that America has been involved in, before or since.

Don't expect any sympathy for the Confederate's Lost Cause, or some kind of honorary participation trophy for a useless war which was started by the South's Plantation Class using poor white sharecroppers as cannon fodder.

I don't get why the descendants of these Southern sharecroppers still celebrate their Southern oppressors. Maybe it's fun to play make-believe in order to convince themselves that all the death and suffering actually meant something.

The alternative to recognizing reality must be too heavy a cross to bear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 07:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that they've locked it in place shows they know it shouldn't be there at all.

They recognized this when they took it off the statehouse in the 2000s. But they had to be sneaky and stick it on a memorial instead. 

It's just Southern spitefulness in full bloom. That's why it will take a supermajority of 66% of both SC houses to take it down. They deliberately wrote this into law when they "compromised" by taking it off the dome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 06:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 740,000 in all, the latest scholarship shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 06:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> rekt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 06:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And did any of the Confederate states make any recompense to the federal government for all of the federal property they seized illegally, including Fort Sumter?

No, they didn't did they? The CSA just seized all federal properties for themselves via worthless declarations, didn't they?

Many Right-Libertarians and Confederate apologists make another religion out the "NAP," the "Non-Aggression Principle."

So, whose property rights were violated here first, exactly? And who was it, exactly, that initiated force in violation of these well-established property rights? Who violated the NAP?

These are questions that make Neo-Confederates *very* uncomfortable. Usually, eyes bulging, they'll start sweating and reddening before finally stuttering out a spittle-flicked "S-S-ST-ST-STATES' RAAAAGGGHTS!!11!1!" before storming off like petulant children who *still*, even after 150 years, refuse to acknowledge that they LOST the duel THEY initiated.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 05:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if Gene Wilder brings in his pets for checkups? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 04:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American Fundamentalist Evangelicals have a great disdain for Catholics.

And boy, are *they* going to be surprised on Judgment Day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 04:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe He meant, "S Words" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 03:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, a link to a Ron Paul affiliated site? Thanks for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 03:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ron Paul fans are crying into their pillows right about now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 02:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The unspoken, cut-to-the-bone truth about George Zimmerman's rabid defenders?

***They idolize him because he actually got to live out their secret "I Took Out a Thug" murder fantasy.***

Honest Zimmerman fans admit this; dishonest Zimmerman fans will lie to you about it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 00:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rich Southerners didn't care about white lives either. That's why the Plantation Owners and their Confederate government sent all the poor sharecroppers to die to defend their profits.

The Plantation Class was willing to send sharecropping whites to die to protect their black slaves, whose forced labor was the source of the all the Plantation Owners' cotton profits. 

Chew on that one, Sons of Dixie: the African slaves' lives meant more to the Plantation Owners than the poor white sharecropping class they sent to fight their battles for them. 

That's why it's so strange that the descendants of these same poor white sharecroppers sent to die still wave the flag of their own oppression at the hands of the 1% of their day, the Plantation Owners' Class. They even still fall for the "Southern Pride" and "Southern Heritage" lies that the Plantation Owners invented to justify the war for their Lost Cause. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 00:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the looney-Moonie paper. They cut publishing to a few days a week when the Church of Unification cut off most of their funding.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 23:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't you be much more comfortable over at Stormfront? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 23:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems than Mike "Defender of Duggar-Diddling" Huckabee and Rick "Man-on-Dog" Santorum have a lot in common.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 23:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> most of us down south have ancestors that fought for the Confederacy . . . I don't see how dishonoring their lives helps heal anything.

Your ancestors were already dishonored when the Plantation Owners sent them to die to preserve their profits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 22:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Flag of Treason against the United States, still favored by Neo-Confederates and the KKK, deserves to reside in the ashbin of history just like the fetid ideology that birthed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 21:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the Santorum Sidestep

Where dancers slip and fall.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 21:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Confederate/KKK flag should be coated in Santorum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 21:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is the Duggar-diddler defender also defending the Flag of Treason against the United States? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 21:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also the KKK's favored flag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 21:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if he uses his Dad Ron Paul's old racist newsletters as rolling papers?

They were rather blunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 20:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "He's not dead yet! He's getting better!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 20:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it odd how anything that addresses right-wing authoritarianism in this subreddit is quickly marked "Off-Topic" and pulled? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 20:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ford Prefect: for your own safety, please stay away from Los Angeles! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 20:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL apologists would justify the LAPD gunning down Ford Prefect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 19:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if we made them pay for the support of the children whose birth they force, they'd seek to *expand* abortion rather than ban it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 19:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The American Right needs to get over its fetus fetish.

Unfortunately, that fetish still brings them votes. Once it doesn't, and begins to *cost* them votes, the American Right's leadership will suddenly forget all about "honoring a 'Culture of Life.'"

They certainly couldn't give a crap about mother and child post-birth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 19:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If so, it seems that the "don't shoot an unarmed person in the head" policy is more open to interpretation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 19:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least since Nixon and the "Southern Strategy."

Perceptive Americans never fell for such deceit. Many others have and continue to, however. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 19:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confederate traitors, evidently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 19:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Birther Blake Farenthold is too far to the left for the Tea-Guzzlers?

Popcorn time!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 19:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unable to control the monster they created. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 18:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giggling while masturbating to the thought, most likely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 18:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the American Right will fight it at every step. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 18:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll probably be along the lines of their already stated "it was an attack on Christianity!!1!" meme-lie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 18:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Says Huckabee, defender of the Duggar-diddler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 18:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The American Right is quickly losing the power to conceal who they really are and what they really believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 18:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "14/88" crowd's newest hero. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dylann Roof Visited Slave Plantations, Confederate Landmarks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 18:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 18:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "But... but... they just want to protect women's health!"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 18:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess Ted's counting on receiving "the End Times Transfer of Wealth from the Wicked to the Righteous" that his father and other Christian  Nationalists have foreseen for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 18:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice how they handcuff the corpse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 18:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it odd how Republicans boast of themselves as "the Party of Lincoln," yet can't even bring themselves to condemn the Flag of Treason? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 18:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about Huckabee's support for the Duggar-diddler? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 18:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One who calls the Charleston Church shooting an "accident"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 17:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh-oh. 

This article is going to piss off Reddit's omnipresent Gunbertarian Downvote Militia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 09:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Were they wrong to feel under assault by Abraham Lincoln? No. Even Abraham Lincoln himself would admit that he forced that fight.

False. Most slave states seceded months before Lincoln was even sworn in.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 08:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. Someone's got to start calling America's regressive states out on their chicanery. 

Money's the one language politicians understand, especially right-wing politicians. They'll eventually to abandon their phony "we're social conservatives and God and Murica" vote-pandering bullshit when dollars, cents, and elections are on the line.

Hopefully we won't have to suffer the Christian Nationalists' delusions of self-superior morality and their accompanying dictates for much longer. America is finally ready to evolve out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 06:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. It's what they do. Must make them feel like big, strong Aryan warriors for a moment rather than acknowledge their own shallow, inescapable existences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
