<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9554</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 12:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only prohibited items they are capable of seizing are pocket knives people forget are in their pocket, and any other bs, not dangerous items.

If you can smuggle a bomb through 67 put of 70 times, the program is a waste </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 12:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Troll post? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 03:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> False report and u get banned? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 14:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It means you are still eating enough to maintain your bodyweight even with your activity level.

Count calories for a week, you might be surprised with what you see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 14:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah ok...... ignorant as hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 21:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tend to lose weight on cruises... I hardly eat much because there is so much to do and see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 12:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, let's just ignore everyone who goes to college, gets a degree for a career, and is fucked cause they can't get a jo b in that field.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A full-time minimum-wage job won't get you a 1-bedroom apartment anywhere in America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 23:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 12:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering they have 2 billion people or so, it is a very small percentage of their population. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 04:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imo you should have split it from 1-10, 10-15, 15-20, 20-25 etc ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 23:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That actually happened... were many news articles about it not too long ago.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 05:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys, it's a joke, not a dick. Stop taking it so hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 04:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait.... Beta is over? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Laffer Curve </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 22:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~SOE~~ DB has decided to dramatically increase the price of many weapons, some of which gave the new players a competitive position against high(er) BRs. TB went from 100 to 875 certs (although the raise could be justified)-- basically, almost all vehicle weapons were raised to 875 certs.

What would be the reason for such an increase? Money -- don't waste your time spewing bullshit and claiming it isn't. This is where the Laffer Curve comes in. DB didn't raise the station cash (or whatever the name of the currency is now) price for the weapons because it would mean that less people would purchase them, they simply raised the price of the certs, in hopes that new players would either rage-quit, or spend money on the weapons.


http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Laffer_curve


Smed, I would be tossing $100 bills at this game if it was well optimized, bugs that players reported were fixed within a week, and the game was focused around **TEAM** play, not solo play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 12:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stfu fanboi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 19:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The welfare system: fucking over those who work hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 04:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still no pics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 22:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you bother posting this.... The article layer admits that it is only a password to a workstation and is useless unless you are in the building. It also doesn't actually control anything... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 12:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Capitalism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 04:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keeping it is theft. Well, if you keep it but don't open it and give it back if hw comes looking for it, it is completely legal. Opening it, using it, selling it, etc is illegal because it is his property. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 03:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You made some good points. That is all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 23:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you are mocked for being fat, doesn't that make you wanna change it more? Actions have consequences, like I will prolly get downvoted by a bunch of butthurts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 21:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't the same. You won't have any modded servers wlth hundreds of random players to play with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 16:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the advice. To be quite honest, I am quite frustrated with the direction Minecraft is headed in at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minecraft needs a building update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 15:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Minecraft desperately needs and update to cater to the needs of builders. Minecraft has ignored the wishes of the players who love building and creativity, and many have stopped playing because of this.

1.) All building blocks must have a half slab and stair version of them. This is not only a very quick and easy addition to the game, it will put the game in a much better state than where it is right now. Imagine how much potential hay half-slabs and stairs will add to the game! 
2.) Vertical "stairs" and "half slabs" must be implemented. This is a long overdue feature that will allow players to be much more creative and add much detail to what they build. 

These two and simple additions to the game would bring back thousands of players who enjoyed building, and played Minecraft because of building. Mojang has ignored the minority of builders and has catered to the childish PvP centered barbarian majority. Minecraft has a lot of potential, please let builders build. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 03:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better sue the shit out of the accuser. It should be a criminal offense for false accusations  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 04:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only they put as much effort into working as they do in their ridiculous riots...

I am more inclined to write a large paycheck to my local PD for keeping me and the rest of my community safe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 14:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I see. Thanks for explaining it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 03:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find this very hard to believe... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 12:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he didn't hit his employer... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Principal was ordered to stop giving teachers "unnecessary paperwork" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 21:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 15:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we had any competition between ISPs they wouldn't have 1.2b to fund the skyscraper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 21:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought abortions not being reverseable was just common sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 21:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you lost fat and gained some muscle? Water weight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 22:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Religion has nothing to do with economic systems. /thread  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 13:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He brought up some good points about the energy use. Everyone goes and bugs an EV to be environmentally friendly however they don't realize all the electricity is being generated by fossil fuels anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 12:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're.....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
