<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4572</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 09:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well enough, were union so there's always the politics that I'm not fond of because of contract issues . But I Just go to work and do my best. You must be talking about Cash Carry. They are label sensitive and understandably so. But I dare anyone to try to keep a label on a frosty block of Western Family Ice cream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 09:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am Oldish (33) And you were allotted 8 characters back in the online gaming infancy days. In the early/mid 90's Microsoft had a server called IGZ (Internet Gaming Zone) that would launch you into a networked DOS promt from a chat box and the players would (Ex: cd/duke3d setup.exe/f4) and enter the games setup menu. Long story short, Its my initials MSD and 3D for my favorite game at the time. And thank you for the compliment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 08:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish, I don't have the sweet ginger tight curl military box cut though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 08:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scenario I described does not happen that often at all. its an error on the side of the Customer(Store) and the distributor (Dudes who re-sent Package) Unfortunately human error is inevitable, this scenario is a double whammy, kinda like a unicorn but for frozen food.  But oh my god I love plastic bags... I live in Multnomah county but work in Clackamas county... You know how hard it is to pick up dog poo with paper bags? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 07:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here](http://imgur.com/cBDPsyR) is me and my Frozen Foods issued freezer jacket for Unified Grocers Milwaukie Oregon. Coming up on 8 years employed. The handle bar stache is standard issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 04:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work in a Frozen food distribution warehouse, I have seen this before. What happens is the store leaves/forgets the product in an insulated [chest or tub](http://www.bonarplastics.com/Portals/0/Templates/images/PB30.jpg) and it sits in their storage with the pallets and what not for a week or more and the dry ice gets used up so it thaws. When the distributor comes to reclaim the chest or tub they throw it back on the refrigerated trailer and it refreezes. The frozen food warehouse employee assumes it's a return (Because its frozen still) and puts it back into the big freezer and then unfortunately it gets sent out to some sad unsuspecting store assuming the product is fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 01:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget the [salt and pepa](http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-yVjqDkwhF-Q/U0tNRUrUBWI/AAAAAAAAMbQ/pbCxVw_8vkE/s400/push-it-real-good-o.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 04:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they local jellybeans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 05:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks delicious! And a little like french toast Cookie Monster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 06:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FAT is not a disability you lazy fucks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 11:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to do thish ash well, but hishtorically it doesh not bode well for my karma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 09:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Plan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 06:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 07:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [video](http://youtu.be/4vTc88Govj4?t=2m7s) if you're interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 10:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Mara Wilson](http://www.celebritymeasurement.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/Mara-Wilson-hot.jpg) is actually pretty geeky hot now a days. (Shes 27), No pervy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 09:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Movember I think translates into Mustache November, Pre-dating No shave November. You're in your 30's like me huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 03:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, I used to hate cilantro with a passion. soapy flavor and all. But later in life I started to like it. I was curious why I hated it and now, buy it in bushels. I found several articles. [Here's one](http://www.nytimes.com/2010/04/14/dining/14curious.html?_r=0) that shed some light on as to why I like it now and didn't before. a slow introduction over time. and for some reason it doesn't even come close to reminding me of soap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 11:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, Its rare you see a newer car with an actual frame not all uni-body.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 11:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is your friend an Oregon resident? I have these at my home and they are big, quick and scary. I was talking to my father one time and thought I saw a mouse out of the corner of my eye... No, it was a big ass wolf spider! Nope de nope da fucking no! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 11:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of has an MGMT feel to it. I like it, Kind of catchy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 07:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Died by his bowl because he was hungry and waiting for food from those he relied on to take care of him.... The saddest thing I have seen in awhile. This brought a tear to my eye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 07:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (3 letter response) Yep! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 10:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this an Iphone thing? I don't get the whole opaque grey bar with white text over picture thingy. I have seen a lot of these lately. I'm poor and have an S4 and am not a gay, retarded, mongoloid sheep with Tourettes syndrome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 09:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 08:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 out of 50 of these fat scoot-about people has a medical condition that makes it so they have to use them. I am big (6'3 260), Part due to genes and part because I love good beer and meat. If I ever got to the point I was riding one of the electric scooters around WalMart with my giant swollen purple diabetic calves, I would re-examine my life choices. There is no excuse for laziness! Most of these Brobdingnagians Choose to be this way because its easier than working. Don't be lazy people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 09:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! Because she's a woman and women do dishes. This should be top comment. Have an upvote you witty sumbitch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 05:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks scary but you know it's delicious. Cant go wrong with pistachios.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 07:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the body of a fat guy who has improved his life by losing a bunch of weight. I can relate, 6'3", 375 senior year to 245 at 32. Congratulations to this dude. Excess skin can only be remedied by surgery unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 10:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They look like deliciously fattening deep fried kiwis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 10:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes Plain is perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 06:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sentiments exactly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 10:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone else gone through this experience? You're at a 7-11 or Plaid Pantry, the line is like 2 people long, you calmly take your place at the end (Curving because the aisles interfere) and someone walks to the other side of the curve and stands there with their delicious treats. For me it's 3 minutes of "Am I going to have to make an awkward situation by saying something?" And then their is the Dick fuck Busy business guy who grabs a paper and walks to the front of the line and throws the money down and raises the paper, shakes it and says keep the penny and walks out while you do the normal person thing and wait your turn. Or how about the fat disability lady who spends 12 minutes buying lottery tickets while 12 people wait behind her blobenly welfare recipient ass, she has nowhere to be, WE ALL DO! That's worse than cutting as far as I am concerned, Plus it's 8:30 and I have to be to work! Who buys lottery tickets at 8:30 in the morning!!! But yeah I hate cutters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 05:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like someone dates a black guy... Okay I'll leave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 10:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just as! Way more WTF than hot girl in pink goo/jewels.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 13:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back story? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 10:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I say we [pray](http://stream1.gifsoup.com/view4/1439296/mc-hammer-u-can-t-touch-this-o.gif). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 06:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm dumb! I thought it was A-Avon, and didn't get it. Then I read the comments. [Every time..... I'm so stupid!](http://www.quickmeme.com/img/1d/1d484e52ea232a8200caa49c64285b0b00e28e5fa7a0a045425215651d43d184.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 09:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you read all the links the others have posted its pretty easy to come to your conclusion. Not creepy... Cool and interesting with all the lore behind it, but not creepy. Very well done mannequin though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 11:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A [photo](http://www.classicalvalues.com/Schlitze2.jpg) from when she was younger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 11:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [Video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RSTeX3Ape1A) if anyone's interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 04:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy too! Ha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 09:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *SHITTY WARR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
