<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5170</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 18:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that the headline is misleading. I also agree with your proposal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Despite Obamacare, US Health System is Still a Complete Mess </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 19:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 20:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats--your weight loss is definitely noticeable! Great job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 20:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic! Congratulations, you are an inspiration! I need to study the keto board but just wondering what your goals are--you say 20 g of carbs on a 2000 cal/day diet. So those carbs are in the form of veggies, and the other 1900 cals are in the form of protein and fat? Do you have a goal for how many grams of each? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 20:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a great idea. I'm going to try it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 20:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations, I'm almost at my first five lost. While it's great to hear the inspirational stories of people who have lost 100+ pounds, to me as a newbie, seeing a post about reaching those early milestones is really helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 20:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an accomplishment! Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 20:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great! I've got a bunch of "thin" or at least "thinner" clothes I'd love to be able to fit into! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The nightmare Ebola scenario that keeps scientists up at night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 20:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 18:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree completely. I think there was a power struggle between conservative and liberal mods, and somehow the conservatives managed to ban several liberal-leaning publications with the very shaky rationales you cite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Send President Obama Ebola as Birthday Gift, Some Israelis Say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 18:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Reddit Have a Transparency Problem? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 04:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GAO report: Voter ID laws stunted turnout </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 04:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 06:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is great, congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 06:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gosh, that is great! Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ebola in Europe: What Went Wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 06:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 15:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 43 Missing Students, a Mass Grave and a Suspect: Mexicos Police </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 01:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal Court Strikes Down One Of The Most Aggressive Gerrymanders In The Country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 01:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Epidemiologist: Stop the Flights Now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 01:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Ebola experts worry virus may spread more easily than assumed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 01:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boehner's Blank GOP Jobs Plan Tweet Leads To Epic Trolling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 00:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Cotton: ISIL Working With Mexican Drug Cartels To Attack Arkansas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 00:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 09:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic! Congratulations, and thanks for sharing your story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans Are Playing Dirty Tricks to Worsen Democrats' Midterm-Voter Problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 07:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those Secret NYC Phone Booth Devices Are Getting Evicted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 07:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Really Small Slice of Americans Get to Decide Who Will Rule the Senate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 07:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYC Phone Booths May Be Tracking Your Cell Phone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 18:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 18:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the GOP hates U.S. history: Inconvenient truths that freak out American conservatives The right is losing its mind over new testing standards that aren't "patriotic" enough. Time for a history lesson! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 20:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 19:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very impressive -- congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 19:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay! congratulations! I've yet to reach my first 5 and can't wait for those lairs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 19:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! I can't wait to add that -5 flair! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 19:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations, you handled things so well! And you are right, emotional eating makes you feel good for about 30 seconds and bad all day and then some. I admire the way you are coping-hang in there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 19:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you buy your lunch at school and get at least one healthy meal there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 19:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What Knutes said. Congratulations, you should be so proud of all you've accomplished and continue to accomplish, and thank you so much for taking the time to share and inspire us all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 19:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree -always cute but now add the heat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 19:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for your reply. It's very helpful. The issue of sleep is especially interesting. I've always been a night owl and now at age 60 it's gotten pretty dysfunctional -- I'm usually sleep-deprived. I've read that regular sleep habits, and adequate sleep, are important to dieting, but changing my sleep habits has been difficult. If I go to bed early I just wake up every 90 minutes. I think I'm going to need to tire myself out with more exercise and then walk bedtime back gradually.

Also glad to hear that diet is 80% of the weight-loss equation because I've let my diet plan get derailed on days I can't exercise, like "why bother, I can't get on the treadmill today so I've already blown it."

Lastly, glad to hear your endorsement of MFP and low-carb. I've tried weight watchers online  but I don't think it's a good fit for me because I like to get the calorie and nutritional info. I think calorie counting is a better fit for me. I like carbs so I'm going to need to watch them.

I'm trying to do a serious diet and lose 50 pounds. I'm 5'6" and 200, got up there gradually over the years, topped out at 211 six years ago, have made half-hearted and inconsistent efforts since then. My weight as a young person was low 120s  but I'd be happy with 150 as a goal for now.

Thank you again for your response -- you are very kind and a great example!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 18:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does she have a master's degree in library science? And how about you share with us what those agents were looking for? It's obviously no big secret if they shared it with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 10:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fantastic! I've got a bunch of thin clothes in my basement I'd love to be able to get into at some point! Thank you for sharing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 10:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think 50 in four months is a fantastic pace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 10:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! I'd love to hear what you did, both diet and exercise-wise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 10:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is fantastic. What was your activity goal? I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 09:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, not so much. The hospital has backtracked on blaming the software:

http://www.nytimes.com/2014/10/04/us/containing-ebola-cdc-troops-west-africa.html

Looks like a case of attempted CYA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 09:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great way to support your local library. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 09:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @purplepooters -- I am a librarian. i work with these systems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 09:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @fucktheecrunch -- At most libraries it's possible for patrons to establish accounts with a login and password beyond their library card number. Patrons can use those accounts to compile booklists of items they'd like to read, to do an interlibrary loan or a hold request electronically, etc. I don't think those accounts would be likely to retain a title after the book was checkout out, but perhaps in some systems they can. Since the patron controls the login, privacy would be maintained, I suppose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 09:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @EuropeanLady -- Yes, that is an unfortunate result of the privacy policy. It seems to me to be the lesser of two evils. Patrons can always keep their own lists of items borrowed, or save the date due reminder slips most libraries print out, which have the titles of the books on them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 09:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @pedrobeara-- if what you are saying is true, your wife is in violation of her professional code of ethics -- I assume she has an MLS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 05:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @Razed -- The circ systems and their servers are pretty secure, contained closed systems. Like an intranet, really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 05:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @fuck_theecrunch -- Not true. I'm a librarian, and every library system I've had experience with automatically deletes the patron's information when the borrowed material is returned. There is no way to retrieve that information. There is no list of what people check out that individual librarians can use or disable. You say that some libraries can override this system and keep the records, but deletion is always the default setup and I've never encountered a library that overrode that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 05:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @Jaydea -- Yes, libraries had to deal with this stuff back in the McCarthy era, and in the 60s as well. The patron privacy policy is longstanding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 05:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @jonnypadams -- In many libraries, you can get Netflix-style recommendations based on your search of the catalogue. It does not depend on what you check out, but what you search for (with no record kept).Try it sometime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 05:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @purplepooters -- Library systems are designed to delete once and for all. They have dedicated servers and tight networks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 05:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @pedrobeara -- Do you work at a library? I do, and you are lying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 05:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @That's the whole point of the articles. Identifying info is deleted from the computers when the materials are returned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 05:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @imadetheinternet -- Why would they take your computers? it was about civil liberties. If you were a librarian, you should be familiar with the Library Code of Ethics:
http://www.ala.org/advocacy/proethics/codeofethics/codeethics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 05:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @fleker2 -- A good librarian can make suggestions based on the preferences you tell her, and many library catalogues have suggested books based on your catalog searches (not your check-outs, just the kind of stuff you are searching for, with no record kept of your search).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 04:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @dagobahh -- I think those cards just had the dates stamped on it if it was a public library. Most "sign-out" library slips were used at elementary school libraries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 04:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @rundmcarlson -- Yes, the terrorists are all flocking to the library. They all have cards.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 04:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @Comeonyouidiots -- You can check out library ebooks from home and read them on your computer or mobile device, instead of contributing to Jeff Bezos. You can also access various proprietary research tools and databases from home, also on that little old computer you seem so proud of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 04:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @big_giant_turd -- Public computers at a library are scrubbed nightly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 04:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @Col Volkov -- Libraries are funded mostly by local property taxes with maybe a very occasional federal grant. Library policy dictates that when materials are returned, the identity of the borrower is deleted. 

Your fun facts are lies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 04:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @toychristoper -- Stop spreading misinformation. Records are deleted to protect patrons' privacy, NOT to save server space. Where do you get that? It is completely untrue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 04:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @Tidec -- You can get the same info from a survey. Also, libraries keep records of the number of times items are checked out, just not who checks them out, so you could draw some conclusions by comparing the checkout rates of various items with the publicly available census info on the demographics of the community, or before and after a historical event, etc. A historian can do plenty of research with conventional historical methods, without prying into the identities, incomes, etc., of library users. An actual historian would know that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 04:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @UltraeVires -- Actually the government was quite interested in a  lot of innocent people in the McCarthy era, and the Snowden revelations show that they still have quite an interest in collecting info on people who turn out not to be threats in any way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 04:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @GannamStylingOnYou -- Unless you're thinking of the stamp with names that appears inside the cover of many school textbooks, if that's really the case, your library was violating the professional ethics of the profession. Way back in the day there used to be slips with due dates, but I've never heard of one with names.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 04:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @aleister -- Donate to your local library's Friends of the Library group, or buy some treats to send over to your local library's staff as a thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 04:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @toychristopher --No, you are wrong. Records are destroyed to protect library users' privacy. I am a librarian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 18:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great job! Now you're paying it forward by inspiring me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michigan Democrat Claims GOP Distributed His Sick Moms Number </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 01:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 15:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations, you are doing a tremendous job --you're an inspiration! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 08:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @dinosaurdinosrawr -- Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reporting on Ebola: First rule is you dont touch anyone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 03:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> College Republicans Dumb Down Voting So Young Women Can Understand It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 21:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> College Republicans Dumb Down Voting So Young Women Can Understand It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 21:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 07:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to finally get serious and lose weight. I'm a 5'6" 60-year-old female who has been gradually gaining weight from my late 30s onward, finally getting into the 200s in the past ten years or so, topped out at 211 about eight years ago, now 201. I'd be thrilled if I could get to 150. 

My goals are to count calories every day with MFP and to get exercise daily. Do people set number goals, in terms of pounds lost per month? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 06:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is so impressive! Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ferguson demands high fees to turn over city files </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 06:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 21:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gosh, you look fantastic! Congratulations! You inspire me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Costs Can Go Up Fast When E.R. Is in Network but the Doctors Are Not </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 20:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uber Used Private Location Data for Party Amusement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 20:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 19:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @Pudums -- No, no, you didn't come off that way. Invisibility is an issue you don't really think about until you experience it. The male gaze can be objectifying rather than flattering but it's something we become accustomed to and we notice when it's lacking. And there is nothing wrong with enjoying the fact that you're visible again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 18:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I'm new here, have lost about five pounds through half-assed off and on efforts in the past couple of months. This may be what I need to get me going. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Voting Wars Heat Up: Will the Supreme Court allow states to restrict voting for partisan advantage? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 18:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 05:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @niamhd--Really nice post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 04:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to see your post, and all the comments in response. My weight gain has been gradual over the past 10 years or so, and coincides with my going from 50 to 60 years old. I know I'm invisible, figured it was a combo of the weight and the aging. I'm actually happy to see it's not all just paranoia in my head and is an actual thing! 

Congrats on your progress! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 04:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations -- I long to be where you are!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Cotton Is Now the Perfect Republican </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 02:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 19:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fantastic advice. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 19:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe start with $5 then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 06:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with allieneeds oats above. You are 22 and working. Can you ask your mom if you can keep out even $10 per week to buy yourself some veggies etc?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 06:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree--you are young and your skin is still very elastic. I don't think your goal--40 lbs on a 6'5" frame -- will make your skin saggy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Is This Mother in Prison for Helping Her Daughter Get an Abortion? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 05:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder: Abortion Restrictions Ruin Womens Lives </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 03:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which American State Should Secede? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 15:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Ryan Declares War Against Math </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 15:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Disavows ALEC: They Are 'Literally Lying' About Climate Change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 23:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 07:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats on the weight loss. Re your question: from your photo, you look young. In my opinion, weight loss comes faster when you're young. Since I've gotten older I've found it is slower going. Now there's some motivation to keep those pounds off! Great job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Surgery, Surprise $117,000 Medical Bill From Doctor He Didnt Know </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 05:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 07:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arizona GOPer: Women On Welfare Should Be Sterilized </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 18:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Cruz-Backed GOPer Wouldn't Say Whether She's On Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 18:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 02:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @Bartleby1955 -- Obviously it's worse, or it wouldn't be noteworthy. Here are the NFL's figures, quoted in the New York Times:

"The N.F.L.s actuaries assumed that 28 percent of all players would be found to have one of the compensable diseases and that the league would pay out $900 million to them. Their calculations showed that players younger than 50 had an 0.8 percent chance of developing Alzheimers or dementia, compared with less than 0.1 percent for the general population. For players ages 50 to 54, the rate was 1.4 percent, compared with less than 0.1 percent for the general population. The gap between the players and the general population grows wider with increasing age." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 06:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @ghost27 -- I think that is great advice. I've been derailed so many times by my compulsive perfectionism, trying to eat only diet food and exercise every single day right from the start. I've recently come to realize that the all-or-nothing approach is sabotaging me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP Senate's first 100 days: Authorizing the Keystone XL oil pipeline, approving fast-track trade authority, wiping out proposed environmental regulations and repealing the medical device tax top their list. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 01:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here Is a Guy Who Put His Head Under a Womans Skirt and Then Pushed Her Down Some Stairs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 22:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 30 Percent of NFL Players Will Get Dementia, According to the NFL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 22:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 20:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @Phredex -- http://www.salon.com/2014/09/12/its_disgusting_and_its_still_about_race_southern_republicans_simply_dont_want_minorities_to_vote/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP Senate Nom Attended Recent Event Hosted By Sandy Hook Truther </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 20:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Running Scared: Georgias Democrats have registered more than 85,000 minority voters (and counting). Republicans never saw it coming. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 04:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sarah Lawrence Student Says Catfishs Nev Schulman Punched Her Repeatedly in the Head in 2006 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 20:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats Shouldn't Seek Revenge for Republican Redistricting. They Should Offer This Deal Instead. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 07:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Foreign Powers Buy Influence at Think Tanks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 08:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats Just Put a GOP Senate Seat in JeopardyAnd Republicans Want to Suppress the Vote to Save It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 23:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 23:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The r/politics mods removed my previous post on this, which was from TPM. Let's see what they do with this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservative Blogger Erick Erickson: Minimum Wage Workers in Their 30s Failed at Life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 23:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Illinois Conservative Activist: Children Should Read Books About Their Same-Sex Parents Dying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 23:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Erick Erickson: If You're Earning Minimum Wage In Your 30s, You 'Failed At Life' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 18:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Armed Border Militia Mistakenly Confronts Group Of Bat Conservationists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 01:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wyoming State Bar Apologizes For Publishing Cheney Bio Bashing Obama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 01:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stop Saying "Officer-Involved Shootings" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 06:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Years of Rape and Utter Contempt in Britain Life in an English Town Where Abuse of Young Girls Flourished </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 05:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Years of Rape and Utter Contempt in Britain Life in an English Town Where Abuse of Young Girls Flourished </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 05:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 7 Times The Supreme Court Has Relied On Sketchy 'Facts' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 04:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ways to Reduce the Kidney Shortage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 08:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VIDEO: Journalist Roughed Up And Removed From Georgia GOP Event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 07:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VIDEO: Journalist Roughed Up And Removed From Georgia GOP Event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 07:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Uber must be stopped The touted start-up is proving to be the embodiment of unrestrained hyper-capitalism. What happens when it wins? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 05:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 19:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @SayYouDo-- A trained professional police officer should do a better job of handling a crowd than "most people."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 19:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @AndroidHelp--That is how the word appeared in the original headline and it is r\Politics First Commandment that headlines must not be altered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least 6 Ferguson officers apart from Brown shooter have been named in lawsuits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 19:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Officer Go F*ck Yourself Out of a Job After Pointing Gun at Ferguson Protesters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 18:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I'm Not Your Brother," Says Officer Tasering Black Minnesota Man in Front of His Children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 18:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-College President: Women Should Drink Less To Stop Men Who 'Misbehave' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 06:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 04:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @ThomasJefferdaughter -- It is about politics in that it is relevant to the discussion of how the political process should deal with institutional racism and the militarization of local police force.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
