<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6670</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girlfriend made a cake for her moms bday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 18:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 21:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "lawl" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shrimp and langostino macaroni with white wine cream sauce </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 04:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First time smoking a chicken </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 00:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 09:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want this to be the case :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He's mad about his new diet regime </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 22:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The moment my cat realized he was obese </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 22:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend had a plate too. This is just half the steak (it was a 17oz cut) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I highly recommend trying it. It has changed meat for me completely. There are tons of diy ways but I just bought a sous vide machine made by anova culinary: http://anovaculinary.com/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow you're right it does look way better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 01:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> here's another dish I posted a while back... I think you may like the plating a little more

http://i.imgur.com/9XOx56o.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 20:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha i could have plated it better... it was late and I was starving and just wanted to eat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 20:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you go:

Seasoned the steak with salt and pepper. Sous Vide with 1 tablespoon butter at 131F for 90 mins, then seared it for 1 minute per side on a really hot grill

Boiled red potatoes, mashed with 10 cloves roasted garlic, salt, pepper, butter, and milk until you reach your desired consistency. I even added the leftover juice from the sous vide bag :)

Zucchini and asparagus were seasoned with salt, pepper, paprika, cayenne, garlic powder, and olive oil. Throw them on a hot grill for about 5-10 minutes, flipping occasionally.

Broccoli rabe was blanched for 1 minute, then sauteed with roasted garlic, salt, pepper, and olive oil. It was my first time trying it, I didn't really like it (tasted kinda like horseradish) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 19:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ribeye has always been my favorite. I actually enjoy the fattiness haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ribeye, garlic mashed potatoes, grilled asparagus and zucchini, and sauted brocolli rabe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 16:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 17:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I couldn't justify the extra $100 for an illuminated reticle. I'll probably never be shooting in low light situations  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 01:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glass is crystal clear, eye relief is about 4 inches I think. Awesome scope tho, highly recommended. It's just enormous, almost 16" with the sunshade on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 17:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The varmint models come with the 26" heavy barrel. I looked at the Magpul stock too, seems way economical specially since you can add the detachable magazine for not much more money. I just didn't want to wait :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 23:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's always great news, haha.

For now I'm just shooting Federal Gold Medal Match 168gr factory ammo. Once I become more comfortable I may start handloading, but I doubt it'd give me any advantage just yet since I'm still learning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 21:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remington 700 SPS Varmint chambered in 308.

I upgraded the stock to a Bell and Carlson Medalist Tactical/Varmint Style 2. Didn't really like the X-mark pro trigger so I swapped it out with a Timney 512. 

Optic is a Vortex Viper HS-T 6-24x50 SFP with milrad reticle. The mount is a Nightforce one-piece direct mount, 20 MOA.

Lastly is the Harris bipod, 9-13 inch. 

This is my first bolt-action and I'm looking forward to getting to know it and shooting a bunch to work on my accuracy. It will mainly only be used as a target gun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Remington 700 SPS Varmint </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 21:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 05:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree, I love that show! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 19:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your poems never disappoint!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 08:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 01:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys are correct... these are udon noodles. Sorry for the mixup  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perfect weather for some ramen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 18:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 21:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except the vast majority of these kids were Muslim... The motive for this attack wasn't over religious extremism but for retaliation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 18:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.azcentral.com/story/news/local/arizona/2014/11/11/mammoth-az-target-of-internet-hoax/18863451/

Good job, reddit... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
