<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5173</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a realistic problem for everyone. Hopefully we can all realize it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry to know this. But I hope you can realize your dream soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are so lucky to have this happy life. I believe that this is the dream of all people but very few of them can realize this dream. So you are lucky! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And people's mutual understanding will lead to the solutions of war, famine and other damages. In fact, if people can think more for others, it is not hard to realize this dream.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a pretty cool dream!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a beautiful dream and good luck to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you can choose one of your dreams to come true, what will you choose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One may have different dreams in different aspects and you must have the one that you really want to realize. What's that dream in your mind?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will you watch sitcoms in you spare time? Can you recommend some great sitcoms to us? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 04:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 04:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People seem to be crazy about this. But the one who is successfully picked by the director will be the luckiest one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 04:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing!! I would like to have the same design in my apartment!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 04:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It may seem crazy but I have to say I'm willing to have the same kind of life! It's for freedom! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 04:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh! Sometimes not very tall can be very active and agility. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 04:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, it's a little bit annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 04:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many friends of mine love this movie, too. they all think it excellent! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? I think word of mouth is the best way for a thing to be accepted by people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
