<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2843</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a number one, and it felt really good to eat because I hit my goal weight a while ago. I usually carb load once a week anyways now. I wore the one white shirt I had. It's a little tight tank top that I haven't worn for years. I felt great and I think I looked great too with my little leather cow ears. Ha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 00:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fresh caprese salad. Fresh tomato, basil, mozzarella, cracked pepper and a drizzle of olive oil on top.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 00:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG IT'S PIKACHU DRESSED AS TOTORO!!!!!!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone find out how tall he is? I've searched for a while now but I can't find anything. I'm thinking he looks like he's about 5'5"-5'8".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dug*...I'm sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only ever had one carb binge dream, and went I woke up I felt sick. I'd eaten and entire meat lover's pizza, three hotdogs with a bun, and a bunch of cookies. So glad it was a dream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is probably the most beautiful tourmaline specimen I've ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have some awesome tools. Thank you for sharing this!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 22:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sure is! Good eye! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is super cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just got this amazing kit from my husband for my birthday, and I made my first project with them. I love tomatoes! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic! Might I add, you have the 'smolder' down pat. Ha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAAAAAMN! That's impressive! And I agree with everyone else, the beard should go. You look awesome! Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do want!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband bought me a super awesome flashlight. I strap it to my belt at night when I run. I leave the light on so cars can see me. It also has a strobe feature that comes in handy for self defense situations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 03:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw, he's waving! Hi Satan!!! :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow, hi! Haha! That sounds like so much work. I haven't shaved my legs in a week (but my leg hair is super fine and blonde too, so it's really hard to see) because I have super sensitive skin and I tend to break out. I tried the veet strips and had welts for over a week. I've never used an epilator before, it sounds painful. 

Anyways, you look amazing and thank you so much for responding to me and for the kind words! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how puppies wiggle when they're really really happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how ridiculously derpy and happy they all look.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 21:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes me sad to know it will get smashed up. Looks like you put a lot of work into it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
