<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1094</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homosexuality "not un-African": report undermines anti-gay laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 17:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our brains become racist when processing ethnicity and accents, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 17:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bioenergy can deliver cleaner future, says global report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 16:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deaths by drug overdose have been on the rise in the US, with a majority of states recording increases from 2009 to 2013. Across the US, 44,000 people died from drug overdoses in 2013, more than double the number in 1999. Nearly 52 percent of the deaths were related to prescription drugs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 16:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Crazy' Kenyan grannies use tricks to save themselves from rape: Across Nairobi, more than 200 elderly women, aged up to 105, are learning self defence to protect themselves against rape, which is widespread in Kenya, particularly in its slums. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 16:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Particle Weirdness Shows Physics Is Right About Being Wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 16:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DuckDuckGo traffic soars in wake of Snowden revelations: Founder of privacy-focused search engine says company can build on audience  and takes a swipe at Google </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 16:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 19 maps and charts that explain pretty much everything about coffee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 15:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany accuses Putin of Cold War reflexes after Moscow beefs up nuclear arsenal "the old reflexes from this time are evidently more alive than what we thought up until last year. I can only warn against giving in to such reflexes and entering into a rapid spiral of escalation of words   then acts" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 15:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kasparov Says Putin Playing Poker, Not Chess "If Russia does not return to the status quo -- before 2014 [before the annexation of Crimea] -- there should be no talk of lifting sanctions, or of warmer relations," Kasparov said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 15:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The women seeking rich older men to pay their university fees: It's been euphemistically referred to as "mutually beneficial, transactional dating" but is the growing world of "sugar daddy" relationships just a sanitised term for sex work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 15:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Experts at a top fertility conference are dismayed at the case of a German woman who after having 13 children has had IVF quadruplets at the age of 65. The episode damages the reputation of in-vitro fertilisation (IVF), which has enabled millions to know the joy of parenthood, they said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 14:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The super materials that could trump graphene </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 14:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps festival of narcissism "Trump is the Frankenstein monster created by our campaign-finance system in which money trumps all. The Supreme Court has equated money with free speech ..., which means the more money you have, the more speech you get. " </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 13:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A radical idea for saving FIFA from itself "federations should become public trusts in which the fans have a voting interest, rather than state-sanctioned monopolies." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 13:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists discover the self-repairing mechanism behind a jellyfishs stunning symmetry "While it took just a few hours for the wounds to heal, the jellyfish didn't create new cells. But two to four days later they were once again symmetrical." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 13:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United Nations annual appeal for international aid has risen 500% in 10 years due to the new norm of multiple humanitarian crises. Only 26% of the money needed has been committed, according to a report published last night. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 12:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greece's central bank has warned for the first time that the country could be on a "painful course" towards default and exit from the eurozone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 12:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] The worlds first spacecraft thruster with a platinum combustion chamber and nozzle made by 3D printing has passed its baptism of fire with a series of firings lasting more than an hour and 618 ignitions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 11:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ahead of pope's climate message, U.S. Catholics split on cause of global warming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have built devices that harness changes in atmospheric humidity to generate small amounts of electricity, lift tiny weights, and even power a toy car. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2015/150616/ncomms8399/full/ncomms8399.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An international team of researchers has discovered traces of methane in Martian meteorites, a possible clue in the search for life on the Red Planet. The discovery hints at the possibility that methane could be used as a food source by rudimentary forms of life beneath the Martian surface. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexican researchers decode name on Mayan King Pakal's tomb: More than 60 years after the crypt was discovered, researchers have revealed its name as The House of the Nine Sharpened Spears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dying white blood cells have been captured on film for the first time, showing them alerting their neighbouring cells to their plight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 17:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 17:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2015/150616/ncomms8414/full/ncomms8414.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A major international study finds that surprisingly few bee species are responsible for pollinating the worlds crops. The study suggests that only two percent of wild bee species pollinate 80 percent of bee-pollinated crops worldwide. The study is one of the largest on bee pollination to date. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 17:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Half of the worlds new power capacity came from renewables last year, with China leading the way </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 17:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have observed, in metals for the first time, transient excitons  the primary response of free electrons to light. Detecting excitons in metals could provide clues on how light is turned into energy in solar cells and plants. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 16:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The new drug that causes users to rip off their clothes and attack with super-human strength I dont know that weve ever had anything thats been imported into Florida thats been more dangerous, Broward Sheriff Scott Israel said. Sometimes it takes five or six deputies to subdue a person." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 16:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tim Hunt should not have quit over 'sexist' remarks - Brian Cox "To have a Nobel prize winner and by all accounts a great scientist and a good person being hounded out of a position at UCL, after all those years of good work in science, I think that's wrong and disproportionate." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 15:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greek Prime Minister Alexis Tsipras charged Tuesday the IMF had "criminal responsibility" for Greece's debt crisis ..."The fixation on cuts... is most likely part of a political plan... to humiliate an entire people that has suffered in the past five years through no fault of its own," </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 15:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A group of researchers from Bristol University has created a prototype artificial skin that can mimic nature's very own master of camouflage, the squid, paving the way for smart materials of the future. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 15:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany reports first death from MERS virus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 14:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syrian doctors to present US with evidence of Assads use of chemical weapons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 14:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Single-celled creature hunts with its complex eye like a sniper: It is perhaps the most extraordinary eye in the living world  so extraordinary that no one believed the biologist who first described it more than a century ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 14:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israeli archaeologists have discovered a rare 3,000-year-old inscription of a name mentioned in the Bible. They said Tuesday it is the first time the name was discovered in an ancient inscription. It is one of only four inscriptions discovered from the biblical 10th century B.C. Kingdom of Judah </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 14:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia will add 40 ballistic missiles to nuclear arsenal in 2015 - Putin: "More than 40 new intercontinental ballistic missiles able to overcome even the most technically advanced anti-missile defence systems will be added to the make-up of the nuclear arsenal this year," </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 13:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The military strategy behind IS conquests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 13:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The world's tallest peak, Mount Everest, moved three centimetres (1.2 inches) to the southwest because of the Nepal earthquake that devastated the country in April, Chinese state media reported Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 13:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eating a moderate amount of chocolate a day has been linked to a lowered risk of heart disease and stroke. Scientists concluded that compared to those who ate no chocolate, those who ate up to a small bar a day had an 11% lesser risk of cardiovascular disease and a 23% reduced risk of stroke. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 10:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British Prime Minister David Cameron has performed a U-turn and ruled out holding a European Union membership referendum on May 5, 2016, a shift to placate some of his own lawmakers who were opposed to it being held on the same day as local elections. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 10:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legal Highs: Welcome to the Cannabis Revolution: A new consensus is emerging that bans on cannabis are counterproductive. Across the world, countries are legalizing its use for pleasure and medical treatment -- but Germany still lags behind. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 18:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk to students: Build me a pod so we can travel through tubes near the speed of sound </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 18:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A species of spider previously thought to have been wiped out in the UK has been spotted for the first time in over 100 years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 18:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://www.nature.com/nnano/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nnano.2015.118.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have demonstratedfor the first timean on-chip visible light source using graphene, an atomically thin and perfectly crystalline form of carbon, as a filament. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In three weeks, being gay won't be a crime anymore in Mozambique </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All 28 member states of the Council of the European Union have to agreed to new European data protection laws that could see tough new regulations unified across the whole of the EU. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 16:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vatican to hold first trial of senior cleric for paedophilia: A former papal ambassador to the Dominican Republic will be tried for paedophilia next month in the first case of its kind to be brought before a Vatican court. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 14:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The world is off course to prevent two degrees C of warming, says energy agency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 14:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man behind Darpa's robotics challenge: robots will soon learn from each other </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 15:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC's Brian Cox: Scientists arent priests of knowledge. Theyre like plumbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 14:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "In Berlin fresh rules for billboard ads showing both adult women and men, females cannot be depicted as 'hysterical,' 'stupid' or 'naive' alongside men presented as 'technically skilled,' 'strong' or 'business savvy.' Adult women must not be shown 'occupied in the household with pleasure.'" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 14:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least 400 million people lack access to essential health services, the World Health Organization and World Bank said Friday in a new report that they described as a wake-up call about the challenges to achieving universal health coverage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 14:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The European Space Agency says its comet lander, Philae, has woken up and contacted Earth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Austrian brothel is offering customers free sex in a summer-long protest over what its owner sees as punitive tax payments. "We are not paying taxes any more. Effective immediately: Free Entrance! Free Drinks! Free Sex!" the Pascha establishment in Salzburg posted on its website. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tiny origami robot self-folds, walks and recycles itself: Made by scientists at Massachusetts Institute of Technology, a 1.7-centimetre-long origami robot made of plastic and containing a magnet can be "programmed" by an external magnetic field. [+video] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 16:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Europe Backs Plan for U.S. to Loosen Control of Internet: The European Council, representing 28 governments, Friday backed that notion, as long as Internet governance is kept free of capture by narrow commercial or government interests. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 15:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [All Spoilers] The most memorable Game of Thrones characters: Researchers from MITs Computer Science and Artificial Intelligence Lab have crunched the numbers on GOT characters using a special algorithm they developed that can predict how memorable a Game of Thrones image will be. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 15:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The FECs cry for help Candidates are interacting with outside spending groups in ways that defy any rational definition of what coordination   independence mean. And here at the FEC we couldnt even find agreement that foreign pornographers shouldnt be spending money to influence American voters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 15:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Humpback whales exhausted as food sources depleted due to climate change, researcher says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 14:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Explosive intervention by Pope Francis set to transform climate change debate: The most anticipated papal letter for decades will be published in five languages on Thursday. It will call for an end to the tyrannical exploitation of nature by mankind. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 14:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ISIS Is Winning the Social Media War, U.S. Concludes: An internal State Department assessment paints a dismal picture of the efforts by the Obama administration and its foreign allies to combat the ISs message machine, portraying a fractured coalition that cannot get its own message straight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 13:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Moroccan magazine said Friday it was recalling its latest issue, whose cover asked "Should We Burn Gays?", after it sparked a fierce debate in the conservative Muslim kingdom. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 13:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A man is lucky to be alive after having been stung between 500 and 1,000 times by tens of thousands of swarming bees near Kingman in northwestern Arizona on Friday, authorities said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 13:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 13:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.1002165 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: Half of all basic life science research is seriously flawed. "researchers concluded that more than half of all life sciences research is not reproducible, and they suggested that estimate is probably conservative. Other studies have put the total as high as 89 percent." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 13:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Camels aged less than four years might be a major source of Mers, according to new research. Scientists looked for evidence of current or past infection in more than 800 dromedary camels.They found that more than 90% of animals became infected by the age of two ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 18:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over 90% of the world's population wants zero carbon emissions "... more than 9 out of 10 people on planet Earth think we should stop burning the oil, gas and coal that have helped boost global temperatures to dangerous record highs." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nobel laureate Satyarthi says up to 500,000 child soldiers worldwide "When I read that a five-year-old child is given a gun to kill an opponent of a militia group in Iraq... and the child could not handle that gun, he was buried alive... That makes me angry. I think this should make you all angry," </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian teenagers 'set on fire' while trying to take the 'ultimate selfie' on train roof </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Burned Bones in Alexander the Great Tomb Give Up Few Secrets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antigravity pump lifts water upwards with no power source: scientists have developed a way to lift water with no need for an external source of energy. Although the technique only works over short distances at the moment, it could be useful for microfluidic lab-on-a-chip devices .. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greece debt crisis: Tsipras's impossible position "the public pressure on Alexis Tsipras is growing - reflecting concern within the EU and the IMF that he has miscalculated the extent to which he can orchestrate a change in policy." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evolution tuned this moths night vision to follow swaying flowers: In a study published Thursday in Science, researchers report evidence that the hawkmoth (Manduca sexta) has used the movement of the flowers it eats as a guide for how to change its eyesight at night. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rubios claim that two-thirds of Americans make less money today than in 2002 gets three Pinocchios </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US climate change deniers lambast the Pope over his environment encyclical  video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Faces French Ultimatum Over Right to Be Forgotten: Frances data protection regulator, CNIL, ordered Google to proceed with delistings of links across its network, irrespective of the domain name. CNIL said it received hundreds of complaints following Googles refusals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 14:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside the Islamic State "There seems little doubt about which of these claims is perceived in Saudi Arabia as more authentic. In an online poll conducted in July 2014, a formidable 92 percent of Saudi citizens agreed that ISIS 'conforms to the values of Islam and Islamic law.'" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 14:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama: Health law has now been woven into the fabric of America Five years in, what we are talking about is no longer just a law. Its no longer just a theory. This isnt even about the Affordable Care Act or Obamacare. This isnt about myths or rumors that folks try to sustain." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 14:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pluto continues to get bigger in the viewfinder of New Horizons' cameras. The Nasa spacecraft is now less than 40 million km from making its historic flyby of the dwarf planet on 14 July. The latest pictures show distinct surface regions - some bright, some dark. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mini-Breast grown in petri-dishes  a new tool for cancer research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attenborough explores ancient oceans in 'wonderful' VR: Sir David Attenborough is now taking us 500 million years into the past and deep under the ocean surface in virtual reality film First Life, debuting at the UK Natural History Museum this June. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interview: Damascus says it has faced worse times, key areas secure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 12:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunscreen layer detected on distant planet: On a blazing-hot exoplanet known as WASP-33b, a team of astronomers including researchers from the University of Cambridge has detected a stratosphere, one of the primary layers of Earths atmosphere. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 12:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The grandparents of three-year-old girl with a rare form of epilepsy have made a $33.7m donation to the University of Sydney to fund medicinal cannabis research. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 09:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dogs snub people who are mean to their owners: study. The findings reveal that canines have the capacity to co-operate socially -- a characteristic found in a relatively small number of species, including humans and some other primates. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 08:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Number of Russians in poverty rises by 3 million </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A male rape charity has had its funding slashed to zero. Where are all the outraged men? "A vital service for men who have been affected by sexual abuse has lost funding, and yet so-called Mens Rights Activists are still more interested in bringing feminists down." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraqi militias retake Baiji from Islamic State group: Iraqi Shiite militias told FRANCE 24 they had retaken control of Baiji, home to Iraqs largest oil refinery, after months of battling Islamic State group militants for control of the strategic city. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polar bear caught eating dolphins and freezing the leftovers "As the climate warms, Stirling (a biology scientist/researcher) believes the sight of polar bears tucking into weird meals could become more common. Polar bears are "willing to take and use anything possible when available", he says." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Soft robot tentacle can lasso an ant without harming it: The soft robot can curl itself into a circle with a radius of just 200 micrometres. This is thanks to its microtube structure, fabricated from a kind of polymer called an elastomer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ghana has suspended a trial for an Ebola vaccine after complaints that locals were being needlessly used as "guinea pigs" in a country currently free of the deadly disease. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neuroscientists capture the moment a brain records an idea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [VICE news documentary] Peshmerga vs. the Islamic State: The Road to Mosul </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA Administrator blasts Congress over spending bill by gutting this program and turning our backs on U.S. industry, NASA will be forced to continue to rely on Russia to get its astronauts to space and continue to invest hundreds of millions of dollars into the Russian economy rather than our own </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] Killer Whales and Humpbacks Hunt Together: Biologist and killer whale expert Tiu Simil explains the amazing "carousel feeding" method of Norwegian orcas, which stun and eat fish one by one and share the hunt with humpback whales. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Increasingly Frequent Call on Baltic Sea: The Russian Navy Is Back "It has sent a blunt warning of Russias disquiet over threats to one of its principal geopolitical goals: keeping a firm grip on energy supplies as a powerful political and commercial tool in neighboring territories" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 15:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers in China and Ireland have developed a simple way of building new stimuli-responsive phospholipids that can self-assemble into hollow spheres and trigger the release of anticancer drugs only when inside the cell lysosome. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 15:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adblock Plus cries foul over Apple plan to stop ads: Adblock Plus maker says Apples built-in system for iOS 9 and its web browser could spell end of Adblocking on Safari </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 15:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'We are the child': the anti-Assad slogan spreading across the Middle East </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 14:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Texas man has died his inside his dream sports car, alongside his pet dog, after the vehicle's lock malfunctioned and the pair perished from heat exhaustion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 14:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1,000 attorneys to represent brutally murdered college girl in southern Turkey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 14:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK leads Europe for wealthy female breadwinners, survey finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 14:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bushs recipe for a better society: Shame "his underlying philosophy is clear, and its consistent with attitudes weve seen among conservatives now in power ...: that the main reason people are broke, unmarried, in prison or unemployed is because its all just too much gosh-darn fun" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 13:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FIFA Chief Blatter Urged to Depart Immediately by EU Parliament: In its resolution on Thursday, the EU Parliament said it condemns the systemic and despicable corruption exposed at FIFA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 13:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkish President Tayyip Erdogan on Thursday accused the West of bombing Arabs and Turkmens in Syria while supporting Kurdish "terrorist" groups which he said were taking their place. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 13:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian Groups Crowdfund the War in Ukraine: Several groups are running online campaigns to brazenly raise money for rebels in eastern Ukraine, helping succor a conflict that has killed thousands. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 12:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A review of UK phone and internet surveillance says current "undemocratic and unnecessary" laws need a complete overhaul. The UK government needed to do more to prove why security services should be able to monitor our web browsing histories for two years - as has been mooted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 11:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Catholics around the world await Pope Francis's encyclical on the environment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 10:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ability to digest milk may have become common only relatively recently in Europe, a major study of ancient DNA shows. The analysis of genomes from 101 ancient adults suggests the gene for breaking down the lactose sugar in milk was still rare in the Bronze Age. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 10:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Turkish police officer that gained notoriety for spraying pepper spray at peaceful protesters, including an academic who became known as the woman in red during the outset of the Gezi Park uprising in 2013, has been sentenced to 20 months in jail and ordered to plant 600 trees. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 17:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 17:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://mbe.oxfordjournals.org/content/early/2015/05/27/molbev.msv128.abstract?sid=ee3c561b-cc9b-4a0c-8c2c-f8cca7e4ce96 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Miners in northwestern Canada have discovered ice age camel bones whose DNA is forcing scientists to redraw the family tree of the now-extinct species. Scientists can now begin to understand why the camels went extinct 13,000 years ago, at the end of the ice age. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 17:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trail-blazing ants show hints of metacognition when seeking food: If true, these ants would be just the second reported case of an insect showing such advanced cognitive behaviour. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 17:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A half-dozen academic journals are investigating allegations that aerospace engineer Willie Wei-Hock Soon, a prominent skeptic of the idea that humans are contributing to global warming, failed to disclose financial ties to a fossil fuel company in papers they published. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 17:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 113,000 people, so far, support an online petition which calls for the regulation of 'excessive homework' in Spain: The campaign is being spear-headed by Madrid mother, Eva Bailen, who began to see the effect up to three hours of homework a day was having on her 10-year-old son. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 17:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nanoparticles target and kill cancer stem cells that drive tumor growth: Researchers have designed nanoparticles that specifically target cancer stem cells to deliver a drug. The nanoparticle treatment, reported in the journal ACS Nano, worked far better than the drug alone in mice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We arent the copyright cops, ICANNs president says: The Internet is inching ever closer to becoming the equal, nonpartisan network it was always meant to be. And one of the top officials leading that charge is vowing not to let any single corporate or govt derail that project  including the U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Norway's coal disinvestment is still just a drop in the ocean </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Soco paid Congo major' accused of Virunga oil intimidation: The BBC has seen evidence that British firm Soco made payments to a Congolese army major accused of using violence to intimidate oil exploration opponents. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our poor sleeping habits could be filling our brains with neurotoxins "As it turns out, beta-amyloid also works to prevent your body from getting the rest it needs, creating something of a vicious cycle for the chronically sleep-deprived." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New images of dwarf planet Ceres, taken by NASA's Dawn spacecraft, show the cratered surface of this mysterious world in sharper detail than ever before. These are among the first snapshots from Dawn's second mapping orbit, which is 2,700 miles (4,400 kilometers) above Ceres. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of people crossed from Syria into Turkey on Wednesday to flee a battle pitting Islamist insurgents against Kurdish and opposition forces for the Syrian border town of Tel Abyad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 15:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK Schools are being sold software to monitor pupils internet activity for extremism-related language such as jihadi bride and YODO, short for you only die once. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 15:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research using high-speed gambling experiments shows that, for most of us, the last experience weve had can be the defining one when it comes to taking a decision, coming at the expense of other experiences weve accumulated further back in time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 15:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis has approved the creation of a tribunal to hear cases of bishops accused of covering up child abuse by paedophile priests. The unprecedented move followed a recommendation from the Pope's newly-created panel on clerical sex abuse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 15:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Nobel laureate has apologised for any offence after he made comments about the "trouble with girls" in science - but said he had "meant to be honest". He went on to say he stood by some of the remarks. "I did mean the part about having trouble with girls," he said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 14:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Worm Turns: Virus Hunter Kaspersky Becomes the Hunted. The IT security firm Kaspersky Lab has discovered a new, powerful cyber weapon, apparently a successor to the notorious Duqu software. But this time the virus hunter itself is a target. Now experts are scrambling to identify who's behind it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 14:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guerrilla Fighters of Kurdistan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 14:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese surgeons have used 3D printing technology as part of a successful operation to separate conjoined twins. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 14:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perrys cherry-picked claim that America would have lost 400,000 jobs without Texas gets three Pinocchios "This is a classic case of politicians manipulating or cherry-picking numbers to put their states performance in the best possible light." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 14:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swedish police arrest two 13-year-olds for murder: In Sweden, children under the age of 15 cannot be charged with a crime or go on trial. Instead, they are placed in the care of social welfare authorities. Police are not allowed to hold children under 15 in custody either, but can interrogate them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists in Sweden are launching their own mead - an alcoholic beverage made from a fermented mix of honey and water - based on old recipes which they say could help in the fight against antibiotic resistance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Near Jerusalem, 1500-year-old Byzantine-era road station and church uncovered on Highway 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 12:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Celestial Butterfly Emerges from its Dusty Cocoon: Some of the sharpest images ever made with ESOs Very Large Telescope have, for the first time, revealed what appears to be an ageing star giving birth to a butterfly-like planetary nebula. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 12:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers in Peru have discovered a trio of statuettes they believe were created by the ancient Caral civilization some 3,800 years ago. The mud statuettes were found inside a reed basket in a building at the ancient city of Vichama in northern Peru, which is today an important archaeological site </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 10:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudi lashing sentence for blogger 'medieval': Swedish FM "My opinion is that it's a medieval sentence. It's a medieval method that does not have its place in a society that allows a free media and allows people to express their point of view," Wallstrom told Swedish Radio in Brussels. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 17:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Virus evolution and human behaviour shape global patterns of flu movement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 17:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The number of Fortune 500 companies led by women is at an all-time high: 5 percent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 17:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Global Struggle to Respond to the Worst Refugee Crisis in Generations: Eleven million people were uprooted by violence last year. Photos and maps show the international response to what has become the worst migration crisis since World War II. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 17:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gay and bisexual men living in European countries with strong attitudes and policies against homosexuality are far less likely to use HIV-prevention services, test for HIV, and discuss their sexuality with health providers, according to research led by Yale School of Public Health </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 16:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finns no longer believe they live in an equal society, study claims: Researchers say they are surprised by preliminary results of a social attitudes survey, which suggests a departure from the traditional view of Finland as a haven of equality and respect for rights. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 16:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The shark from Jaws is polling better than all of the 2016 candidates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 16:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Defying death is causing back pain, bad teeth and depression: About 95% of people have at least 1 health complaint, with a third having more than 5. Becoming better at avoiding early death means we spend longer being susceptible to diseases and disabilities that result from our bodies wearing out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 16:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 15:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://www.nature.com/nnano/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nnano.2015.115.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An international team of researchers has developed a method of fabricating nanoscale electronic scaffolds that can be injected via syringe. The scaffolds can then be connected to devices and used to monitor neural activity, stimulate tissues, or even promote regeneration of neurons. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 15:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peering Into a Black Hole: Astronomers hope the Event Horizon Telescope, a synchronized network of radio antennas as large as the Earth, will take the first ever picture of a black hole, an abyss so deep no light can escape. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 15:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> X-rays capture super-fast nanoscale film: By uniting the worlds brightest synchrotron x-ray source with photography processes dating from the 19th century, scientists have tracked photochemically-driven crystal movements in greater detail than ever before. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 15:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why it took us so long to match Apple on privacy  a Google exec explains </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 15:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stanford engineers develop a computer that operates on water droplets: engineers have developed a synchronous computer that operates using the unique physics of moving water droplets. Their goal is to design a new class of computers that can precisely control and manipulate physical matter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 15:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Defense Secretary Donald Rumsfeld now said that the goal of creating a democracy in Iraq was "unrealistic" and that he was "concerned" when he first heard the idea floated by former President George W. Bush, a stark admission by one of the Iraq War's biggest defenders. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 14:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 14:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of Nicholas White who was stuck for 41 hours https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p_bMhNI_TY8. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two nuns have been rescued from a lift in Rome after being trapped for three days without food and water. The nuns became stuck on Friday at the Marist convent after an electrical power failure. They cried out for help but there was no-one in the building over the weekend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 14:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syria's brutal conflict has left more than 230,000 people dead including almost 11,500 children since it broke out in 2011. The toll does not include some 20,000 people who have disappeared after being arrested, 9,000 people in gov't detention, and at least 4,000 people held by the IS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 14:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans might as well pound sand "After months of trying to weaken Hillary Clinton by pounding her with everything theyve got, the amount of progress Republicans have made is pretty close to zero." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 14:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secretive donors gave US climate denial groups $125m over three years: The secretive funders behind Americas conservative movement directed around $125m over three years to groups spreading disinformation about climate science and committed to wrecking Obamas climate change plan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A cat which accompanied her owner across the desert from Sudan to Libya and then on a migrant boat to Italy has been taken into quarantine on the island of Lampedusa after authorities promised to reunite the pair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NY police chief Bratton says hiring black officers is difficult: 'So many have spent time in jail' We have a significant population gap among African American males because so many of them have spent time in jail and, as such, we cant hire them, Bratton said in an interview with the Guardian. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US police kill more in days than other countries do in years: The Guardian has built the most comprehensive database of police killings ever published. Compare the findings from America to those from the UK, Australia, Iceland and beyond, and the contrasts are shocking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 12:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research has found caffeine can help manage stress and potentially prevent conditions like depression and memory loss. The researchers fed mice caffeine in their drinking water, then put some of the animals under stress. The caffeine had a calming effect on the mice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 11:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Marry me or be my slave': Islamic State emir's ultimatum to a young Syrian widow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 11:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goodbye, roaming charges. The borderless SIM is finally here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 11:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside Mosul: What's life like under Islamic State? Secretly filmed videos obtained by the BBC's Ghadi Sary show mosques being blown up, abandoned schools, and women being forced to cover up their bodies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 10:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gay Muslim filmmaker risks death in pilgrimage to reconcile faith and sexuality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doctors in China have removed 420 kidney stones from a single patient. While having 420 kidney stones sounds uncomfortable, it's a long way off the world record. In 2009, a doctor in India removed 172,155 stones from a patient's left kidney during a three-hour surgery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have built a tiny mesh-like electronic sensor, rolled it up into a hypodermic needle   injected it into the brain. The device taking this fantastic electronic voyage may soon be able to zap tumors, repair damaged spinal cords or even connect parts of the brain like an artificial synapse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 12 mesmerizing animations show how the logos for Apple, Coca-Cola and more have evolved </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Will Increase Training of Iraqi Forces Fighting ISIS, Obama Says Although it is going to take time, and there will be setbacks and lessons learned, we are going to be successful. ISIL is going to be driven out of Iraq, and ultimately, it is going to be defeated. Mr. Obama said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malaysian authorities arrest a European man for allegedly stripping naked and urinating on Mount Kinabalu prior to a deadly earthquake, reports say, an act that some locals believe angered tribal spirits and caused the quake. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 16:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Escaped New York prisoners may have had help from staff - governor: "I would be shocked if a guard was involved, and that's putting it mildly," Cuomo told CNN. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 16:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syria to hike pay of frontline soldiers with bonus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 16:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nations First Operational Satellite in Deep Space Reaches Final Orbit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 16:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Billionaire Cartier Owner Sees Wealth Gap Fueling Social Unrest We cannot have 0.1 percent of 0.1 percent taking all the spoils, said Rupert, who has a fortune worth $7.5 billion, according to data compiled by Bloomberg. Its unfair and it is not sustainable. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 15:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On the edge of space: A photographers out-of-this-world selfie, 70,000 feet above the Earth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 15:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than half of Britons would vote to remain in the European Union if a planned referendum on the country's membership of the bloc were held tomorrow, according to a poll on Monday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 15:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Serbia's capital city will soon have a new monument honouring Gavrilo Princip, the Bosnian-Serb nationalist whose actions triggered a chain of events leading to World War One. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 15:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reality doesnt exist until you look at it, pioneering quantum physics experiment finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 15:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers in Switzerland have designed a system where children teach robot students how to write, and in the process improve their own handwriting skills. This learning by teaching paradigm, they say, could engage unmotivated students as well as boost their self-confidence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 14:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Delhis New Two-Finger Test Guidelines Really Say "The internal examination to determine whether a womans hymen is broken is used as proof of sexual intercourse but often also as evidence to question the alleged victims moral character." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 14:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Public to Supreme Court: Dont gut Obamacare "By a margin of 55 percent to 38 percent, more people say the court should not take action to block federal subsidies in states that didn't set up their own exchanges, according to a new Washington Post-ABC News poll." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 14:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bees are 'sick of humans' but man will feel the sting: In a worrying development which could threaten food production, South Africa's traditionally tough honey bees -- which had been resistant to disease -- are now getting "sick of humans", with the population of the crucial pollinators collapsing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 14:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-Vaxxers Are Using Twitter to Manipulate a Vaccine Bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 14:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet the Malala of Syria: Muzoon Almellehan is trying to convince parents to let their girls stay in school rather than marrying them off as child brides. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 13:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Training to Become the First Civilian Artist in Space </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 13:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The world's first artificial leg capable of simulating the feelings of a real limb and fighting phantom pain was unveiled by researchers on Monday. Surgeons first rewired remaining foot nerve endings from a patient's stump to healthy tissue in the thigh, placing them close to the skin surface. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 12:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis's critique of free-market economics has made him an icon for the Left and prompted claims that he is a communist. The leader of the world's 1.2bn Catholics has called capitalism a source of inequality at best - and at worst a killer. Is the Pope, as his critics claim, a red radical? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 12:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Face to face with Islamic State: The BBC's Orla Guerin is given exclusive access to members of an alleged Islamic State militant cell. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 15:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greek Prime Minister Alexis Tsipras failed to deliver alternative economic reforms that he had "promised", says European Commission president, Jean-Claude Juncker. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 15:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "GOP leaders justify their anti-voting agenda as an answer to voter fraud, but voter fraud is an imaginary problem. In fact, Republicans want fewer people to vote, especially fewer poor and minority people, because low turnout tends to favor the GOP, and poor   minority people tend to vote for Dems" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 14:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dazzling jewels from an Ethiopian grave reveal 2,000-year-old link to Rome: 2,000-year-old treasures from the Roman empire and the Aksumite kingdom, which ruled parts of north-east Africa for several centuries before 940AD, have been discovered by British archaeologists in northern Ethiopia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 14:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having a stroke ages a persons brain function by almost eight years, new research finds  robbing them of memory and thinking speed as measured on cognitive tests. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 14:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ISIS Falls For Fake Battle for Iraq City: Two Iraqis invented a fake town, named for a butter churn, then claimed ISIS was defeated there by Shia militias. Fans of both fell for the gag. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 14:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Queen bee syndrome  displayed by leading professional women who keep other females out  is a myth, according to a new study. Researchers at Columbia Business School in New York claim that a lack of women in top roles is down to mens determination to retain control. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 14:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 13:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( Really sorry to hear that! I hope she gets better soon. Stay strong, brother.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Secret History of SEAL Team 6: Quiet Killings and Blurred Lines: The unit best known for killing Osama bin Laden has been converted into a global manhunting machine with limited outside oversight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 17:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 14:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://www.bloodjournal.org/content/early/2015/04/22/blood-2014-07-587329 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have discovered that a rabbit virus can deliver a one-two punch, killing some kinds of cancer cells while eliminating a common and dangerous complication of bone marrow transplants. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 14:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
