<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2037</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DOTA Network servers seem to be back up, for me at least. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 21:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No Goblin Techies though :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would a petition do anything to help restrict the foreigners queuing for US servers and ruining games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 09:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To preface this, I have no problem with foreigners queuing for US servers if they can speak English. But if you can't speak English, you shouldn't be allowed to queue for US servers. Because once again I'm playing ranked captain's draft tonight and all but one of my teammates speaks English, and guess which one immediately steals captain? Yep. And then proceeds to pick a team that none of us want, and go 0-20 intentionally feeding the entire time while buying couriers and sending them into the enemy. 

Something needs to be done. Reporting doesn't do anything permanent, they'll be back in ranked doing it again in 5 games. An idea I saw in some other thread was a kind of flag where if a person is queuing for US servers but can't speak English, you get enough people to flag them and they can't queue for US servers any more. I fully support this idea. In a team-based game such as DOTA you really do need all 5 people being able to communicate and work together. I've met more than my fair share of Russians, Hispanics, Germans, etc. who come to US servers simply to troll and ruin games for us. And if people try to flag English speakers, whether they're trolling or butthurt or for whatever reason, I'm sure it wouldn't be hard to ask a few basic English questions to prove you can read/speak/write it.

What if reddit designed some sort of petition and submitted it to Valve? Or something. We talk all day about wanting something done, would it be possible to actually get the ball rolling here and try to get this fixed? This isn't just another circle jerk complaint thread, but if anyone is actually interested in coming up with a solution and trying to get it implemented I'm fully for it and will support in any way I can.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The inside of this pepper was happy to see me! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-09 17:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are the servers broken tonight or is it just me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 08:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Randomly three hours ago I went from being able to play fine to having a good two second lag in everything in the entire game. I usually queue for US East/West servers, but even tried a Europe East/West one and it was the exact same. Nothing changed on my computer, and nobody else is using my internet.

Anyone else experiencing horrid lag tonight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watched a Jackie Chan movie, tried to do a somersault through a swing while yelling "I'M JACKIE CHAN" and fell flat on my face. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 21:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Happened when I was eight or so. My father watched it all happen and I think he fell over laughing. It still cracks him up to this day.](/spoiler) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the implications of this Russia/Ukraine conflict? Could this start another World War, or will it be a localized skirmish, etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 21:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also if anyone has links to articles explaining what's going on over there like I'm five, that would be much appreciated. I've tried to read some things but honestly it just confuses me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 [M4F] - Bored and horny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 05:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ladies only please - christhegecko </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20/M open to both guys and girls opinions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 21:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just found this subreddit and was curious as to what the world thinks of meh. 

* Selfie: http://imgur.com/a/B3HGD#0

* Face selfie: http://imgur.com/a/B3HGD#1

* Shirtless: http://imgur.com/a/B3HGD#2

* This is probably the best recent higher quality picture I have of myself, from a few weeks ago before I got my eyebrow pierced: http://imgur.com/a/B3HGD#3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Audio Engineers of Reddit, how is your career like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 05:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm considering a career in Audio Engineering to help my electronic music production passion and was wondering if there were any on here that would be able to give me a quick run down on what you actually do and can do with the information and degree earned from a major in Audio Engineering. 

I don't know if this is related, but if I want to work with speakers and setting up audio/visual music and light shows and etc., what would that be? 

Thanks guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There was no other name they could come up with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 00:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Improvising. If you keep your keys on one of these, use it as a makeshift roach clip. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-21 07:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I see your doorbell, and raise you a door knocker that I painted on. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 07:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> before and after makeup [fixed] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-18 11:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wolfgang Gartner- Redline (Justin Perea Remix) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 09:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/trees, meet Nessie :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-05 21:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well this happened </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-17 09:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Totally Not Awkward (x/post from funny) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-14 05:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Totally Not Awkward </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-14 05:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To any Redditors currently in/graduated from college with a degree in Marketing, would you be able to answer some questions within? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-03 11:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple friends and I were thinking about starting a business down the road, and one of the things I was thinking I could help out with was marketing for it, but really have no idea what it's like. 

What are the kinds of classes that go along with that major?

What kind of job work would I be doing in the future? If this would vary from company to company, is there any kind of guideline or across the board generalization of it?

Is the job market good for people with this degree? As in is someone with this degree a sought after person for companies and businesses?

If our idea falls through, is this degree something I'll be able to fall back on in the future? 

These questions may be kind of vague, and I apologize if they are, but any help at all is much appreciated :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alien Seed - The Workingmachine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-31 11:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aphrodite - Wobble </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-31 11:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you get started doing cool fractal imagery? Text inside for examples, don't exactly know the best way to word the question. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-24 08:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically I'm wondering how you get started doing art like this: http://i.imgur.com/syuRD.jpg or http://www.weepeeple.com/images/i-sleep-only.jpg or http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/9/94/Www_y23_com--fractal----Lg_Z010121Z.jpg.

What programs do you need, any beginners guides, etc. Any and all help is appreciated :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baauer - Yaow! (Steven V's Dirty Edit) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-05 07:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Experience in Racing Games: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-26 00:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does a period look like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 13:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Icelandish: Almost as confusing to spell as captchas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 13:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As someone just getting back to reddit at 3 AM: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-13 09:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So the theme for Wednesdays is music, how about everyone go to their music playlists, put them on shuffle and link the first 5 songs that pop up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-01 13:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Blue Oyster Cult - I'm Burnin' For You](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pTvbXMRMnHo)

[Fine Cut Bodies - Beaver Blink (Ooah remix)](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nGyJbMCfjRU)

[Pink Floyd - Another Brick In The Wall](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iU2-r_0CtIo)

[DJ Q - Sound of Violence(2 step)](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DJnCBJ9WUSc)

[Blink-182 - Up All Night](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iRB4pykTjGg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My smiling doggies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-25 22:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For my cake day today I'd like to share with you all the first bowl I ever owned, what were some of yours? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-25 21:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teenagers these days... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-25 21:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perfect? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-24 04:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook Burn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-03 22:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thinking about starting to play the Ohio lottery, any tips or tricks to increase my chances of winning? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-30 16:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going for the mega millions or anything like that, mostly what I'm interested in is playing scratch offs to win a couple hundred or thousand dollars. I was thinking about just buying a few cards a week, probably the $1 or $2 cards, but I have no idea which cards give the highest chance of winning or if there is a specific strategy or anything. I did some googling but it all was really confusing. 

If anyone has any tips or tricks that they could share it would be greatly appreciated! Thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bassinine - Moonwatcher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-29 21:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone been to a Skream and Benga show recently? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-26 19:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and some friends are debating on whether or not to drive to Chicago this weekend for Skream and Benga, and I was wondering what their shows have been like recently? I remember a video from not too long ago of people complaining they were starting to play "brostep" at their shows and was curious if it would be worth it still. Are they playing tunes from their early days where each set was an absolute banger or are they playing mostly their new stuff which I personally am not too big a fan of? Thanks in advance.

edit: [This](http://www.clubtix.com/images/event/full/1601_image_1.jpg) is the event page and line-up for the night, we're all mostly going for Feed Me but wanted to know if Skream and Benga would be worth the trip too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> a sure sign of drunken food purchases (FIXED) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-28 22:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slim Jims, Chicken Nuggets and Tator Tots on a Combination Party Pizza. Munchin food :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-22 04:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anybody help identify a song in the movie Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-18 22:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It starts at around 1 hour 5 minutes in, right before the scene where they tie up their neighbor and make off with the van with the traffic warden inside.

It sounds like a bass guitar riff, but I'm wondering if it's just that or if its a part of a greater song? Any help is greatly appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Construction Worker Laziness; Level: 50 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-17 19:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women of reddit, how do you feel about hairy men? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-12 21:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chest hair, leg hair, back hair...is it a turn-off? Or maybe a turn-on? Do you find it attractive or unattractive?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OPM - Heaven is a Halfpipe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-10 02:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hmm, I Don't Think So. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-04 17:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fellow Ents, care to help me name my new piece? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-31 02:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/VDFaq

It's clear at the moment, but the more you smoke it it will turn blue. In case you can't tell, the thing on top is a gecko.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Smoking Buddies' Reactions When I Light Up A Bowl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-29 22:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for some good, wobbly jungle DnB. Any good recommendations?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-20 03:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couple sample songs I found that describe perfectly what I'm looking for: 
[Ed Solo   Deekline - Ghost Town](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mHh3_AaRALw)
and
[Ed Solo   Deekline - Ragga Tip (Walk And Skank)](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T9ntK6618Qs)

Thank you in advance!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That's totally a Ferrari  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-17 23:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Were all the sidebar links used for cinsere's personal gain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-17 04:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or were some of them legitimate websites? Wondering because I noticed they were all gone and I have hopefully saved up enough money for a nice new bong but none of the helpful links are there ): 

Or does anyone know a website that would be good for ordering various smoking devices? Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inappropriate Radio DJ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-16 21:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favorite opera to this day [FIXED]{FIXED} </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 04:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flame and Encode - Space Pioneer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-28 02:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help me out redditors, a friend ran away from home and her mom is trying to press truancy/runaway charges to the police. Story inside, what is the worst that could happen to her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-19 00:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically it was Friday, their last day of school before winter break. She's 16 and she left after 2nd bell to go to a friend's house and get drunk. She was expecting to be back to school in time to catch the bus, but ended up getting really sick and got into an argument with her mom about not being home, resulting in her mom telling her NOT to come home, and that she doesn't want to "see her face again". So she stayed overnight at this friend's house, and went to another friend's house the next day to stay. Her parents are divorced, and apparently right now she is en route to her dad's while her mom is talking to the police about "pressing charges" for truancy and being a runaway.

What I'm wondering is, what are the possible outcomes? If you're a runaway, I believe the police just take you back home right? If you're a truant, if all they do is hear about it, and don't catch you in the act, I'm assuming the only thing they will do is tell the school and let the school handle it, correct? And her mom currently doesn't know she was out drinking, but apparently an ex-boyfriend who heard about all this is spilling the beans to her mom and may tell her, so if the police find out about underage drinking what would result of that? And is the friend she drank with and stayed with, who is about to turn 18, in any danger of punishment? 

Any help is very appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only one I've read too...(FBF) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-18 09:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pink Floyd - Let There Be More Light </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-05 06:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HIFW Somebody drops the weed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-01 01:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Doors - Light My Fire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-30 22:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Third World Success </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-28 12:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Music Friday: Who likes Smashing Pumpkins? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-25 18:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm sure we've all felt this way </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-21 23:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skyrimming, the newest dirty verb.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-18 23:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teen guys, how long do you last during sex? Let's be honest here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-18 23:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've sort of been having a problem with my new girlfriend. We've had sex a few times now, and a couple times I'm able to go for 15-20 minutes, but then others I blow within 2 or 3. Is this normal? People always try to brag like they've gone for hours on end, but I feel like that isn't the truth and its a subject most of us don't want to face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm very smart, I promise [FIXED] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-12 18:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Like every new meme, it will also be completely overposted and dead in a matter of 5 days.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-11 00:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vapour - ft Jaz - "Shake It" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-01 23:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favorite part about Halloween: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-01 01:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They asked for it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-25 22:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HIFW] I ride with kids who just got their license. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-25 21:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could have one sound effect play every time you come, what would it be? Probably NSFW. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-24 07:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine would be the yell Eminem does in "Just Lose It", for the lols. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cincinnati Ents! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-23 09:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mt. Washington here :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey AskReddit, what was the reason you started coming to Reddit, or how did you hear about it?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-22 20:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine personally was through rage comics and hearing about f7u12.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL That in 1985, Ronnie Lott, a 49ers Cornerback, crushed his pinky finger in a game and in the off-season faced the choice of intricate finger surgery and possibly missed playing time, or amputation of the tip of his finger. He chose amputation and played on for six more years. That's dedication. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-19 21:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HIFW] I discovered r/woahdude  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-07 05:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slowpoke finally hears the news </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-07 05:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found this on the same website as the petition everyone is signing, an unfortunate discovery. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-04 23:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the link: http://www.whitehouse.gov/ondcp/marijuana

Some things I would like to point out to potential readers: 

"In 2009, marijuana was involved in 376,000 emergency department visits nationwide." Check the link, our own government doesn't even know how to properly site sources. The link doesn't even mention the word Marijuana anywhere in it. "Drug related" does not mean strictly marijuana. 

"And the science, though still evolving in terms of long-term consequences of marijuana use, is clear: marijuana use is associated with addiction, respiratory and mental illness, poor motor performance, and cognitive impairment, among other negative effects." Their source on this one is valid. However http://www.erowid.org/plants/cannabis/cannabis_myth9.shtml has legitimate research stating otherwise. An interesting thing I've noticed: the government always quotes "science" or "scientists". They have their funded websites saying everything the drug does to you and how it works and how bad it is. But in textbooks and every pro-marijuana website out there, actual college studies and experiments are sited. Ones that result in favor of the pro-marijuana side. Just thought that was funny, that even though the "science" favors one side, actual real-life tests with real-life humans prove otherwise. I encourage you to read the other 13 myths they bust. They site every study and source too. 

"Furthermore, the Administration opposes drug legalization.  Legalization threatens public health by increasing availability of drugs and undermining prevention activities." Alcohol is legal. Nicotine is legal. Nicotine is a drug. Alcohol is a drug. It is possible to overdose on alcohol, and it happens every day, and impossible to overdose on marijuana. Millions of people die each year from these two drugs that are perfectly legal to consume if you are of age. I'm not saying there are no marijuana related deaths, but if the government tries to say they oppose drug legalization, they can not turn a blind eye to the things that kill Americans every day. Potentially fatal drugs are even prescribed to people; drugs like Vicodin, Percocet or Morphine. 

Does anyone else see this as an outrage or is it just me? The government and anti-drug agencies endorse half-truths and force opinions based on pure bullshit or skewed facts. 

Maybe this is just a rant from a sad ent, but I would love to see the day when people told the facts. Even if it meant their position was compromised. The fact that it was only a click or two away from our petition is what really frazzled me. 

I will support the petition wholly, and I hope all you fellow ents will do the same. Marijuana will be legal, or at least decriminalized, some day. I'm awaiting it eagerly :)

TL;DR: Mad ent rants about government's stance on marijuana. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every Man's Dream </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-02 20:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's cold and I can't text with mittens on. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-02 08:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for good ideas for webpage pranks or gags, maybe AskReddit can help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-30 03:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something along these lines: At a set time during the day, but not too often to make it annoying, have the image of a small bug slowly walk across the screen and see how many people you can trick into thinking its a real bug.

Not the coolest idea ever, I know, but maybe we can have some fun with this topic for potential April Fool's Day gags?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Ultra Violet light is used on certain foods to kill bacteria, and also to change other factors such as flavor, color and shelf life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-29 21:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first thing I noticed in the "Happy Birthday, Awesome Picture" post: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-27 05:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scumbag Marijuana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-23 00:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Foamo - Jookie, gnarly tune.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-22 05:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dark tune, Demon - "Cardiac Attack" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-19 00:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Made a Mix that I think turned out pretty well, could I get some feedback from the r/dubstep community? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-18 14:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Men of the world, we are doomed.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-18 05:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stupid teachers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-16 01:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there somewhere to buy r/trees stickers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-15 22:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Treestrees is saying shop closed, is there anywhere else anyone knows of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Or maybe Scumbag Success Kid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-15 22:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rusko - Cockney Thug (Caspa remix)  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-15 12:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At a [9], my eccentric teacher looks like this guy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-15 12:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did any other Ents love watching this when they were younger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-14 04:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Albert Einstein's brain was basically stolen after his death, and that researchers may have found a contributor to his extraordinary genius in Glial Cells, of which Einstein had more than the average man.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-12 23:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Massive tune, Mala- Eyez </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-11 19:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank god for Cool Co-Workers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-06 01:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cool Co-Worker! Happened today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-06 01:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the main reasons I hate driving at night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-03 03:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favorite "real dubstep" track, an absolute banger. Loefah   Skream - 28g </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-01 01:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Excision and Bassnectar - Nation  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-01 01:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I feel when a hot girl likes my Facebook status </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-31 06:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If only most of r/adviceanimals were like GGG. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-31 05:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For you Forever Alone smokers:  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-28 04:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm surprised I understood it in the first place. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-25 21:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liquid Sex [7] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-22 04:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saves my life every summer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-15 20:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I feel at an [8] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-14 07:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh god (Just Happened) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-12 06:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How music looks/feels for me high/DAE feel like this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-09 23:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First I'm all like [this](http://imgur.com/yXTjw).
Then I turn on the music and I'm all like [this](http://imgur.com/cWHKq). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I laugh whenever I read a terrible, yet funny, pun: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-07 06:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least he didn't report me.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-07 05:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My reaction to r/jailbait: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-05 05:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bitches also love synonyms. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-04 18:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Makes sense in my mind. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-03 04:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawnmower Rage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-30 00:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Still good even as an adult. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-28 19:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She wouldn't even push me on the swings after this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-28 02:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Especially sucks if you have no mutual friends. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-27 22:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ILI - Cincinnati, Ohio. AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-27 10:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least we're not Cleveland.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So this is how it happens. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-27 09:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
