<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8843</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Insomnia: Magnesium Citrate and 5-HTP supplements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 15:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 15:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There is a significant difference in the interpretation of scientific studies when compared with the desired

Scientific studies do seem to work in terms of statistical significance, as the article says a sleeping pill such as Rozerem makes you fall asleep ~15 minutes quicker and makes you sleep for 20 minutes longer. Considering the potential side affects of the morning hangover and addiction that would seem to be a small benefit. Why do you disagree with this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 15:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sometimes find that I am similar. If I get a good nights sleep then I seem to be punished for it the next day by being awake for about 24 hours even if I am tired after 18.

I am currently trying Magnesium Citrate and 5-HTP which are showing some early signs of being useful, have you tried those? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 signs that your insomnia may actually be sleep apnoea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 15:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is insomnia just your natural sleep pattern? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 12:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seasonal Affective Disorder and insomnia: Why do we live in the dark? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 16:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Insomnia and acupuncture: don’t waste your money </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 11:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sleeping pills are useless and even dangerous! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 11:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sleep Restriction Therapy for insomnia – more harm than good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 04:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
