<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9683</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cavs trade 3 non-guaranteed deals, Dwight Powell to Celtics for Keith Bogans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 01:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul George can now put weight on leg, back to doing upper body work in gym </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 00:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BREAKING NEWS(no pun intended): Rajon Rondo broke his hand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 00:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GameTime: Paul George Interview On Broken Leg Injury | September 23, 2014 | NBA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 08:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 12:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you really knew me, you'd think I look really stupid.
I'm actually very shy and only show my wacky, crazy, loopy, Hopsin(Ill Mind 4), energetic side around people i know well, and the internet is my second home sooooo yea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ariana Grande - You Don't Know Me Lip Sync </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 12:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Unusual Year Of Paul George! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 23:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **All The Crazy Things That Happened to PG or PG did**

* Was in the MVP Race
* Dating Doc River's daughter
* Supposedly impregnated Callie Rivers(Doc's daughter)
* Impregnated stripper, Daniela Rajic.
* That 360 WINDMILL DUNK!!!
* Supposedly had sex with Roy Hibbert's wife/fiancée
* Became Instagram/Twitter's most popular fisherman(imo)
* Lost his mentor(Danny Granger), to a trade.
* Struggled a bit (in last 2 months/playoffs) not as bad as Roy
* Verbal fight with Wizard's Fans
* The Concussion
* Set offseason goal to get more physical: "No More McDonalds"
* Suffered compound fracture in right leg. (tibia, fibula)
* Buys a Ferrari
* Announces number change to 13, imminent on return.
* Officially changes social media usernames to YGTRECE
* Does Ice Bucket Challenge
* Calls out fake instagram account of himself.
* Make Ray Rice comments
* Apologizes

Did i Miss any??? **Comment What I Missed Below**

**EDIT:**(what i missed, thanks for the comments)

* Catfished by gay guy
* Got Robbed 
* Made USA team
* Carried team to Conf. Finals despite team struggles
* 3rd most in allstar votes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 22:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 02:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pekovic isn't a great defensive player either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pacers sign D-League All Star Forward: Arinze Onuaku </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 02:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 20:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U got Kik? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 20:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the end of the day Salmons, Stiemsma, heck even Kwame Brown and Smush Parker all of them  Andrea Bargnani. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 19:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what if Bennett plays to full potential, you could have Brewer, Martin, Thad-Young, and maybe trade Pekovic and Barea for a good backup Center or PG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 21:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, The Knicks and Kings have a much better chance of getting Rondo, if we trade anyone, we're done. Let's see how Hibbert and West lead the team this year. Maybe Stuckey can put up big numbers, his stats when he got starter minutes were just slightly worse than D-Wade this season. Let's hope Solomon Hill is a decent player. Lastly, let's hope Solomon Hill doesn't become the most improved player and Larry Bird does something stupid like trade PG, like they did with Granger, and let's hope they don't trade Hibbert for Monroe, cuz Monroe is only gonna demand a huge contract or leave in free agency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 23:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get too fancy, I would recommend at most, a free throw line finger roll, to look like you're gliding. Jump from as far as you can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 22:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Singleton, but I feel like Dahntay Jones, Jordan Crawford, or Ronnie Brewer would've been better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JENNIFER LAWRENCE NEWS: RIP 80% of the Internet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 17:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 17:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> idk if firstrowsports.eu has fiba, but u can try </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 17:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another thing i forgot to add, is
If i make another Cavaliers Mix in the future.

What would like to see?
1. LeBron 
2. Love 
3. Irving
4. All 3?
5. Waiters
6. Other (comment suggestion) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kevin Durant - The New Breed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 15:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lAYtyt_811U </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 16:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for your sympathy...
...but i thought Joel Embiid was coming back later this season?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 16:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) i made it, glad u enjoyed it, im a pacers fan, but i cant wait to see what he can do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 16:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we should waive Rasual Butler or Donald Sloan 

i really want to see some better players :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best Players To Sign? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 15:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking since we didn't get Shawn Marion (the next juwan howard, riding the bench for rings)

Maybe Dahntay Jones, Ronnie Brewer??

or should we go for more offense? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Embiid Trailer: Joel Embiid - The Beginning Is Nigh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 15:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 14:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but people could troll youtubers who upload things to their second channels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 12:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it looks like this for me http://prntscr.com/4hld2c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joel Embiid - The Beginning Is Nigh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 09:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 14:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really late, but I'm really nice:

Enjoy(even tho it's a fake pic):http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-9kPCkTpAsOE/UcBS6cwWMBI/AAAAAAAAAKU/lB9OfpMu-C4/s1600/191746700_Selena_Gomez_The_Big_OMG_fini_Swimtrun_123_357lo.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch my video, i think you all will like it, considering stupidity is laughable on the interwebs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 08:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How To Play Pokemon On iPhone Android and Windows Phone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 23:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-29 07:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I don't know if people are still looking at this. But....without further ado..

My name is Tim, I posted gaming videos, sometimes Chatroulette trolling, and occasionally a tutorial. 

I do have a capture card for PS3 gaming, but I need to buy HDMI Cables and PS3 HD/AV Component cables

I'm only 15, and I've had a YouTube account since I was 9 lol, but this channel isn't the one from 2007, I made this to start a new chapter in life.

I struggle with depression and anxiety like many teens but I'm also very socially awkward so YouTube is my way to escape from reality, somewhat.

I don't really like posting just gameplay, I like to discuss thing, I'm just not a vLog person so, I commentate over gameplay.

I hope you enjoy my content and subscribe.
Remember it's not an obligation, only subscribe if you like it.

www.youtube.com/user/MrEXGamingTV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 05:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol Nintendo is like Nokia...#unbreakable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 04:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever thought of embracing the fact that you made a mistake. For instance, I once did something on instagram that made me look gay in front of most of my friends, but I eventually embraced it, if I accidentally did something "homo" I'd just say "oh well I guess I'm gay" and people would laugh. Soon everyone forgot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
