<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2704</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 21:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty new to knitting this scarf and the other Gryffindor one I made are my first creations hah...  I believe I used a 16" round needle for the entire scarf. Used a crochet hook to place the tassels. As for the yarn I just picked two colours I liked of the same thickness. I used different thickness for the Gryffindor one than the slytherin same needles though I prefer my scarves to be knitted in the round that way they are double thick with no ugly side c: I can provide the knitting pattern if anyone is interested.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 11:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snake needed an xray c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 07:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nymeria after the dire wolf from asoiaf
And orochi after the dragon for okami c: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> finished my slytherin scarf for myself made a Gryffindor one for my bf too c: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 06:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 06:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a royal python if anyone wanted to know  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> took an xray of a snake at work, thought you lovely snake lovers would enjoy it as much as me c: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 06:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 07:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do it usually to help shed, mine however goes in there to soak and then she poops lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 07:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well we also sedated him c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 01:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We used a bolt cutter to remove it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> dog at work got this stuck on his face </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 01:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 01:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks c: 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 18:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recommend removing all substrate and replacing with paper towel till mites are gone, give all the hides a good wash in scalding water. As for the spray I'd has an ivomec spray and give the snake an ivomec injection if you can it works the best and is easily available at local vet clinics    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 18:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's a salmon boa and her and her name is Nymeria. This is the first time I've seen her soaking on her own c. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> my baby soaking herself for once </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 18:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 17:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work at a zoo as a veterinary technician and I also do animal husbandry ect. All the animals at my zoo receive a very high level of care. There's very careful guidelines that have to be followed to remain a member of caza! We clean daily, sometimes more then once, feed multiple times and different ways and provide extra enrichment daily as well all the animals I work with daily are very happy and well cared for. Medical issues are dealt with by the veterinarian right away. I can't speak for all zoos but the one I work at is great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> a dog learned a hard lesson today when he came to my work with this stuck to his jaw. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 21:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
