<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8683</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am a somnophiliac. Sleeping women give me a boner. AMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-05 00:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Somnophilia

I have a sexual fetish that is fueled by sexual encounters (touching, kissing, simply looking, etc.) with a woman who is sleeping or unconscious, solely based on the fact that she is sleeping or unconscious. Basically, narcolepsy is my biggest turn-on. If I'm so much as in the same room with a good-looking, sleeping woman, you can bet I'll get a huge boner just from watching her sleep.

I also watch a lot of sleep fetish porn, and I have acted on this fetish in real life (with consent).

Ask me anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Math lessons from Professor Hobbes. (tigers are great at math. It's instinct-- tigers are born with it) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 23:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you respond when someone asks "How are you?", and what's the best response you've heard from someone else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 23:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My response: "I'm good, thanks. Yourself?"

My favorite response from someone else: "Not bad for an old man." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I thought of 10 Guy as soon as my friend said this to me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 16:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many of you are like me and haven't accomplished much because no one realized you were depressed at the time when you most needed help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-03 23:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been depressed for at least ten years. I lost the only job I had about a year and a half ago and haven't been able to find work since. I didn't graduate from high school because I was in too shitty of a mood to even go most of the time, and when I did, I couldn't focus.

I've had one girlfriend (who was only with me because she was desperate), and almost my entire family thinks of me as "The one who sits in the dark basement all day and doesn't talk to anyone."

I wanted to be a writer when I was around 13-15 years old (23 now), and I started numerous novels, but never came close to finishing any because I lacked the drive, motivation and commitment needed for something of that nature. I've written a single article for some site you've never heard of, got good feedback on it, but still find myself unable to do anything significant in that regard.

I've been on anti-depressants for two months. I stopped taking them recently because I couldn't afford to pay for them anymore. I felt no different while taking them, and I feel no different quitting them cold turkey.

Anyone else? Anyone at all in this position? Or at least a similar one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Most Intoxicated Man In The World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-03 23:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Karma Whore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-03 19:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone noticed that Calvin generally ignores when people refer to Hobbes as a stuffed animal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-03 17:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would think, if Hobbes is a real tiger in Calvin's world, he'd take exception or at least say something about it. But he just sort of shrugs it off every time.

Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE call people by names they don't prefer, because you like that name better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-03 17:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad Luck Brian's plans for the night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-03 06:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you most commonly start and end phone calls? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-02 16:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To this day, I still can't believe I did this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-02 15:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: I'm a 23-year-old male. I've never masturbated. I've never experienced an orgasm. I've never ejaculated (while awake). I am essentially immune to blue balls. How is this possible? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-02 01:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a virgin-- the one woman I have had sex with gave me no stimulation through intercourse. I didn't feel anything. She felt a lot though. Ask our neighbors _

She gave me oral and handjobs, however, which were amazing. But I never came. I never had an orgasm. I just felt like I was going to explode the whole time, but I never ever came. Not once.

I feel fine. Other than, you know, chronic depression. But my balls feel absolutely fine. I don't get any pain down there or anything.

How is this possible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm 23 years old, I've never masturbated, I'm not a virgin, I've never had an orgasm, and I have frequent wet dreams. AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-01 15:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a wet dream last night. Prompted me to make this. I could sort of feel it when it happened, but I was like half asleep (closer to being asleep than awake), so I didn't really do anything. I just let it happen and fell back asleep.

**EDIT:** I am a male. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2007 New England Patriots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-01 13:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For one of the only I times I can ever remember, I find myself disagreeing with Hobbes.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-01 02:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I only wanted some bacon... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-30 21:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ever since I started feeling a little strung-out lately, with the release of NBA 2K13 nearing... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-30 14:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love how Calvin's intelligence for his age makes it difficult to explain "Little kid" concepts to him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-30 11:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worst Day Ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-30 06:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good Guy Greg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-29 18:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the Rocky movies, the fighters often exchange punches without even attempting to block their face with their hands/arms. Which part(s) of famous movies do you recall being very unrealistic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-29 01:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're supposed to say "I don't get it." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-29 00:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The NBA is going to start giving players fines for flopping? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-29 00:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We still say "God bless you" or "gesundheit" when someone sneezes, even though it's common knowledge that a sneeze is not a premonition of anything fatal. What other traditions exist that don't really make sense under the surface? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-28 21:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE wish they had a personal chef, but would be too scared that they'd poison your food? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-28 15:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I listen to a lot of rap music, and I swear this happens at least once in every song </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-27 12:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How do "butterflies" (in your stomach) help when you're in a situation that causes you to feel them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-26 22:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually, when most people feel butterflies, they become nervous and unable to perform the task at hand (talking to a beautiful woman, playing in a significant sporting event, fighting, etc.) as well as if they didn't have butterflies.

Am I right to assume that most bodily functions such as this occur because of evolutionary traits that were at one time useful? If so, how exactly does this help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A collection of Calvin's polls on his dad's position as "Dad" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-26 18:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skeptical Third World Kid doesn't like pranks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-26 15:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post your favorite non-last-panel gags from Calvin and Hobbes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-26 03:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Calvin: Are you mad?!
* Mom: I *will* be, if you don't hop to it.

http://assets.amuniversal.com/054af702250a102d94d7001438c0f03b

* Dad: Next time we should take the tiger and forget the kid.

http://assets.amuniversal.com/3563f4f8250e102d94d7001438c0f03b

* Mom's reaction to being told that Calvin is inventing a robot to make his bed and wants a grant (3rd panel):

http://www.gocomics.com/calvinandhobbes/1989/08/30

* Calvin: What could possibly go wrong?!
* Hobbes: Whenever you ask that, my tail gets all bushy.

http://assets.amuniversal.com/070ae0802509102d94d7001438c0f03b </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm forever alone... but willingly. Am I an anomaly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-25 00:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off, for reasons I don't think are necessary to discuss, whenever I find a woman who's willing to put up with me, I get *extremely* attached. I'm not the type to constantly call or want to be around a girl, but when I am around her, I smother her. I touch her, I hold her, I tell her to hold me, and I basically give her no room to breathe. I know it's annoying, but I can't help it. It just happens.

On top of that, I'm extremely fucked up psychologically. I'm clinically depressed and possibly bipolar. I'm very sensitive emotionally, which can lead to a lot of conflict in a relationship.

I also hate intercourse. I'd much rather spoon or grope a woman all night long than have sex. Weird, I know. I really have no idea why I am this way. And I'm not assertive in any way in the bedroom. I prefer the woman to be aggressive. Turns out that most women want the opposite.

All in all, almost nothing about me is conducive to a happy, healthy relationship. I used to mope and be angry about this, but I've pretty much accepted my fate as a forever alone.

Is there anyone else out there like this? Or am I *truly* forever alone in this regard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I thought my first kiss with my first girlfriend was a beautiful, magical moment. Turns out, it felt to her as if I was eating her face like a donut. When have you discovered that a great moment in your life was actually horrible for the other person/people involved? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-24 15:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't believe someone I know said to me "lol, I just realized I have an Xbox 360" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-24 15:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When's the last time you were embarrassed because you were unaware that people could see you doing something? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-24 14:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't understand the strip in which Calvin's dad talks to Calvin about a record player </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-24 01:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I feel when I eat slower than my friends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-23 11:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High Expectations Asian Father adopts John Cena </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-23 11:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I was younger, my parents wouldn't let me watch Looney Tunes because Foghorn Leghorn spoke such bad English (saying things like "I'm gonna learn ya how to _____"). What rules did you have to follow growing up that you now realize were kind of silly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-23 09:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sometimes I wish there was some sort of uniform "internet text" default </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-23 09:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel like a lot of people probably go through this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 12:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My ex did this to me. I think "Overly Attached" doesn't do her justice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 01:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something about you that is viewed as negative, even though you feel it shouldn't be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 20:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, I don't think I can bear going to my cousin's funeral tomorrow. How (if it's even possible) can I tell my family without seeming insensitive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 14:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was really close to my cousin-- we're both around the same age (23-25), and he was a really happy, mellow, down-to-earth guy. He made people laugh and didn't bother anyone, and I always loved hanging out with him (and I usually hate being around people in general-- that goes for everyone, even my close family).

I got the news on Sunday, and it's taken me until about a day or two ago to finally be able to handle it and try to live my life normally, but I'm still struggling. I'm afraid that if I go to the funeral, it will just devastate me all over again, and I dread having to feel that pain ever again.

What can/should I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE realize that they read a lot faster than their friends? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-19 11:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend is playing Madden 13, and he just got an Achievement. When he hit the Xbox guide button to see what it was, I read the description in about a second. He left it up for at least four seconds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just slept for 18 1/2 hours. What's the longest time you can ever remember sleeping, and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-19 03:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Think of the person in your life that you're closest to. If this person put a loaded gun to your head and asked you to trust them not to pull the trigger, would you? Why or why not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-19 03:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You can erase one emotion from your psyche forever. You will never know what it feels like. You'll forget that you ever felt it. No situation will ever cause you to feel this emotion. What do you choose and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 14:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_emotions#Parrott.27s_emotions_by_groups

You can choose what's listed as a primary, secondary, or tertiary emotion. Up to you.

I get the feeling that "Longing" might be a popular choice. Maybe some Redditors want to be a super badass and will choose "Compassion" to get back at people who wronged them without regretting it.

Of course, "Sadness" would be a good choice as well, for obvious reasons.

What say, Reddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just realized that life is one big, sick, macabre joke (warning: morbid) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 12:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In life, you have two options-- die before the people you love, or watch the people you love die, knowing you can do nothing about it.

What a choice. I can't deal with this. I have no idea what the hell to do. I'm considering finding a way to live far away from everyone who knows me, and forging no new relationships with anyone there. I can't go through the grief of losing a loved one again-- I'm too sensitive emotionally. And I can't imagine my family seeing me on an autopsy table, unmoving... dead.

I can't fucking do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "He never risked shit-- he hoped and he wished it, but it didn't fall in his lap, so he ain't even here."- Eminem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 10:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking of himself in a verse that describes a hypothetical "alternate universe," I suppose, in which Marshall Mathers didn't have the will to pursue his rap career.

Full lyrics:

http://www.azlyrics.com/lyrics/bob/airplanespartii.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you think ancient man felt when trying to figure out mysteries of the universe? When trying to understand life, death, etc.? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 09:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think he wondered when he viewed the death of another human being? What did he think was the difference between a dead body and a living one? When looking into the sky and seeing stars, and attempting to understand simple concepts like day and night, or abstractions like life and our place in the universe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've never seen any man in my family ever cry, with one exception. Is that why I can't cry myself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 09:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My cousin just died in a car accident... please make me feel better </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-16 20:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to do anything I can to take my mind off of it, but all I can do is hear my dad's words over and over again in my head.

"James was killed in a car accident..."

"We just came from the morgue..."

"He looked like he was sleeping..."

My cousin and I were as close as brothers. I have no idea how I'm going to possibly deal with this. My body feels like it wants to sob profusely, but I just can't... I feel like I'm going to throw up, but I can't do that, either...

I don't know what to do... please make me feel better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why does eating after taking a pill help the pill take effect? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-16 16:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unfortunately, happened to me. I even got one as I was making this meme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-16 01:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ever since I started taking anti-depressants, I've been experiencing sometimes-random, extremely intense head tingles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-15 15:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They either happen at completely random times, or when I see/hear/think of something funny or interesting. They get so intense sometimes that I get dizzy and lose my balance (but I haven't actually fallen because of it). At that point, I usually just have to "shake the cobwebs" and it goes away.

You might be thinking that it's not head tingles that I'm feeling, but I've experienced head tingles for a *very* long time (I remember my first one was because of a girl I liked in kindergarten), so I know what they feel like.

It's very weird, but it's sort of an intriguing feeling, because I was not aware at all that ASMR could be this intense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I still don't know why so many people try it. We just outnumber them too much. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-15 14:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calvin subtly explains the concept of slang </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-14 20:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me, five minutes into an attempt to make a gourmet dinner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-14 15:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am a somnophiliac. Sleeping women give me a boner. AMA (repost from a week ago). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 06:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Somnophilia

I have a sexual fetish that is fueled by sexual encounters (touching, kissing, etc.) with a woman who is sleeping or unconscious, solely based on the fact that she is sleeping or unconscious. Basically, narcolepsy is my biggest turn-on. If I'm so much as in the same room with a good-looking, sleeping woman, you can bet I'll get a huge boner just from watching her sleep.

I watch sleep fetish porn (it's the only porn that can hold my attention), and I have acted on this fetish with multiple women in the past (with their consent, of course). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forgetful cashier rage (just happened) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 19:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the majority of the population was left-handed, how would the world be different? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 02:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would doorknobs be on the left? Would we drive on the left side of the road instead of the right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scumbag DMX </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-10 15:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else resent hearing anyone talk about his/her boy/girlfriend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-10 14:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get instantly raged (internally only) whenever I see anyone say the words "my boyfriend" or "my girlfriend," anywhere at all, whether I know the person or not.

Yes, I have a problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is it attractive for an attractive member of the opposite to be dripping wet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-09 14:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being wet isn't comfortable, nor is it conducive to sex. It'd be a hassle to clean, the person who's wet would be cold, and the person who's dry would be getting wet needlessly.

Yet, this:

http://www.blocsuite.com/home/wp-content/uploads/Shenese6.jpg

Is considered attractive (even if you don't find the girl in general attractive, stay with me anyway).

Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My sister and her husband are getting evicted on the 15th and they want to move in with me-- tell me if I'm wrong for saying no. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-08 10:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am a somnophiliac (sleep fetishist). AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 19:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Somnophilia

I have a sexual fetish that is fueled by sexual encounters (touching, kissing, etc.) with a woman who is sleeping or unconscious, solely based on the fact that she *is* sleeping or unconscious. Basically, narcolepsy is my biggest turn-on. If I'm so much as in the same room with a good-looking, sleeping woman, you can bet I'll get a huge boner just from watching her sleep.

I watch sleep fetish porn (it's the only porn that can hold my attention), and I have acted on this fetish with multiple women in the past (with their consent, of course).

A note: Before anyone asks, yes, this is a re-post. I enjoy answering questions about this and I find that people like asking about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you in particular (or someone you know) have any external stimuli that consistently affects your dreams? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 22:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, some people believe that spicy food and junk foods can cause nightmares.

I've noticed that whenever I take sleep aids, I tend to have extremely long, very vivid dreams that I can easily remember when I wake up.

Do you know of anything that you do before going to sleep that affects the content of your dreams, or whether or not you dream at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have no idea why we even came up with this abbreviation if we're not going to use it properly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-12 02:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Odds that my problems will be solved by obtaining a proper laptop charger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 11:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/techsupport/comments/wywgj/how_can_i_keep_my_motherboard_and_processor_from/

We figured out that using a different charger than the intended = bad. But right now, I'm very short on cash, and I can't afford to buy a new charger unless I'm *positive* that it will help my computer run better.

What think, r/techsupport? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am a 23-year-old male who has never masturbated in his entire life. Not once. AMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 01:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also haven't had any physical contact (let alone intimate contact) with a woman in over a year and a half. I've also never had an orgasm with the exception of frequent nocturnal emissions.

Ask me anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High Expectations Asian Father does not approve of John Cena </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-01 17:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I heard a foreign person say "This is an interesting new," and then it hit me... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-01 17:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of my friends found an envelope in her mailbox today. It was labeled with the name of someone she doesn't know, and there was $170 and a key in it. How would you handle this situation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-01 02:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has no idea what the key could be for, and she lives by herself-- before she moved in, no one with the name that was on the envelope lived there (previous tenant had been there for at least a decade). The envelope only had the name on it (no address, no stamp), so it was clearly not mailed.

What would you do, Reddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't think she heard it, though... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-01 02:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a forever alone with man-whore friends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-31 09:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Men: If you were raped by a woman, would you tell anyone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-31 07:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or would you be too embarrassed, due to the societal viewpoint that being raped by a woman makes a man look weak? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The cashier at a store near my house just asked me why I'm so happy all the time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-31 01:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has this ever happened to anyone else? Am I the only one who has a tendency to mask his depression in public (and apparently do a damn good job of it)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every time I see one of those "My boyfriend/girlfriend doesn't help me through my depression" posts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 20:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I did this last night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 19:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I still have no idea what he was trying to say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 18:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend literally just said this to me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 17:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does society perpetuate celebrity worship? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-28 04:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Society seems to think that if people make much more money than the average person and also appear on television as part of their job, they're somehow above us "normal" people. They get giddy and excited just to see these people, and if a celebrity so much as talks to someone or writes their name down for someone, OMG IT'S AMAZING I CAN'T BELIEVE IT

We treat these people as if they're demigods, then get upset/perplexed when their egos become huge. They're people just like us. They eat, sleep, and shit just like us. They do what they're good at to earn an income just like us.

But apparently, talking to a celebrity or getting an autograph is a big deal, even though there's absolutely no tangible or intangible benefit of doing so. Meeting an actor, a pro athlete, etc., doesn't make someone's life better, but society has brainwashed us into thinking that's the case.

Again, they're just people doing what they're good at to make a living. Nothing more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE have no idea how people confuse "dominate" and "dominant" on the internet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-28 01:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am soooooooo high right now... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 20:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... I think. I have no idea, since I've never been drunk or high on recreational drugs before.

I was recently prescribed an antidepressant called "vilazodone" by my doctor, and I started taking them two days ago (today was the third day I've taken it). Ever since I started using them, I've been feeling really, really weird (strange too, considering that I was told, and have heard, that these things take at least a month to work).

Anyway, since taking it for the first time, I feel the strangest combination of the following:

* Slight nausea
* Lightheadedness/dizziness (sometimes feels like my head is "spinning")
* Fatigue
* Horniness

I have no idea if this is normal or not, or even if it's a placebo effect at work, but... it feels sooooooo goooooood... _

I'm not at all concerned or asking for a diagnosis. Just bored and thought maybe someone would find this funny/intriguing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you believe it's possible to commit a murder and leave no evidence of the crime? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 10:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that, with modern forensics, it's impossible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You'll never catch Kobe Bryant saying this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 10:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why was it so easy for me to get a prescription for antidepressants? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-25 23:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to the doctor's office for an infection in my finger, got that taken care of, and then asked him about possible psychiatric treatments for my depression.

He asked me 7 or 8 questions from a questionnaire about my general emotional state and afterwards, I was prescribed vilazodone and given a starter kit.

I could have easily lied on the questionnaire, considering it was obvious how the questions were structured and how I'd have to answer them to give the impression that I'm depressed.

Am I missing something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The gift and curse of never masturbating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-25 23:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE see a group of people (be it large or small) doing/saying something stupid, but choose not to speak up because you know it's a battle you can't win? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-25 01:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unfortunately, every time I get into a heated argument with a friend or family member </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-24 22:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sign-up rage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-24 18:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every single time I lie over something petty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-24 16:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you can't touch type, just take your time... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-24 08:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just say "Midnight" and go with it... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-23 17:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I personally always picked "Truth"... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-22 17:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can I keep my motherboard and processor from overheating (I already use a laptop cooler)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-22 17:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a specific make and model (Dell Precision M6400) that I think has problems with overheating in these two areas. I'm already using a laptop cooler, and right now, without really doing anything except surfing the internet, my CPU is at 63 C and the motherboard is at 69 C. When it gets to this point, it has trouble loading any videos at all and it feels extremely hot to the touch (may also be an issue with an overheating graphics card).

What can I do, if anything, to keep it cooler? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Most Depressed Man In The World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-22 03:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens when you combine Forever Alone and depression (first-- be nice) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-22 02:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate it when parents do this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-20 15:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://assets.amuniversal.com/106a4fac250a102d94d7001438c0f03b

Then again, Calvin's such a little rotter that you might feel like ignoring him isn't the worst thing his parents could do o_o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am a somnophiliac. AMA (repost from two weeks ago). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-19 22:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy answering questions about this, so I wanted to field another AMA. I'm kind of bored. Anyways...

Somnophilia is a sexual fetish associated with extreme attraction to a partner who is sleeping or unconscious solely because of the fact that they are sleeping or unconscious. This is not a rape fetish-- taking a partner against his or her will has nothing to do with this.

I watch lots of sleep sex porn (it's the only porn that can keep my attention) and yes, I've fooled around with women as they sleep (with their prior consent).

Ask me anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do many redditors dislike reposts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-19 17:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with reposting the same content in the same subreddit, some time later? It's the only way to expose one's post to more people (and thus get more distinct responses) after the original has died. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone successfully been able to keep a workout routine while fighting depression? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-19 16:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It feels like my depression and my exercise regiment are constantly clashing. To work out consistently requires energy, willpower, and motivation, all of which the parasite known as depression feeds on. 

Sometimes I'll be fully rested but unable to work out because I don't have one or more of the above necessities. Does anyone have any suggestions as to what can help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am going to ask WWE Diva Beth Phoenix to go on a date with me in mid-September. AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-19 00:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, really.

I am more attracted to Beth Phoenix than I have been to any woman in my entire life, and I refuse to settle for admiring from afar.

Ask me anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least he wants to be clean... sort of... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-19 00:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am a 23-year-old male who has never masturbated in his entire life. Not once. AMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-17 21:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also haven't had any physical contact (let alone intimate contact) with a woman in over a year and a half.

**EDIT:** I've also never had an orgasm.

Ask me anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The worst part about never masturbating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-17 15:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An accurate summary of what it's like to be the youngest of three sons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-17 15:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Except my socks. Because that'd just be weird... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-16 14:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In my opinion, the greatest "Calvin and Hobbes" storyline of all time... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-16 14:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.gocomics.com/calvinandhobbes/1991/03/18

Things that stood out to me:

-At one point, Calvin (or at least the "real" Calvin combined with the "good" Calvin) smiles for 16 straight panels. I always look for stuff like that (I'm weird), and I can't remember another time he smiled for even four straight panels.

-Hobbes notes at the end of the story arc that Calvin is "The only person [he knows] whose good side is prone to badness." But, Watterson immediately asserts (through Calvin) that it might not have been simply a case of Calvin being so bad that not even the incarnate of his good side can't resist being evil.

Calvin claims that "He could only be perfectly good as an abstraction. In his human manifestation, he wanted to throttle me," implying that simply by being human, it was impossible for "Good Calvin" to be flawlessly benevolent. Watterson was clearly making a point about human nature and perhaps our inability to resist the allure of sin.

This is part of the reason I resent when people disregard Calvin and Hobbes as "just a newspaper comic." Both Watterson and his writing are extremely deep, and his ability to express fundamental truths about things like this, and the world overall, is the reason I've re-read all of the collections at least three times each. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In September, I plan to go to a wrestling show and ask WWE Diva Beth Phoenix on a date (yes, really). What can I do to maximize my chances of success? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-16 02:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fell for her the moment I laid eyes on The Glamazon. I adore her combination of physical strength and feminine beauty, and I refuse to admire from afar. I'm going after what I want.

Tell me how I can give myself the best chance to be successful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Part of the reason I'm an atheist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-16 01:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In an effort to gain weight, I've been living solely on peanut butter sandwiches and milk. What foods have you eaten exclusively for at least a two-week span, and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-16 00:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every time a girl signs off as soon as I send her a message </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-15 23:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was amazed as a child when my friend once said "Ass" in front of his parents and didn't get in trouble. What was/is allowed at your friend's house that you were absolutely forbidden to do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-15 13:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The worst is "Comment/sub and I'll release Part 2" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-14 22:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He's like their lovechild... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-14 12:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The one opinion upon which Calvin and Bill Watterson totally disagree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-14 12:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I never use umbrellas when it's raining (or at any time)-- to me, it's just water. What do you refuse to do that is very common amongst most people? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-14 12:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dwight Schrute is not an R. Kelly fan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-14 11:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Or maybe they just don't like cursing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-14 11:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> But only because I don't smoke or drink... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-14 11:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else love cloudy/rainy days? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-14 08:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it when I wake up in the morning and the sun isn't shining, and the sky is gray and cloudy and everything is just as dismal as it can be. 

And I absolutely LOVE rain. The stronger the downpour, the better. Sometimes I open my front door and just stare outside for the entirety of a thunderstorm. The sound the rain makes as it hits the ground, the dreariness, I just go crazy for it.

If your answer is "Yes," why do you think it is? For myself, I imagine it's for two reasons-- one, because I like to see nature matching my own mood (which is usually "Bleh"), and also because that type of weather keeps people from going outside, which I like (I hate people in general). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This may seem obvious, but please... if you know there's a good chance that the relationship won't last, for whatever reason, tell the other party ASAP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-14 07:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 23/M, just got quasi-dumped without even seeing the woman in person. I won't bother with details, since this isn't a blog... we met on Reddit, we clicked almost instantly, we started to fall for one another (as much as two people can who interact only through text), and then she told me that it's "inevitable" that she'll eventually forget about me once school starts.

I could live with being 3,000 miles away from her and probably never getting the chance to ever see her in person. I realized that from the start. But I thought at the very least, we could be long-term internet friends who occasionally send each other naughty messages.

But when she told me that our relationship was basically going to self-terminate in the near future, it hit me like a ton of bricks. I wasn't even mad at her... I was just disappointed at life.

I'm overly emotional for a guy, so it probably hurts a lot more than maybe it would for someone reading this, but I think, no matter what, something like this will almost always be painful.

So, please... if you find someone you like, and they like you back, for the love of all that is holy, **tell him/her not to expect a long-term relationship of any kind if you know that it won't work, for ANY reason at all**. Please. I don't want anyone else to feel like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I used to think it was ridiculous that Spider-Man could effectively "hide" by sticking to the ceiling. What aspect of a certain comic book did you eventually realize is more realistic than you thought? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-14 06:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was just silly that people couldn't see Spider-Man when he's on the ceiling. I'm like "He's right there! Just look up!" Then, through my own behavior, I realized that people in general tend to ignore the ceiling when they walk into any given room. There's no reason to acknowledge it-- it's just... there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I may have just driven a perfectly good person, and one of the best people I've ever known, to suicide or self-harm... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-14 04:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I met her on Reddit. We live on opposite ends of the country, so being together in person was never a realistic option. Even still, we hit it off. AIM chats full of kisses and 3s and sometimes naughty exchanges when we were feeling horny.

We made each other feel better when we were down and we tried our best to make sure neither of us stayed down for very long. I'm not afraid to say that we may have been falling for one another.

Earlier tonight, though, she told me that soon, we wouldn't be able to talk to me very much, since she starts school soon. I could feel the relationship starting to dissolve as soon as she said that, but I tried to be strong. I asked her to promise to try her best to not forget me, but she said she didn't want to, because it's inevitable.

It hurt badly, and I didn't know what to say. The fact that I didn't respond immediately seemed to worry her-- she said that she felt bad, but I tried to make us both feel better by flirting playfully. Eventually, she remarked that I was hers and hers only. I replied, without thinking, "Until you forget about me." It was a cry for help... I didn't mean it. I just wanted her to make me feel better about it.

She then told me she was going to leave, and even though I literally begged and pleaded, she still signed off. Usually, if I were to say "Please don't leave," she would become sympathetic and lovingly stick around, for me.

This time, she left without even acknowledging my pleas for her not to.

There's a giant knot in my stomach and I feel like my heart has been irreparably torn asunder. I feel like I don't deserve to live for what I may have just done, and I now have no way of contacting her outside of Reddit.

Please, if you're reading this... *please* come back to me. Don't do the unthinkable. I couldn't live with myself... just let me make it better... I promise I can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every single time the electricity won't come back on... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-14 01:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ladies of Reddit-- how much do you value height in regards to a man's attractiveness? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-13 15:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm about 6'4, and I've heard a few women say that they love it when men are as tall as I am. One even responded with "Fuck me now" when I told her how tall I am. I guess maybe I don't see it because I'm used to my height or because almost everyone in my family (and a lot of my friends) are tall. I dunno.

How much do you personally value height, ladies?

**EDIT:** Also, how tall is *too* tall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm sick of all these posts that say "Stop letting _____ get to you" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-13 11:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a nice message, but it's not realistic. Humans cannot perfectly manipulate their own emotions and make themselves feel however they want. If they could, no one would ever be sad or angry for more than 2 seconds at a time.

It reminds me of when parents tell their kids they can be whatever they want when they grow up. You don't really mean it-- you just say it so that they'll have confidence to go after what they want. The difference is, we're not kids, so don't treat us like it. Please don't patronize us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Once you click any part of the video, you've surrendered control... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-13 11:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I apologize, on behalf of my gender, to all the women who have been the victims of one night stands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-13 07:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I definitely did one part of this... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-12 21:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whenever I see other people with personality quirks similar to mine... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-12 16:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't possibly be the only one... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-12 15:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now that the Nets have moved too Brooklyn, they literally have at least two teams in every major US pro sport... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-12 15:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I like his a lot better than mine anyway... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-11 18:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post your favorite "Calvin and Hobbes" strip motifs and at least one example </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-11 17:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it when Calvin is interacting with another character, and through the first three panels, Calvin is visibly upset while the other character continues to bug him. Then, in the last panel, Calvin just explodes with anger.

http://cdn.svcs.c2.uclick.com/c2/4224a582250b102d94d7001438c0f03b
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the point of hiding the score of new posts if you can just go to the comments and see it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-10 15:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't wanna be that guy, but when Calvin is carrying Hobbes (as a stuffed animal)... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-10 14:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... what's actually happening in Calvin's world in which Hobbes is a real tiger? It's been established that Calvin struggles to keep Hobbes' weight on his shoulders (usually when giving him a boost). So when other characters see Calvin with stuffed-animal Hobbes over his shoulder, is he actually carrying him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do women like diamonds so much? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-10 00:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there more evidence for the existence of Bigfoot or the existence of God? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-09 22:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, we have the Patterson-Gimlin film in favor of Bigfoot, which still hasn't been completely debunked by science, whereas we have pretty much nothing visual for God or Jesus in that same regard. It seems that a lot more people believe in God than believe in Sasquatch, though.

I hope this post isn't breaking the rules-- just something I always thought about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You have no idea what hot is... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-08 22:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IAmA somnophiliac. AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-08 22:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somnophilia is a sexual fetish associated with extreme attraction to a partner who is sleeping or unconscious solely because of the fact that they *are* sleeping or unconscious. This is *not* a rape fetish-- taking a partner against his or her will has nothing to do with this.

I watch lots of sleep sex porn (it's the only porn that can keep my attention) and yes, I've fooled around with women as they sleep (with their prior consent).

Ask me anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do shooters/action games need sliders like sports games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-08 22:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sports games implement sliders that allow you to tailor the game almost exactly to your liking, and as a result, give yourself a unique experience based on your skill level and style of play.

Shooters and action games only offer different difficulties (as far as I know). If they offered adjustable sliders, like:

* User/AI bullet damage

* User/AI melee damage

* User/AI accuracy

* User/AI speed

etc., I think that these types of games would be a more fun experience for a lot of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Laptop overheats constantly, performs better when not plugged in </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-07 09:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Dell Precision M6400 with a 512MB NVIDIA Quadro FX 2700M. I think there's some sort of issue with the graphics card or the motherboard overheating-- I did some research but wasn't able to find anything definitive.

I had to buy a new charger after the original charger died, and the power brick on the new charger is way smaller than the original. It still fits in the laptop and charges it, but it takes forever to do so, and the laptop itself performs better when it's not plugged in. It never overheats while running on the battery, and I can actually watch 1080i videos without skipping.

I have a laptop cooler on which I constantly keep the laptop, but it still overheats randomly sometimes, but usually when I try to watch any video (it's like 50/50 as far as being able to watch a video without overheating).

When it overheats, it gets approximately as hot as the surface of the sun, and everything just kinda lags and the CPU Usage jumps to 100% and can stay there for minutes at a time. I've never had problems with the laptop shutting down due to overheating, however.

Any tips? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She must have been staring at that IM box for hours... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-03 13:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How every athletic big who plays with Chris Paul probably feels sometimes... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-03 13:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did you learn for the first time, by reading Calvin and Hobbes, that you remember to this day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-02 11:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I learned that girls have two X chromosomes, and whenever I want to make sure I'm remembering that fact right, I think of this strip:

https://thecomicninja.files.wordpress.com/2012/04/calvin-and-hobbes-x-chromosomes.gif?w=640

Calvin and Hobbes also introduced me to the concept of being avant-garde. I also learned certain words like:

* Theology
* Atrophy
* Somnambulism
* Stupendous (hey, I was young) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT Request: Help an insomniac doze off for a good night's sleep </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-02 09:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had trouble sleeping for a long time (mostly because of depression and anxiety), so I normally use OTC sleep aids, but I'm short on cash now and didn't have time to buy anymore after running out.

As a result, I've slept for about three hours in the last day and a half. Help me snooze. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's like an endless loop of scumbaginess </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-02 09:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just found out that I'm a somnophiliac. What's the general feeling towards this sexual fetish? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-02 06:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somnophilia is a sexual fetish associated with arousal by a sleeping/unconscious partner because of the fact that they *are* asleep/unconscious.

How do you feel about this? Would a fetish of this nature turn you off? Do you know anyone who has it? Do you personally have it (probably a long shot)? Any questions for someone who does (i.e., me)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [M4F] 23, Philadelphia. Fun-loving, somewhat quirky guy looking for female company, nearby or not </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-01 21:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been single for almost a year and a half, and I don't really go out much. I live alone, and it gets lonely here by myself. I'm kinda nerdy (as if that's not a given), and I've got a good, quirky sense of humor. I love talking about myself and my weird personality (but not in a conceited, all-about-me kinda way), and I love listening to others talk about themselves. I really enjoy meeting new people and learning more about them, and I'm not judgmental at all. I just like when people are willing to be themselves, since I'll do the same.

I don't drink or smoke, and stay in the house a lot, but I'm always up for trying new things. Even if you're not in my area (or even in my country), feel free to PM me. I'm down for anything from meetups to casual chats to harmless flirting and anything in between. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much value would I get at GameStop for the following? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-01 10:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Xbox 360 w/60 GB hard drive
NBA 2K12 (very good condition)
Madden NFL 12 (very good condition)
Wireless controller w/charger

I've tried finding someone I know, or someone who knows someone I know, to buy it since I'll undoubtedly get more profit from a personal transaction, but no one's budging. What would GameStop give me for this? I'm guessing approximately peanuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That gray timeline bar pisses me off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-29 21:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wish my Xbox Live friends would do this instead of just ignoring me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-29 07:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I go to bars/clubs to meet women? And how much does fashion affect the way a woman perceives a man? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-28 07:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really go out, so I don't have any dressy clothes (my clothes are in good shape, just not very formal). No button-ups, no nice pants (just black jeans), etc. I wouldn't want to go to a club in a t-shirt and jeans... would I? I would say my tees are nice, but a button-up would be better, obviously. I'd buy some collared shirts and stuff if I could, but I'm broke as all hell.

I don't even know if I should go to a bar or a club. I've never been to one in my life and none of my friends will go with me. Maybe I should go somewhere else to meet women (I don't have a job right now and I'm not in school)?

What think, seddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 23 [M4F] Philadelphia area - No woman has ever been able to give me an orgasm. Who wants a challenge? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-28 05:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going to pretend I'm some sort of sexual god-- I've just never had an orgasm. Everything else is fine. I get it up just fine, but I've never blown a load in my life (and I've some good, long-lasting sex/blow jobs/hand jobs/etc.).

I'm not necessarily asking for just sex or a FWB, but I have been feeling a little horny lately and I could use an outlet. I enjoy going down on women and using my mouth (and my tongue especially) in a lot of ways, so I won't ask you to do all the work. I also live by myself, so roommates/siblings/parents won't be an issue.

I'm a single black male, I stand about 6'3, and I've been told that I have "good hair" (it's curly and soft). I'm kinda slender with a sort of dark mocha complexion I guess. Around the same as Will Smith, I think.

Also, just in case people might not understand what I'm saying, I've never been with a man (I'm not gay, but I'm not homophobic, either). I just said "No woman" in the title to specify.

As I said, I definitely wouldn't mind an actual relationship, but I feel irresponsible if I didn't tell you I was feeling horny, and that's part of the reason I made this post.

Anyways, any ladies who want to see if they can be the first or are looking for a guy to spend time with in the Philadelphia area are free to send me a private message (or respond to this post if you want). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you have a crush on a celebrity? Would you be willing to ask him/her out on a date, or would you be too scared of being rejected/embarrassed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-27 06:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm pretty sure I desperately need therapy/medication, but I can't afford it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-27 05:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been terribly depressed for the last ten years, and I think I grew used to it eventually, so I never sought help when I could afford it. I've lost my most recent job since and have been applying for work over the last year and a half and have yet to be even considered by anyone. I have no money saved up and none coming in.

People have suggested to me that certain clinics will offer a sliding scale of payment based on your salary, but I have no salary.

How useful is 2-1-1? Would they be able to help someone in my position?

Any other suggestions? Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a software program that can be used to view GIF files? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-26 13:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a guy who wants his legs and forearms to be completely hairless. What are my best options and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-25 15:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you rather have a FWB who's your dream man/woman physically, or a boy/girlfriend who's only moderately attractive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-25 12:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's say the FWB will be a 10/10, and the boy/girlfriend will be a 7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't masturbate at all (ever) and I haven't had any contact with a woman in over a year. How is this possible? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-25 08:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 23-year-old male, and like I said, I haven't had any contact, let alone intimate contact, with a woman in a year and a half. I don't masturbate-- I never have, and I never feel a desire to. I get aroused sometimes, obviously, but I never feel the need to masturbate.

I was with my last girlfriend for about a year, and she couldn't make me ejaculate at all. She'd give me blow jobs and hand jobs, and I'd get erections, but I would never orgasm at all. During intercourse, I could make her cum, but not the inverse. I don't know if I don't like vagina or just didn't like hers. I haven't had sex with any other woman.

I've never felt an actual orgasm in my life, although I can say without a doubt that I've had wet dreams. How recently? I just woke up from one.

I thought everything I just described (i.e., no source of sexual release-- at least while awake) would lead to blue balls, but I don't think I have it. Is my body just compensating with the nocturnal emissions? Is living this way unhealthy (it doesn't really bother me at all)? I don't feel repressed sexually or anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does a man know if he has blue balls? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-25 05:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Administrative assistant" (read: secretary) out of work for nearly a year and a half </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-24 14:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had no luck at all even getting called in for any interviews-- the only times I did, I realized they were scams.

I have four years of work experience as an administrative assistant at the University of Pennsylvania, and I mostly apply to secretarial positions, but no one even considers hiring me. I use monster.com and Craigslist for the most part.

I've even gone to every place of business within about a mile of my house (no car), and they didn't get back to me. I've gone to my local mall... nothing.

Any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't help but wonder this every time I suggest it to my friends... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-24 13:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I feel on those "Meh" days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-24 12:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Probably because his parents wouldn't keep him around if he was... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-24 12:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maybe it means both... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-24 11:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you're the one making the call, you don't get to ask this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-24 11:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
