<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6494</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i love that one! i've read it so many times! Have you read NoEnd House? thats another one that i find equally well written </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll look into it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that sounds really creepy? The only two Stephen King books i have read are The Dome and The Stand. But this one sounds interesting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's a great question! i really think it depends on the crime, criminals age, current mental state, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its a haunted video game pasta, its alright, not terrifying by any means </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you! i look forward to reading it :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> about to read it right now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is it about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i've read squidward suicide and i find it really disturbing. could you send me a link to Ted the Caver? i havent read that one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that makes sense. I dont like to pull out the "self harm" card because i dont want to come off as unstable or attention seeking. I like to focus more on why and what is causing my depression as i know it has led to my self harm and anxiety </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best scary story/creepypasta you've ever read? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your opinion on the death penalty? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 04:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm so sorry that happened to you, stay strong :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 04:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pray? are you personally religious? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 04:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's a great idea, how can we get them to see this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 04:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> care to elaborate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 04:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that must have sucked, at least she was discreet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 04:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fair explanation. Do you think there is a way to differentiate teens from adults in this subreddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 02:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This used to happen to me a lot when i was full-out addicted to self harm and was trying to stop. I felt like i wasnt me without cutting. I've been clean for about a month now and i still get random urges to cut "for old times sake" its truly something difficult that we have to deal with </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats the worst experience you've had with someone finding your cuts? (TW?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 02:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in a summer production of "Chicago" and at rehearsal i was very overwhelmed. I went back into the dressing room and used a hanger to cut two thin lines on my wrist. Once I calmed down a bit and had paper towel wrapped around my wrist, a girl from the cast walked in. She gasped as she saw the blood-stained towel around my wrist. I tried to call out and stop her but she was gone. She ended up telling everyone in the cast and i was taken out of the show, as well as hospitalized for a week for "unstable behavior" what kinds of stories do you have? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 02:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fair enough, i only ask because its hard to explain where my depression came from and why i have it. People always assume i'm "exaggerating" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 03:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i can feel the same way, one moment i'm leveled and calm, and the next i feel like curling up on the ground and not talking to anyone. Its very hard for me to get out of these situations, if its possible to remove myself i always do. It's whats best in that situation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> acquired a new skill last night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-24 18:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-23 23:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely understand how you feel  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 21:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you! I unfortunately reside in high school, so when i have my attacks within school its very hard for people to know what is going on. My teachers handle it very well, but you can't expect every person in your school to be mature and respectful towards you, you know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else feel guilty after they have anxiety attacks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 19:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always feel guilty about what i do when i'm in the middle of an attack. When people try to help i always flinch away  terrified, like a wounded animal. Days later i have this lingering guilt and paranoia about what that person thinks of me now that they've seen me act this way. This only brings on more anxiety. Anyone else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 19:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it just interest me, this whole subreddit interest me a lot, somethings (like this) may be a little too much for me, but many other posts i thoroughly enjoy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 19:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm aware now, curiosity got the best of me, can you blame me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-21 04:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish i had a cat or dog to help me, as i know they are proven to help people with depression, but its not something that is available to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-21 02:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is really well done, i spent an hour or two getting through it, ive ended up exactly where i am right now. It makes me feel a little better knowing that it's all "normal"

(P.S a little part of me got attached to the kitten in the story, i think ill have to get myself one) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-20 23:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i dont know what to feel, i stumbled across this and i am a mere 14 years old. im shaking....most things dont faze me either but this....i cant even think right now.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-20 21:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BAD VIBES BAD VIBES </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its mind blowing to me, really, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 03:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 02:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i personally loved Toy Story 3, it was a tear-jerker for me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite Disney Movie of all time and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 02:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 02:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like my coffee like i like my women,

without a dick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 02:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hide and seek with you friends someone abandoned  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 02:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i was aloud to sleep over at boys houses all my life. As long as i said i wasn't "dating" said boy i had no restrictions on where i went and where i slept. You can see how my young immature self took advantage of that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-13 04:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 03:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that "God" was always watching so i showered with shorts and a tank top on until i was probably 10.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 02:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no matter where you are, who you are, or what you do, there is always someone who hates your guts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 02:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to be a pirate princess warrior from space

im still working out the kinks but i def working on it
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 02:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it really grinds my gears when i fuck bitches and dont get money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 03:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i do! it is that of a mouse :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is one physical and one emotional trait you love about yourself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 03:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lets spread self love and confidence. 

i love my eyes and my sneeze! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 03:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my ability to help others work through their problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The last thing i expected to see at school </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 03:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 02:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are tons of amazing stories on this thread, and it kind of makes me feel a little boring. I spent my last day on my roof listening to The Strokes.  I had taken enough pills to (what i thought) end me, and i just relaxed. though suicide is not a light subject, i do admit what was supposed to be my  last day was very peaceful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-13 03:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you could menstruate with lipstick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
