<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4305</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do ultra rare almost mythical books actually exist in some secret collectors circle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Movies and books love to use the idea that ultra rare almost mythical text exist and are sought after by some super rich illuminate type collectors. Are there any actual cases of this? Books that pop up from time to time and biders go crazy over or we'll know text that are thought to be lost but rumored to still exist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 23:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always ment to make a playlist like this and this song sometime around midnight.( http://open.spotify.com/track/7Hn0bZgca6QFz6OyKkvAi6 )would be at the top of the list.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 22:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Living in a college town. After about 25 you reliZe all the people your age either move out of town or get married and settle down. On the plus side if you don't mind dating 18+ there is always a new batch every September.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Nsfw) Bandit shot in the eye during bus robbery. xpost- r/wtf - u/FluffyZebras </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 08:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 08:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally thought I was gonna open a r/justiceporn link. The fact that he's a bandit makes this so much easier to wach, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 05:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got a circumcision at age 32.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] Crazy bar/lounge in the movie Enter the Void and in ASAP rocky a video L$D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 00:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the movie Eter the Void and in ASAP rocky a video for LSD there is a super crazy looking lounge. I'm pretty sure it's in Tokyo but my research has turned up nil. Here are a few pics.
http://factmag-images.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/06/videos-524-616x440.png
http://www.thehydramag.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/11/backofhead.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 06:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The kill list, such a solid crime movie that takes this super WTF turn at the end. Super good worth the watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 15:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fit couple

http://imgur.com/a/39nsK

Credit to U/lobo2ffs
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 17:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I get mad or irritated I roll my tongue under itself and bite down. Done it ever since I was a kid.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 20:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Working at a co-op grocery store or whole foods type store tend to draw the more hippy/hipster folk. Often, deep compassionate, sometimes misguided and naive but happy and a pleasure to be around for the most part.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 11:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bucket list for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> destiny map inspired tattoo (need help) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 21:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super Tits! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 02:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> super tits! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 02:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd  like more than a 10 song collection. I always thought that there should be records or tapes hidden through the world that you could collect, turn in, and they would be added to the playlist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 05:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Arcade shit" I'm gonna start using that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 01:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so metal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 10:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, made my night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 07:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im waiting for one of the two kids to pipe up "dude that's me on the left in the photo, check it out here's the pick from my perspective." Reddit destiny and shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 23:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My high energy playlist. A mix of everything with a kick.
http://open.spotify.com/user/1260051296/playlist/3DSJUXLTZCmLf9WV11euJD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 21:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once woke up with a horrible foot cramp but was having a gout flair up at the same time so the pain from the gout made me unable to move my foot to uncramp it and it was this vicious cycle of cramp/gout pain for about ten minutes till it finally worked itself out. Fuck gout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 05:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a legit question, maybe there is just so much porn on the Internet that given a chance for a random image the odds favor porn. Id like to see a ELI5 on this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any one else ajusting their gym routine so Tuesday is their rest day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 23:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 03:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a you young boy I saw The Cure, brad renfro and the young boy from Jurassic park, about two youths trying to find a cure to one of the boys HIV. I was not emotionally ready for that.

As an adult I had a friend recommend the boy in stripped pajamas, I put it on all willie nillie not knowing what I was getting into. Again I was not prepared. *sigh*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 17:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the greatest sets ever. Always been one of my favorites. Wish we could see her now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else having issues with destiny LFG app </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 03:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I'm getting is a blank index and no options to post. I've tried re-downloading the app but no luck. Any one else have/had issues?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> any one else having trouble with the destiny lfg app. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 01:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 00:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shannon Figa. Oldie but goodie.

Keep it up though great shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
