<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject765</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My perfect apple today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recant my foolishness and endorse a Baratheon stag surrounded by flames or a flayed stag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Petition to change the downvote button to a Stark wolf! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does Dreadfort feel about this much needed change? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 03:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 03:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burlingame, CA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 02:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> plus too old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 02:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what else won't get old? Olly....after I kill that motherfucker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know there are growers, not showers; but are there showers, not growers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 23:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you opened your belt your dog was like "God dammit. Jacking it again?!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 06:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dad telling me to lie and then telling me to tell the truth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 18:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A while back my Aunt got me and my father tickets to a baseball game for father's day. They were for both of us but she gave the tickets to me so they were my responsibility. The day of the game she texted me "How's the game?". The only problem was that...we forgot to go. We had been looking forward to it for a while but the day of we just both completely blanked. (She gave us the tickets a little over a month prior).
I was sitting with my dad when we got that text but it was already too late to make it in time. He told me to tell he we're having a great time and I agreed because we thought it would have been insulting to say that we forgot (We didn't want to look like the gift didn't mean anything to us because it did).
Around 20 minutes and a lot of cussing in frustration from both of us later he says that I should tell her the truth. *I* should tell her the truth. I take full responsibility for forgetting about the game (well, 96%. I was his present too!), but he told me to lie to her! My question: Is my dad the asshole? We ending up telling the truth which was the right thing to do (and she was understanding), but in this situation was my dad in the wrong to tell me to tell her the truth after he told me to lie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like he could really use a brother right about now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 16:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think about if he wasn't your brother. Would you be putting up with his crap? Probably not. But, as his brother you still have a duty to do what you can to help him. That doesn't mean letting him sleep for free in your home, but take him to AA meetings if the drinking is a serious problem, help him find a home he can afford and at the very least talk to him, he sounds lonely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 16:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try your best not to lead her on. Opening the snapchats is telling her you're still interested (even in you're only interested in her body). I would suggest not opening the snapchats anymore. That being said I don't believe you are an asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 06:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with most of what you said until the end. I don't believe she is entitled or spoiled, or rather I don't think you have the ability to gather enough information from the text to make that assumption. What I do think is that she is a kid with maybe a little bit of a quick temper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 06:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like this girl was trying to get a reaction out of you and has been for the past few weeks. Are you an asshole for letting her get under your skin? I don't think so. Should you have said that? Probably not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like you made him really happy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Calming intensifies*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 00:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Portal 1 ending song will always have a place in my heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 00:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *burrrrrrn*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burlingame! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to join the Democratic party </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why "flammable" and "inflammable" mean the same thing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 05:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 23:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's ok, simple misunderstanding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 23:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually his name is Bret, not Brett </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 08:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> .....no....Pork sausage!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: Majestic SF Puppy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 01:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: Majestic SF Puppy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 01:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 04:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of up and coming talent in this thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 17:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the whistle blows for a foul on the floor, players stop playing; Unlike in football, when there is a flag in a play players keep playing. The only thing I could think of would be after a foul players could have like a 3 second time window where the play continues and they have a free shot of some sorts. If they make it, the foul is declined, if they miss it, they rewind the clock and he gets his shots, but that seems too complicated to be doing consistently throughout a game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 00:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we all forgetting Marie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 18:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So when someone dies who other people cared about but you didn't, you try to belittle them and make them feel small because there are other problems in the world. If you think being an arrogant asshole to others by guilting them with your unjustified egotistic attitude makes you a better person, let me tell you it doesn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 06:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frank's homosexuality will come out and cause a major scandal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 05:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god. That gif just works so perfectly. Great job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: Family Dog in SF </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 04:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It amazes me that more people don't understand this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 04:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 00:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Locke vs. Hobbes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 00:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. This is the first one in here that really made me think about my original belief. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 23:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/aquariums
Nothing makes you feel better than a group of people who share your hobby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 23:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank you all for being so nice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 07:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a nice change of pace to have a subreddit where people are so kind and supportive. You guys are the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 07:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because no one has said it yet in this thread, Wilfred is the greatest show on the goddamn planet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
