<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4803</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 09:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one is from LA in Los Feliz neighborhood called Churro Borough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They actually already make a horchata flavored ice cream here to go with the sandwich. Mine was a spanish latte flavor. They also make a spicy hot chocolate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is from Churro Borough, a ice cream/churro shop in Los Feliz in LA. They are the self-proclaimed place of the "original churro ice cream sandwich."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I counter your diabeetus with insulin. Boom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure you can. Eat it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I counter your Belgian ice cream sandwich with my Mexican churro ice cream sandwich </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 03:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In exchange for giving up badge. Wow this was such a trap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 23:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the input man! Leaning towards letting it ride. Go Dubs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 05:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you were in this position, what kind of small bet would you put on cavs? Or should I assume if warriors have such a big home court adv., wait to see if cavs lose game one and then take a cavs hedge? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 02:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would you hedge this if you had warriors 5:1 during the season, 200 to win 1200 and cavs at 17/10? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 07:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aaron Rodgers + Hugh Laurie = you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 16:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this where tree sap comes from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 17:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TOR -7 at Brooklyn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 08:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would also love 1st half picks as well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 03:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bar 9 collective in Culver City is one of the best kept secret coffee shops I've ever had in LA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 18:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I'm asking, how do people feel about the ROK manual espresso maker? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a good espresso machine without breaking the bank </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 18:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for a decent espresso machine, but not one that's too cheap like those you can find in Walmart. Any suggestions? What do you guys think about the Waring Vero Barista? It looks nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coffee in Las Vegas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 22:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm moving to Las Vegas next week and I'm afraid there won't be any good coffee shops/roasters there. I've previously lived in very coffee-friendly cities, SF and LA, so I might be a little bit spoiled. 

http://sprudge.com/jackpot-big-cash-payout-for-finca-las-vegas.html

This article is over 2 years old and I'm pretty sure there hasn't been any progress. Anyone have any suggestions or am I shit out of luck for the next 3 years?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 09:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly hope after reading all the responses to this thread that future sitcoms learn the lesson about love stories like this. Hint hint New Girl... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 06:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sean connery?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-25 23:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the one LEGO to rule them all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ecuador/Galpagos/Peru in April </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 21:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for some tips, particularly the Galapagos. There are so many cruise companies and many itineraries to choose from. Looking for something that's inexpensive (I know, difficult) to moderate, definitely not luxurious. Specifically, looking to be there April 15-20. Also anything to do in the Guayaquil and Cusco areas. Also one day in Lima. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 18:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nutella </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 20:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> have you ever considered a choose your own adventure book instead with alternate endings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 21:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really great photos. Are these post-edited? If so, how much editing did you do? Lightroom? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone ever won anything by collecting the game pieces on McDonald's Monopoly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 23:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm starting to suspect that this is a ploy just to buy their food... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 19:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is seriously one of the more cooler activities I've seen at con. Will be definitely keeping a look out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 04:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't have them where I live. How much did they cost? I love the designs. Would they be able to ship them??  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 03:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you get those coffee bags? I've asked roasters before and they don't sell them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-07 01:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awesome, totally looking forward to kickstarting this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-07 01:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't sold in the states is it? How'd you buy it? Also how would yours be different from this one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-06 22:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let us know when this gets on kickstarter. I'd definitely be interested in this. Hario is coming out with their own drip machine later this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
