<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4100</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (No Spoilers) Just caught an early screening of Southpaw. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really liked it. The reception's been pretty mixed on Rotten Tomatoes so far, and most of it has been because of how predictable it can be at times. 

Honestly, I didn't really care if the movie didn't break any new ground for the boxing/redemption genre. It was engaging, shot beautifully, and the actors were phenomenal (cue Eminem) in their roles. Oona Laurence did exceptionally well as the daughter. 

Bottom line - great film to check out if you're into fight films. And arguably even better if you're not too familiar with the genre just because of how accessible this one felt. 

I'll be here to answer any questions you guys have on the movie!

Synopsis: As the boxing industry begins seeing a decline in ratings after the fight between Pacquiao and Mayweather, executives begin engineering a genetically modified hybrid boxer to attract viewers. But when things make a turn for the worse after the new experiment goes on a rampage, it's up to pro boxer Billy Hope (Jake Gyllenhaal) and his raptor hype crew to rescue the industry from certain extinction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 07:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We get the force we deserve </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 06:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **MY WIFE DIED HERE** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 20:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **THEN YOU ARE LOST** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 10:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 07:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funnily enough, that's exactly what I had it renamed as on my Facebook page. 

'Kings   Queens' was a favorite of mine by 30 Seconds to Mars back in the day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 06:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sakura Micron Pens. Hands down. They're what I used. Get the 8 pen pack off of Amazon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 20:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. If you guys want them! 

It's going to take a bit of time - I'm still touching these up and finishing more as part of a set. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 20:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm working on Blue right now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 20:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the "Kings" was in reference to them being the two rexes ("rex" meaning "king" in Latin) on the island.. and I was an idiot for not realizing how that'd conflict with the queen thing before I hit submit with that title.


I'm probably pulling a Kanye and changing the title when I think of something new because now it's bothering me too. Thank you, by the way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 18:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am - I put my name and website up on the side of the artwork (hopefully it's not too obnoxiously placed).

Thank you, by the way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kings of Nublar, Ink, 3217 x 1522 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 17:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 17:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I was going off the "rex" (king) in both their names! Believe me, I still had a hard time choosing between that and "Queens".

EDIT: Okay, I'm starting to regret the title. I'm going to pull a Kanye here and change it. 

..Whenever I think of a good one.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kings of Nublar [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 17:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 08:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This clears up Trent Reznor's win for me. I was beyond excited when *The Social Network*'s score got the Oscar, but at the same time surprised considering Trent utilized two tracks from his Ghosts I-IV recordings for Nine Inch Nails. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "official" reason for the I-Rex is to introduce something new and unparalleled so park attendance would rise, yeah. But if you go back and listen more closely to the things Dr. Wu and Hoskins say, there's a different story.

Remember how Wu couldn't disclose the information to the guy that literally *owns* the park? The cuttlefish DNA for camouflage was one of the things he didn't tell. It was part of the modifications he made to the I-Rex for InGen's military agenda. The I-Rex wasn't built like a damn tank to "up the 'wow' factor" at a theme park at all; it was built to win a war.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 11:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jurassic Five 

Jurassic Park 6

Park 7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember getting the same exact chills when the original theme by him [played at the end of Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, Pt. 2.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pEKA6rmVfW8)

I don't know how Williams does it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My parents literally went to their first  ever midnight premiere for it, and I haven't seen them enjoy a movie so much since we bought the first on VHS. 

It wasn't an Oscar contender by any means, but it was still the most fun I've had watching a movie in a long time. And that relieved the hell out of me because I don't know how pissed I'd have been thinking about how I spent from elementary school to the end of my college career  searching up "Jurassic Park 4" had this thing pulled a Chinese Democracy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW the original soundtrack starts to blare in Jurassic World as the park is shown for the first time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 14:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 08:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just went and banned a subreddit? Probably not a good idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DINO SEASON APPROACHING </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 19:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 19:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The park's been open for years by the time this movie takes place. And within years, people tend to forget a lot. Hearing about a tiger mauling a man or a chimpanzee ripping off a woman's face doesn't stop us from going to the zoo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 03:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone please GIF that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 22:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *DISTANT ROAR* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 21:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **SHE'LL KILL ANYTHING THAT MOVES** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 17:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm seriously regretting listening to 'Our Rex Is Bigger Than Yours' right now because it sounds like the backdrop to a complete spectacle. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 00:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *You've got to mean it, Harry...* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 16:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rian Johnson confirmed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 09:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just went and made a new alien? Probably not a good idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 12:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me, we've been breathing it for centuries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 21:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MY NAME IS ALAN GRANT, AND I AM THE SMARTEST PALEONTOLOGIST ALIVE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 08:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, how bout it, Hank? Should I let you go? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 22:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [opening scene for Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, Pt. 1](http://youtu.be/uffmqrjaSh4). It establishes the movie's departure from the others in tone perfectly. 

I love how the music transitions as Hermione walks away from her home. Right when the title pulls up, it immediately shifts to a feel of "now shit's about to down." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 19:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOOOOOOO that's my poster on number 6 WE MADE IT FAM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 01:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 04:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa. I liked The Lost World, but it always felt a HELL of a lot longer than the first movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 02:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just had a mental vision of a velociraptor going 'papoy'... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 13:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> uuuu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 13:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. Haha that's pure Indominus madness - the thing's jaw is literally supposed to open up to a 90 degree angle [[SPOILERS]](http://i.imgur.com/NotXoH6.jpg). I think they're really trying to push for its unnaturalness.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 13:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went off leaked images and screenshots from the trailer. The two dinosaurs I mentioned are the ones supposedly used to create the Indominus Rex in the movie, and I wanted to try my own take on what that could have resulted in. 

Yeah, it doesn't exist - that's where I saw a fun challenge to take on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 13:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!

Typically on movie posters they put the director's name above the film title in really fine print. It's part of all the credits that get written on the poster. Colin is still pretty new, but his name doesn't go up there to help market the film too much - that's why it's always done in really really fine print.

But if I did want to market it with someone's name, then I'd definitely highlight it more. Like you said, though - Colin's still relatively new to the game so he normally wouldn't be treated like a household name just yet. 

The problem with saying "Steven Spielberg Presents" is that he's only an executive producer for the film, and the authorship is usually credited to the director. If I wanted to market Spielberg on this then I'd say something in bolder letters like "From the producers of *Jurassic Park* and *Transformers*".

TL;DR marketing is weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 13:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, thank you! They don't even need it; the recognition would be awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 13:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are. The arms were a lot bigger in my original drawing (and more correctly placed in terms of anatomy), but had to be adjusted to fit in the circle. The [original movie's logo](http://i.imgur.com/uPNp7UO.jpg) did the same thing with the arms of the [skeleton on the book's cover](http://i.imgur.com/UKs7lN6.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 06:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh absolutely. It parallels the first film by making the logo of the theme park the logo of the film itself. I'd have been a bit frustrated if they went with anything else. 

Thanks, by the way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tried out a logo concept with the Indominus Rex. I used Carnotaurus and Majungasaurus skeletons to make it as accurate as possible. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 05:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 03:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing the placement for the "Damaged" tattoo was done to make a twisted pun. Brain Damage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 17:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ***TYRANNO SEASON APPROACHING*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 11:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they moving? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 06:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep in mind that the title of the movie (in America, at least) is Batman v. Superman, and not Batman vs Superman. I think this movie will be more a battle between ideals than pure strength. The "v." would make sense, considering that'd make it more of a civil dispute than a cage match. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 02:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHERE MY THUGGERS AND MY CRIPPERS AND MY BLOODERS AND MY BROTHERS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 22:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much Five </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 03:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's to you, Phil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 05:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol the dude's name is PhoneFanatic1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 15:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ..The... the video..? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 17:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell, even then, Kanye's still diverse with his portfolio. His records get influenced by everything from Nina Simone to films like Ghost in the Shell.

He understands his niche, but he's a lot less likely to be afraid of stepping out of it every now and then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 05:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they sample the tripod's horn from Spielberg's War of the Worlds? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
