<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5807</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Individuals Who Believe in the Paranormal Develop More Causal Illusions than Nonbelievers in the Laboratory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who claim to be experts in a topic are more likely to fall for made up facts on that topic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 19:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analysis shows that pesticide residues in food are at levels far below those that would pose any health concern. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 15:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Failure to attain a high school degree is associated with a higher risk of premature death. The researchers suggest that a lack of education leads to the adoption of unhealthy behaviors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 21:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top scientists are reporting signs of life on comet 67P. "I am here to make a prediction: this claim will vanish, never to be heard from again." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 19:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have found the first evidence for STDs in honeybees. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 19:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pre-crastination: Why the opposite of procrastination can be just as bad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 07:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> KFC Plagued By Urban Legends Fueled by Psychology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 05:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Primatologists have recorded the first spontaneous case of a chimpanzee drumming in a way that resembles music. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 15:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Online communication as a window to conspiracist worldviews </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 21:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a limit to temperature? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers envision Earth as a giant computer, determine its storage capacity and power by calculating the total amount of DNA and the overall rate of DNA transcription. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 21:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure I'm buying Kate Mara as Johanssen. Hopefully she'll prove me wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Creationism can be used in science classes to teach the scientific method. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 21:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Creationism Belongs in Science Class: A professor teaches creationism in her classes in order to have students debunk it with the scientific method. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 21:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Insect Mating Behavior Has Lessons for Drones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 01:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 21:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to journal article: http://journals.aps.org/prl/abstract/10.1103/PhysRevLett.114.215001 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists move one step closer to mimicking gamma-ray bursts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 21:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New discovery could lead to sunscreen in pill form. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 04:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study links infections to a decrease in cognitive ability. The researchers found that the more times a subject was hospitalized for an infection throughout his life, the lower he scored on a test of cognitive ability. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 15:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 15:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry! I've posted a link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 15:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to Study: http://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nclimate2631.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exposure of US population to extreme heat could quadruple by mid-century </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 05:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's a particle accelerator in the Louvre. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 16:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New analysis finds that if the world built nuclear power at a similar rate to Sweden or France, all fossil fuel electricity could be displaced in 25-34 years, reducing carbon emissions by half. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 15:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First-born siblings show better second language skills than later born siblings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 19:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that flossing is not supported by scientific evidence. It offers little to no benefits over daily toothbrushing alone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 18:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Computer scientists find that 1980 music had the lowest stylistic diversity of any other decade. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 21:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Targeted antibiotic treatment plans could be used to reduce antibiotic resistant genotypes in bacteria. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 01:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the first time, astronomers have detected visible light directly from an exoplanet. The effort is a proof of concept for a new way to detect exoplanets. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 17:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review finds that intake of vitamin and mineral supplements are generally associated with an increased risk of cancer and heart disease. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 17:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chimpanzees from a troop in Senegal make and use spears. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 01:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have captured the first MRI video of a joint cracking, finally resolving that the "pop" is caused by a bubble forming in the joint's synovial fluid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 22:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smiling makes you look older. Smiling people were perceived as 1-2 years older than when they had a neutral expression. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 15:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 07:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bottled water is one of those uniquely American enterprises that's a mx of marketing genius and questionably legal tactics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A study of university faculty members finds that they are more likely to hire a woman over a man as an assistant professor in engineering, psychology, or biology by a margin of 2 to 1. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 21:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If marijuana is a schedule 1 drug, caffeine should definitely be one, too. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 04:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study finds an association between eating out at restaurants and high blood pressure. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 00:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Science Behind the Perfect French Fry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 01:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 17:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But graphene glitter. GRAPHENE glitter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers take another step toward functional nanobots. They outfitted bacterial spores with tiny flecks of graphene armor capable of activating electrodes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 15:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After using search engines, people overestimate their ability to explain ideas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 19:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We Should Have a Better Condom by Now. Heres Why We Dont. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 19:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fast food is just as effective as exercise supplements at helping athletes recover after a workout. In a study, there were no differences in muscle glycogen levels and subsequent performance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 15:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A glimpse inside a macroscopic quantum state: Researchers detect particle entanglement in a beam of squeezed light </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 00:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simple Messages Help Set the Record Straight about Scientific Agreement on Human-Caused Climate Change: The Results of Two Experiments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 04:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neurofeedback training could potentially be used as a treatment for criminal psychopaths. In a new study, psychopaths who used it experienced reductions in aggression and impulsivity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 14:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Contrary to popular belief that regular pornography use can give men erectile dysfunction in partner situations, a new study finds no link between the two. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 17:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
