<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7370</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's just how they are spelling deli </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crab cake sandwich from Chick and Ruth's Delly in Annapolis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is Chessie and today is her first day at her new home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 23:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've seen 3 different ones just this morning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 13:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 23:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They had just finished eating so that's partially true  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yesterday we picked out our new family member, can't wait to bring her home in 4 weeks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 23:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pic of a bridge near my house at sunset </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 23:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I imagine America will react to the DeflateGate results </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 22:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you rather be Bill Gates or Harry Potter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 15:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Makes the day just a little better </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 16:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW when I'm at the club talking to some girls and I suddenly can't find them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 02:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm talking to some girls at the club and I suddenly can't find them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 02:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 00:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was young, maybe 6-7, I woke up in the middle of the night to my mom looking out the window and mumbling. She kept saying some like How come the sun isn't up? Its going to be in so much trouble when I tell its mother." I was understandably confused and kind of scared and when I asked her what she was doing she kept mumbling about the sun not being up. She then went to bed. I brought it up to her and she swears it never happened. I've always just assumed she was sleep walking but it was super weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 04:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like good sushi a lot but I know what you mean, I'm never full after eating it and neither is my wallet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 04:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WaWa coffee is the best for a gas station, way better than Sheetz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 04:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never heard of this place, where are they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 04:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were pretty decent before they became a nationwide chain but now sadly I would have to agree with you. I do still buy their salt and vinegar dry seasoning for use at home, shit is delicious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What restaurant do you not understand why its popular, and why do you dislike said restaurant? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 04:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 01:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FRANK AND BEANS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
