<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject138</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio Gov. John Kasich is the newest entrant to the crowded Republican field for 2016, and his supporters are trying to steer the conversation towards his economic bona fides. But Kasichs record on the economy has one major flaw: In 2014 he signed a bill freezing a successful clean energy program. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 01:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> By forcing the candidates to respond, these activists have changed the tone for the 2016 election season, putting Democrats on notice that they cannot expect the support of black votersparticularly young black voterswithout speaking directly and meaningfully to issues of race and state power </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 01:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greenland's glaciers flowing into the ocean are grounded deeper below sea level than previously measured, allowing intruding ocean water to badly undercut the glacier faces. That process will raise sea levels around the world much faster than currently estimated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 01:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yes, Donald Trump gave everyone Lindsey Grahams real cellphone number. And hes not sorry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 01:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leader of Qaeda Cell in Syria, Muhsin al-Fadhli, Is Killed in Airstrike, U.S. Says - The Pentagon said on Tuesday that the leader of the Khorasan Group, a shadowy militant cell in Syria, was killed in an airstrike in Syria this month. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 01:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Nasa camera on the Deep Space Climate Observatory (Dscovr) satellite  hanging in gravitational balance between the Earth and the sun  has returned its first view of the entire sunlit side of the planet from one million miles away. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The French Scrabble champion who doesn't speak French - Despite his linguistic handicap, Richards has just won the francophone world Scrabble championships after reportedly memorising the entire French Scrabble dictionary in just nine weeks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Obama said Tuesday that opponents of the nuclear deal with Iran were behaving like those who pushed for war with Iraq more than a decade ago, and said the United States should choose diplomacy instead of another rush to armed conflict. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> By gathering climate-conscience mayors from Europe, South America, the United States, and even Iran, the Holy See is slowly crafting a global coalition of partner cities united in their support for helping stem the effects of climate change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This year the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Eleventh Circuit has been hearing arguments about a Florida statute that says doctors cannot ask a patient about gun ownershipincluding safety issues and children's accessunless they believe such information is relevant to the patient's medical care. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Citigroup Inc's consumer bank has been ordered to pay $700 million in relief to borrowers for illegal credit card practices, the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Urged on by anguished testimony from the father of a murder victim, Congress plunged into a heated debate over immigration on Tuesday as GOP lawmakers vowed to shut down funding for so-called sanctuary cities like San Francisco that shield immigrants from deportation by federal authorities. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missouri state Rep. Paul Joseph Wieland (R) does not want his daughters health plan to cover birth control  even though two of those daughters are adults. So he and his wife sued the Obama administration. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 23:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Lufthansa plane with 108 passengers on board nearly collided with a drone as it approached Warsaw's main airport on Monday afternoon, the airline said on Tuesday. The drone came within 100 meters (330 feet) of the Embraer plane when the Munich to Warsaw flight was at a height of about 760 meters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 23:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United States said on Tuesday it was disturbed by anti-U.S. hostility voiced by Iran's top leader after a nuclear deal, as both countries' top diplomats sought to calm opposition to the accord from hardliners at home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 23:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Obama called for all flags at the White House and all federal buildings, including overseas embassies, to be lowered to half-staff to honor the five troops killed in a shooting rampage at a Chattanooga, Tenn., reserve center. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 23:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian Town Near Ukraine, Once Quiet, Now Buzzes With Military Activity - In last years invasion of Crimea, Moscow deployed Russian soldiers whose only disguises were uniforms without identifying insignia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 13:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For G.O.P., Pope Francis Visit to Congress Comes With Tensions - While he has made no changes in church doctrine, Francis has forcefully staked out ideological ground opposite that of Mr. Boehner and his party. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 13:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For years, residents of remote villages in Kazakhstan have been plagued by a mysterious sleeping illness, causing more than 140 villagers to fall asleep at random, sometimes for up to six days at a time. No one could provide a solid explanation of exactly what in the hell was happening, until now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 02:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two tickets for the Transylvania music festival? Thatll be two pints of blood, please. It may sound like a bad episode of Scooby Doo, but organisers of the Untold festival in northern Romania are offering festivalgoers discounts if they donate blood before buying tickets. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 02:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Public Enemy? At Home in Mexico, El Chapo Is Folk Hero No. 1 - When Jos Antonio Sevilla and his three brothers learned that the notorious drug trafficker known as El Chapo had escaped from prison, they jumped out of their chairs and shouted with glee. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 01:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Nobody Intervened in the July 4 Metro Murder - Bystander apathy is a psychological phenomenon in which witnesses to a person being harmed are less likely to intervene the more people there are present. This is thought to be a consequence of the herding instinct of human beings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 01:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Speaker John Boehner (R-OH) took to Facebook on Tuesday to recast Californias worst drought in 1200 years as a man-made water shortage  not worsened by climate change, but by President Obama himself. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 01:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Humans may decide to curb the greenhouse gasses that are changing Earth's climate, but the ocean will warm and rise for centuries regardless, US government scientists said in a new report released Thursday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 01:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To Mars and boldly beyond: space missions to look out for - Nasa has hatched an, arguably, even bolder plan to send a robotic spacecraft to grab a four-metre chunk of asteroid, tow it along and place it in orbit about the moon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 00:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The [Greek] crisis was exacerbated years ago by a deal with Goldman Sachs, engineered by Goldmans current CEO, Lloyd Blankfein. Blankfein and his Goldman team helped Greece hide the true extent of its debt, and in the process almost doubled it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 04:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Vladimir V. Putin of Russia pushed back forcefully on Thursday against calls for an international tribunal to investigate the downing of Malaysia Airlines Flight 17 over eastern Ukraine last year, even as other world leaders were demanding accountability </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 03:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a video released Wednesday night, multiple police officers seem to be holding 28-year-old Sandra Bland to the ground while she cries out, You just slammed my head into the ground, do you not even care about that? Three days later, Bland was found dead in a jail cell. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 03:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alaska will become the 30th state to accept Obamacares optional Medicaid expansion, after Gov. Bill Walker (I) announced on Thursday that he will use his executive power to bypass the GOP-controlled legislature and implement the policy on his own. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 03:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Max Blumenthal, The Next Gaza War - After years of fruitless negotiations, Israel has rewarded Palestinians living under the rule of PA President Mahmoud Abbas with the record growth of Jewish settlements, major new land annexations, and nightly house raids </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 02:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Obama on Wednesday said bluntly that the actions described in accusations that the comedian Bill Cosby drugged women for sex would constitute nothing less than rape, and he said the country should have no tolerance for such actions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 02:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The CMP and other groups of its ilk have been making an issue of tissue donation for a long time. The "harvesting" and "trafficking" of baby parts is a known anti-abortion talking pointin fact, the video opens with footage of news stories about the selling of fetal tissue from over a decade ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 02:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Man Took On Fox News And Became A Hero To His City - He didnt want to just duck his head and hide, because he knew how that looked on TV. So he addressed Fox News directly: Fox News is not real news. And youre not a real reporter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 02:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama and mass incarceration: How much power does the federal government have to solve this problem? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 02:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The remains of long, thin cells preserved inside the 50-million-year-old fossilized cocoon of an unknown worm species represent the oldest animal sperm ever found, say researchers at the Swedish Museum of Natural History in Stockholm. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 02:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Obama on Wednesday urged lawmakers to support the nuclear deal reached with Iran, saying that failure to put it into effect would increase the likelihood of war in the Middle East and accelerate a nuclear arms race in the region that would threaten the safety of the United States. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 02:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> During a White House press conference about the Iran nuclear deal, a reporter asked President Barack Obama to respond to the rape allegations against Bill Cosby. In response, Obama strongly implied that Cosby is guilty. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 02:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article is not off topic, but if you like I can peruse the front page of r/politics and find several stories that you didn't remove because the person posting isn't under the same level of scrutiny as the articles I post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vigorously challenging his critics, President Barack Obama launched an aggressive and detailed defense of a landmark Iranian nuclear accord Wednesday, rejecting the idea that it leaves Tehran on the brink of a bomb and arguing the only alternative to the diplomatic deal is war. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Florida Congressman Claims Donald Trumps Candidacy Was Orchestrated By Democratic Party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton and Scott Walkers vision for America: The two candidates just gave speeches that reveal our ultra-polarized future. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. retail sales unexpectedly fell in June as households cut back on purchases of automobiles and a range of other goods, raising concerns the economy was slowing again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Katherine Johnson, Mary Jackson, Dorothy Vaughan, Kathryn Peddrew, Sue Wilder, Eunice Smith and Barbara Holley  all names that have been largely forgotten by the American public. And yet these black, female mathematicians were crucial in the success of the Nasa space missions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The federal agency that oversees the safety of the nation's pipelines failed to follow through on congressional reforms that could have made a difference in a May break that created the largest coastal oil spill in California in 25 years, a House committee chairman said Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why North Carolina Is the New Selma - Selma in 1965 and North Carolina in 2015 show how far conservative white Southerners will go to maintain political power. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Wal-Mart Stores Inc (WMT.N) employee sued the retailer on Tuesday, saying its prior policy of denying health insurance to the spouses of gay employees violated gender discrimination laws. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An anti-abortion group on Tuesday released an undercover video of an executive at Planned Parenthood sipping red wine while discussing in graphic detail how to abort a fetus to preserve its organs for medical research  and also the costs associated with sharing that tissue with scientists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A prominent psychologist ousted from the leadership of the the USs largest professional psychological association for his alleged role in enabling and covering up torture has enlisted a former FBI director to fight back. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 04:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservationists on Friday protested a U.S. decision not to prosecute a Utah hunter who mistakenly shot and killed a gray wolf that had gained an international following for being the first of its kind seen at the Grand Canyon in 70 years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 04:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An eight-mile convoy of pickups, motorcycles and cars wound through a central Florida town on Sunday in a show of support for the Confederate flag, as a backlash against its banishment from public landmarks across the South picks up steam. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 04:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Voter's Question to Jeb Bush: Would You Carpet-Bomb ISIS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 15:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Mexican drug lord Joaquin El Chapo Guzman, head of the powerful Sinaloa cartel, has escaped from a maximum-security prison for the second time, Mexican officials said as they launched a manhunt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 12:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Were Already In The Worst Case Scenario For Sea Level Rise - People always talk about the year 2100 when they talk about sea level rise, she said. Its not going to stop then; it will keep rising after. Its important to realize the decisions we make today will influence that trajectory. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 12:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexico's most notorious drug lord Joaquin "El Chapo" Guzman has escaped from a high security prison, officials said on Sunday, the second time he has given his captors the slip in 15 years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 12:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 04:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
This advice originates in long years of military training for hand-to-hand combat.  
  
1. There is no such thing as a "fair fight". That being said, avoid fighting all-together, but if that option is off the table, go for the opponents' soft spots and joints. This includes the eyes, throat, stomach, groin, knees, elbows, shoulders and feet. It only takes two pounds of pressure to snap a knee or elbow.  
  
2. Keep moving your feet, don't lock your knees, and watch your opponent's midsection because it will indicate where the next attack is coming. Stay on your feet but keep in mind that the goal is to neutralize your opponent and make them no longer a threat. The eyes and throat are prime targets because both areas are important to the average person. If your opponent is worried about losing an eye or the ability to breathe, he/she is more likely to disengage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Militants attacked two hotels in Mogadishu, Somalias capital, with grenades, bombs and heavy gunfire on Friday in what appeared to have been coordinated attacks, witnesses and officials said. At least 18 of the attackers were killed and at least six civilians were wounded, officials said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 03:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Several brands of crayons and toy detective kits have tested positive for asbestos, a known carcinogen, according to a report released this week by an environmental group thats advocating for the government to crack down on the substance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 03:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A rare surviving example of an Enigma machine, used by the German military to send coded messages during the second world war, is expected to fetch 70,000 at auction next week. The machines were vital to the Nazi war effort but the Allies broke the codes  a feat said to have shortened the war </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 03:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senators want the FCC to look into broadband pricing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High Heat Measured under Antarctica Could Support Substantial Life - Nearly a kilometer below the ice scientists have found a Yellowstone-like geothermal glow that could create life-rich subglacial lakesand lubricate Antarctic ice loss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Newest Argument For Wedding Cake Discrimination </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Early Friday, President Obama announced that he will designate three new national monuments, permanently protecting more than one million acres of public lands. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new NASA study of ocean temperature measurements shows that in recent years, extra heat from greenhouse gases has been trapped in the waters of the Pacific and Indian oceans. Researchers say this shifting pattern of ocean heat accounts for the slowdown in the global surface temperature trend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Early Thursday morning, the South Carolina House of Representative voted 90-24 in favor of removing the Confederate flag from Capitol grounds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kremlin critics say a climate of fear is growing in Russia after the upper house of parliament drew up a list of "undesirable" civil rights organizations and two similar groups decided to close. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even if world manages to limit global warming to 2C  the target number for current climate negotiations  sea levels may still rise at least 6 meters (20 feet) above their current heights, radically reshaping the worlds coastline and affecting millions in the process. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Florida Supreme Court on Thursday ordered the redrawing of some of the state's U.S. congressional districts before the 2016 elections. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The anguished national debate over the future of the Confederate flag exploded on the House floor on Thursday as Democrats, led by black members from the South, beat back a push by Republicans to allow Confederate symbols at national cemeteries. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nasa is all set for next weeks historic Pluto fly-by having reactivated the New Horizons spacecraft following a malfunction last weekend. The 14 July fly-by will take place on the 50th anniversary of Mariner 4s visit to Mars, which was Americas first successful planetary fly-by. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 01:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. authorities foiled attacks planned around the Fourth of July, arresting more than 10 people in the month before the holiday who were inspired by Islamic State online recruitment, FBI Director James Comey said on Thursday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 01:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate change has narrowed the range where bumblebees are found in North America and Europe in recent decades, according to a study published Thursday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 01:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Satanists Are Fighting Americas Restrictive Abortion Laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 01:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The battle over the Confederate flag landed with ferocity Thursday in the U.S. Capitol amid an unexpected debate on the display of the southern Battle Flag in federal cemeteries for veterans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 01:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Data breaches at the U.S. government's personnel management agency by hackers, with suspicions centering on China, involved millions more people than previously estimated, U.S. officials said on Thursday. The Office of Personnel Management (OPM) said the stolen data included Social Security numbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 01:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia vetoed a British-sponsored draft resolution in the United Nations Security Council on Wednesday condemning the Srebrenica massacre of 1995 as a crime of genocide, marking a new low in relations among world powers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 02:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-U.S. Vitriol in Iran Reaches New Heights as Nuclear Talks Seem in Reach - Anti-Americanism is a pillar of our system, said Nader Karimi Joni, a reformist journalist. Now that we are in direct talks with the United States, the reaction is to oversell anti-Americanism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 02:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congressman: Stop Worrying About Climate Change, Focus On Crimes Against Christians - Duncans outrage over DHS studying climate risks may have to do with the fact that he doesnt think climate change is real. He stated as much on Wednesday at the hearing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 02:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baltimore Police Commissioner Is Fired by Mayor - Mayor Stephanie Rawlings-Blake of Baltimore announced on Wednesday that she had decided to replace the citys police commissioner, Anthony W. Batts, citing a recent crime surge within the city as the primary reason for her decision. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 01:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP Governor Messes Up His Veto Power, Accidentally Extends More Benefits To Immigrants - The Bangor Daily News reports that, perhaps due to a misunderstanding about the states legislative process, LePage has allowed at least 19 bills to become law that he intended to veto. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 01:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suspected Boko Haram fighters have killed 26 people in night attacks on two villages on Lake Chad over the weekend, Chadian officials have said. "The two villages were attacked by surprise on Saturday and Sunday night. There were 13 dead in each attack," a Chadian official said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 01:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Bill Cosbys Court Statements Were Revealed - Weighing Cosbys diminished privacy interest against the publics interest in accessing his deposition, Robreno decided that the publics interest should win out. Cosby failed to show good cause as to why his deposition should remain secret. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 00:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Is What Happens To Court Clerks Who Refuse To Issue Same Sex Marriage Licenses - the lawsuit will not be dismissed until and unless we have an agreement from Clerk Lang that her office will issue marriage licenses to all couples, gay and straight, without delay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 03:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greg Grandin, How Endless War Helps Old Dixie Stay New - Starting around 1898, well before it became an icon of redneck backlash, the Confederate Battle Flag served for half a century as an important pennant in the expanding American empire and a symbol of national unification, not polarization. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 01:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Obama administration on Tuesday announced an initiative to help low- and middle-income Americans gain access to solar energy, part of a series of steps President Obama is taking to tackle climate change, according to administration officials. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 01:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When drugs are used to coerce sex, it's rape. Even if you're Bill Cosby - A man like that uses substances to prevent her from saying no, because he doesnt care if she says yes. A man like that wants a woman incapacitated in order to rape her, not in order to have sex with her </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 01:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five million public school students in Texas will begin using new social studies textbooks this fall based on state academic standards that barely address racial segregation. The states guidelines for teaching American history also do not mention the Ku Klux Klan or Jim Crow laws. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 14:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philae comet could be home to alien life, say top scientists - Features of the comet, named 67P/Churyumov-Gerasimenko, such as its organic-rich black crust, are most likely explained by the presence of living organisms beneath an icy surface </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 13:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Western Canadian province of Saskatchewan said on Sunday it was evacuating an additional 8,000 people from the far north of the province, as wildfires continue to spread and threaten homes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 13:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Too few diagnostic laboratories, too many poorly-trained health practitioners and thousands of infected people living in crowded, unsanitary conditions has made India home to the world's largest epidemic of drug-resistant TB. More than two million Indians every year get the highly contagious disease </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 13:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese stocks rose on Monday, as an unprecedented series of support measures unleashed by Beijing brought some relief to a market whose headlong slide over the past three weeks had raised fears about the stability of the world's second-biggest economy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 13:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A solar-powered airplane currently soaring over the Pacific Ocean, from Japan to Hawaii, has set a slew of new world records, logging the farthest and longest flights made so far in a solar-powered aircraft. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 12:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State suicide bombers on Sunday blew up an explosive- laden truck near a power plant that serves the northeastern city of Hasaka, the latest attack after their expulsion from most parts of the city, the Syrian army said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 12:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An air strike on a sports field in Ramadi shortly after midnight on Sunday killed at least 50 people and left more than 30 people injured. At least 23 people were killed and around 40 wounded after shelling north of Fallujah. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 12:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bush, whose wife is Mexican and three children were raised to celebrate their bicultural roots, showed a flash of anger on Saturday as he said that he absolutely took personal offense when Donald Trump recently described Mexican immigrants coming to the United States as rapists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 03:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian President Vladimir Putin called for dialogue based on equal treatment and mutual respect with the United States on Saturday in a congratulatory message to President Barack Obama marking U.S. Independence Day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 03:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 03:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This submission is clearly about politics and if you're too obtuse to see that, please find another subreddit to moderate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China froze share offers and set up a market-stabilization fund on Saturday, the Wall Street Journal said, as Beijing intensified efforts to pull stock markets out of a nose-dive that is threatening the world's second-largest economy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 03:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to Forgive the Black Church -  My thoughts on the church as a teenager and as a young adult were clear: Christianity was the religion of our enslaver. It was the justification for our bondage, and so long as we continue to pray to White Jesus, we will continue to be in chains. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 03:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SpaceX Rocket Failure Threatens Support for Commercial Spaceflight - The destruction of an unmanned rocket Sunday comes at a tricky time for NASA and the International Space Station </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 03:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal and local authorities have found that the man charged in the shooting deaths of nine black people in a South Carolina church last month had been in contact with white supremacists online, although it does not appear they encouraged him to carry out the massacre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 03:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Protesters calling for the ouster of President Rafael Correa have filled the streets of Ecuadors largest cities in recent weeks in some of the largest antigovernment demonstrations here in years, creating tensions on the eve of a visit by Pope Francis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 03:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Jim Carrey's Anti-Vaccine Rant Totally Backfired - The family of an autistic boy is pretty annoyed with Jim Carrey for using the boys photo to accompany a Twitter rant against vaccinations, according to a report in Buzzfeed News. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 03:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heinrich Wieland, the biochemist who defied the Nazis - During a meeting, one of Wielands new students rushed into the room declaring, Heil Hitler. Wieland instantly apologized, I am sorry. This young man just arrived yesterday. In a few days he will have learnt how to greet correctly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mitt Romney is having a slumber party this weekend at his New Hampshire compound with some very interesting guests: Gov. Chris Christie of New Jersey and Senator Marco Rubio of Florida, along with their families. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Signs of Water Ice Detected on Comet Surface - The Rosetta spacecraft, currently orbiting Comet 67P/Churyumov-Gerasimenko, has spotted 120 bright, reflective spots on the surface of the comet, for which water ice is a plausible explanation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Militants in Egypt's Sinai peninsula fired rockets into southern Israel on Friday in an incident that caused no casualties but appeared to be linked to fighting between Islamist insurgents and Egyptian security forces. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State militants indulged in new public displays of artifact destruction this week, sledgehammering a half-dozen statues said to have been stolen from the ancient Syrian city of Palmyra. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its Perfectly Legal For This Tennessee Hardware Store To Refuse Gay Customers - Im going to take more persecution than them because Im standing for what I believe in. He will sell to gay people so long as they behave and dont express their opinions in the store. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 01:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I cheered! I cried! Nothing 'inferior' about this women's World Cup - There is really only one reason the public doesnt follow womens sport in the same way they follow mens  there is no way to follow it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 01:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A freight train carrying flammable and toxic gas derailed in eastern Tennessee, igniting a fire in one car and spreading noxious fumes that forced the evacuation of more than 5,000 people and the hospitalization of 25, officials said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 00:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> H.J. Heinz Co on Thursday completed its purchase of Kraft Foods Group Inc, creating the third largest food and beverage company in North America and fifth largest worldwide. The new company, Kraft Heinz Co, will have roughly $28 billion of annual revenue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 00:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wisconsin Governor Scott Walker on Wednesday signed a bill into law that bans the manufacturing and sale of personal care products containing tiny plastic beads that are known to pollute waterways. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 00:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In whats been called a major blow to Shells Arctic drilling plans, the Obama administration released a new permitting decision Tuesday which found that, due to wildlife protections, the company cant simultaneously bore two wells into the Chukchi Sea. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 03:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists appear close to pinpointing why a swine flu vaccine given to six million people in Britain triggered the devastating sleep disorder, narcolepsy, in rare cases. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 03:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kurdish offensive in Syria has Ankara on its toes - Turkey worries about expanding cooperation between US-led coalition and Kurdish YPG forces. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 03:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Is Losing His Insane War Against Mexico </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 03:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Macy's Fired Donald Trump With This Epic Statement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Fox News commentator Glenn Beck has suggested a boycott of the just-announced Disney film about the celebrated English naturalist Charles Darwin, during an episode of his nationally syndicated radio show. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Fox News commentator Glenn Beck has suggested a boycott of the just-announced Disney film about the celebrated English naturalist Charles Darwin, during an episode of his nationally syndicated radio show. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super-Muscular Pigs Created by Small Genetic Tweak - These double-muscled pigs are made by disrupting, or editing, a single genea change that is much less dramatic than those made in conventional genetic modification, in which genes from one species are transplanted into another. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 02:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Tuesday, Brazil and the United States announced a joint effort to address climate change and boost renewable energy during a visit by Brazilian President Dilma Rousseff to the White House. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 03:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The day will officially be a bit longer than usual on Tuesday, June 30, 2015, because an extra second, or "leap" second, will be added. "Earth's rotation is gradually slowing down a bit, so leap seconds are a way to account for that," said Daniel MacMillan of NASA's Goddard Space Flight Center </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 02:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Misty Copeland Is Promoted to Principal Dancer at American Ballet Theater - Even as her promotion was celebrated by her many fans, it raised all-too-familiar questions about why African-American dancers, particularly women, remain so underrepresented at top ballet companies in the 21st century </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 02:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Ku Klux Klan plans to hold a pro-Confederate flag rally at South Carolina's capitol, where a statue of a former state governor who championed white supremacy was vandalized on Tuesday amid scrutiny of symbols associated with slavery. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 02:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Revelers at Istanbul's annual gay pride parade were knocked off their feet by water cannons, and hit with rubber bullets and tear gas after Turkish police moved in to disperse the crowd on Sunday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 12:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/politics mods do not appear to like my titles but there is nothing editorialized about this one. It came straight from the article and clearly represents the gist of the story. If the title is editorialized, then the entire article is also an editorial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal officials are investigating last week's Charleston, S.C. church shooting as a hate crime, and the U.S. Justice Department could weigh in in the coming weeks with a federal hate crimes charge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 16:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In California, Water Restrictions Above Ground and Leaks Below - It is awkward, after all, for a government to tell its citizens to let their lawns dry out when water main breaks can send millions of gallons flowing through city streets. And so California is looking to become more watertight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 15:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From the Arabian Peninsula to northern India to Californias Central Valley, nearly a third of the worlds 37 largest aquifers are being drained faster than they are being replenished, according to a recent study led by scientists at the University of California, Irvine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 15:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creative Advice for Donald Trump, a Proudly Egotistical Showman - No braggadocio, no 757s or helicopters (as much as I love them), a different Mr. Trump would be portrayed, Mr. Davis wrote. Remember this morning when you said he was really down to earth? Right now that is simply unbelievable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 15:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The only words he uttered were to tell Tunisians to get away. It was tourists, he made clear, he wanted to kill. Fifteen of them were British, a spokesman for the British Embassy in Tunis said, a number that is expected to rise as more bodies are identified. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 14:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Vatican on Friday signed a treaty with the state of Palestine, a development that the church hopes will lead to improved relations between Israel and the Palestinians. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 03:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Is the Big Secret Surrounding Stingray Surveillance? State and local law enforcement agencies across the U.S. are setting up fake cell towers to gather mobile data, but few will admit it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 03:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This was the best week of Obamas presidency - It was a moment of considerable weight and significance: A black president leading a congregation in song at a place where nine black people were murdered by a man with the apparent goal of starting a race war. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 03:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Columbia University Board of Trustees voted Monday to make the university the first in the nation to pull its investments from the private prison industry. The university will divest from two major for-profit prison companies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 04:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starfish Show Tracking Tags Who's Boss [Video] - Starfish are famous for their ability to regenerate a disconcertingly large chunk of their bodies if dismembered. Now they also seem capable of expelling disconcertingly large objects through their skin. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 04:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two years ago, on June 25, 2013, in Shelby County v. Holder, the Supreme Court invalidated the centerpiece of the Voting Rights Act. Tomorrow, congressional Democrats will introduce an ambitious new bill that would restore the important voting-rights protections the Supreme Court struck down. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 03:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Horses that heal: they can also hear the human heartbeat within four feet, and research on heart-rate variability indicates that horses have a profound ability to synchronize their own heartbeat with that of human beings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 03:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An initiative to remove the Confederate flag from the South Carolina State House grounds picked up steam on Tuesday, a week after the massacre of nine black church members, and criticism over the emblem long associated with slavery spread to other U.S. southern states. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 03:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese City Defends Dog Meat Festival, Despite Scorn - Through an open door, a man in a white T-shirt could be seen working silently in dim fluorescent light. With a small club he bludgeoned dog after dog, pausing periodically to move the dazed animals with tongs clamped around their necks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 03:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you've wondered what happened to President Obama's request for congressional authorization for military action against ISIS, you are not alone. Some members of Congress have grown impatient enough that they have tried to force leadership in the House and Senate to act. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 15:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State militants have sown landmines around ancient ruins in the Syrian city of Palmyra, captured by the Islamist group in May, according to a British-based monitoring group. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 14:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While the country  and South Carolina, in particular  is once again debating racism in America, NBCs Meet the Press on Sunday offered a video of men in prison expressing regret for their own gun violence. All of the men in the video are black. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 12:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China's dog-meat festival targeted by animal rights campaigner (video) - Yang Xiaoyun, 65, spent more than 15,000 last year buying dogs from meat vendors to save them from the dinner plate. Thousands of dogs, many believed to be stolen pets, are killed for their meat at the summer festival </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 12:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United States and its allies won't let Russia "drag us back to the past", U.S. Defense Secretary Ash Carter said in an address in Berlin on Monday, as he accused Moscow of trying to re-create a Soviet-era sphere of influence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 12:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Taliban attacked the Afghan Parliament on Monday just as lawmakers were convening for their third attempt to confirm a defense minister, while in northern Afghanistan a second district fell to Taliban insurgents. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 12:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two weeks after Turkey's parliamentary elections, experts agree on one thing: No one really knows what's going to happen next. Turkey's June 7 election left Turkey's long-ruling Justice and Development Party, known by Turkish acronym AKP, short of the majority it needs to govern alone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 13:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cables Released by WikiLeaks Reveal Saudis Checkbook Diplomacy - Before becoming the president of Egypt, Mohamed Morsi wanted visas to take his family on a religious pilgrimage. A Lebanese politician begged for cash to pay his bodyguards. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 13:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of revelers, new-agers and self-styled Druids descended on the ancient stone circle at Stonehenge on Sunday, catching a brief glimpse of the sun as they marked the summer solstice - the longest day of the year in the northern hemisphere. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 13:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> http://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2015/jun/21/rally-calls-for-confederate-flags-removal-from-south-carolina-legislature-grounds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 12:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hundreds of people gathered at South Carolinas state house on Saturday night in support of demands lawmakers remove the Confederate flag from flying on its grounds in the aftermath of the Charleston killings where the shooter killed nine people because they were black. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 12:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tara, a tabby from Bakersfield, Calif., has won an honor that so routinely goes to that other kind of pet, it's known as the Hero Dog award. This time, the Society for The Prevention of Cruelty to Animals Los Angeles had to scratch out "dog," and etch "cat" on the trophy instead. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 08:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The future of the Confederate flag that flies on the grounds of South Carolina state capitol consumed the Republican Partys presidential field on Saturday after Mitt Romney, its nominee for president in 2012, demanded its removal, calling it a symbol of racial hatred. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 07:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In First Batch of Released Cheney Papers, a Peek at a Polarizing Figure - The documents are limited in scope and contain no major revelations about the issues that dominated the era, like Iraq and terrorism. The papers are mainly memos, fact sheets and news articles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 07:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The nonpartisan Congressional Budget Office said Friday that repealing the Affordable Care Act would significantly increase federal budget deficits and the number of people who are uninsured. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 06:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawmakers...seem resigned to the view that if 20 small children killed at a school cannot move Congress, then nine black men and women shot dead by a white man during Bible study will not, either. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 06:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New DNA Results Show Kennewick Man Was Native American - Kennewick Mans genome also sheds new light on how people first spread throughout the New World, experts said. There was no mysterious intrusion of Europeans thousands of years ago. Instead, several waves spread across the New World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 04:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The US Treasury Is Finally Going to Put a Woman's Face on Paper Currency - As exciting as it is to finally have a woman on a piece of the nation's currency, it doesn't make a whole lot of sense to bump Hamilton, a founding father and original Secretary of the Treasury, but leave Andrew Jackson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 03:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ancient skeleton of Kennewick Man became the focus of a bitter $5m court battle between the US government, which planned to return the bones to Native Americans for reburial, and scientists, who wanted to study the remains. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 03:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama's repeated use of the phrase "at some point" and his acknowledgement that "politics in this town foreclose a lot of those avenues right now" are absolutely striking. This is the most powerful politician in the country acknowledging that he has little to no ability to effect a change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 03:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last month, the Federal Communications Commission announced plans to subsidize broadband internet service for low-income households. Today, the commission voted on the matter, approving the addition of internet subsidies to the Lifeline program that already offers both phone and prepaid wireless. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 03:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Is Sick Of Mass Shootings And Wants Congress To Do Something About Gun Control - We dont have all the facts, but we do know that once again, innocent people were killed in part because someone who wanted to inflict harm had no trouble getting their hands on a gun." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 03:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis Backs Science, Warns of Climate Risk - Whats generating the most attention, though, is the popes decision to delve into international politics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 03:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The longtime mayor of Charleston called Thursday for bolstered gun-control laws hours after an assailant opened fire in a historic African American church, killing at least nine people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 03:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Several young girls attended a public meeting recently to express their concern about the treatment of animals in Cecil County, Maryland. Adults responded to their participation by shouting racial insults at the girls. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 03:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All Systems Go for NASA's Mission to Jupiter Moon Europa - "Observations of Europa have provided us with tantalizing clues over the last two decades, and the time has come to seek answers to one of humanity's most profound questions." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 03:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. House of Representatives plans to bring legislation central to President Barack Obama's Pacific Rim trade agreement back to the floor for debate on Thursday, giving lawmakers a chance to deal with it in a different format. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 03:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hundreds of thousands of Haitian migrants and Dominicans of Haitian descent faced the risk of deportation from the Dominican Republic on Wednesday as a deadline for enforcement of a new immigration law approached. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 03:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A white tiger that had survived this weekends torrential flooding killed a man on Wednesday and was shot and killed itself, putting a horrifying end to a thoroughly depressing and occasionally bizarre few days for residents in Tbilisi, Georgia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 03:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An investigation by the authorities in Switzerland into the activities of FIFA, world soccers governing body, will include the examination of more than 50 suspicious financial relationships, the countrys chief federal prosecutor said on Wednesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 03:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 03:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article is a good example of the reasons for not allowing the industry giants to decide on net neutrality laws. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AT T Mobility LLC has been slapped with a record $100 million fine for offering consumers "unlimited" data, but then slowing their Internet speeds after they reached a certain amount. The company says it will fight the charges. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 03:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Egyptian court sentenced deposed President Mohamed Mursi to death on Tuesday over a mass jail break during the country's 2011 uprising and issued sweeping punishments against the leadership of Egypt's oldest Islamic group. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 03:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps spectacular, unending, utterly baffling, often-wrong campaign launch - This is the whole thing about fact-checking Donald Trump: He is un-fact-checkable. That's his gift and his angle. As he made clear today, he says whatever he wants for as long as he wants, because, why not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 03:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With a string of victories over Islamic State, Syria's Kurds are proving themselves an ever more dependable ally in the U.S.-led fight against the jihadists and building influence that will make them a force in Middle Eastern politics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 02:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Senate on Tuesday reaffirmed a ban against torturing detainees and moved ahead on a more than $600 billion defense policy bill that is entangled in a broader fight in Congress about caps on Pentagon and non-military spending. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 02:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bush Works to Recover From a Shaky Start - He just hasnt met the expectation level of what we expected of a Bush, said Senator John McCain, Republican of Arizona, who is supporting Senator Lindsey Grahams candidacy but likes Mr. Bush. And thats been a hindrance to him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 15:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Roman Catholic archbishop of St. Paul and Minneapolis and a deputy bishop resigned on Monday after prosecutors recently charged the archdiocese with having failed to protect youths from abuse by pedophile priests. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 14:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United States carried out an airstrike in Libya early Sunday against the mastermind of the 2013 terrorist seizure of an Algerian gas plant that left 38 foreign hostages dead, American and Libyan officials said on Sunday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 14:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Omar Hassan al-Bashir of Sudan, who faced arrest on charges of crimes against humanity and genocide, appeared to have slipped out of South Africa on Monday morning, dealing a serious blow to the International Criminal Courts six-year campaign to bring him to justice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 14:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a pre-emptive strike against a forthcoming United Nations report on the war last year between Israel and Palestinian militants in the Gaza Strip, Israels Foreign Ministry on Sunday issued a lengthy paper arguing that its troops adhered to international law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 14:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The long list of things O'Reilly knows nothing about begins with history. Actually, he makes up the history as he goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside The Messy Kansas Fight To Save Face On Tea Party Tax Cuts - We knew back in 2012 when the debate was going on about the tax bill exactly what the ramifications were going to be. Our finance folks ran the numbers and made it very clear that wed be $1.2 billion under water by now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 12:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israeli soldiers have killed a Palestinian man by running over him with their vehicle during clashes near Ramallah in the occupied West Bank, authorities say. Abdallah Ghanaeim, 21, died on Sunday morning after a soldier driving a military vehicle struck him during a dawn raid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 12:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkish President Tayyip Erdogan said a snap election would be "inevitable" if both the ruling AK Party and the main opposition fail in efforts to form a new government within the constitutional limit of 45 days. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 12:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran expressed concern on Friday over cyber-security of nuclear talks with six world powers after reported cyber-attacks on venues linked to the negotiations on its disputed nuclear program, the semi-official Fars news agency reported. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 03:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The good news: Polar bears, imperiled by climate change, appear to have found something new to eat. The bad news: It's dolphins. Scientists studying bears on the Arctic shores of Norway found several of the white-coated predators feasting on the remains of white-beaked dolphins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 03:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Democrats dealt President Obama a humiliating defeat on his free-trade initiative Friday, derailing a key priority for the president and rebuffing his rare, personal pleas for their support. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 02:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A local leader for the NAACP civil rights group is under investigation in Washington state for identifying herself as black on a city job application, as a Caucasian couple claims to be her biological parents. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 02:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rachel Dolezal exposes our delusional constructions and perceptions of race - As Greer wrote, Dolezal shows us how stupid the construct of race is. It can get you killed and it can get you an NAACP presidency. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 02:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Energy industry groups and states that oppose new U.S. rules for hydraulic fracturing on public lands are headed to court this month to try to block the regulations a day before they are to take effect. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 03:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. has spent more than $2.7 billion on the war against Islamic State militants in Iraq and Syria since bombings began last August, and the average daily cost is now more than $9 million, the Pentagon said Thursday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 03:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New U.S. Internet traffic regulations, known as net neutrality rules, will go into effect on Friday after a federal appeals court rejected the telecommunications industry's request to partly suspend their implementation while they are being litigated. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 03:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Israeli military has cleared itself of culpability in one of the most controversial incidents in last summers Gaza war: a missile attack that killed four children on Gaza beach and injured a number of others. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 03:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A French court rules on Friday whether former IMF boss Dominique Strauss-Kahn is guilty of sex crimes and if the man once tipped to become president of his country goes to prison. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 03:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The world is watching South Korea as the latest outbreak of Middle East respiratory syndrome (MERS) unfolds. But how exactly the virus jumps to humans in the first place is still unknown, and clues to that puzzle lie thousands of kilometres away. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 03:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A giant ring around Saturn is even larger than thought, spanning an area of space nearly 7,000 times larger than Saturn itself, researchers say. "We knew it was the biggest ring, but know we find it's even bigger than we thought, new and improved," the study's lead author </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 03:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A schoolboy doing work experience with an astrophysics professor has discovered a new planet 1,000 light years from Earth. Newcastle-under-Lyme school pupil Tom Wagg was 15 when he went for his work placement at Keele University, where he spotted a minuscule dip in the light from a faraway star </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 03:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A privately funded space advocacy group has deployed a solar sail in orbit. Such spacecraft could open up cheap space travel and provide ways to drag space debris out of orbit. LightSail uses no fuel. Instead it relies on a large reflective sail to capture the momentum inherent in sunlight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 02:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People often assume that the poor are less competent than the wealthy. Some even suggest that the poor have flawed values or ways of thinking. But my colleagues and I have recently found that the poor outperform the rich at some financial decisions. Under poverty, people develop a unique expertise. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 02:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An American man has been killed in Syria, a State Department spokesman said on Wednesday, declining to provide details. Department spokesman Jeff Rathke identified the American as Keith Broomfield. NBC News reported Broomfield was in Syria fighting alongside Kurdish forces </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 02:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Barack Obama on Wednesday ordered the deployment of 450 more U.S. troops to Iraq's Sunni heartland to advise and assist fragile Iraqi forces being built up to try to retake territory lost to Islamic State. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 01:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox host Megyn Kelly said Monday evening that the 14-year-old black girl who was thrown around and sat on by a police officer in McKinney, Texas, was no saint. Kellys comment was one in a series aimed at justifying police conduct outside the neighborhood pool party. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 03:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a major shift of strategy in Iraq, the Obama administration is planning to establish a new military base in Anbar Province and send hundreds of additional American military trainers to help Iraqi forces retake the city of Ramadi and repel the Islamic State. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 03:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
