<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9974</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, [i love adding new folks too](https://www.goodreads.com/user/show/28108653-jash-comstock) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In your opinion, what makes a great Goodreads/LibraryThing/other review site review? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a goodreads user, as I am sure many of you are, and I am trying to up my review game. I want to contribute and participate in quality and thoughtful dialogue about the books I read. What makes a great review? What format tips, content tips, or other suggestions would you make to someone trying to improve their reviews? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 13:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus was not a politician. In fact he tended to stay out of political discussions altogether (Matt. 22:21) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 04:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the tsp website (not my pay). Once you enroll you should get a letter outlining how to log on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 02:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the answer I was looking for, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 00:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize it is already diversified, I never said it was not. But there is a spectrum of funds to contribute to, and I was just curious if there is any value to contributing to more than one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TSP question; is it wise to put all of my contribution into a lifecycle fund, or should I diversify my contributions into various funds? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 23:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 21:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either would be fine with me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SMAB; I am looking for books documenting the multicultural history of America. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 18:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone recommend books documenting U.S history from a multicultural perspective? Something that explores the various influences that melted into the pot of our melting pot? Specifically African and Hispanic influences on early American thought, history, and culture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 07:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a progressive Democrat and I agree with you. Background checks and registration are about as far as much gun control as I support. I am a proud gun owner myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 05:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arguably it was FDR's fleet of weapons that saved England from being captured. They were pretty much done for on their own.



And if they had been occupied, I sincerely doubt that it would have meant global domination for the Nazis. The U.S. was not even in the picture at that point, FDR and the Russians likely would have routed the Nazis even without the help of England. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What world leader, living or dead, would you want in charge of your nation during the zombie apocalypse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 05:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The zombie apocalypse has come, but you are able to teleport any world leader from the past or present to take charge of your nation to respond to the apocalypse. Who do you choose and why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 05:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering the ridiculous gaggle that is the Republican party, he might not be as done as you think he is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think Hillary is more hawkish than Bill? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the things I admire the most about Bill Clinton's legacy is his emphasis on a peace-oriented foreign policy. Hillary seems to have a more hawkish legacy, support for the Iraq war, a hawkish time as Sec. Of State. 



What do y'all think?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a working class Centrist Democrat I have long felt my party was moving away from me, Jim Webb inspires my optimism. I know he is unlikely to win against Clinton, but it is nice to know that my party isn't totally progressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the Democratic nomination race wont be a Clinton coronation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 18:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should the Army go back to tech ranks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 18:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I understand the Army used to have two enlisted promotion tracks, one for leaders/NCOs and one for technocal experts (spc4 etc)

Why did we stop? Has pushing all soldiers into a leadership track had a serious impact on the NCO corps? Do you think we should go back to that practice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Can anyone explain if the flat straw hats are symbols of the U.S. Democratic Party? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 21:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird question I know. I do not see them as much anymore, but in old photos I always see Democrats wearing flat round straw hats (kind of like Barbershop Quartet straw hats) to conventions and stiff, usually with a patriotic band around the hat.. Can anyone explain whether this is strictly a Democrat thing and where it started? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 07:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, grouchy ass soldiers typically are preferable in the field to relaxed and comfortable soldiers. Ain't nothing wrong with a few bad attitudes every now and then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 21:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That he served with the [7th Infantry Division](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/7th_Infantry_Division_(United_States)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1746 map of London now available as an incredibly detailed Google map </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 08:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1746 map of London now available as an incredibly detailed Google map </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 07:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When America's Librarians Went To War </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 07:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 05:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Afghanistan. Totally different culture, and totally different experience being in a third world country </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 07:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude is lucky to have a girl who trusts him against such accusations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 06:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to participate! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 22M, bookworm looking for friends. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 06:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am interested in history, gardening, fiction/literature, travel, and writing. I am fairly friendless (though not exactly antisocial). Anyone want to be my friend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 06:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on what you mean by "check out". Finding a girl attractive is totally natural, and appreciating it is totally ok in my book. Slobbering over her like a piece of meat is something else altogether. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 22M/ looking for female friends to talk to. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 06:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a 22 year old bookworm and very shy with women/females and just want to expand my friend base to include more women. I thought perhaps reddit would be a good place to overcome my lifelong shyness with girls. I hope I am not coming off as pathetic/creepy, just looking for friends..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 22 [M4F] Northern NY (Originally from Alabama) - Shy soldier looking to overcome shyness with women. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 06:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am very shy with women/females and just want to expand my friend base to include more women. I thought perhaps reddit would be a good place to overcome my lifelong shyness with girls. I hope I am not coming off as pathetic/creepy, just looking for friends.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 04:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love firearms. I go to the range, hunt, and other firearm related hobbies.



I am also a huge gearhead, I love working on my motorcycle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jim Webb to make decision on presidential run in few days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 22:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 06:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take a dance class. There are no downsides.

1. You will be more confident.


2. Ladies generally find dancing attractive. 

3. If you are single, dance classes are often a great place to meet other singles.




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 06:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I talk to most kids near my age I think *god my generation is a bunch of fucking morons*. 



I do not like to identify as a millenial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 02:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Short answer; because Turkey has been at odds with the Kurds (the folks fighting ISIS) for a very long time. Many of the Peshmergas that are fighting ISIS now were fighting Turkey not long ago. 



They want ISIS to beat the Kurds (though they won't admit it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missouri Food Pantries Help Clients Grow Their Own Produce </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 01:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interested in travelling to Sri Lanka. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 18:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the soldiers I serve with is originay from Sri Lanka and will not stop bragging about the country. This has really made me want to see the place for myself, but I do not hear about a lot of Sri Lanka tourism. 


**Length** Around a week. 


I love exploring Buddhist sacred places, and love seeing places that are out of the typical tourist paths. I have heard quite a bit about Sri Lanka's tea and spice production, this would be interesting to learn about first hand. I love food and am a lretty adventurous traveller.



Can anyone speak from experience about travelling to Sri Lanka? Any recommendations or warnings? What about websites, books, or articles about Sri Lanka that would be useful for my travel research.?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 02:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not think English as a major was a mistake. College was a mistake. I have tons of debt, no job, and I am only now getting trained in a trade that can actually profit me. Many college grads are unemployed, while certified and unionized allied trade workers have phenomenal jobs. College is not for everyone, and do not let anyone tell you that you need to go to college to be successful. You need to have skills to be successful. There are other ways to procure those skills than college. Trade school, apprenticeship, the military etc can all make you *way* more successful than college and are way cheaper.. 


It is something to think about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 02:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. American high school kids are pretty much told that success= college. Blue collar jobs are seen as last resorts  by many. The truth is certified, unionized blue collar jobs make phenomenal money. Trade school is cheaper than college. Employment is way steadier and almost guaranteed in many areas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 02:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took all the basics, focused on tons of English and lit courses. I went to college (worst mistake of my life) for English, and I have been in the Army for the past four years... finally paying off debt. I wish I would have pursued trade school or an apprenticeship after highschool, college only gave me debt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Time of the Kurds; a great rundown of the Kurdish ethnic group. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 01:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is your favorite Democrat and Republican President of all time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Who is your favorite Democrat President of all time?

2. Who is your favorite Republican President of all time?

3. Explain your choices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 14:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is significant that nearly every post 9/11 vet in the house and senate is a Democrat. Nearly every veteran caucus is a Democrat majority caucus. 



Most vets benefits were initiated by Democrats; the Montgomery G.I. Bill, Post 9/11 G.I. Bill.... And then uou have the so called "Fighting Dems" who took the Hill in '06, all Veterans, all critical of how Bush handled the GWOT, all Democrats..


I just do not understand why vets would support the hawkish right... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 14:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats awesome, I just saw the 173rd flag and was curious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 04:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you serve with The Herd? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 03:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your father sounds like an amazing man. Thank you for sharing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 02:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which individual in your life is the greatest example of work ethic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 02:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which products and services do you associate with the American working class and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 02:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 00:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 


You made some really great points. I had never thought about how lower income people spend more money on things that actually benefit the economy, while higher income people are more likely to spend their tax cut on luxuries.. 



I am not entirely sold on the idea of progressive taxes, but you certainly gave me some food for thought to chew on.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 22:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Politics are not allowed in /r/military </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can we as a party attract the veteran voting base more effectively? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 22:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Veterans overwhelmingly support Republicans. It has been this way pretty much since FDR.. As a veteran myself, I see many of my brothers vehemently opposed to the Democratic party because of assumptions about our patriotism etc.. What message should our party extend to vets to let them know we are looking out for them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 20:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The growth of a language as an international language is an organic thing, not something socially engineered by a board or anything. I am a native English speaker, and I agree that it is not the best language for international business use, but it is not something we can just change. It rose to power when the US spearheaded the growth of global economy. The organic nature of things like the languages people choose make it difficult to change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: I do not believe in a progressive tax system. Change my view. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 20:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe in a flat tax system, where everyone pays the same percentage of their earnings in income tax. I do not believe in a progressive tax system where richer people pay a higher percentage than poor people. I am a working class democrat, but I do not see a progressive system stimulating economic growth. It seems to me that it is punishing somebody for making more money, making it more desirable to stay in the middle class instead of encouraging people to work their way up into a higher class.. On the other hand, I believe a flat tax based would be fairer. Rich people would pay more (because 15% of a million is higher than 15% of 35'000) but would still be encouraged to leave their capital in the US economy instead of finding ways around the tax code... Can someone make a solid case for a progressive tax system directed at a working class guy like me?
_____

 *Hello, users of CMV! This is a footnote from your moderators. We'd just like to remind you of a couple of things. Firstly, please remember to* ***[read through our rules](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/rules)***. *If you see a comment that has broken one, it is more effective to report it than downvote it. Speaking of which,* ***[downvotes don't change views](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/guidelines#wiki_upvoting.2Fdownvoting)****! If you are thinking about submitting a CMV yourself, please have a look through our* ***[popular topics wiki](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/populartopics)*** *first. Any questions or concerns? Feel free to* ***[message us](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=/r/changemyview)***. *Happy CMVing!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: the difference between left/right wing politics in America and left/right wing politics in the rest of the world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 15:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I understand correctly, the labels *left wing* and *right wing* mean something different here in the US than the rest of the world. Is this true? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 01:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes indeed. Womens liberation and boobies  are a winning combination for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 00:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blue dogs aren't the ones involved in this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Democratic Trade Rift Could Give Rise To 'Tea Party' Of The Left </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 00:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DNA Confirms Kennewick Man's Genetic Ties To Native Americans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 00:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Istanbul Bookstore Caters To Syrian Refugees In Need Of A Good Read </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 00:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Overparenting Looks Like From a Stanford Deans Perspective </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 03:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 02:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Wet T-shirt Contests </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 02:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best you can do right now is look at their records I recommend [on the issues](http://www.ontheissues.org/default.htm).

Most of the candidates have not laid out clear cut policy stances yet, its too early in the race. For now they are just gonna talk about vague things like income inequality, climate change, etc without clearcut solutions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 02:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/ornitholoqy101 doesn't like boobs?


Neither did Stalin you commie bastard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 02:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The typical chain of unit sizes goes like this; **Platoon** led by a Lieutenant and Sergeant First Class, **Company** led by a Captain and First Sergeant, **Battalion** led by a Lieutenant Colonel and Sergeant Major, **Brigade** led by a Colonel and Command Sergeant Major, and **Division** led by a General and Command Sergeant Major.


A regiment used to be the equivalent of two battalions, but now it is used by various sized units. 


An Airborne unit is a unit that is made up of Airborne Paratroopers, that trains to deploy via parachute into combat when needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 23:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even in my dreams you blind me.

Not the kind of blind that takes away sight;

But the kind of blind that, taken breathless by a sight 

Attracts attention to that great sight in such a way 

That nothing else can be seen

For your colors are the only true colors.

Your contrast stands out against the blackness 

Like a veritable sunshine of bright eyes

And waves of hair that compete with the ocean in grace. 

I stumble around unsatisfied

For in having seen a sight so blinding

My vision remains imprinted with you.

Now, neither in this world or the one made of dreams

Could I ever have an unclouded view.

For you pump through my veins 

And leak from my pores

And my vision is blinded by you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Feeding The Homeless Runs Afoul Of The Law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 18:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Feeding The Homeless Runs Afoul Of The Law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 18:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 00:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Emma Stone

2. Michelle Rodriguez

3. Rachel Ray (my parents never understood why 30 minute meals was a favorite show of mine)

4. Kim Possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: the basic tenets of Hinduism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 00:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explain what "militant unionism" is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 15:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have often heard the phrase uses in reference to the IWW and sometimes the ILWU, but have never understood it. Can someone explain it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 01:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing like a little Bohemian Rhapsody.



[This is my all time favorite version](http://m.youtube.com/watch?v=dQw4w9WgXcQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 01:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Piss on this other guy's lawn and eat his bowl of gravy train white humping his bitch.



Edit; I am a dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 01:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the ol' [switchit redde-roo](http://www.reddit.com/r/gameofthrones/comments/39alh6/s1_spoilers_remember_when_we_all_hated_this_guy/cs2apmx?context=1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explain what "militant unionism" is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 20:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have often heard the phrase uses in reference to the IWW and sometimes the ILWU, but have never understood it. Can someone explain it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course she has pubic hair. They are water moccasins. They won't turn a man into stone, but will make him rock hard... if you know what I mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recommend something melancholy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 05:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recommend something melancholy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 05:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has been a day of sad memories, and I honestly just want to drink deeply from the bitter cup. Can y'all recommend the most melancholy songs you know? I want to be swept away by blunt force lyrics and sad, slow songs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 03:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never convicted, I was typing on my touchscreen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kalief Browder, the young man who spent three years on Rikers Island without ever being committed of a crime has taken his own life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 03:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kalief Browder, the young man who spent three years on Rikers Island without ever being committed of a crime has taken his own life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 03:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 05:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You obviously have no clue what Capitalism is. None of those nations have free and unregulated economies. They are mixed economies. 


Workers own the means of production in those nations through cooperatives, and are backed up by very strict economic regulation from the state. None of those nations have government planned economies because as I have been saying all along *not all forms of socialism advocate state run economies*. Communism advocates state control, many socialists do not advocate for state control of the markets. Hell, Anarcho-Syndicalists and Libertarian Socialists are against the existence of **any state at all**.




For the record, I am neither a Socialist, or a Communist, I am a Laissez Faire Capitalists Libertarian. I just don't wrongly represent people I disagree with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question for nonMarxist socialists about the use of money in a socialist society. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 04:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I understand it, Marxists advocate for a moneyless society. 


What about non Marxist socialists? what role would money play in a socialist society? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 04:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are using poor examples of Sanders' Democratic Socialist line of thought. China is nowhere near his radar. China is in the Marxist line of thought.


Sanders advocates Democratic Socialism, as found in Canada, Denmark, Finland, the Netherlands, and other European nations. Contrast the living examples of these Socialist nations to China (and more extremely North Korea) and you can see in living color the difference between Democratic Socialism and Communism.


I am not down voting you, maybe the community just thinks you are wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 03:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democratic socialism is reformist not revolutionary. They do not want to overthrow/abolish the state and monetary system, they want to reform the state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 03:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is a Democratic Socialist,  not a Marxist/Leninist. In policies he is more of a progressive.


He advocates worker control of the means of production achieved through democracy. 


Communism advocates participation in class revolution culminating in the abolition of class, state, and money.


They are two totally different things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 02:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just have to come to terms with the fact that your brother is a different person than you, and entitled to his own choices and lifestyle. Do you, and let him be him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's talk about immigration. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 02:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your ideal end state for U.S. policies on immigragion?



What realistic reforms would you like to see implemented after this next election? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your thoughts on the TPP? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 02:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The President is obviously for it, but many unions are very upset about the fast track in the TPP.


1. What are your thoughts on the TPP?

2. Do you think Democrat support for the TPP could affect the traditionally strong bond between organized labor and our party?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: the difference between progressivism and neoprogressivism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 02:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 02:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which specific policies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 02:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. When has he ever voted against his declared opinion?


2. Which specific socialist policies?


3. He is a social democrat not a communist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 00:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you think Bernie is a communist you are an idiot.


He is a social democrat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 19:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about Sanders?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you vote for Bernie over Hillary? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 15:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Would you vote for Bernie Sanders over Hillary?


2. Would you vote for Bernie over Rand?


Why or why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate Rejects Extending Veterans Benefits To Married Gay Couples And Their Kids </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 02:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 02:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I named that legislation because you wanted proof that he supported worker control of means of production.



It is more than a label, it is a perspective he actively embraces and one I reject. If he really is the socialist he says he is, I worry about his end state goals because I do not support the economic end state goals of socialism or social democratism in the slightest. 



I would prefer a candidate more in line with Clinton's third way approach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 02:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does not boil down to this specific legislation, it is the outlook of socialist economic policy. I just don't think I am comfortable supporting someone whose economic outlook is that far left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 01:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, that is the very definition of a socialist, which he identifies as.


Second, [here is where he actually presented legislation supporting it.](http://www.sanders.senate.gov/newsroom/recent-business/worker-owned-businesses-2014) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 01:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly socialist insistence on worker control of means of production. My outlook on economic issues varies from his, I support a freer economy with a strong federal infrastructure. 



That being said, I don't hate Sanders. I totally support his stance on civil liberty, marriage equality, foreign policy etc. I will also add that Vermont has some of the most lax gun laws in the nation, which I support as a second amendment loving Democrat (who said deep blue states have to hate guns?) 


I just don't know if I would support him over Rand, who has pretty identical views on civil liberty, foreign policy, and the like but an economic outlook I am more comfortable with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 01:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Socialism's main goal is worker control of the means of production.


Progressivism is a philosophy pursuing a mixed market  "third way" economy.



There are some pretty strong differences between the two. I am neither a socialist or progressive though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 01:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Registered Democrat. I align more with Blue Dogs/New Democrats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 01:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rand is not Ron. I don't believe he would destroy welfare, state education, the IRS etc. His goals are more geared towards dismantling the NSA's power, hopefully supporting marijuana legalization, and other civil liberties.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 22:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I would vote for Rand over Hillary.



I would not vote for any other republicans, they are all GOP establishment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 21:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yes](http://nypost.com/2015/04/28/bernie-sanders-to-run-for-president-as-democrat/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 21:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So in your opinion the only true populism is one in which the party "for the people" remains exclusively revolutionary?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 18:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I would vote for Rand Paul. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 17:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In what way? What information? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 17:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends which Republican.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 15:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I am not that far left. I am a moderate/centrist Democrat. Believe it or not [less than half of Democrats identify as "liberal"](http://www.gallup.com/poll/180452/liberals-record-trail-conservatives.aspx).


Not all of us are as progressive as Sanders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts on the current wave of Left Wing Populism rising around the world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 15:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you view the rise of Syriza in Greece as a good thing, or negative thing for Socialism?


What about the rise of Left Wing Populism of parties like the Citizens Movement in Mexico, and even candidates like Bernie Sanders running for the U.S. presidency as an open Left Wing Populist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alabama Senate Votes to End State Marriage Licenses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 23:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its Time to Let Edward Snowden Come Home - The New Yorker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 23:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 17:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am an Alabama resident currently stationed in NY. So much for Republicans sticking up for Servicemembers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 17:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine would be Jim Webb, though I know it is next to impossible. As a Veteran, I respect his service immensely, his Centrism aligns with mine, his proven record as senator  and Secretary of the Navy. I think he would make a phenomenal President. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If any Democrat of your choice could get the 2016 nomination, who would it be and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 17:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 16:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I did not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 16:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 80% Democrat, 37% republican </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 02:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A government that does not spy on me, start useless wars, and does not infringe on my civil liberties </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 22:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are the blue dogs still around? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 21:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok.. I didn't come here to argue about gun control. I do not mind background checks, but I oppose legislation that tries to ban guns and magazine size. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 18:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I am a Sanders fan myself. But isn't he an independent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Republican wondering if I would fit into the Democratic Party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 18:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to be a moderate republican with some libertarian leanings. I have just gotten to the point where they have totally ran away from me. I have voted Democrat in the past, and am thinking about becoming a registered Democrat. I thought I would ask for advice finding a place in this party.



I support civil liberties totally. I support drug decriminalization, marajuana legalization, and marriage equality. I support drastic immigration  reform. I consider myself a Square Deal Democrat. I advocate for total transparency  in government, demilitarization of police forces, prison reform, and an end to mandatory minimum sentencing. 



On the other hand, there are a few issues I worry would put me at odds with the Democratic party. I do not support gun control. I generally prefer the state to stay out of the markets (though I am a not a rabid welfare hater or anything). 


What do you say? Am I at odds with the party? Are there any factions/caucuses or anything that I might be able to connect with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Afghanistan vet considering Americorps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 05:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone heard of other vets joining Americorps? I know many volunteers are fresh out of college. I have been in war, been shot at, done Army stuff, but I am looking for a new way to connect with the world and serve. Would I be out of place amongst other volunteers? Would my services put me at an advantage? I would really prefer volunteering in urban areas affected by heavy gang violence, or something that can really use my skills is there something like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Afghanistan vet considering the peace corps. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 05:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone heard of other vets joining the peace corps? I know many volunteers are fresh out of college. I have been in war, been shot at, done Army stuff, but I am looking for a new way to connect with the world and serve. Would I be out of place amongst other volunteers? Would my services put me at an advantage? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 04:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you comfortable with the state of human rights within U.S. prisons?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 03:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incredible, but sad discovery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wreck Of A 221-Year-Old Slave Ship Is Confirmed Off South Africa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 03:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wreck Of A 221-Year-Old Slave Ship Is Confirmed Off South Africa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 03:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 03:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe in a 1984 media conspiracy, but I believe most of the media is bent way beyond any hope of objectivity. The media is controlled by vapid and sensationalist western culture. This is why guys like Hannity, Bill O'Reilly, The Reid Report etc exist. 


I tend to get my news from NPR, Reuters, and BBC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's talk about prison reform. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 02:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. What  do you see as the ideal endstate of prison reform (how would you like to see the U.S. justice system ideally operate)?



2. What realistic steps would you like to see taken now to reform the prison system? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A caveman returns to his tribe after having investigated a wildfire, where he found/tasted the burnt carcass of an antelope, thus becoming the first human to taste barbeque. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 01:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 06:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freckles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 20:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why the rest of the world hates us. We act like 2 year olds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What were the reasons that Texas declared independence from Mexico for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 02:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Was Santa Anna a particularly oppressive leader?

2. What events caused Texas to declare independence from Mexico?

3. Were there many in Texas who remained loyal to Mexico? (Like the Tories in the American Revolution)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What were the reasons that Texas declared independence from Mexico for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 02:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Was Santa Anna a particularly oppressive leader?

2. What events caused Texas to declare independence from Mexico?

3. Were there many in Texas who remained loyal to Mexico? (Like the Tories in the American Revolution) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 17:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bite the Buffalo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 21:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not all Muslims do those things, Islamic Extremists do. Just like Christian extremists during the Holy Roman empire murdered thousands of "barbarians" at the sword for not converting, Mormon extremists took child brides (statutory rape), Japanese nationalist extremists killed themselves in Kamikaze strikes at Pearl Harbor. 


Extremism takes on many forms. Blanketing an entire demographic with the actions of a few nut jobs is unfair and unAmerican. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 20:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have 15 wives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 02:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New officers think they are kings, when really they are dumber than privates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 02:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *American Sphinx: The Character of Thomas Jefferson* by Joseph J. Ellis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 02:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Join the military. I have a successful career, good pay, steady work, and good employment opportunities when I get out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 01:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotten married, gone to Afghanistan, lost good friends, became a leader in my field. I am nowhere near the same kid I was five years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
