<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8459</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one is great... [if you'll allow it.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lpKQHpMGMNQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The world was created for people my height! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nazi Robot Movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 11:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend and I were talking and were wondering if there is a movie where the Nazis created an army of robots? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 14:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what is.... Mars?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 11:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erasing the ending from your mind more than likely won't be possible, but I've read the book and the clues Q picks up on can still interest you. Try to say no to your temptation of googling the ending of a book and remind yourself that it'll just ruin the book, this would be one of those things you can add to your list of experiences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet strangely better than anything I could do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ducks are awesome friends and their quacks makes me laugh every time, what isn't to love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thumbnail made me think she had a beard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit was the one that created that fear for me... whoo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck a monkey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 15:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The control governments have over our lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bad guys always lose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 11:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Borderlands, It's funny, not too hard to get the hang of and helps teach the importance of skill and stat point placement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 11:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't know. Some beliefs are that we're reincarnated (What as is based on how good you were in your previous life), we go to an alternate plane e.g. Heaven/Hell, our souls are trapped on earth forever or until a goal is completed, we're ghosts with a purpose or that we simply die and that's it, nothing happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 10:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :O It's the all original, all game changing "Fall Out..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 12:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this in a universe that is excluding Vault 108 and the one true god(s) Gary?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 12:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you watch the Fallout Lore series you'll learn about the water merchants who were able to obtain water that was deep inside the earth that had its radioactivity filtered out by the ground. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 11:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the major flaws in this is in some of the video's we're shown, they give footage of us in the vault and say events transpire while we're down there :/. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 11:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amata's my bae.... shame all she ever does is hate you for doing the right thing :(. Really wish they expanded her more as a companion atleast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 23:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He shall make for a great companion in a desolate vault, or a great prop (or a thousand) for a social experiment.While you're at it, you should take up metal working too and make him some power armor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 23:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem like an awesome dad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 14:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dude earlier today who showed his mouse pad resulted in me buying one of the two bears highfiving.... HYPE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the positive side you made it to the toilet in time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 13:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Codsworth will be my going out on adventures companion because I wouldn't be able to handle Dogmeat being injured in fights... also Codsworth can talk to me and stop me from going completely insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
