<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7011</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lucas is my bet for Big A and Marion is BW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just talking out my ass here, but being in a mental asylum may undernourish someone. I've seen lots of blondes dye their hair black. You never know. We've never seen lucas' parents. We don't know if he's adopted. But again, I'm just trying to justify it. I could be completely wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't know. Either Charles is dead and he's impersonating him or hes somehow Charles. People can look years younger than what they really are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just compare the activity of him and someone like Julian Morris.  I know people may say that Julian won't post to give it away, but I think Brendan is posting more because he knows he'll be revealed as A. He hasn't appeared on PLL since the Xmas episode yet all of a sudden he's posting a lot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right but there was also a coincidence for Charles and Melissa in Black Widow Farm, yet people believe that. I'm just saying it's odd Freddy was used at the end of the episode and then there's a photophrapher named Freddy Lucas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol no but the name. lol the name and the fact that he's a photographer and look as this https://twitter.com/brendanrobinson

He is SO PLL Active compared to Drew and Julian, even Vanessa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freddy...Lucas...Photo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freddy...Lucas...Photo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It HAS to be Lucas. I am 1,000% sure now it's Lucas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So spoiler...but look at this website...hmmmm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you get cake, and he gets cake, and EVERYONE GETS CAKES </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pll themed shower thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wait a fucking minute...if the time jump is five years later and they're graduating in 2012, that means they'll be in the future, 2 years ahead of now. So we'll know who Uber A on the same year they do, 2017. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahahah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
