<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5236</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Louisiana hacker held without bond, allegedly controlled thousands of computers while living in his grandparents home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? How long is he gonna do this for? Come on guy...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw it while I was in. E6 and an E4 get caught stealing ammunition and selling it. E6 dropped to E5 and good to carry about his career, while the E4 went to E1 and was kicked out of the army. The militaries justification, the E6 had more time in service and was valuable enough to the army to keep around due to rank and specialty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 07:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hungry, man... All right, yo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 06:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont think thats how hyphens work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, you gonna use punctuation or not? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can do anything </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 00:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> at a water park </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 00:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you fucked us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Louisiana Police officers placed on leave after burglary suspect allegedly shot himself while in police custody with a police-issue Glock 27 he found in the police car. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 00:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **"It's a water park. And they ran out of water," says Vega Crain, who waited for two years to see "Panic! at the Disco".** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Water Park in Louisiana runs out of water during Panic at the Disco Concert, Panic ensues. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 22:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it was a she dumbass. look at those sexy ass feminine fingers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 09:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive traveled. I know what different Islamic cultures are like. Thanks but no thanks on the read. I was just giving my opinion on the hijab. You can keep your hijab. I don't give two flying shits. While you're at it just where two. Or three. Knock yourself out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 09:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. You're wrong. Those comparisons arent at all similar. You can't compare lingerie to a hijab. It's obviously not fashionable if it's the highlight of an article about a woman winning best dressed. The articles pretty much says hey look this girl who won best dressed even though she wears this stupid oppressive shit scarf.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 09:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what type of winter coat you wearing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 09:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> turn it around </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 09:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a Hijab for men in Islam? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 09:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say an article of clothing that exist for women, but not men, and is sole purpose is modesty is pretty oppressive against women.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
