<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1446</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apparently the Shaun The Sheep Movie is only coming out in the US now. You should all go see it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It came out here a good few months ago and it's terrific, I'd love to see a British stop motion animated film do well in America.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I was just playing along with nomefish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 01:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But The Muppets Show is in the same universe as the latest two films. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And only a week after they said we wouldn't see it. For anyone who doesn't know the actual show is about the Muppets working on a talk show hosted my Miss Piggy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What should be on everybody's bucket list? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 20:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably my favourite Hollywood Handbook episode and one of my firsts. The Bababooey bit is so funny to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 20:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say the fish in Finding Nemo were more similar to real fish than that main dinosaur. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. I actually watched the G.I Joe episode of Community recently and I could only hear Diane and not Annie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was actually Daniel Radcliffe?? I thought it was Paul F. Tompkins again, since it sounded like  his Andrew Garfield. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 11:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly this status could very much just mean Tig is officially leaving, the show might still continue without her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 01:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I meant non-main character. 

Yeah, last night I was actually watching the G.I Joe episode of community and I heard Diane whenever Alison spoke instead of Annie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 21:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping we'd get a full episode about the Back To The Future 9/11 conspiracy video.

Also does anyway have a link to the original Harmontown Hollow Earth episode? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 21:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the credits it says "This film was shot on location in New York City, which is almost like another character." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 21:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really remind me of someone but I can't put my finger on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 21:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's been a while but music rights work completely differently for UK television, anything that isn't scripted sort of has the same rules as radio. They own the rights to play it, not to sell it. As long as you don't sell DVD's with the music you can put any music the channel owns, and all of the big channels have deals with the music studios. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 02:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe people seem blind to this fact. For some people under the age of 30 Star Wars is some old films they haven't seen or those 3 films that came out that everyone hated. I have quite a few friends who only went to see the prequels when they came out during the hype and are turned off Star Wars completely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 21:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I really need Simon for the christmas livestream.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 14:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like an actual Christmas Special though, with actual character development. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 13:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never realised she did Vincent! You can hear her all over though yeah, most notably the older girl of Horsin' Around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> me too. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 20:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pm please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 17:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 16:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you haven't watched Bojack Horseman, he's in the new season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 11:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially because it looks like they did a HD conversion of the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he link to my facebook page? I guess he just reversed image search? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hollywood Facts: The Theme Song: The Board Game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? But this is way too spooky for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm probably going to have this for about a year. I had my last one for a year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really, basically just take a screenshot of your facebook page and put it in the layer above the picture. Then I exported the image that fit in the profile box and then I exported the image that fit in the cover box. The templates are just sort of the ones on  Facebook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit. Well fuck mobile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not actually literally set a few neighbourhoods over from Phineas and Ferb. If you read the source for that it says "And what's really cool is that -- in my mind, anyway -- Mikey Murphy just lives a couple of neighborhoods over from Phineas and Ferb." It's not like a true spin off or anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My new Facebook cover and profile picture. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 00:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My laptop doesn't play it better. Simple as that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody still play Minecraft on Xbox 360? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of the people I used to play with have migrated to different games or the One. So if you still play this please add GT: 
"CianHatesPeople." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 12:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I can't really imagine Kermit sticking his hands up in the air and screaming awwwaaahahhaha in this new style and tone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 12:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can have both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 12:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enjoy the karma s4082211.

Also feeling a little down since this is the first UTU2TM since Harris left us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 18:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow I'm surprised they didn't show Elizabeth Banks in the trailer. Maybe they're doing the same joke in the actual premier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TruTV Prank Lineup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 18:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 11:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or 18.
Source: Born in 97 and am 18. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping for it to come out this week. Only two more days then!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure you're thinking about this way more than Paul but the other british characters from him are.. the pie minister, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A subreddit or website that has a list of real life achievements that you can claim by submitting proof. A new achievement is available everyday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/showerorange could be one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the problem with this is that to offer a sale on an item it has to have been that price in the past month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 11:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good one.

EDIT: I thought Spontenation had begun at the end there since I had it queued up. I was confused as to why Paul was reading an ad for his show on his show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Billy and Mandy and Codename Kids Next Door were on the same level of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I seen the thumbnail I assumed puppeteers would be under the table but they're fully visible! I love this so much. If you're willing to have writers on comic con panels the puppeteers should be there too. 

This is a very rare occurrence and I'm surprised it happened. It's probably the only thing I disagree with Jim Henson on, he was on the side of always keeping the puppeteers a secret.

EDIT: Also wow that whole Promo we seen is completely thrown out the window. I will say the plot to this show sounds more Muppets Tonight that The Muppets Show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 00:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a TV movie. They've done a bunch of these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 22:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It feels like a biopic about the inventor of time travel at times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 19:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should get her to do this if she hasn't seen Star Wars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
