<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9536</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey club with a side of God's gift to Earth.... Truffle Fries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 19:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's in Blue Ash, a small city outside Cincinnati, OH.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 15:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it is a potato latke, also very delicious!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Classic Rueben from Rascals New York Deli (not in New York) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 20:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Hoo knows why' pork, chicken, fries, all covered in cheese, hot sauce, white bbq sauce, and traditional southern bbq sauce. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 22:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 01:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Saul is dead, yet. When Saul asked to speak to Carrie on the phone when he first escaped, he made her promise to take him out if he were to be captured again and Carrie failed to keep this promise. She had to deal with the emotions that followed that decision. I think somehow Saul gets "captured" or taken again by Haqqani, thus Carrie will have to deal a similar decision of killing both Haqqani and Saul, OR there is a possibility of Saul taking his own life while killing Haqqani at the same time. Either way, I think Saul's capture really took a toll on Saul not only physically but mentally and morally. When it comes down to it either Carrie "pulls the trigger" killing Saul and Haqqani, or Saul does it. Either way I'm ready for the new episode now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 20:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sitting in class when I opened the post, instant goose bumps  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
