<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9812</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually read in well lit areas. Today, for example, I read at work during lunch at about 1130...started falling asleep. 

As for a more interesting book, any suggestion for someone who used to read a lot of fiction stuff? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting sleepy while reading: print vs. ebooks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am trying to get back into reading regularly. Most times, I prefer print books over ebooks but whenever I read I start to fall asleep regardless of the book's content. If anyone here has also experienced this, is there a way to combat this? Will ebooks perhaps keep this from happening? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There isn't any save data in the cloud since this particular PS account doesn't have Plus; another user on the console has it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Far Cry 4 save data was deleted but it looks like there is still campaign data saved on the console. Is there any way to recover the campaign and progress since it seems as though there is still data from the game in the system storage? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 04:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 04:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 04:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info. We don't have any assets together. We have only purchased small things that, to me, are inconsequential. There is a child involved however. She's three and I was there when she was born and have raised her since yet she is not biologically mine. My name is even on her birth certificate so I fear this could complicate things a bit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 03:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, neither of us has a lot of money and we don't have any assets together. She has told me in the past that she wouldn't want anything from me and I believe her considering the state of our relationship currently. I had figured that our individual incomes and debts would be unaffected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 03:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you happen to know how much it costs to file it yourself? I would love to avoid lawyers; I don't believe that we need one considering we wouldn't really be arguing over anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My wife and I are considering uncontested divorce. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 02:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the past couple years, we have been in a slow decline. Various things happened that dampened our feelings for each other until, now, we are more friends than a married couple. We have been thinking about uncontested divorce, or as it's called here in Illinois, a dissolution of marriage. Does anyone here have any experience with this and know how it works in this state? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 07:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kansas - Carry On Wayward Son </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My 3-year-old daughter likes to play Bloodborne </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 23:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
