<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7371</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just wanted to remind people that this was here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 17:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fire and Rain by James Taylor. It's about his girlfriend dying on a trip home to surprise him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frankly I think it's ridiculous that anyone sees more potential in Brown than they do Revere. Brown has proven to be ineffective in every outfield position and his offense is terribly inconsistent. He is at best a AAAA-level ball player; too good for the minors but not good enough for the majors. I'd take Revere over Brown any day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 16:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was always a fan of Next Door Nikki </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the point of the sub is to pick one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 16:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off let me just say you're FAR too hard on yourself. The first step in success in changing how you view yourself. Find one thing you do like about yourself and, for a time, focus on how awesome you are at that. Then build from there.
Second, ADHD will always keep you from being "normal" but that doesn't mean it has to hold you back. There are a lot of ways that those of us with ADHD have it better than those without; we have more varied interests, we can get to be good at a lot of different things, and we can task-shift better (good in jobs requiring attention to lots of things), to name a few. 
ADHD is an obstacle that needs to be overcome, but it is far from impossible. All it takes is you making the decision to not let it get you down and to find a way to make it work for you. Figure out what pulls your attention and focus your energies on it, and you can and will succeed. 
You can do this, man. I believe in you.

Also, let me just add that you have a very good writing voice. Maybe try writing more: journals, short stories, poems, whatever. Not only is it good for our brains to write stuff down like that, but you may find your path in it. Just a thought.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 18:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
