<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5170</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Men who harass women online are quite literally losers, new study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The so-called pro-life activists playing "gotcha" with a doctor who thinks and speaks in clinical terms essentially wants more people like me to clasp hands with a pathologist before they start to cut on a dead baby to find out why it is in front of them instead of in the nursery." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MODERN MEDICINE Why I Had to Buy My Wife's Inhaler on the Dark Web </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 05:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goodbye To All That Gawking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News is not real news: San Francisco City Supervisor owns anonymous Fox News troll harassing him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 04:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This new bill would add $9 billion for medical research. Here are 5 reasons critics are terrified. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 06:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The rise and fall of the German Empire: What Greeces crippling bailout deal reveals about the future of Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 18:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Laziness Dogma </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 18:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do You Know How Your Daughter Died?" When Gloria Huang was declared dead in a Qatar emergency room, her parents had no time to grieve before they were caught up in a legal nightmare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 17:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 06:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, that's not what they're calling austerity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Federal Court Just Threatened Citizens United </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 20:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austerity Has Failed: An Open Letter From Thomas Piketty to Angela Merkel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 15:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This map shows how red states increase inequality and blue states cut it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 16:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the First Time in 12 Years, Measles Has Killed an American </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 07:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iowa Catholics Will Put GOPers In 'Awkward Position' On Climate Change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 05:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> can Gay Marriage Defeat the Islamic State? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 17:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a fast-changing culture, can the GOP get in step with modern America? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 17:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doom for a Cynical Assault on Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Roberts Courts Reality Check </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Krugman: Hooray for Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EXCLUSIVE: Presidential candidate Donald Trump has ignored five jury summonses in past nine years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 07:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 17:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! You are an inspiration!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Charleston Shooter: Racist, Violent, and Yes  Political -- How could it not be political, when the Republican Party has weaponized its supporters and made violence a virtue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 17:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Georgia Newspaper Retracts Alert Saying 'The Sun Just Exploded' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The facts vs. David Brooks: Startling inaccuracies raise questions about his latest book </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 15:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Krugman: Democrats Being Democrats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 15:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Does Obama Want This Trade Deal So Badly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Santorum Says Only Having 4 People Show Up at Campaign Event Is Part of His Plan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 15:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 19:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look fantastic! I'm still avoiding photos but you are an inspiration! Congrats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reporter stumbles across ALEC meeting, gets kicked out of hotel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reporter stumbled across the meeting while on vacation with his family,and Koch lobbyist got him thrown out of the resort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legislators and corporate lobbyists meet in secret at Georgia resort </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Agony of Medical Bills Even for people with generous insurance plans, a trip to an in-network doctor can result in thousands of dollars in unexpected charges. Can anything be done? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 04:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 19:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look great! Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Public Editor: NYT Stringer's 'Jewish Litmus Test' Was 'Unacceptable' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 02:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judith Miller And James O'Keefe Discuss Ethics In Journalism (VIDEO) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 02:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk Says Attending the Birth of Your Child Is No Excuse for Missing a Work Function </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 23:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Washington Post's Police Problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 15:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman uncovers two-way mirror in a bar bathroom; owner says it'll stay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 16:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Gawker's Union Effort Is A Big Deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 16:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Krugman: It Takes a Party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 18:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dallas Observer Editor Still Confused by Women a Who Play Music </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 00:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Other Indiana Law: The First Woman Jailed For 'Feticide' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 16:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you or your cat been eating fish caught by slaves? Probably! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 02:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans Unveil Plan For Replacing Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 18:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Lost Possibility: Women on Miscarriage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 14:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Consumers Getting 'Skinned' by Health Insurers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 00:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Francisco 49ers Linebacker Retires at 24 Over Head-Trauma Fears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 14:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Your World Is On Fire': Ted Cruz Shouts Insane Rhetoric At Terrified Little Girl In New Hampshire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 23:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bush calls net neutrality craziest' idea Ive ever heard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 04:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lumber Liquidators Linked to Health and Safety Violations: 60 Minutes found that Lumber Liquidators' Chinese-made laminate flooring contains amounts of toxic formaldehyde that may not meet health and safety standards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 21:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Democratic Progressives Survived a Landslide: They ran against Wall Street and carried the white working class. The Democrats who shunned populism got clobbered. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 20:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saving Obama From a Bad Trade Deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 20:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans hankering for ground was against ISIS. What could go wrong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 20:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Behind Supreme Courts Obamacare Case, A Secretive Societys Hidden Hand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 07:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 17:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm back starting over after a grand total of 5 pounds lost and regained on round one. I'm 61, much older than most folks here, and at 5'6" am weighing in at 202. I have put on the weight gradually over the years. I tend to be sedentary and am a stress eater. My goal is 150, using My Fitness Pal and aiming to walk 10,000 steps a day with a tracker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 17:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 17:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a bad spell a couple of years ago and ended up going to physical therapy for it. They told me that freezing one of those ridged Ice Mountain water bottles and rolling that under your foot for about five minutes a couple of times a day is helpful, as is spreading and then relaxing the toes on the foot, also for five minutes or so a couple of times a day. I agree that getting lighter is probably the ultimate fix! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rahm Emanuel Runoff: Chicago Mayor Tied to Lobbyist for City's Red Light Camera Firm, Review Shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 17:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Power to the Partisans: the Supreme Court's conservatives think democracy is overrated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 08:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HILLARY EMAIL SCANDAL? NOT SO FAST </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 07:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 19:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, what a noticeable difference, and in only a month! Congratulations! Do you mind if I ask what your daily calorie allotment is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 19:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you doing for the plantar fasciitis? I had it a few years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 19:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, that is their standard response -- that and saying that the tax cuts didn't work because they just weren't deep enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Scott Walker Antidote: Minnesota </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 17:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker Wants Colleges to Stop Reporting Sexual Assaults </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 00:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker Wants Colleges to Stop Reporting Sexual Assaults </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 00:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Justice Roberts Just Tip His Hand On Key Obamacare Ruling? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 18:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton has a plan to fix Washington. It is not a good plan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 16:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Partial Accounting of the Damage Netanyahu Is Doing to Israel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 16:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> O'Reilly Under Fire, Threatens New York Times Reporter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 15:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Male Politician Thinks that Your Vagina and Stomach are Connected </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 05:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Idaho Lawmaker Learns a Valuable Lesson About the Female Reproductive System </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 23:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 17:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a dietician associated with the practice that's treating your dad? Or one his doctor can refer you to? That might be one source of advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rudy Giuliani, American Soviet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 08:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rudy Giuliani's fall from America's Mayor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 16:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 16:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Irrational wouldn't bother me as much as the ideological bias I see. Seems like right-leaning mods have managed to ban all posts from certain publications, and now they are also going after posts that are unfavorable towards Republicans from their list of allowed publications, using laughably inappropriate rationales. 

Pretty ironic for a political forum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 18:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This post has been banned from r/Politics, supposedly because Giuliani is a "private citizen" (He's not, he's a public figure) and the column is just nasty old gossip (It's not, it's all on the public record).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 18:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the mod reply I got when I asked why it was being censored: 

from hoosakiwi[M] via /r/politics/ sent 45 minutes ago
"The entire post is about a private citizen and his statements about Obama. More than half of it is about the personal life of that private citizen (Mr. Guiliani). It is not explicitly political and at best could be seen as a gossip article."

Here is my reply to the mod: 

Mr Giuliani is a public figure. He is still referred to as "Mayor Giuliani" and he tried to win the Republican presidential nomination in 2008. He made the remarks about Obama's lack of love of country in a speech to a political gathering, and the remarks were widely reported by the media. If Giuliani wants to be regarded as a private citizen, maybe he should not speak at political gatherings about political figures, then follow up by talking to the press about it.
In addition, all of the facts in the article you censored are a matter of public record.
Do the mods have a system of checks and balances or is one mod's decision final? This is pretty clearly an attempt to shield Giuliani.
P.S. Learn to spell the name of the "private citizen" you're trying to protect.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 18:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You had a pretty face before as well, but now you're a stunner! Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 17:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, somehow not knowing my calorie count with WW always bugs me and the fruits especially can add up. Thanks for your reply, and congratulations on doing a fabulous job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 17:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is obviously censorship on the part of the mods -- happening more and more. Message them bit don't expect a change of mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 16:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are adorable. One question: how did you do both WW points and MFP? I tried that for awhile and it drove me crazy. Recently dropped WW and trying just MFP alone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police: Michigan GOP Official Fatally Shot Herself While Adjusting Bra Holster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 04:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 04:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a good analysis of what the threats against Rome actually mean: 
http://www.theatlantic.com/features/archive/2015/02/what-isis-really-wants/384980/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A perfect storm brews in the Middle East: Mistrust between the Obama administration and Benjamin Netanyahu has widened even further in recent days because of U.S. suspicion that the Israeli prime minister has authorized leaks of details about the U.S. nuclear talks with Iran. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 19:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Illinois Governor Acts to Curb Power of Public Sector Unions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 16:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 19:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Guess it's out with the pointless "healthy" ready meals and back in with elbow grease and proper food!"

Yeah, I come back to that conclusion every time I try the prepackaged stuff for awhile. I also tend to get less tired of the homemade dinners, even if I repeat them often, than I do with the frozen stuff, much of which tastes kind of the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 17:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it will turn out to be more complicated than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 17:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really interesting study -- thank you for posting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 16:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People in Montana aren't required to get malaria shots because unless they leave the country they don't get malaria. You include a quote saying that epidemiological studies show that Hep B can be transmitted in daycare. It can also be transmitted from pregnant women to their children, or from close contact in the home.

Hep B in its chronic stage can be symptom-free and can go undetected for decades. Has every parent and daycare worker been tested for it?The Hep B vaccine is safe. It gives immunity for 20-30 years and possibly for life. The consequences of getting the disease are extremely serious. Risk-benefit analysis would seem to indicate that the Hep B vaccinations are a reasonable solution to a threat to public health. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 04:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of the situations you mention is the same as needlessly spreading a very communicable disease to a vulnerable population such as infants or the immunocompromised. The line should actually be drawn not at smoking outside in my vicinity, or at coughing or having the flu, but at putting others at risk of catching an extremely contagious disease that can bring serious complications or even death to vulnerable individuals -- a disease that would be virtually nonexistent in this country if people would resume vaccination at the rate they vaccinated 15 years ago.

Vaccinations -- and the isolation of those with communicable illnesses -- are not a new idea. Ever hear of leper colonies? Modern medicine has come up with vaccinations, so isolation is not needed much anymore -- unless you refuse to partake, and in that case civil society has the right to protect its members from preventable risks. Here's an article about the legal history of compelling vaccinations in our country from the current online Atlantic:

http://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2015/02/cowpox-and-the-constitution/385245/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The vaccine delayers: They hate anti-vaxxers  but don't quite vaccinate on time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 01:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Schools Are Dealing With Anti-Vaccine Parents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 08:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 04:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny! That's just how I feel! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawmakers: Utah should be first, feds second in oath </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 04:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State Selling, Crucifying, Burying Children Alive in Iraq-U.N. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 04:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arizona Says Rape Victim Knew The Risks, Asks For Lawsuit To Be Thrown Out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 03:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Utah GOP Lawmakers Seek To Swear To State Ahead Of U.S. Constitution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 03:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 03:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The context is the current MMR vaccine, and the Disney outbreak. Measles is much more easily communicated than the other diseases you keep bringing into the discussion. In logic and debate, changing the terms of a discussion is known as a "red herring." People use it when they can't make a legitimate counter-argument on the actual subject under discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 05:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, the context of this discussion is the MMR vaccine. You keep trying to change the subject. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pat Robertson Rails Against Fluoride In Water And Vaccine Mandates (VIDEO) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 23:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 23:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kids -- and adults -- who are not vaccinated do constitute a public health risk, as the Disneyland case shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 23:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People with AIDS don't pose any danger to the public, and I don't think they are being referred to in the current debate about the MMR vaccine, are they? Although I suppose if they have an impaired immune system, they themselves are endangered by exposure to unvaccinated people -- all the more reason to worry about those unvaccinated people being in public places.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 19:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AIDS is much less easily communicable than measles. Who said anything about AIDS? Is there a vaccine for AIDS? Are you able to follow an argument? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 08:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @FlowCannon -- A parent's decision not to vaccinate impacts those in the community who cannot be vaccinated -- infants under one and people getting chemotherapy, for example. I'm okay with people having the freedom to not vaccinate, but then they will need to give up sharing public space with other people, whom they are putting at risk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 08:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @WowLucky -- A parent's decision not to vaccinate impacts those in the community who cannot be vaccinated -- infants under one and people getting chemotherapy, for example. I'm okay with people having the freedom to not vaccinate, but then they will need to give up sharing public space with other people, whom they are putting at risk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 08:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @planetofjunk -- A parent's decision not to vaccinate impacts those in the community who cannot be vaccinated -- infants under one and people getting chemotherapy, for example. I'm okay with people having the freedom to not vaccinate, but then they will need to give up sharing public space with other people, whom they are putting at risk.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 08:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But people should be required to have their children vaccinated if they want them to go to school, travel, or sit in the waiting room of a pediatrician's office with other children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 08:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the exact same thing, Eliot_2000. He isn't ignorant, he's an opportunistic, cynical liar who is indifferent to the harm caused by his pandering to the stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 08:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @Fuzzymuscles -- Infants under one year of age are too young to be vaccinated. People who have compromised immune systems, like those who are getting chemotherapy for cancer, can't get vaccinations either. 

These groups depend on "herd immunity," which is produced when a high percentage of the general public is vaccinated. If more than 95% of a community is vaccinated, the unvaccinated people are very unlikely to be exposed to the disease. 

So by having your kids vaccinated, you are protecting those in your community who can't be vaccinated -- the very young and the very sick. These are the two groups that would also get the most seriously ill if they got the disease, whether it's measles or whooping cough or whatever. Also, vaccinations are not 100% effective, so even a few vaccinated people can end up with the disease if they are exposed to it.

So those people who refuse to vaccinate their kids are not only putting their own kids' health at risk. They are also putting other people's kids (or older relatives with immune problems) at risk too. 

It's a public health issue.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Want To Vaccinate Your Kid? You Should Get Fined $5,000 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 06:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-Vaccine Doctor: I Don't Care If My Kids Make Others Gravely Sick (VIDEO) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 06:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Read Roald Dahl's Powerful Pro-Vaccination Letter (from 1988) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 08:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Trade Away Our Health </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 08:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most Republicans Say They Back Climate Action, Poll Finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 08:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dems Warn They Can't Counter The Koch Brothers' $1 Billion In 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 02:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 19:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very broad interpretation of what is off-topic. Speaker of the House invites foreign head of state to speak, cuts president out of the process. How is that not US politics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 18:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really hard to find a publication that has your take on the matter, eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wikipedia bans five editors from gender-related articles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 17:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 17:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly don't know. I put it out there because the banning of five female editors by an overwhelmingly male arbitration board seemed concerning to me. Please feel free to post opposing views of the situation.

There is an article in The Guardian that may be more even-handed. I'll post that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "20-Week Bans Are Devastating for Women Like Me" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 17:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can We Solve Our Child-Care Problem? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 01:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 21:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what is rehosted about this article, mr mod? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 21:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conservative mods got MJ banned awhile back. It has nothing to do with rehosted content, really, as you can see from the lack of links or attribution to any other original "host" of the story in the MJ piece -- the publication is just too liberal for the mods. Same with Salon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama's calls for government-run Internet service stoke GOP ire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 06:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joe Walsh Calls for More Terrorist Attacks on Journalists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 06:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 19:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it was a couple, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 19:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As you say, testing is a very personal decision. Congratulations on the birth of your son! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theyll come for The Daily Show next: Why satirists always threaten fundamentalists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 17:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Blame for the Charlie Hebdo Murders By George Packer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 08:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charlie Hebdo and the Right to Commit Blasphemy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 02:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cartoonists Pay Tribute to Charlie Hebdo Victims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 02:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photos: Paris Mourns Slain Charlie Hebdo Cartoonists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 02:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Newspapers and All Major American News Networks Decide Against Showing Charlie Hebdo's Muhammad Cartoons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 02:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservatives Know the Latest Obamacare Challenge Is WeakThat's Why They're Trying to Spin John Roberts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 09:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Md. Politician Kirby Delauter: Reporters Can't Use My Name Without Permission! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 18:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Md. Politician Kirby Delauter: Reporters Can't Use My Name Without Permission! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 18:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Obama Unbound effect  or Viva Obama? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 17:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When New York City Police Walk Off the Job </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 20:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police Respect Squandered in Attacks on de Blasio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 15:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP Congressman Cant Recall Whether He Spoke to White Supremacists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 04:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 07:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great job! Congrats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 07:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obamacare has brought health care costs down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Krugman: Tidings of Comfort </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 19:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
