<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1094</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The foreign volunteers fighting the Islamic State group </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 15:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Human body not designed for homosexuality, says Mexican Church </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Angry French tobacconists have dumped four tonnes of carrots outside the ruling Socialist partys headquarters in protest at plans to force the introduction of plain cigarette packets. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Ted Cruz is holding up a bipartisan bill whose defenders say must pass in order for America to gain more credibility on Internet issues. The reason? Politics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A university is in "exploratory discussions" to build the world's deepest swimming pool for spaceflight and human endurance research. The proposed 50m (164ft) deep pool at the University of Essex would be far deeper than NASA's own 12m (40ft) deep training pool in Houston. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 13:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astronomers witness assembly of galaxies in the early Universe for the first time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have unpicked how the skin of the Texas horned lizard funnels water towards its mouth - and copied the principles in a plastic version. This reptile can collect water from anywhere, including the sand it walks on; the fluid then travels to its mouth through channels between its scales. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 10:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nearly half of Australia's digital users illegally download movies, TV shows and music on a regular basis, a government survey has found. Illegal downloads would lessen if content was cheaper and available at the same time as in other countries. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists in China have developed a new method for connecting energy devices without using wires. Not only are the devices easy to make, they continue to work even when bent or twisted  a vital trait for flexible electronics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great Recession was good for the environment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://jmh.sagepub.com/content/early/2015/07/21/1557988315596224.full </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Men who become fathers experience weight gain and an increase in body mass index according to a new, large-scale study that tracked more than 10,000 men over a 20-year period. Men who didn't become dads actually lost weight over the same time period. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nineteen-Year-Old Takes on Intel in a Bid to Make Computers Less Power-Hungry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just one in three weddings in England and Wales has a religious ceremony </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some 7,000 tons of radioactive water at risk of leaking into the ground still has to be removed from underground tunnels and other locations at the Fukushima No. 1 nuclear plant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Zealand has refused a mans claim to become the first official refugee from climate change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 15:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> " ... its selective outrage  quick response on McCain and crickets on anything else  only enhances its image as a party that couldnt care less about anyone who isnt white, Southern, straight or male. If the GOPs goal is to never win the White House again, its off to a great start." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The remains of Jewish gas chamber victims subjected to Nazi anatomy experiments have been uncovered at a prestigious medical research facility in the eastern French city of Strasbourg. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The French-language Scrabble world championship has been won by a New Zealander who does not speak a word of French, competition organisers say. Mr Richards is reported to have learned the French dictionary and conjugations in nine weeks earlier this year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 11:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 10:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://press.endocrine.org/doi/abs/10.1210/JC.2015-2284 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have found that genes that control the biological clocks in cells throughout the body are altered after losing a single night of sleep, in a study that is to be published in the Journal of Clinical Endocrinology and Metabolism. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 10:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sexist men who abuse women on the internet are compensating for their own poor performance, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finland Shows Why Many Europeans Think Americans Are Wrong About the Euro </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Irregular sleeping patterns have been "unequivocally" shown to lead to cancer in tests on mice, a study suggests. The report, in Current Biology, lends weight to concerns about the damaging impact of shift work on health. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most Israeli Jews favour return of Gaza settlements: Some 51 percent of Israeli Jews said they were in favour of rebuilding the Gush Katif group of settlements, located in southern Gaza and where more than 8,000 Israelis lived prior to the 2005 withdrawal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A man has celebrated 30 years since his heart-lung transplant - thought to be the longest anyone has survived after the procedure. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Polansky: The moon landing inspired me to become an astronaut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theres yet another use for marijuana: It may help to heal broken bones: Researchers have found that cannabidiol  an element of marijuana that does not get people high  improved the healing process in rats with broken leg bones after eight weeks, according to a new study. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astronauts' skin gets thinner in space, scientists say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 15:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The one image that tells you everything you need to know about Bernie Sanders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 15:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese man builds fake police station in flat and poses as cop in elaborate con: In a money-making venture, a Wuhan man called himself inspector Lei, established a fake interrogation room and even had a siren for his car </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australian Feliks Zemdegs takes title at Rubik's Cube World Championship: The 19-year-old completed the traditional 3x3x3 Rubik's Cube with a staggering average of 7.56 seconds and best score of 5.695 seconds, narrowly missing the world record of 5.25 seconds held by American Collin Burns. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Despite scientific evidence to the contrary, a small group of otolaryngologists have repeatedly testified, on behalf of the tobacco industry, that heavy smoking did not cause the cancer in cases of dying patients suing for damages, according to a study by a Stanford University researcher. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 16:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 15:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://www.ajpmonline.org/article/S0749-3797%2815%2900146-4/abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A team of researchers has found an alarming rise in the lack of self awareness among children and teenagers in the United States. Specifically, way more overweight adolescents are oblivious today to the fact that they ought to lose weight than were in decades past </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 15:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The perceived trustworthiness of an inmates face may determine the severity of the sentence he receives, according to new research using photos and sentencing data for inmates in the state of Florida. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 15:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An international team of astronomers have used the European Space Agency's Gaia satellite to discover a unique binary system where one star is eating the other, but neither star has any hydrogen, the most common element in the Universe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 15:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "You might think that the recent poll showing Trump spiking among Republicans is about Trump. It is not. It is about the GOP and its very dark soul when it comes to immigration. The rank and file didnt much care for Trump as recently as May. It swooned this month when it discovered hes a bigot." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 15:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super-cheap origami disease-testing kit can be printed on demand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 14:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese 3-year-old with swollen head saved by first ever 3D-printed skull transplant surgery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 14:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A font that automatically censors NSA spook words as they are written </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 14:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker wants to drug test food stamp recipients. That shows why hell never be president. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 14:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK mass surveillance laws are unlawful, it's official: The High Court ruled today that sections 1 and 2 of Dripa are unlawful because they breach Articles 7 and 8 of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey is stepping up its role in the fight against Islamic State extremists after realising the threats to its own security from jihadists and responding to pressure from its Western partners, analysts say. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gose Is a Beer That Keeps Summer Cool: The wheat beer, an ancient German style that just five years ago was largely unknown in the United States, is tart, almost sour, like a lemonade. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 11:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The mysterious way your body changes with the weather: Does the damp cause arthritis? Can air pressure shifts bring a headache? Will the temperature influence a baby's sex? BBC's David Robson finds some surprising evidence for the folklore. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 10:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The chance of returning to a normal weight after becoming obese is only one in 210 for men and one in 124 for women over a year, research suggests. For severe obesity, shedding excess weight in a year is even more unlikely, a study of UK health records concluded. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 10:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4,000-year-old tablets found in Turkey include womens rights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greece debt crisis continues to expose European divisions: France and Germany may be managing Europe, but it is clear that they do not share an idea for its future. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arctic deal bans North Pole fishing: The US and Russia are among five countries to have signed a deal to prevent commercial fishing in the melting Arctic sea ice near the North Pole. Norway, Canada and Denmark also backed the agreement signed in Oslo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient owl vomit may show 'dramatic' human impact on ecosystem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taxing the calories in sugary drinks could encourage healthier choices, study says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How NASAs new map of Mars stacks up against some of the worlds all-time great maps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How NASAs new map of Mars stacks up against some of the worlds all-time great maps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Drunk' squirrel causes hundreds of pounds of damage: A 'drunk' squirrel turns beer taps on, opens bags of crisps and smashes glasses at a private members' club. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. fracking linked to higher hospitalization rates: People who live in areas near hydraulic fracturing are more likely to be hospitalized for heart conditions, neurological illnesses and cancer, according to researchers from the University of Pennsylvania and Columbia University. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oldest Dentistry Found in 14,000-Year-Old Tooth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vatican had more than a billion euros off books before financial clean-up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study, published in The Lancet, says higher levels of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere could be causing nutrient deficiencies around the world. The study predicts that by the year 2050 at least 138 million more people will be placed at risk of a zinc deficiency. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia plans fuel shipments to Syria from Crimea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have discovered a winged dinosaur - an ancestor of the velociraptor - that they say was on the cusp of becoming a bird. The 6ft 6in (2m) creature was almost perfectly preserved in limestone, thanks to a volcanic eruption that had buried it in north-east China. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transgender people in Ireland have won legal recognition of their status after a law was passed allowing them to change their legal gender with no medical or state intervention. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a bunch of government space geeks at NASA won the internet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theres a new super PAC for Bernie Sanders. It wants billionaire donors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spanish town makes the siesta compulsary by law: A Valencian town is living up to the Spanish stereotype by bringing in a law that ensures each citizen has the right to enjoy an afternoon kip. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Groups backed by secret donors take the lead in shaping 2016 elections "These tax-exempt groups  which can keep their donors secret even as they sponsor hard-hitting ads  are being increasingly embraced by campaign operatives looking for new ways to influence the political environment." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft has launched a free online tool to help try and prevent the spread of child sexual abuse images. PhotoDNA is a free cloud-based service that can be used to hunt down and remove these photos from the web. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The EU has warned of increased tensions amid claims that Russia has redrawn a section of Georgia's de facto border with South Ossetia. Georgia says Russian troops installed signs marking the "state border" of the breakaway region of South Ossetia further inside Georgian territory. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists in India have developed a low-fat version of ghee that cuts the cholesterol content by 85 percent in a move that could give a much-needed boost to fitness levels, a senior researcher said Thursday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks Cables Show a Saudi Obsession With Iran: A trove of documents reveals how the Saudi governments goal was not just to spread its strict version of Sunni Islam but also to undermine its primary adversary. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Allegations against Assange may be written off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schaeuble Shrugs Off Greek Vote Saying Euro Exit Is Best: German Finance Minister Wolfgang Schaeuble told Greece the only way itll get a debt reduction is to leave the euro and cast doubt on the countrys ability to even complete negotiations on a third bailout. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 11:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rich countries rejected an international plan to let the UN help fight tax evasion: Transparency advocates tell Quartz that the US was particularly responsible for blocking the provision; Treasury Department officials in Washington and with the delegation did not respond to requests for comment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 10:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A young woman who died hours after being admitted to an Ebola treatment unit on Sunday became the second Ebola fatality since Liberia was declared free of the virus on May 9, government officials said on Wednesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 10:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The lower house of Japan's parliament has approved two controversial bills that change the country's security laws, despite protests in Tokyo. The changes would allow Japanese troops to fight overseas for the first time since World War Two. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 09:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists in China have built a thin film that retains its antifogging properties even under an antireflective coating. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jupiter Twin Discovered Around Solar Twin: An international group of astronomers has used the ESO 3.6-metre telescope to identify a planet just like Jupiter orbiting at the same distance from a Sun-like star, HIP 11915. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than 50 child soldiers recruited by the IS group in Syria have been killed since the beginning of this year. The Syrian Observatory for Human Rights said it had documented the deaths of 52 child soldiers, all under the age of 16, who had been part of IS's "Cubs of the Caliphate" program. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Preliminary study says medical marijuana could literally save lives: a new NBER working paper found that access to state-sanctioned medical marijuana dispensaries is linked to a significant decrease in both prescription painkiller abuse, and in overdose deaths from prescription painkillers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weedkiller suspected of causing cancer deemed 'safe': A best-selling herbicide that the World Health Organisation suspects causes cancer could get a new lease of life in Europe after being deemed safe by a key assessment based largely on classified industry reports. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Chinese court ordered a mugger's intended victim to pay his attacker 70,000 yuan ($11,000) after he fought off the attempted robbery and beat him up, state-run media reported Wednesday. The court sentenced the mugging target, identified only as Yuan, to three months' probation along with the fine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey has put a travel ban to Turkey on 15,000 suspected foreign fighters heading to Syria and Iraq, Foreign Ministry spokesperson Tanju Bilgi said on July 15, as Ankara ramps up measures to counter the Islamic State of Iraq and the Levant (ISIL) threat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans knee-jerk hatred of the Iran deal "This is legislating by reflex  a mass knee-jerk by the Republican majority in Congress. Those who howled 'read the bill' during the health-care debate couldnt be bothered to read the nuclear agreement before sounding off." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey fails to prosecute two Chechens for beheading three priests in Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chimaera device paves way for wireless pain relief: A prototype surgical tool that combines preoperative CT data with state-of-the-art sensing technology could put the ability to carry out complex operations in the hands of many more doctors, according to its developers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research says human impact on the oceans is growing  and climate change is the biggest culprit: Within the two-thirds of the ocean experiencing an increase in stress, the researchers found that 5% of the worlds oceans are heavily harmed by human activity and likely require immediate attention. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 12:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United States handed back to Iraq on Wednesday antiquities it said it had seized in a raid on Islamic State fighters in Syria, saying the haul was proof the militants were funding their war by smuggling ancient treasures. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 12:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tiny beating human heart made from scratch: By recreating the physical forces that developing cells experience, stem cells have been coaxed into forming microscopic beating hearts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 10:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Humans have more primitive hands than chimpanzees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 17:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Smart capsule' is potential new drug-delivery vehicle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 17:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Belgian government is working on new legislation concerning the composition of mayonnaise, one of the most popular Belgian toppings on dishes and part of the classic Belgian dish chips with mayonnaise. The present law that goes back to 1955 is obsolete, manufacturers claim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 17:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 17:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0028390815002178 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Challenging the idea that addiction is hardwired in the brain, a new UC Berkeley study of mice suggests that even a short time spent in a stimulating learning environment can rewire the brains reward system and buffer it against drug dependence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 17:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heres how data caps really affect your Internet use, according to data: It turns out that data caps are incredibly effective at getting people to use less data, and not merely on cellphone plans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The plant that can kill and cure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google accidentally reveals data on 'right to be forgotten' requests: Data shows 95% of Google privacy requests are from citizens out to protect personal and private information  not criminals, politicians and public figures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google accidentally reveals data on 'right to be forgotten' requests: Data shows 95% of Google privacy requests are from citizens out to protect personal and private information  not criminals, politicians and public figures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Like Sitting, Standing in the Workplace May Have Long-Term Health Consequences </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey blocks pro-ISIS websites in crackdown on recruitment networks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Outrage as 11 Sudanese women face 40 lashes for wearing trousers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Billboards advertising services such as hotels, restaurants and service stations will no longer be allowed at the entrance of French towns and villages of under 10,000 residents, as a law voted in 2010 came into effect on Monday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia puts its law above European court rulings: Russia can avoid implementing European court judgments if they conflict with the Russian constitution, a top Russian court has ruled. Russia is legally bound by the European Convention on Human Rights. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Jeb Bush told the New Hampshire Union Leader that 'people need to work longer hours and, through their productivity, gain more income for their families.' Simple as that, beleaguered American middle-class proles. Youre slacking. The echo of Romneys infamous '47 percent' remark was unmistakable." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The goal to get HIV treatment to 15 million people by the end of 2015 has already been met. The landmark figure was reached in March - nine months ahead of schedule. It follows decades of global efforts and investment to get antiretroviral drugs to those in need. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 12:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 11:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the research paper: http://arxiv.org/pdf/1507.03414v1.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two fossilized teeth of what could be the largest carnivorous dinosaur that ever existed in Japan have been found in a geological layer some 81 million years old in Nagasaki, the city and a Fukui prefectural museum said Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 10:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists at the Large Hadron Collider have announced the discovery of a new particle called the pentaquark. It was first predicted to exist in the 1960s but, much like the Higgs boson particle before it, the pentaquark eluded science for decades until its detection at the LHC. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 10:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate change risks should be assessed in the same way as threats to national security or public health according to a new report. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 10:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have achieved the total synthesis of a scarce natural marine product that may become a powerful cancer-fighting agent  the molecule shishijimicin A. Lab tests more than a decade ago proved it to be more than 1,000 times as toxic to cancer cells as the anticancer drug taxol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 18:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Solar Powered Family Car Generates More Energy Than It Uses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 17:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comcast is charging $300 for its answer to Google Fiber a month: That's $100 less than the price Comcast currently offers for its top Internet speeds  and nearly four times as fast. Compared to Google Fiber, it's twice as fast and $170 more expensive per month. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 17:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The number of anti-Semitic attacks recorded in France during the first quarter of 2015 increased by 84 percent over the corresponding period last year, a watchdog group said. The worst of the attacks this year occurred on Jan. 9, when an Islamist killed four Jewish shoppers at a kosher supermarket. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 17:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis acknowledged on Monday he had neglected problems of the middle class and said he was willing to have a dialogue with Americans who disagree with his criticism of capitalism. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 16:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New evidence has been gathered to back up claims a UFO landed near a US airbase in Suffolk, a former deputy commander has claimed. Col Charles Halt told the BBC he saw unidentified objects at Rendlesham Forest in December 1980. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "In thrall to part of their base, GOP lawmakers have thrown in their lot with an overwhelmingly white, aging constituency, beyond which they see no future. The United States, ever more diverse, is changing fast; House Republicans, fearful of that change, prefer scapegoats to solutions." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The supernova world has a new brightness champ. A supernova discovered on 14 June appears to shine more than 400 billion times brighter than the sun would if they sat next to each other. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian President Vladimir Putin said on Friday Greece had not asked Russia for aid to overcome its debt problems and that he hoped the crisis would be resolved soon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A crucifix sculpted in the shape of a hammer and sickle presented to Pope Francis in Bolivia has caused a stir among Catholic commentators. But while some reports said the Pope was taken aback by the present, the Vatican has played down any row. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German authorities are moving toward officially recognizing as a genocide the colonial-era crackdown in Namibia by German troops more than a century ago in which more than 65,000 ethnic Hereros were killed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tunisian authorities on Friday were investigating the disappearance of 33 residents from the same town after families reported they had left overnight to join Islamic State militants in Libya, locals said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A large, meat-eating pitcher plant in Borneo has evolved a unique way to communicate with bats that it hopes to attract. The plant, Nepenthes hemsleyana, communicates via special structures that reflect the bats' ultrasonic calls right back to the flying mammals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 14:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In IS-ruled Raqqa, new class divide creates tensions with local Syrians: 'Muhajireen' foreigners 'live like princes' while locals in Raqqa complain of harassment and being treated like second-class citizens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 14:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Sanders might just become some GOP-leaning voters' favorite 2016 Democrat -- and not just because he's giving Hillary Clinton a tough time. It's not hard to see some of his positions appealing to more libertarian voters like former Ron Paul fans who prefer Sanders over Rand Paul." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 14:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Infrared light speeds up healing by turbocharging our cells: The properties of water are altered by near-infrared light, which could drive the energy-producing mitochondria in our cells to work harder and heal us faster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 14:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 12:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry! My bad! Totally missed it while checking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Ecstasy, Aspirin, and LSD Look Under the Microscope </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 12:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Naps May Improve Our Frustration Tolerance: A short nap could reduce impulsive behavior and improve the ability to withstand frustration, a small study suggests. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 12:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Petro Poroshenko said on Friday the threat of terrorism had "significantly risen" in Ukraine, describing the country as awash with weapons trafficked from the east where a shaky ceasefire has eased fighting against pro-Russian rebels. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 10:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have discovered that living near trees is good for your health "they found that 'having 10 more trees in a city block, on average, improves health perception in ways comparable to an increase in annual personal income of $10,000 or being 7 years younger.'" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 10:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surge of Ebola in Liberia May Be Linked to a Survivor: The conclusion was made by scientists who analyzed the genetic sequence of the virus from the body of a Liberian boy who died of Ebola last week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 09:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study suggests that smoking tobacco is associated with an increased risk of developing psychosis (particularly schizophrenia). People who suffer from psychosis are 3 times more likely to smoke cigarettes than healthy controls, according to the meta-analysis published today in Lancet Psychiatry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 09:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Study: Heat is Being Stored Beneath the Ocean Surface </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 09:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nobel medal to be auctioned to help train scientists: The proceeds are to be used by The Sir Hans Krebs Trust for its work "to provide grants for the support of refugee scientists and the training of young scientists in the biomedical sciences," Sotheby's auction house said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 18:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Law Would Let China Cut Off Internet During Emergencies: Chinese authorities have periodically deployed such measures during unrest in Uighur and Tibetan ethnic-minority areas in Chinas west. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 18:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Denmark: Bronze Age gold spirals unearthed in field </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 18:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2015/150702/ncomms8501/full/ncomms8501.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super graphene can help treat cancer: researchers have found a graphene coating that will help boost the effect of chemotherapy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists Demonstrate Animal Mind-Melds: New studies say rats and monkeys whose brains are linked by electrodes can coordinate their brains to carry out tasks, often better than individuals do. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 16:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0131809 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A lack of education could be just as dangerous as smoking, study: the study calculated the health risks of low educational attainment in the U.S. and found that more than 145,000 deaths could have been prevented in 2010 if adults who did not finish high school had earned a GED or high school diploma </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 16:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huge New Survey to Shine Light on Dark Matter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 16:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using gene therapy, researchers have restored hearing in mice with a genetic form of deafness. Their work, published online July 8 by the journal Science Translational Medicine, could pave the way for gene therapy in people with hearing loss caused by genetic mutations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 15:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The Federal Election Commission, deadlocked between its Democratic and Republican members, has essentially stopped enforcing campaign finance laws. The Internal Revenue Service has also all but given up enforcing the laws that govern tax-exempt nonprofits and their political activities." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 15:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A species of blindsnake has been observed decapitating termites, then feeding on the thorax and abdomen before discarding the heads. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 15:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Applying mild electrical stimulation to an area of the brain associated with cognitive control helps people with schizophrenia to recognize errors and adjust their behavior to avoid them as much as it helps healthy subjects do so, according to a new study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 14:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Project Fi review: The most remarkable feature of Googles new cell service: With Project Fi, Google has developed what for most city-dwellers will be a cost-effective and reliable alternative to traditional cell service providers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 14:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sharks Discovered Inside Underwater Volcano </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 14:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The rise and fall of Quaaludes: Quaalude was popular in the US in the 1970s. Now, the drug is back in the headlines after the revelation that comedian Bill Cosby admitted getting them to give to women he wanted to have sex with. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 14:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The worlds fossil fuel companies risk wasting billions of dollars of investment by not taking global action to fight climate change seriously, according to the chief economist of the International Energy Agency (IEA). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 14:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To avoid a government shutdown in the fall, Congress needs to act now "for many in the GOP, the temptation to repeat the past is irresistible. With control of both houses of Congress, they hope the House and Senate can agree on a budget and either force it on Obama or blame him for a shutdown." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 14:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkish protesters have attacked the Thai consulate in Istanbul following the deportation from Thailand of about 100 Uighurs to China. No injuries were reported. Rights groups have criticised such deportations, saying Uighurs face persecution in China. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 12:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rare genetic mutations occur more often in schizophrenia patients, UCLA researchers find </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 11:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Global warming skeptics cite personal weather observations as the key reason for their views </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 11:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People using anabolic steroids to improve muscle growth and sporting performance are far more likely to experience issues with their memory, according to new research from Northumbria University. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia vetoes move at UN Security Council to describe 1995 Srebrenica massacre of Bosnians as a "genocide" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 16:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet the NASA astronaut who is still excited to fly after 3 rockets exploded </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 16:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> According to a new study with rats, that high-fat indulgence literally changes the populations of bacteria residing inside the gut and also alters the signaling to the brain. The result? The brain no longer senses signals for fullness, which can cause overeating--a leading cause of obesity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 16:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study has examined the comments on climate science-denying blogs and found strong evidence of widespread conspiratorial thinking. The study looks at the comments made in response to a previous paper linking science denial and conspiracy theories. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 15:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 15:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://jrs.sagepub.com/content/early/2015/06/01/0141076815593403.abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study finds tests conducted in the 1960s and '70s in Sweden that showed that mammograms could reduce breast cancer mortality by an amazing 20 to 25 percent is flawed and that the reduction in deaths is actually closer to 10 percent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 15:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some 240 people, mainly Christians, have been brought out of Syria's second city of Aleppo and taken to Belgium, the government in Brussels says. The operation took place over two months and amid great secrecy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 14:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This man risks his life every day to rescue kidnapped women from Islamic State </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 14:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sarkozy signs petition to protect empty churches from conversion to mosques </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 14:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps false comments connecting Mexican immigrants and crime: Four Pinocchios </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 14:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 14:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi lucastars - 

I was recently told by your co-mods that that title format was ok. What do you suggest the title to be?

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tunisia has announced plans to build a wall along its border with Libya to counter the threat from jihadist militants. It would stretch 160km (100 miles) inland from the coast, and be completed by the end of 2015, Tunisian Prime Minister Habib Essid told state TV. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 14:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps false comments connecting Mexican immigrants and crime: He earns Four Pinocchios </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 14:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside the Highly Organized and Flexible Fighting Force of ISIS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A bill which will allow Chileans to grow small amounts of marijuana for medical, recreational or spiritual use has been approved by the country's lower house of Congress. The measure will allow each Chilean home to grow up to six plants. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 07:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Belgian town 'opts out' of EU-US trade treaty (TTIP): To make sure the people who live there are aware of the motion's defiant content, it sent out a press release titled St. Gilles - Zone outside the TTIP market!. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bonobos use a range of tools like stone-age humans: The chimps' randy relatives have been seen using tools as shovels and levers in captivity, and even fashioning a spear to jab at a researcher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Japanese research team has found 24 geoglyphs on Perus Nazca Plateau that are believed to be older than the famous hummingbird and monkey geoglyphs at the UNESCO World Heritage site. The geoglyphs are believed to date back to 400 B.C. to 200 B.C. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian police on Tuesday launched a campaign urging people to take safer selfies after around 100 were injured and dozens died this year in gruesome accidents while striking high-risk poses. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Consumer group wants government to make Google give Americans the right to be forgotten online: Consumer Watchdog argues that withholding that ability from U.S. Internet users is unfair and deceptive -- two types of business practices the FTC is charged with protecting consumers against. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have developed a new design for a cloaking device that overcomes some of the limitations of existing "invisibility cloaks." The tech behind this cloak will have more applications than invisibility, such as concentrating solar energy and increasing signal speed in optical communications. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 16:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic Battalions, Stocked With Chechens, Aid Ukraine in War With Rebels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 15:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French special forces have killed a militant Islamist in Mali who was said to have been freed in exchange for the release of French Serge Lazarevic. Ali Ag Wadossene, a senior member of al-Qaeda in the Islamic Maghreb, was killed in northern Kidal city, a French army statement said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 14:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gallup polling shortly before the holiday weekend showed more Americans leaned toward the Democratic Party than the Republican Party in the second quarter of the year. That's a shift from the end of last year, when more people identified with the Republicans ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 14:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [All Spoilers] After unveiling a special edition of Game of Thrones Monopoly earlier this year, HBO is now coming out with a new board game tied to the hit show: Risk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 14:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie closes the enthusiasm gap over Hillary on Twitter: Hillary Clinton may be the focus of the mainstream media, but Bernie Sanders has closed the enthusiasm gap on Twitter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 14:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The new left-wing council in the Spanish capital Madrid has said it plans to remove all names relating to Gen Francisco Franco's dictatorship in streets and squares. Some 167 streets are still named after regime figures. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 13:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study of first-time smartphone users reveals devices may be detrimental to learning process </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 13:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hundreds of lawyers have registered to defend two women who went on trial in Morocco on Monday accused of "gross indecency" for wearing dresses considered provocative, an activist said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 11:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manoeuvring the colourful tiles of Tetris can help block flashbacks of traumatic events, even after the memory has fixed itself in your mind. Playing the game could be an easy way to reduce the risk of post-traumatic stress disorder. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 19:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having children later makes parents happy: A study shows that delaying family formation is associated with higher satisfaction levels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 19:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Removing 'elixir of age' could stop memory loss: Blocking a protein that builds up with age has been shown to aid memory and help mouse brains remain young. If true in humans, a drug could halt memory loss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 18:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astronomers use cosmic gravity to create a black-hole-scope </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 18:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research suggests driverless robocabs could be good for the planet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 18:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are the Greeks celebrating, ask baffled Germans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 17:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pushing for 4 percent economic growth, Jeb Bush faults Obamas zombie economy "But Bush still hasn't laid out an economic growth plan, despite months of suggestions by him and his aides that he will do so. On Monday, aides wouldn't say when a more specific plan might be forthcoming." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 16:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A group of Evangelical Christians in Brazil have launched a social network where swearing and erotic content in any form is completely banned. There are 600 words which are forbidden on the site and an "Amen" button for expressing appreciation for a post. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 16:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The majority of children living in areas of Gaza hardest-hit during last year's conflict are showing signs of severe emotional distress and trauma, including frequent bed wetting and nightmares, a global children's charity said on Monday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 15:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One Man's Desperate Quest to Cure His Son's EpilepsyWith Weed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 13:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German conservatives are destroying Europe with austerity, says economist Thomas Piketty I am much more afraid that the conservatives, especially in Germany, are about to destroy Europe and the European idea, all because of their appalling failure to remember history. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 11:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former French president Nicolas Sarkozy pressured the countrys football federation to vote in favour of awarding the 2022 World Cup to Qatar, FIFA president Sepp Blatter said in an interview with a German newspaper Sunday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 13:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The tragedy giving hope to Syria's women </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 12:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkish nationalists protesting China's treatment of ethnic Uighur Muslims attacked a group of Korean tourists in the heart of Istanbul's old city on Saturday, mistaking them for Chinese nationals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 22:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Champagne granted world heritage status by Unesco: Unesco decided that the vineyards, wine cellars and sales houses where champagne is produced and sold were culturally significant. It was one of 11 sites given World Heritage status by Unesco at a meeting in Germany on Saturday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 21:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Panama too drops out of Trumps Miss Universe pageant: They say the move is a message of solidarity to Mexicans offended by Trumps recent description of Mexican migrants as rapists and as people who bring drugs and crime to the United States. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 21:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sturgeon kills five-year-old girl boating with family in Florida: The fish leaped into the boat  and the girls mother and nine-year-old brother were also injured but their condition was not known </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 21:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany says it wont leave Greece in the lurch: German finance minister, Wolfgang Schuble, appears to back No vote in last-minute intervention on Saturday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 20:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ISIS video shows mass execution in ruins of Syria's Palmyra </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 19:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United States of Beer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 18:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weve finally hit the breaking point for the original Internet: It's finally happened. The North American organization responsible for handing out new IP addresses says its banks have run dry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 16:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
