<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8834</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cast Iron Pizza From Scratch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 19:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Attempt at Cast Iron Pizza </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 19:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 17:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize that is ridiculously fast, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 00:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many people trying to tear down other people's explanations in this thread. The title wasn't, "Tell Us What Makes You Believe God Is Real and Atheists Will Come in and Call You an Ass For It." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 10:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't stop the signal Mal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 04:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude threw an elbow at him, but we can just keep calling Delly dirty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 04:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JR with a smart foul this time?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the Best Way to Fix Paint Chips </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 21:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just noticed a few scratches/chips on my car and was wondering what the best way to fix them would be. I know there is touch up paint available at most stores, but is it better to have them taken care of by my dealership? This is a 2015 black Mustang.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would anyone downvote you for this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Cavs - Bulls
* Cavs - Pistons
* Cavs - Wizards
* Cavs - Celtics
* Cavs - Heat (once upon a time)


Can't say I'd agree with you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Playoffs: Scouting Hawks-Cavs" Anyone with ESPN Insider Access? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 23:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://espn.go.com/nba/playoffs/2015/insider/story/_/id/12906521/2015-nba-playoffs-atlanta-hawks-versus-cleveland-cavaliers-preview </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 15:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know him personally? Or are you basing this off a drunken rant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cavaliers reportedly have 'legitimate fear' that Kevin Love leaves as free agent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 21:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 23:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After watching both videos, you can pretty much tell that he has nowhere near the same speed that he did previously. Definitely past his prime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 17:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every account on reddit is a bot except you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 01:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You play on Gangrene? I do too. What area are you based in? I almost never see people grouping on this server.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 21:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not unplayable. I had a ton of fun playing with a friend last night. Sorry that you don't feel as though you can participate in alpha access anymore :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 20:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With MW2, your account was not tied to the "physical copy" you purchased. You could just make another account, which was what most people did. Also, on PC this was mostly because of the internal issues that were going on over at IW.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 19:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This right here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 19:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the best time ever playing last night as well. First time venturing into PvP. Don't let the haters get to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 16:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think he can have Steelheart's powers, due to the fact that he almost died to Obliteration multiple times towards the end of the book. Maybe I read it wrong though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 15:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that people don't like Sera does not mean she isn't a very well written character. I enjoy that there are characters that I outright do not like in my games. It makes it that much more realistic to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 19:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man. Appreciate the info!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 16:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> link to said discount? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 23:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came for the picture, stayed for the gifs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HELP] "Changing equipment is disabled at this time" after Wicked Eyes and Wicked Hearts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 00:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After finishing the mission I found out that I was unable to change any party members out of their formal attire from the ball. The problem is, all my auto-saves are from AFTER the mission and every single one I load has the same problem. If I go back to an earlier save, I will have to replay a large segment of the game. Can anyone help with this? I have not been able to find any information from EA/Bioware in regards to this problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 00:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Nope . I Hate trick and i Have a feeling that only kids and unitelligent people love him

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 16:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too gimmicky in my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 22:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dredd. Karl Urban can make even Doom watchable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 03:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man...you are a great person. That first picture definitely pulled on my heart strings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 03:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pheasant Run is better in almost every way, and it's just right down the road. I'd look there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 22:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes...the Call of Duty community at its finest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 13:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is this from </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 16:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which tweet was that? Sorry, I'm not big on the twitter scene.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 02:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Police </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 22:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lost my license for 6 months, so basically every day I get home from work I play league for about 4-5 hours now. Went from silver to plat in that time and on my way to diamond.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 20:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, Destiny is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 00:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My last relationship </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could Josh Gordon Reports Be Wrong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 23:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 17:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YAY!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 06:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 20:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 590 is so close the difference is negligible. Also, the film will easily surpass that number with DVD/Blu-Ray/Digital sales.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 20:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have a right to criticize, as well as to speak with your wallet. However, to call a company terrible in many ways without any justification or examples is just childish and entitled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 18:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't disagree more. People tend to act entitled as if Riot owes them something, when in reality they are providing a service that is free that you have no obligation to invest any of your money into.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 20:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yolo Queue is the heart of the game. LCS, and E-Sports in general is the advertising budget.

I could not agree more with this statement right here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 20:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did anyone else think Resident Evil when he first opened up the mansion doors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 01:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 18:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct me if I am wrong, but if they included the .gifs for the animations (when available) in the client install, how would this affect load times at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 04:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comments are filled with armchair therapists. Be warned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 04:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are some champs that I will not play strictly due to lore. 

ex. Darius, because Garen is my nigga.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 04:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant Text: 

 "So as anyone who has watched the Vi champ spotlight may know, Vi was originally intended to be a top laner.

 She's got a lot of cool gameplay in top lane with the Q charge up and E cleave but, honestly, she's just too fair up there for too long compared to our current crop of top laners. In the early game she has meaningful mana costs, telegraphed attacks, and massive cooldown windows for her passive and all of her spells (P - 18, Q - 18, E - 14 per charge, R- 150). I actually think top lane Vi could be a pretty awesome experience for both sides of the lane if we did stuff like lower her CD's or buff E's range and mana cost but then jungle Vi would go to crazy town. Could nerf jungle Vi to compensate but then are we screwing over the many Vi mains who prefer her out-of-lane experience? It's a tough call. 
All this said, SmashGizmo got diamond last season almost exclusively with top lane Vi. He'd typically play conservative until 6 focusing only on CS and rush an Iceborn Gauntlet for the extended dueling power and mana to offset her high costs. Turns out if a Vi manages to stay even until 6 there is not a single character up there (not even Irelia or Jax) who can beat her in a straight up 1v1. Her burst and sustained damage output is insane when she gets the chance to use it and her late game with top lane items is monstrous for the enemy teams' squishies (or at least it was in season 3, a lot has changed since then)." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vi Top Becoming Viable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 04:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
