<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9876</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> See the Amazingly Detailed Build of this Pint-Sized Barrel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If not making new designs, I'm imagining new designs for the next project. If not that, I'm reading books about designs for ideas. Pretty boring huh. And I am not helping you out, am I? I think I have more serious problem here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maximize Your Outdoor Space With A Pallet Coffee Table On Wheels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> jun aoki evokes a cascading waterfall with lavenue shanghai in china </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read once that war persists to exist because some powerhouse from rich countries are manipulating poorer nations to go to war for their own financial gains. Who do you think can produce those high powered guns and fighting tanks? War is an expensive conflict that oppressed the poor and benefits the rich.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 14:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally envy this dude for the friends that he has. I can't even have one due to busy schedule.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Florida parents try to ban children's books set in Iraq and Afghanistan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you there, mate. Never believe everything you read on the internet. It is a very dangerous world especially for the young guns.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever happened to the international laws against child trafficking and child labor? Where are the authorities responsible for these issues and what are they doing? And if I may say, it doesn't only happen in Asia. It happens in Europe, too. Let us not be partial here and condemn only the poorer countries. That's one reason why richer countries can get away with their crimes because many of us turn a blind eye when it comes to bigger countries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abandoned lots in Chicago will soon be a home for shipping containers repurposed to offer permanent shelter to homeless people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a lazy and impatient eater like me, this won't do. But I admit that he has some skills there developed through years of practice for sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 18:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always the view. It's my favorite part working in a construction company. You always get to have a chance to enjoy what other people can't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 15 Amazing Ideas to Display Your Indoor Plants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Article] How To Use Regret To Fuel Your Dreams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that guest book will surely land in a special place of the said hotel. Say a museum. That is, if some unknowing staff will not throw it away in the basement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SimplePrints Launches Photo Magic, A Photo Book Publishing Service That Works Over SMS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
