<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1642</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna be honest and say that I don't really believe in ghosts, but  it'd be pretty awesome if something changed my mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep that's the site I've been looking at lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me and my friends were considering exploring some haunted spots in the Columbus OH area... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 15:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would anyone be interested in YouTube videos, stories, photos, or anything like that? There's quite a few of them around here, and I'm thinking of making something of a series about it. Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 14:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did email them, they've just ignored it so far lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know how many hammer of God box mods were made? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 23:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got number 114, I was just curious about how many were actually produced lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 15:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like you're referring to his head... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No job, no juice! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 11:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I've been without a job for a bit now, and I can't justify spending money on things I don't need. I've got money for bills and such, but my home is definitely more important than vaping lol. Calling on the kindness of a stranger to help me out of a tight spot. Anything you might be giving I'm taking! Thanks for reading (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Are tattoos at home really that bad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 09:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to start off by saying I'll only get tattoos professionally, but are scratchers really that bad? I don't mean your tape player engine with a guitar string, I mean a legitimate artist with a legitimate gun, but between jobs or something like that. It just seems like most people take a stance where it isn't okay no matter what. What kind of problems do people typically run into in these situations?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 09:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't downvote him guys, he just ran out of bombies. We've all been there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 09:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol do you even vape? Those cloudz are weeaakk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 21:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can try God Damnit!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 21:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I picked it up for 65 in Lancaster Ohio at upright vapor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 14:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dual parallel royal wire 20g 7 wrap lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upgraded from my Buddha to a centurion. Love it! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 10:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 09:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of a certain game I just lost... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Panera bread! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 13:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, I was homeless for a long time, and I know how hard it can be. I've been meaning to pass this knowledge on to people who can use it, so here it is. Panera bread! Most panera bread's donate to local food shelters, but significantly more often than you might think the shelters don't show up to take it. They wrap everything in two or three layers of plastic before they throw it out. They throw everything out at about 10 to 11pm from the previous day, so it's still fairly fresh. Panera pretty much kept me alive for a long time, so I'm hoping it can help someone else. Thanks for reading! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I've kinda got a general idea of a nerf herder in my mind. Please forgive me for being so prejudice :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 10:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 10:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leave it to a scruffy nerf herder to judge your hygiene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSbattle: this chick laughing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 18:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should've expected Jorge to be involved... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 10:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So long, thanks for all the- fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 12:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/nottheonion  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 12:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These remind me of these "pocket pets" a co worker of mine made. link to the fb page for those who are interested: https://www.facebook.com/pages/Pocket-Pets/616869738409460?fref=ts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 11:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speed camera vans **hate** this one easy trick! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 11:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The streets are getting ***ruff*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 08:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every Zelda game ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 11:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 50 hours in
"This park is really neat and tidy" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 06:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Local fence takin' out the trash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 21:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i Mean, would the horse sized duck still have hollow bones? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
