<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9584</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 23:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Takenoko Collector's Edition](https://cf.geekdo-images.com/images/pic1813947_md.jpg) is a giant version of Takenoko and can be yours for the low low price of [$299](http://www.coolstuffinc.com/p/193447) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can get it to the table a lot and you have the right group for it, **Sheriff of Nottingham** is a lot of fun and great value. But you *need* the right group for this. It's very dependent on people willing to play loose, get into the theme etc. It falls very flat if you don't.


For pure gaming, absolutely get **Castles of Burgundy**. It scales magnificently from 2-4, has tons of replay value and is loads of fun. Has some luck with the dice rolls but you can mitigate that with knowledge tiles and worker guys. I love the tactical feel at 2P of blocking your opponent and the more strategic feel at 4P of focusing/maximizing your own strategy first and foremost. All time classic. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Reddit, what song just puts a smile on your face and makes you happy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts on The Luminaries? Just started it and am struggling badly to get into it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every sentence just seems so drawn out   unnecessarily convoluted; like it was written to appear as lofty as possible. I read my fair share of literary fiction, but this is a pain to get through and I feel like it greatly distracts from the narrative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be your friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [My comment reply above](https://www.reddit.com/r/boardgames/comments/3e28tk/can_you_convince_me_to_buy_your_favourite_board/ctaxfsk).

Also, I paid $25 for the expansion. It's $35 now n Amazon. That's not ridiculous at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably somewhere in the middle. Owner Covering His Ass vs. Anonymous Internet People Comments...either side has plenty of reasons to be dubious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the owner's statement. She was kicked out, not for being in the women's bathroom, but for being in the bathroom with another occupant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't have said it better myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a must buy. The new races are unique and totally offer a new experience for the game. You can play with just them, you can mix it up with the base races, play on either board. But the way the new races play just offers such a new experience. I think they're so brilliantly put together. If you like TM, even if it only gets to the table a couple times a year, it's a must-have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 15:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't buy **Terra Mystica** (and the Fire   Ice Expansion) I will punch you right in the mouth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 05:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. God forbid there's an attractive female anywhere near you while attempting to order a drink. You will wait. Forever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 23:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I'm just going to flat out disagree with any list that has Ascension anywhere near a top anything list. Especially if it's a deck-builder list without Eminent Domain or Core Worlds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 22:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to make a pun with silver or Ag. I can't think of anything. So, vAgina.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that was a question about board games to play in the car. OP here specifically said "Not boardgames" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where else would you ask about not board games? [AskReddit Seems to Have Been a Good Place for This](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/2mveq3/whats_a_good_game_to_play_on_the_road_that_isnt_i/). 


Also lots of other threads shown [here](https://www.google.com/webhp?sourceid=chrome-instant ion=1 espv=2 ie=UTF-8#q=games%20to%20play%20in%20car%20site%3Areddit.com safe=active) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to clarify, did you come to /r/boardgames to specifically not talk about board games?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 18:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dr. Ramsey? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 05:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then don't watch it. How is this that hard?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 23:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dodge Grand Cairavanditioner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 23:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link staying blue. Blue like the color of the crease his skate was in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Link](http://www.coolstuffinc.com/p/208629) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blaine is a pain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. If you want to climb up your grammar and English language pedestal, learn how to spell and use proper grammar. 

2. You are correct, being an asshole and reading have nothing to do with each other. However, as I initially said, it's fairly obvious what OP was trying to say, without going out of your way to be a dick and take the sentence as literally as possible using his poor grammar. 

3. Even with OP's poor title, there is absolutely nothing that would imply causation of Shaggy being Arab-American "BECAUSE" the guy who voiced him was Arab-American. Literally nothing. 

4. Again, sorry for "you" education.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So $23.40 basically. That's half the price that it normally is. I don't know much about this game. Must buy at this price? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you can finish reading the sentence and aren't an asshole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  When I'm board I like to paint Wood grain.

You missed a golden opportunity there, OP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you know what a sphere is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what OP was referring to: Casey Kasem being of Arab descent, not Shaggy. Poorly worded title, but still, it's not hard to glean the meaning.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't ask me silly questions

I won't play silly games

I'm just a simple choo choo train

And I'll always be the same.



I only want to race along

Beneath the bright blue sky

And be a happy choo choo train

Until the day I die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck you, I like Amy Schumer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha. To be fair, looks like OP added "University" in the title so it's totally original and not plagiarized.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I want to trade is fortune   Glory and no one wants it :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you learn that because you've seen this TIL on the front page so many times? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank god he turned down the Sabres 3yr/$15million offer. That was crazy money for him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can buy a Lane Bryant gift card at a discount. Then you can trade that to someone's mom for cash at a big discount. Then use that cash to put towards board games! I found the board games, everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the correct answer. These things are a godsend. Setting up Le Havre? Keep each good in a container and plop them down in their places on the board. Same for Agricola and Caverna (damn you and all your pieces, Uwe!). Love these.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 22:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's a list](https://boardgamegeek.com/geeklist/186405/best-solosolitaire-games-bgg-2015-edition], but I'm guessing you've seen that as you named the top 3 on it. I also enjoy playing Agricola solo, although the set up isn't the quickest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Option A: Spite them and keep winning

Option B: Intentionally lose for awhile to lull them into a false sense of security. Then continue domination at your leisure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to be rude, but a pretty simple search for gateway games either here or boardgamegeek.com will give you more than plenty of answers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 19:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Played this at snakes   lattes. we pushed the sticks all the way in and the balloon never popped. It was fully inflated, but the sticks were real cheap and kept bending. So much anxiety during the game, with no pay off. That's one big blue ball.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 18:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've been there at least the last two years. So are some of those chains in the galleria mall. I hate that. Leave this to local restaurants only.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SALE] XCOM: The Board Game $29.99 at CSI </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pour frosty into everyone's order of fries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/iJlGi4S.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 21:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe the JCC has leagues. At the very least, I know they do for squash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, there were a couple times in the first third or half of the book as it jumped to a new chapter   date that I had to skim back real quick to remind myself which date I had just been in. But once you got into it, it was easy to tell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 21:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I asked my SO if she wanted to play a couple of my unplayed games before my new ones arrive in August and she just laughed at me :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 21:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not directly, no. Tactics cards don't count for anything until they're actually put into play.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 21:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a flag is (correctly) claimed, it cannot be unclaimed later because a tactics card would allow a wild or extend it 4 cards needed instead of 3. If the flag is claimed, it's claimed for good. Which is the reason for the "advanced" rule it offers in the instructions, that a player cannot claim a flag until the start of their following turn, so to allow a player to stop a flag from being claimed via a tactics card. 


source: I asked this same question awhile ago here :) enjoy the game, it's great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 21:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Abyss** has absolutely gorgeous artwork. 

**Tokaido** is a very clean, attractive looking game.  

**Evolution** has beautiful, watercolor style art. 

In **Fresco**, you play as a master painter and it's a very good looking game. 

**Pictomania** is a pictionary-esque game so it's drawing based with a little bit more going on. Lots of fun. 


/u/r2d8 getinfo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just finished All The Light We Cannot See...one of the most beautiful works I've read in quite some time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 21:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Doerr's writing was some of the richest and beautiful prose I've come across. His descriptions of geographical settings, or especially the feelings/emotions/thoughts of his characters were astounding. I loved the long, detailed, textured, rich descriptions amid the quick, staccato chapters and asymmetrical timeline. The immensity for which I ended up caring about all these characters, whether minor or major left me not wanting the book to be over. Can't say enough good things about this novel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yea. I wrote above that our group's first game was Settlers. Then we got into Puerto Rico. Played both of those a ton as we got into the hobby. Settlers doesn't come out anymore, but Puerto Rico does from time to time. Love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. One thing I liked too is that you can basically pick how long you want the game to be. You can start with a ton of money or very little money if you want a longer or quicker game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fun. I have to play it more to give a better opinion. It was a newer purchase as well so I've only had a chance to play 2P once. So there's always that first play stumbling. But I enjoyed it a lot. I think it'll play better with 3 or 4 people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, I guess our mutual acquisition disorders unite us. We have steady group of 5. One guy doesn't really buy any games, another has a handful, and then the other 3 of us are the main collectors. Rounds the collection out nicely as our tastes reflect our collections. I think we have only have a few games that overlap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my gaming group, my one friend has a collection twice the size of this and another is close behind me. They have Glory to Rome and Innovation. Enjoy them both! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 16:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've definitely had my eye on Roll for the Galaxy and La Granja. I'll take a closer look at Elysium and Marco Polo. I've had a bunch of recent acquisitions and the kickstarters coming soon, so I'll add them to my holiday wish list...if my acquisition disorder can hold out that long :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 16:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Dead of Winter. My collection was almost all heavier euros, so I've been trying to round it out a bit to have something for all occasions, and getting some lighter games when the brain burn gets high. Which is why 1775 is so high on my favorites. It's definitely not Twilight Struggle. You're moving armies around the board and it's a ton of direct conflict with some dice roll (which is done in a really neat way). The 2v2 (you can also play 1v1 with each person controlling both armies on a side) aspect creates a great environment for the game. I love it. It's on the lighter side, it's not terribly long at all but it has great replay-value and a good amount of strategy and decision making. It's just fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [COMC] About 2 years in the making. Thought I'd finally share! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 15:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Imgur Link](http://i.imgur.com/7Hcaw2i.jpg)

I had gotten into the hobby 4-5 years ago when my friend picked up Catan, and we played that to death over the next year. Then he found Puerto Rico and that opened the floodgates for our group. A couple years ago I picked up Dominion Intrigue and Agricola to start my collection. It's grown and grown from there. 

[On top]

* Core Worlds, Five Tribes, Trains, Blueprints and some party games: Time's Up!, Wits   Wagers Party and Pictomania. If you look veeeery closely you can also see Fortune   Glory hiding in there. 

[Top Shelf]

* Bohnanza, Race for The Galaxy, Babel, Splendor, Stone Age, Mr Jack Pocket, Takenoko, Settlers of Catan, Le Havre   1775 Rebellion.

[Middle Shelf]

* Dominion Intrigue/Dark Ages/Hinterlands/Guilds, Star Realms, Eminent Domain, Castles of MKL, Tzolkin, Dead of Winter


[Bottom Shelf]

* Last Will, Agricola, AquaSphere, Brass, Terra Mystica and Fire   Ice Expansion, Twilight Struggle, Bora Bora   a Trains map expansion



[My personal favorites!]

1. Terra Mystica

2. Le Havre

3. Twilight Struggle

4. 1775 Rebellion

5. Dominion

6. Eminent Domain

7. Bora Bora

8. Tzolkin
9. Agricola 

10. AquaSphere 



Five Tribes   Core Worlds are new purchases so I haven't gotten them to the table yet. And I already know I'll have to get at least one Core Worlds expansion. Brass was a January purchase but still hasn't made it to the table unfortunately. I have the Evolution + expansion   Mottanai Kickstarters coming in August (hopefully) so I'll have to get those played before the new ones come in. Fortune   Glory I just hate. Maybe it'd be more fun if I gave it more of a chance but there's just too much going on for me to make it fun for what it is. 


let me know what you think! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a ton. Toronto easily has the most of any city. Just google it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recent Civilization: The Board Game sale on Amazon - did anyone else get the wrong item? I just received A Game of Thrones LCG: Illyrio's Gift Chapter Pack instead of Civilization. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 14:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The link to the sale was posted here a couple weeks ago. I just got the package and the seller said there was a mix-up with the product codes, and they're issuing a refund. I would like Civilization though. Especially at that sale price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 22:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally any thing in the world that you want.

That leaf outside? Grab it, tell everyone it's the first player marker.

A spoon from the kitchen? Leader gets the spoon now.

That bobblehead you got at a minor league baseball game? Goes to the leader.

Your high school diary? Drop that in front of whoever goes first.


Some lint from your belly button? That's caveman lint now. Goes to first player.


That blu-ray copy of Alec Baldwin   Sarah-Michelle Gellar's Suburban Girl that you got at a white elephant party? First player is now the suburban cavegirl. 


Hopefully this helps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 15:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tenacity? In the entire NHL, only Stamkos, Perry, Kane, Nash, Toews and Ovechkin have scored more 5v5 goals than Kessel since the 2010-2011 season. In that group he also has more 5v5 assists than Ovechkin, Nash, Perry and Stamkos.


He's not some wussy powerplay only skill guy. You don't score that many points on even strength without playing hard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 05:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any drinking game that has this many rules is no longer a game. It's work. Simplify. Kill a zombie...drink. Lose a survivor...drink. Crossroads card goes into effect...waterfall drink. The dog dies...pour one out for your homie. If your friend is taking too damn long on his turn...drink because it's your god damn drink and you can drink whenever you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 22:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good call. She might know your username. Play it safe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 22:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And she's an avid baker. Might have a winner here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, whose boobs are the best boobs? [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 22:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shipping from Buffalo, NY

[FT/FS]

* **Fortune   Glory: The Cliffhanger Game**: Played once, didn't like it. Near perfect condition

[W]

* Cash/Amazon $

* Roll For The Galaxy

* Keyflower

* Eminent Domain Expansions

* Core World Expansions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this game gets a ton of love here, but it just falls flat with me. I bought it while aboard the hype train after its initial release, and have played it about 10 times since. The first couple plays were fun, but then it just never progressed. My biggest issue is that I never get a real sense of completion. The castles seem small at the end, and there tends to be AP by the master-builder which stagnates the game at times. Each play, I'm just underwhelmed after.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 15:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You described **Eclipse**. Save for a little bit more and buy Eclipse. 


Star Realms plays just like Ascension basically. You're not building anything. Just laying cards out. If you have to pick between Star Realms and Race For the Galaxy, it's RFTG every day of the week. Star Realms isn't on Race's level at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 18:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bummed that Xia: Legends of a Drift System got shut out. That game is freaking awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 14:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please rearrange the top shelf so Terra Mystica Fire   Ice and Sherlock Holmes aren't in between much wider boxes. It's making me uncomfortable. 


Other than that...great collection! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 16:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that for purchasing, but Costco still allows me in the building to see if a membership is something I'm interested in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 16:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I have to create an account just to look at your website...f*** you, website.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SALE] Sentinels of the Multiverse: Enhanced Edition $18 at Miniature Market ($27 at CSI, $27 at Amazon, $26 at Cardhaus) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 15:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 21:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I own **Five Tribes** and my best friend has **Istanbul** and **Concordia**. I would say, hands down, Concordia. It plays wonderfully with all player counts, the replay-value is tremendous with the randomized goods tiles, card order and now with the various boards. I love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 15:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can find it all on Amazon when you look at games. They have weights and dimensions listed for everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 15:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just hit [Adv. Search](https://boardgamegeek.com/advsearch/boardgame) next to the search bar at the top. Then enter the search parameters you'd like, and hit submit. Then just sort by the rank in the left column. Easy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 15:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my lifetime I was roughly 0-6375463549 in playing Carcassonne against my friend John. Each game, played out like the last: my meeples scattered in unfinished castles, starving along roads to nowhere, slaughtered in fields outnumbered two to one. I'd watch his scoring marker danced along the track, circling and circling the board. Adding expansions only made the misery more prolonged, more insufferable. 


Yet I persevered. Then one day (oh this glorious day!), did the tiles fall into my favor. Square by square, I completed majestic, shielded castles. I built long, windy roads that had a beginning and end. I frolicked in the fields my opponent dared not enter. And I won. By the angels in heaven and the hammer of Thor, I won. 


With my new found confidence and Carcassonne prowess, we reset the battle field so I could take back to back victories. 


And I got killed.


But I will always have that one. That sweet, sweet one. Damn you, John.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 15:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is a list of board games filtered by weight of 1-3, sorted by BGG rank](https://boardgamegeek.com/search/boardgame?sort=rank advsearch=1 q= include%5Bdesignerid%5D= include%5Bpublisherid%5D= geekitemname= range%5Byearpublished%5D%5Bmin%5D= range%5Byearpublished%5D%5Bmax%5D= range%5Bminage%5D%5Bmax%5D= range%5Bnumvoters%5D%5Bmin%5D= range%5Bnumweights%5D%5Bmin%5D= range%5Bminplayers%5D%5Bmax%5D= range%5Bmaxplayers%5D%5Bmin%5D= range%5Bleastplaytime%5D%5Bmin%5D= range%5Bplaytime%5D%5Bmax%5D= floatrange%5Bavgrating%5D%5Bmin%5D= floatrange%5Bavgrating%5D%5Bmax%5D= floatrange%5Bavgweight%5D%5Bmin%5D=1 floatrange%5Bavgweight%5D%5Bmax%5D=3 colfiltertype= searchuser=kcbarn playerrangetype=normal B1=Submit) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was the first Neil Gaiman book I'd ever read and I finished it in a day. I couldn't put it down. Loved it. The world he painted in this was so magical and rich and vibrant, you could feel it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favorite openers as well. From the first sentence you just know something is off about this world and are hooked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha. Cloud Atlas was one of the books I knew I'd hate after the first page. I always finish the book I'm reading. I don't give up on the book, I just can't leave them unfinished...unless the book is Cloud Atlas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had this book on my shelf for probably 2 years now and haven't opened it up. Maybe I'll finally have to this summer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 23:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pinochle all night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What book(s) did you fall in love with after just a page or two? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 23:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What drew you in about the book? Something with the character or a specific quote? The language and/or the prose? How did it go from there...were you disappointed at the end or did you still love it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SALE] North Wind $24.99 at CSI ($39 Amazon, $33 Cardhaus, $34.49 MM) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 15:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Battle Line rules question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 04:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playing battle line my friend took a flag with 345 straight flush. The cards played out meant I couldn't take this flag at all so he claimed it. However, later a tactics card came into my hand that gave me a wild 8 of any suit which gave me the ability for a better straight flush. Can I still play here and take the flag back or is it dead?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 15:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks very similar to Wits   Wagers. If this is a retheme of Fauna, can people familiar with Fauna shed some light on the differences between that and Wits   Wagers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 23:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and if you run out of space, you can put the stuff from the shoeboxes into the empty game boxes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 22:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You're right. No jokes allowed on the internet!](http://i.imgur.com/EHZ5y6n.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 22:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Like this](http://i.imgur.com/l7mScRq.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 22:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/boardgames/search?q=power+grid restrict_sr=on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 19:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First...I own Domion Intrigue along with Hinterlands, Dark Ages, Guilds and the rest of my group has the base, Seaside, Prosperity. I've played it a ton. Don't let some of the poor artwork blow the game for you. And to the theme nuts out there...who the hell cares. It's a game where you use the 10 kingdom cards available to get the most VP's. And it works beautifully. With the wealth of expansions (and cards in each expansion) the breadth of replay value is, perhaps, unmatched. It's an easy game to learn, and one that also has a lot of depth and strategy (see www.dominionstrategy.com for that). Dominion has reached the status it has because it is great.


Secondly, I also own **Eminent Domain**, **Core Worlds**, **Trains** and **Star Realms**. I guess I like deck builders. Dominion will always be my favorite, but I love the mechanics of Eminent Domain and Core Worlds. They each offer unique experience (Eminent Domain with role sections and followers, Core Worlds with invasion types, worlds, etc). You can't go wrong. The only downside to Core Worlds is that you really need the expansion(s) to make it a complete game so it turns into a $60 game. If theme is important for you, which it seems to be, Core Worlds offers, in my opinion, the best theme of any deck builder. 

Trains works well with theme as well with the enhanced mechanic of an actual board and pieces. It's pretty much Dominion with a board. You feel more of an experience like you're building a train line (even if it just little cubes). 

Star Realms is fun for up to 5-10 plays. 

DC deck builder is terrible. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 18:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Type in a real sub and yes, it will link you right to it. It helps if you understand jokes, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 18:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out /r/digitaltabletop. They'll have a list of available app versions of games. There is definitely the most on iOS (compared to android, etc) and there are a really good amount of quality games (with quality digital implentations).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 17:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that still open? Childhood flashbacks! As an animal obsessed kid sitting in the rear-facing seats of my parent's car, it was the best thing ever. Monkeys climbing on the car, lions sleeping, giraffes looking into the window and other animals around. It was great. That being said, I'd be worried to go back, see it through the eyes of an adult and it being a total let down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Show Idea - Celebrity American Gladiator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 17:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have the gladiators be celebrities. Terry Crews, The Rock, Jason Statham, [Nathan Jones](http://www.imdb.com/name/nm0428923/?ref_=tt_cl_t6), Dave Bautista, Chris Hemsworth, Rhonda Rousey, Brienne of Tarth, Gina Carano (again), Laila Ali, [Olha Korobka](http://www.polska-sztanga.pl/modules/coppermine/albums/userpics/10010/75pluskorobka.jpg)


Contestants could be "regular" people, and maybe even have other celebrities be the contestants for sweeps episodes if you can get any that would try. 


Arnold hosts. 


[Mo](https://michaelcerio.files.wordpress.com/2012/01/quirk.jpg?w=830) referees.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 15:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the game you're trying to figure out which potions combine to create spells. The app randomizes this so each game is different. So you use the app to take a picture of two ingredient cards and it tells you what it becomes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 15:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Alchemists** uses an app as a core mechanic in the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 14:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Alchemists** is a pretty heavy game. There's a lot going on there and the teaching/learning time is *steep*. It's a really great game, but if you're wary about dropping some heavy on your friends, you might want to wait on that. **Ca$h 'n Gun$** and **Mascarade** aren't really competitive. They're more just social party games and Mascarade offers some deduction elements. 


**Battlestar Galactica** plays well with 5P if you want to go the co-op/traitor route. Take a look at **Power Grid** for a classic medium weight that plays well at 5.  **Kemet** is a medium-light game that works great at 3-5. It's quick, action packed war game and not too hard to get into at all. You can even combine it with **Cyclades** which is super cool. And there's always **Cosmic Encounter** for a crazy good time. 

/u/r2d8 getinfo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 22:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the WWII street would win. It has soldiers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 22:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/im10andnaturegrowingthroughabandonedthingsiswtf
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This link stopped working </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reference sheet on back cover of rule book is great tho. Makes it real easy to glance at what card icons mean. First playthrough is definitely a lot of just learning the cards and seeing how they play out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 15:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Last Will** is a great game. Just have to get your mind working towards $0. It's a pretty simple game at it's core. Each round you pick turn order   week's plan, send out a couple workers to the board, play action cards in your hand. That's it. The real decisions is really in the planning board, making sure you give yourself enough cards or actions that you need that round.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 15:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How's the replay-ability? Are you done with the game once you know the scenarios? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SALE] Tragedy Looper $21.99 at CardHaus ($27.49 at CSI, $27.59 at MM, $36.95 at Amazon) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 15:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 14:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll sell you my copy.


So, definitely yay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 22:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> House Rule #1: Don't House Rule Games.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 22:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't played **1812**, so I can't say for sure. I can say that 1775 has a higher rating on BGG, and watching Tom Vasel's [review on 1775: Rebellion](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OIxBHGyMXzE) he says it's superior to 1812. 

Here are also a couple of links comparing [the](http://www.reddit.com/r/boardgames/comments/2jzrfl/wsig_1812_the_invasion_of_canada_or_1775_rebellion/) [two](https://boardgamegeek.com/thread/923364/comparing-1775-1812). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 22:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out **1775: Rebellion**. Lighter war game, lots of fun. Very historical, tactical, some card drafting (you have 12 cards, 3 in hand at a time), moving soldiers around Colonial US   Canada. Lots of fun. A bit lighter than your traditional war game. I think the 2 v 2 aspect is a fantastic option as well you don't see often.


/u/r2d8 getinfo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 21:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Spot is a Rochester thing.


That's not even remotely true. Spot's first ever location and headquarters are in Buffalo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 21:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> check meetup.com for some local gaming groups.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 21:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I google "toronto board game cafe" one of the top results is an article about the top 20 board game cafes and bars in toronto. 

So, amidst a ton of competitors and (probably) the most successful in the world in Snakes   Lattes, I vote to name it Good Luck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 23:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if she had 5, then she was either holding more than more than 3 cards in her hand or she was stockpiling all of them on purpose (which would take at least 9 turns, and likely more) at the sacrifice of only having   using 5 regular gems, which doesn't seem an efficient use of gems. All the meanwhile, you would be left with full reign over the regular gems. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 23:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> News show with only positive, uplifting news.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 22:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it would take awhile. You can only hold 3 cards at a time. And you can only get one wild at a time. Theoretically, a person could get 3 wild gems and then play one of their cards-in-hand with all regular gems, while holding their wilds, but that'd be hard to do. And not remotely efficient. While they're taking 1 wild at a time and not playing any cards, everyone else is getting 2-3 gems turn and/or buying cards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 22:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can take 1 wild token when you stash a card into your hand. You can't have more than 10 total tokens in front of you at any given time.  There are no limits on *holding* a certain color token as long as your total is 10 or under </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 18:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't tell if there was just a ton of effort put into a joke there, or there was no joke at all... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This might help a bit](http://fivethirtyeight.com/features/designing-the-best-board-game-on-the-planet/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, don't beat yourself up. It was a good hour of hearing about games I've never heard of that no one will want to play :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Strategy] My hog rider attack strategy questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During clan wars, I've been using a hog attack strategy that seems to be pretty hit   miss lately. It's especially miss if there are inferno towers. I use 38 hog riders (max), 10 barbarians (max) and 25 archers (max). 


I typically send the hogs in at the same side side of the base, but slightly apart to form 2 close by fronts. For spells, I drop 4 heal spells for them throughout the attack. 


I run into issues if 1. there are inferno towers, they destroy the hogs. or 2. I get unlucky and hit a lot of traps. If the base also has a good amount of upgraded wizard towers or archers, that gives them problems. 


What could I do to tweak this attack to make it a little more viable and consistent? Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the ever motivational Gilfoyle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, still follow the rule. It adds a little strategy of blocking your opponent from grabbing 2 fairly easier. You'll still be able to grab 2 if you really need (I'd still advice grabbing 3 two turns in a row) fairly regularly as you or your opponent returns gems to the stack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SALE] City Hall $30 at Miniature Market ($41.37 at Amazon, $41 at CSI, $39 at Cardhaus) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 14:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 19:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Brain fart. Thanks for pointing that out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 18:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that as huge as it looks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
