<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1485</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the least surprising news of the day, I've found that the biased SJW-type presenter also works for the BBC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A guy using proper logic to point out lies and injustice by feminism. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A guy using proper logic to point out lies and injustice by feminism. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unsurprisingly, the rather biased feminist interviewer also has a job at the BBC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A guy using proper logic to point out lies and injustice by feminism. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he'd have just shouted racist at her it would have been much more entertaining (and appropriate). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even from a British perspective it's usage in this instance is completely inappropriate and quite offensive given the circumstances (surely the correct term is "civil rights campaigner" or "gender equality activist". That said, the rest of the article isn't too bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fancy dress dad's rights campaigner found hanging in jail cell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A somewhat disappointing headline, but the comments section is simply magical.

From what I've read of this case it seems extremely complicated and it seems this guy has been failed by the state throughout his entire life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fancy dress dad's rights campaigner found hanging in jail cell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fancy dress dad's rights campaigner found hanging in jail cell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Come on Myleene (don't be a crummy mummy) - Fathers4Justice launch Myleene Klass Advert </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grandparents blocked from adopting their three-year-old granddaughter hit out at 'wicked' treatment that 'shouldn't happen in civilised society' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grandparents blocked from adopting their three-year-old granddaughter hit out at 'wicked' treatment that 'shouldn't happen in civilised society' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diane Abbott Trolled. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 32 boys dead in South African circumcision initiation season, half a million hospitalised between 2008 and 2013 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diane Abbott Trolled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets not link to total fabrications please. it doesn't even allow comments so how is there any value at all in such a link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy trolls racist politician while she's interviewed on live TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comrades! Labour leadership hopeful Jeremy Corbyn invites Gerry Adams and Martin McGuinness for a cuppa in Parliament </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 20:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman who had sex with 14 year old boy sentenced to 40 years in prison, with 39 years suspended </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Campbell Co. Teacher's Aide Sentenced For Sex Crimes With Minor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman demanded home, then falsely alleged rape: prosecution says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman demanded home, then falsely alleged rape: prosecution says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feminists disrupt equality speech in Ottawa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 06:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 05:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are no less than three "Boys are Stupid, throw rocks at them" products on the B N website. Most responsible companies withdrew these products either in 2004 or in the follow-up campaign last year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the best summary of the case for those who want to know the detail. There's a lot of myths out there so it's well worth a read of the truth: http://espn.go.com/espn/otl/story/_/id/12976615/detailed-look-hope-solo-domestic-violence-case-includes-reports-being-belligerent-jail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> here's the best summary of the case for those who want to know more: http://espn.go.com/espn/otl/story/_/id/12976615/detailed-look-hope-solo-domestic-violence-case-includes-reports-being-belligerent-jail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The story is out there if you read the right articles. The best summary is this by ESPN: http://espn.go.com/espn/otl/story/_/id/12976615/detailed-look-hope-solo-domestic-violence-case-includes-reports-being-belligerent-jail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hope Solo to appear on Kids Choice Sports award show, even after arrest for assaulting a minor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 01:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hope Solo to appear on Kids Choice Sports award show, even after arrest for assaulting a minor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 01:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 01:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Double standards.

No. Siddique's religion is an integral part of his work/fame. He's a leading Muslim, not simply a regular/occasional Muslim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 01:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologies, I just basically took the title from the video to avoid suggestions of editorialising. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hope Solo to appear on Kids Choice Sports award show, even after arrest for assaulting a minor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 00:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 23:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny how in all of these scandals the opinions are left-wing or anti Conservative/UKIP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 23:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You know how often they mentioned him being a Christian?
 Fucking never.

That's probably becasue he was Jewish: http://www.haaretz.com/jewish-world/jewish-world-news/1.638528




**edit**, awww he's deleted the post. Real shame, a true classic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 22:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  To be fair, this statement could be used for any actual terrorist group to justify their actions. Isis "only adopted their tactics" because...

Not really, it say they only use the tactics becasue of the failure to uphold the law. The likes of ISIS hate the most fundamental features of our system of law and even democracy itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privileged Feminists STUNNED by Empirical Evidence - feat. Mike Buchanan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 22:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 22:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From a few years back but I was reminded of the story today as there's controversy over them doing similar things to other groups of late.

Also this hasn't been posted before nor does there seem to have been an apology for what happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK government aligns Fathers4Justice with terrorist groups </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 22:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leading Bristol Muslim and former government adviser, Farooq Siddique, charged with rapes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 22:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC News Editor Trolls Jeremy Hunt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 22:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dave Blasts NUS Over CAGE Jihadi Baddies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 21:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 19:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of their 2011 presentation which lymped in Fathers4Justice with the 9/11 attacks, the IRA and Animal Liberation Front.

https://www.timeshighereducation.co.uk/news/second-thoughts-on-extreme-tactic/418439.article?sectioncode=26 storycode=418439 c=1

The Fathers4jjustice smear was not only more severe, but also less accurate given they just wear silly costumes. The worst they do is occasionally throw various pancake ingredients at Labour politicians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Myleene Klass' ex Graham Quinn slams star on Twitter as he denies taking her money and claims she won't let him see their children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 18:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 08:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2000 people clearly disagree with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 08:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best parts starts at 9 minutes in: https://youtu.be/8eHLnb6kYnc?t=9m9s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 08:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By far the best part starts at 9 minutes in: https://youtu.be/8eHLnb6kYnc?t=9m9s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 07:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also served as a Minister according to the Sun, so that excludes about 70% of those on your list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privileged Feminists STUNNED by Empirical Evidence - London Live TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 07:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privileged Feminists STUNNED by Empirical Evidence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 07:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 07:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's 545 under 24 year olds vs 104 women of any age (and it's less than 104 these days.) The actual number of male suicides is over 4,500. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bristol school won't take children back to Butlin's after 11-year-old 'attacked' by woman on ride </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 01:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Author drops UCL from 1m will over Sir Tim Hunt's treatment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 22:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 21:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice to see the Universities disgraceful behaviour starting to have consequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 20:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A reminder of Burchill's previous thoughts on male suicide: http://www.theguardian.com/theguardian/1999/oct/16/weekend7.weekend6

"Well, if the men who manage football think that 545 under-24 male suicides a year is a more frightening statistic than two women killed each week - and hundreds of thousands injured every year - by the men they live with, then they must be even stupider than they look; though it's hard to imagine, I know. But I can't help feeling they're on very dodgy ground, taking on the young male suicide thing. For a start, it's a phony panic, catering to that lowest of modern male desires - to be a victim"

"That young men succeed in suicide more often than girls isn't really the point. Indeed, the more callous among us would say that it was quite nice for young men finally to find something that they're better at than girls." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Julie Burchill talks of guilt after the death of her son Jack Landesman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 20:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Author drops UCL from 1m will over Sir Tim Hunt's treatment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 17:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Author drops UCL from 1m will over Sir Tim Hunt's treatment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 17:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 03:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meanwhile far worse happens to millions of babies and it's 100% deliberate every single time. If they're rally unlucky they'll live in NYC and some sicko with herpes will suck the blood from the wound afterwards (and the government will be ok with it too!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senior MP accused of child sex abuse: Two MPs report same serving Labour politician to police over sex attacks and corruption claims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 00:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Security Guard Doing His Duty Gets Slapped By This Lady </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 03:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Security Guard Doing His Duty Gets Slapped By This Lady </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 03:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Foreign national slaps policeman after he refuses entry to book launch by former PM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 03:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 00:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that it's legal to carry out similar mutilations on boys show the law to be inconsistent and therefore flawed.

Of course the way to fix this is to protect boys from mutilation too,  but anyone supporting mutilation can take the opposite position an argue they're being discriminated against and they should be able to cut girls just as other cut boys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 00:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That study is at odds with most other research (and it even says as much in the link). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 23:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There aren't any 'benefits' to FGM. There are to circumcision. 

Actually, pretty much every supposed "benefit" of MGM also applies to FGM.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 23:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There's no apparent evolutionary sense to wanking

Not true at all. It cuts the risk of prostate cancer and also helps maintain sexual function. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rich and Famous: Owen Jones Joins the 1% </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 22:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 22:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The topic of the story is the mutilation of children's genitals without their consent. If we made it illegal to mutilate all kids , regardless of gender, you'd instantly take away one of the best arguments supporting FGM.

People opposing MGM are the biggest opponents of FGM - they go further than feminist opponents of the practice and want to protect all victims of mutilation instead of just a small percentage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 17:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We need more mental health initiatives.

That's true and mental health may have been one factor here, but I object to this statement on its own - it's now standard response to these cases and pretending that mental health care is the main issue is used to gloss over the abuse men face in our society.

This guy was denied access to his kids, and in most cases these denials of contact are quite clearly wrong. He killed himself in prison, where he had already been subject to violence and it's highly doubtful that he should have even been there in the first place.

If we allow men to be mistreated again and again, and then imprison them for highlighting such abuses (where the abuse continues) then inevitably some will reach breaking point, regardless of whatever mental health care is available.

We need to fix the root causes of these problems, sometimes that's mental health, but mostly it's the shocking way men are abused and mistreated by society. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> J4MB publicly challenges the Cabinet Office in relation to honours presented recently to two lying feminists, Laura Bates and Caroline Criado-Perez </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 11:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fathers 4 Justice splinter group 'disqualified from Alexandra Palace soapbox race for being too political' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 10:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 10:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to hear about your loss, this is a reminder of why we're all here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 10:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His imprisonment was as result of his protests, not for any actual crimes: http://newfathers4justice.co.uk/2015/06/06/suffragent-free-haydn-burton/

Of particular note, is that his arrest was at the hands of Hampshire Police, who have also engaged in some extremely distributing practices against the founder of the original Fahters4Justice, a case which also involved alleged misconduct by a Conservative MP. Matt O'Connor of F4J is currently been dragged through the courts by the police and has also been subject to physical attack by Conservatives at his own home!

So in summary, in one county we have a corrupt police force going out of their way to target all fathers rights campaigners who dare to engage with Conservative politicians, and there are very close ties between Conservative politicians in this country and the police force.

Essentially it seems that the the country in question is not a safe place for anyone concerned with equality for fathers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fathers 4 Justice Superman Haydn Burton A5941DH who protested agaist PM in Witney found hanged in HMP Winchester </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 02:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Music teacher from Leeds who had sex with a vulnerable boy of 17 is jailed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 04:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could we do something nice for this guy, maybe raise some money for him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Accused teen-basher Hope Solo gets 'Kids' Choice' spot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daves embrace of the spurious gender pay gap will just cut men's wages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge says "regret" at root of rape case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge says "regret" at root of rape case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 19:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   They have to be as unbiased as possible when reporting the news and they enforce this heavily. With any news they have to be as unbiased as possible.

They're supposed to be unbiased, but they're terrible when it comes to gender issues. It's now basically a feminist organisation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 09:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U.S. soccer thinks she does as do over 10k people who favourited their tweet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 07:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And to think just last week US Soccer proposed putting Solo on the new $1 bill! https://twitter.com/ussoccer_wnt/status/617868478607921152 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 07:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And just last week US Soccer proposed putting Solo on the new $1 $10 bill! (with their proposal being retweeted 6K times!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 07:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just last week US Soccer proposed putting Solo on the new $1 bill! https://twitter.com/ussoccer_wnt/status/617868478607921152 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 07:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just last week US Soccer proposed putting Solo on the new $1 bill! https://twitter.com/ussoccer_wnt/status/617868478607921152 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prosecutors, city seek reinstatement of charges against Hope Solo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prosecutors, city seek reinstatement of charges against Hope Solo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prosecutors, city seek reinstatement of charges against Hope Solo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prosecutors, city seek reinstatement of charges against Hope Solo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prosecutors, city seek reinstatement of charges against Hope Solo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crown Prosecution Service challenged to prove the legality of male genital mutilation (and fails) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> J4MB publicly challenges Theresa May MP, Home Secretary, over MGM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> J4MB publicly challenges Theresa May MP, Home Secretary, over MGM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My son was murdered by his girlfriend - I don't want other men to suffer in silence because of abuse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 05:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My son was murdered by his girlfriend - I don't want other men to suffer in silence because of abuse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 05:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man arrested for giving 1 to homeless man wins payout </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 05:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea, sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There isn't one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 03:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy who made this video made countless other equally good one on other gender related issues, with hours and hours of original content interviewing figures such as Erin Pizzey. His original channels have disappeared, but some of the best vids are mirrored on other channels. Search for "manwomanmyth" for more similar content. 

The follow channel has mirrored quite a few of the videos:
https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC71JvwMCwlbATlyWBonidug

Here's a good one to get you started: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mjwe6ECiXi4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Laugh, But British Feminists Have Formed Their Own 'Women's Equality Party' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Laugh, But British Feminists Have Formed Their Own 'Women's Equality Party' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Womens Equality Party: for ladies too nice for politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Womens Equality Party: for ladies too nice for politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 05:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, and this case is elevated well above those in significance becasue Solo is representing her country rather than just dong her day job by playing for a random team/business </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 05:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It was looked into and there was no hard proof Solo was the instigator just a bunch of he said she said

The case was dismissed on procedural grounds, therefore the allegations haven't actually been "looked into" yet in court. There's also rather more proof in this case than a great many other cases that end up in court. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 05:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Does that mean the celebration of the US victory is something to be questioned? I don't think so.

If she'd maybe have stayed away from the celebrations then it wouldn't be so bad. Perhaps if the other athletes had come out against domestic violence then it would be a little more tolerable. But if even 10% of the allegations about Solo are true then she shouldn't have been on the team and therefore any victory is going to be tainted by that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 05:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There was bunch of he said she said going on and dismissed like a normal case.

No, it was dismissed on procedural grounds. This dismissal gets appealed on Monday so there's still a very real chance of her facing justice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 05:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Because one person on the team is a dickhead, you can't celebrate winning a world cup? 

No, you suspend said person from the team before the tournament and have a squad completely free of violent assholes who are all fit to represent their country.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 05:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The outcome of the Women's World Cup has nothing to do with the handling of Hope Solo's case.

Of course it does, Sole played every minute for the winning team! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 05:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only just found this article and this is my only account here.

It's a highly topical story - prosecutors are expected to appeal the dismissal of the case on Monday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are we celebrating U.S. Soccer? - The handling of the Hope Solo case diminishes from the World Cup title </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 04:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are we celebrating U.S. Soccer? - The handling of the Hope Solo case diminishes from the World Cup title </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 04:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are we celebrating U.S. Soccer? - the handling of the Hope Solo case diminishes from the World Cup title </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 04:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are we celebrating U.S. Soccer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 04:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hope Solo had restraining order at school from girl she called a 'fat bitch' and 'whore' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 04:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hope Solo endorses "equal pay" for female athletes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 04:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crown Prosecution Service challenged to prove the legality of MGM (and fails) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 03:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MP's son attacked by girl gang in Leicester Square KFC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 19:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police find malnourished teen weighing 47 lbs in roach infested home, two arrested </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 19:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After serving 7 years in jail for 'rape', Bombay High Court acquits man of all charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reinstate DeAndre Johnson, stop blaming for being a victim of assault and defending himself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 05:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reinstate DeAndre Johnson, stop blaming for being a victim of assault and defending himself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 05:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reinstate DeAndre Johnson, stop blaming for being a victim of assault and defending himself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 05:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Students Told to Take Photos With a Consent Contract Before They Have Sex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 04:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 23:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd normally condemn you for linking to such a hateful site, but it does at least seem to be allowing comments, so that makes it excusable in my book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  people who couldn't beat 13-14 year old boys

One of the team members is allegedly very good at beating boys... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First cousin marriages in Pakistani communities leading to 'appalling' disabilities among children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 19:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The charges were only dropped on proceedural grounds, this is being appealed in a few days time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the 6% figure include all the additional still births and miscarriages etc? The article also only spoke about defects diagnosed in infancy, health issues can emerge later in childhood or even as young adults and perhaps they're being glossed over too?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-circumcision crusader targets Bono </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 05:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World Cup Women Players Overpaid Compared To Male Counterparts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 02:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World Cup Women Players Overpaid Compared To Male Counterparts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 02:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 11:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  'Debunking feminist myths'? Ugh.

Did you actually watch the video?, I know it's long but at least view the first 5 minutes. Whatever you opinion of his other politics it's clear he's an MP who taken the time to research an issue in depth, ask questions, study the data and find the truth. I doubt you'll see a better performance from any politician from any party, and its' a real shame there weren't more there to hear what he said and learn from his work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 09:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Davies has done some fantastic work highlighting sexism in the prison and justice system and debunking feminist myths. This speech is well worth watching:

http://human-stupidity.com/stupid-dogma/mens-rights-feminism/conservative-backbencher-philip-davies-thoroughly-debunks-feminist-politicians-politically-correct-nonsense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's not fair on men that women prisoners don't have to wear uniforms, Tory MP complains </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 09:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 07:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And only two women in the top 100 (with one of those set to lose her top 100 place in August) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 06:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's saying most of the crap ones who lose drop out. If you're good at what you do then you obviously wouldn't drop out for the reason he suggests and therefore his point doesn't apply to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Funeral services Sunday for Glenn Ford, exonerated death row inmate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 05:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Philip Davies has been working to highlight inequalities in the prison system for years now, he's gone from basically knowing nothing about the issue and believing all the feminist lies to being the most knowledgeable person in Parliament on the topic. It's really worth watching some of his speeches on this issue, please consider following him on twitter and tweeting in support of his work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Detailed look at Hope Solo's domestic violence case includes reports of her being belligerent in jail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably the most comprehensive article on this topic, useful for dispelling some myths about the case that seem to be flying around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably the most comprehensive article on this topic, useful for dispelling some myths about the case that seem to be flying around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Detailed look at Hope Solo's domestic violence case includes reports of her being belligerent in jail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Detailed look at Hope Solo's domestic violence case includes reports of her being belligerent in jail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 01:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Looks at your post history

While we're on the topic of post histories, care to explain yours? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Social worker escapes jail after admitting having sex with child in her care </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 01:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I hadn't heard of the idea of men being on the ends of the spectrum and women in the middle. It's a compelling idea but probably not 100% accurate. 

it's absolutely accurate and absolutely the perfect argument to explain the lack of female geniuses and chess grand masters, becasue the differences are by far  the most significant at the genius level extreme of the spectrum.

There's also evidence to suggest that the male curve is shifted very marginally to the right of the female one. This difference is extremely small, but it magnifies the differences at the extreme right of the curve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not necessarily defending his body language during all the discussion. However, if an opponent makes a point that ridiculous/extreme then laughter can be an appropriate response at that immediate moment. If she'd have been able to debate properly and left out the most idiotic "arguments" then there wouldn't have been anything to laugh at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 23:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That victim blaming point really was worthy of a laugh though, by then I was laughing too. Nothing wrong in laughing when something is that ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 23:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At club level yes, but this world cup has received plenty of hype. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 23:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  she defending her sister from her nephew

Solo went to the nephew/sister's house drunk (in her car). She insulted him about his weight, was asked to leave but then followed them into the house. She then attacked the nephew and he restrained her. After he was persuaded to release her she attacked thim again repeatedly punching him in the face smashing his head into the concrete. Solo's half sister then tried to protect her son, at which point she was then also repeatedly punched in the face by Solo. The nephew grabbed the BB gun t try to get Solo out of the house, and Solo later lied to the police that it had been a real gun.

Both the victims had visible injuries and Solo swore at the police and even threatened them when arrested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 21:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where were the people who claim to care about domestic violence though? How many domestic violence charities condemned her? How many feminists and other activists did so and started contacting sponsors etc?

I've seen one politician condemn what she did and one player (and she was retiring anyway). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 19:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ..said the mod of /againstmensrights! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Milo Yiannopoulos explains patiently to a feminist why most top chess players are men </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 18:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Milo Yiannopoulos explains patiently to a feminist why most top chess players are men </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 18:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 18:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the charges were dismissed.

They were dismissed **on procedural grounds**, not becasue of any evidence pointing to her lack of guilt. This dismissal of the charges is now being appealed by prosecutors, so there's a good chance she'll end up on trial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Domestic violence and America's greatest female goalie: Double standards much? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 18:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Domestic violence and America's greatest female goalie: Double standards much? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 18:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Milo Yiannopoulos explains patiently to a feminist why most top chess players are men </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 16:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC 'lining up female political editor' to replace Nick Robinson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 04:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eastern Cape hospital faces crisis due to initiate influx </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 03:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eastern Cape hospital faces crisis due to initiate influx </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 03:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 18:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The BBC does exactly the same thing in the UK, their Comic Relief campaign donates to the "Paws for Kids" charity helping the pets of women and children who are victims of domestic violence. Meanwhile men barely get a penny from anyone.

This issue was identified as early as 2007: http://archive.spectator.co.uk/article/24th-march-2007/16/read-the-small-print-before-the-next-comic-relief </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 18:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually it's the rarity of them getting caught and the prosecuted which makes it news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 18:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're clearly discriminating by gender, that's my point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We NEED more female Engineers! Feminist Illogic EXPOSED (feat. Mike Buchanan) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 05:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We NEED more female Engineers! Feminist Illogic EXPOSED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 05:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> False rape claim woman given community payback order </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 05:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> False rape claim woman given community payback order </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 04:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> False rape claim woman given community payback order </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 04:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Primary school teacher struck off for praising Isil murder of Alan Henning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 04:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 17:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Greens really are now the most sexist political party in the UK.

They only want men to go to prison, men appear to be completely sidelined in the party (despite them claiming to have equality when it comes to the leadership and deputy leader position). Can you name a current Green Party figure who isn't female? When did you last see a male from the party sent to be their representative on TV or speaking at one of their press conferences?

Looking at Bennett's background we see she worked for the extremist feminist organisation the Fawcett Society and therefore it's no surprise she comes out with sexist rubbish such as this. No wonder so few males vote for the party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 17:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Mansplaining" is a sexist term invented by feminists so they can avoid debate with men and instead play the victim any time they get something completely wrong.

More recently they've introduced other similar sexist terms such as "manspreading" for when a person supposedly takes up too much space on public transport.

it's quite incredible to see feminists such as Bennett supporting such sexism as feminists pretend to be in favour of gender neutral terminology at all times, yet here they are inventing more and more unnecessarily gendered language (and quite unpleasant and sexist language at that). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian Lawmakers Consider Letting Cops Shoot at Women, Crowds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 06:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian Lawmakers Consider Letting Cops Shoot at Women, Crowds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 06:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Julie Burchill - 'Suicide is a side-effect of affluence. You didn't get many suicides in Jarrow in the 30s. It is one of those problems with no solution' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 06:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pregnant careworker Kerry Horsfall jailed for having affair with teen boy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 06:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lionesses: Our sympathy towards Laura Bassett is sexist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 05:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lionesses: Our sympathy towards Laura Bassett is sexist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 05:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ashley Cole: MGTOW and Self-Preservation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 05:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit revolt flares again as AMA moderator sacked the day after a disastrous Jesse Jackson Q A </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 05:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian police are prohibited by law from shooting at female criminals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 03:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 08:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit Revolt Flares Again as 'AMA' Moderator Sacked the Day After a Disastrous Jesse Jackson Q A </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 07:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit Ask Me Anything Goes Horribly Wrong For Jesse Jackson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 07:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 07:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The admin who runs AMA losts her job shortly after this, so there may well be a major men's rights angle to the current Reddit meltdown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit Ask Me Anything Goes Horribly Wrong For Jesse Jackson - asked if was regretful for, rushing to judgement after condemning the perpetrators of the Duke lacrosse rape scandal, the user also asked if he and Al Sharpton, still support Crystal Mangums false rape allegations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 07:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 02:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'd promote gender equality for everyone rather than just special privileges for women (which is was feminism has become). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian Libertarians in Revolt After Party Leadership Suspends Anti-Feminist Candidate Lauren Southern </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian Libertarians in Revolt After Party Leadership Suspends Anti-Feminist Candidate Lauren Southern </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian Libertarians in Revolt After Party Leadership Suspends Anti-Feminist Candidate Lauren Southern </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 03:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but those facing such charges would expect to be suspended. If she's actually guilty of attacking a child then she gets banned from the team for good, not simply suspended. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch: Amazing footage shows Nissan Micra driver passing a motorcyclist by undertaking on the pavement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 23:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suspend Hope Solo Immediately </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 22:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 21:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any policies to reduce the gender education gap (something that's actually a genuine issue) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Furious Rotherham taxi drivers threaten strike action over new regulations in wake of abuse scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 20:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Cricket widow' pensioner who beat her husband of 50 years with a rolling pin because he didnt spend enough time with her is spared jail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 19:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Cricket widow' pensioner who beat her husband of 50 years with a rolling pin because he didnt spend enough time with her is spared jail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 19:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 19:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There is no blatant sexist double standard. Male athletes beat the shit outta females all the time, and get slapped on the wrist

In some of the cases where males have been suspended it was actually the female who attacked first. We see the same double standard in the music industry - Chris Brown gets vilified for abusing his partner, yet Amy Winehouse, Whitney Houston, Cheryl Cole all get a pass and in most cases boast about their abuse and sometimes even make money out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 19:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's to say I'm fully in favour of suspension? I'm sharing an interesting video, there's an argument for innocent until proven guilty, though a precedent has been set with many other male athletes, so in the US at least she need suspending. There would be an alternative or reinstating others accused of domestic violence. My main concern is the blatantly sexist double standard rather than taking a stance on which of the two options would be correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 19:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes an argument in early June which exposed the true facts of the case and thus made an extremely compelling case for her suspension, nothing has changed since then has it? Obviously it's a little late now, but the fact is that every game Solo plays just compounds matters and arguably brings shame on the team, making it difficult for fans to get behind them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 19:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good argument there, really convincing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suspend Hope Solo Immediately </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's ongoing news. Every match she plays and ever game the USA win makes the story bigger and bigger and makes the problem worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that the USA have progressed to the final means we'll see this abuser representing her country on the biggest possible stage in her sport. The plus side to that is there should be even more attention in her case when it comes to court. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
