<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8318</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buzzfeed Users... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 09:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 01:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The raptor is running in slow motion at first and it speeds up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 03:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hehe this is rad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 04:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahahahaha this is GOLD! Using it right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 21:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> appreciate it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 21:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey thanks man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 22:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Mac,
why are you going to Tucson AZ instead of Tempe or Phoenix? We hate Tucson here. It's the asshole of Arizona. :(

also I made a shitty music video for Special K last night [:)](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iu-QZmMtY74)

blessed be you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 19:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's like Mountain Dew and Coffee Creamer put through some filters in Final Cut... haha I bullshitted so hard. But now that I have the idea I'm gonna try and put some more effort into it and make something cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just shot and edited a shitty psychedelic Special K music video. It was supposed to look like lava </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 06:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it just me, or is SNL Black Skinhead on here has soooooo much more energy than the original track? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 06:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you happy with the current state of society? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 03:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super dope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 11:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember back in the day on Rotten Tomatoes, it was at an 85%, which was pretty good. Now it's at 93%. Time has definitely been very good to Jurassic Park. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 11:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tyler the Creator, The Doors, Mac Demarco, David Bowie, Pink Floyd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 10:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. What, did he manage to see his Bernie Sanders button on his tiny phone screen from 15 feet away? Yeah, bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 14:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't techno so shitty? Even disco seems punk. The water's so filthy, it's no wonder why we're drunk.

Chinese Fountain by the Growlers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 08:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, this is my first time voting but I'll vote for him! I just hope it's not a lost cause. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 00:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna play devil's advocate here: I was pressured into going to college and it was actually extremely beneficial for me. I learned a lot about growing up and figuring out what my place in the world is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 00:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, and I also think they did it to set up the joke where Lowery goes in for the kiss. I felt the cringe in the theater as he went in for the kiss like Owen did and they played it off perfectly. Biggest laugh in the film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 00:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually have a younger cousin that behaves exactly like the youngest kid, believe it or not. I thought he was the most realistic character in the entire film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 05:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is his contract with Disney? He is the Tonight Show host on NBC, which is NBC Universal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 10:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha that's awesome. Makes me really miss Richard Attenborough to imagine that he could have been in this movie. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 10:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha but I mean *this* exact shirt that I posted. Literally that one. Idk if it's just sold in high volume where I'm from (Tempe, Arizona) or what. I am not lying when I said I counted 17 in one night. That isn't including other varieties of the classic logo shirt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILER] Jimmy Fallon's role.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 10:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is exactly like Richard Kiley's in Jurassic Park. "The voice you are now hearing is Richard Kiley! We Spared No Expense." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 10:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they were totally aware of that and the movie was being very self aware. That guy, Lowery, is basically the audience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 10:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I LOOOVED the new score, and I'm happy the Composer tried to do his own thing without relying *too* much on the original themes. Even though there was a ton of the original in this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 10:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nooo no no, that isn't a hybrid. That's a dimorphodon, a real thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Imagine how many people wore this exact shirt this week. I counted 17 people (including myself) at the premiere. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 08:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 09:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually funny, I actually like the fact that it's reverse because it makes it unique. I always thought it was weird that they did that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I compiled all the Jurassic Park things that were in my room. I'm so excited to see the sequel I've been waiting my entire life for! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 01:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
