<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7767</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spotify has some interesting default lyrics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 11:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 11:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thinking about this today when I saw the Fuze "Half Lemonade, Half Tea" dispenser at Subway.  I thought, isn't that an Allrnd Paaamler?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 10:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Derek Zoolander Center for Kids 

who can't read good



^and ^who ^wanna ^learn 

^to ^do ^other ^stuff ^good ^too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can track virtually everything and even control the car on the Jeep via the 3G network.  They say (about half way down the article) that the escalade and Q50 are similarly exposed.  

I'd disable Infiniti connect if you have it until they get a fix

EDIT: Infiniti's response quoted from the article. 

 When WIRED told Infiniti that at least one of Miller and Valaseks warnings had been borne out, the company responded in a statement that its engineers look forward to the findings of this [new] study and will continue to integrate security features into our vehicles to protect against cyberattacks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hackers that compromised newer Jeep Cherokees say the Q50 is 3rd most vulnerable car out there. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 11:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant user name? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 10:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the CEOs priority is making more money this 3 months than last 3 months, and they won't be there in 5 years, they won't care about no one being able to buy things then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sociopathic would be a better fit. "a person with a personality disorder manifesting itself in extreme antisocial attitudes and behavior and a lack of conscience." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was the point.  He played a sociopath.  No conscience, just do what you want to do.  

If you look closely, every time you see his bed at his apartment, it looks as if it's never been touched, only there for decoration.

He never sleeps.  He looks up stuff all day on the internet for things he's interested in, and then out all night looking for things to film. 

I thought it was pretty subtle and clever way of showing how abnormal he was beyond the actual character.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is about the same, except I run the Michelin Super Sports.

I'll get 30-40k miles on them and when I went to the track, I was able to get them so sticky that I was picking up chunks of rubber from other cars and they would be melted to the tire.  I was passing Porsche's, SRT8's, RX-8's and even a Z06.

Worth every penny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 06:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did that last year, but still paid near double for just one day.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 03:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "injury or disease/disability" -- they wouldn't choose this. Nobody chooses to be disabled.

 "Is it so strange to then consider those agreements as decisions made by two people, not just one?"   You work, I stay home.  We both agree to this.  However, it's implied that if we get divorced, your mutual agreement with this arrangement means that I won't have much in the way of making money on my own, so as long as I'm are ok with that. Deal.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 03:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand the argument when kids are involved, kids cost a retarded amount of money in child care otherwise.  

But I'm still talking strictly about divorces where you have to pay for your lay about spouse to do nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 03:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll seconds this.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give me three reasons that a person, without kids, would choose to stay home and "incur the risk of never being financially solvent again if I ever decide to leave you".

In today's world, there is no reason a person NEEDS to be a stay-at-home [whatever].  They choose to.  They can get a job like everyone else, or don't get divorced.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 01:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never mentioned kids were involved did I.  Just talking about the marriage in general.  I think someone might be projecting a little.   If you can't afford kids, don't have them.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 00:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure replacing it with [this](http://www.zspeedperformance.com/ZSpeed-HD-Concentric-Replacement-Clutch-Slave-Cylinder-CSC-zsp2006.htm) will be way cheaper than what I had to go through. 

This part was recommended to me by the guys at stillen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 00:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but then where would those people park? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 00:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had my slave cylinder fail taking with it the master cylinder, clutch, and flywheel. 

So now that that's all replaced with upgraded parts, the only issue I seem to have is if I go from 4th to 6th, it'll grind 1/2 the time.  So I just have to shift to 5th then 6th quickly.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 22:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was in command for 10 min and he saved thousands of lives including Kirks.  Guess Thor was just getting started </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 22:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bloodrayne? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 22:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait... There was a XIII-3? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 22:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Columbia university? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 22:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point of divorce is to break all ties to that person, not to continue to shell out money for decisions they were willing to accept. 

 If you can't support yourself, it's your own fault.  Gender equality and all that.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 22:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's too bad.  The coupe 6MT version is amazing.  It's quieter than stock while cruising and sounds awesome under acceleration </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 21:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, it was a ninja edit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 21:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While she was sleeping, he sang to her (teaching her how to sing subliminally) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 21:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Myy power ooover youuu, grows stroooger yeeeet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 21:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That voice which caaaalls to me, and speaks my naaaame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 21:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surge pricing is cheaper than no ride at all.  Faster too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 21:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Relevant CGP Grey video] (https://youtu.be/uqH_Y1TupoQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 21:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's part of divorce.  If you don't want to be with somebody, you shouldn't have to have any responsibility towards them.  It's bad enough that you usually have to split the assets.  That should be enough.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 21:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preach on brother </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 08:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more about the safety implements.  They have to add more things to keep you alive that weighs you down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 20:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I'd get [this](http://m.autotrader.com/cars-for-sale/vehicledetails.xhtml?listingId=378268313 featureCodes=1066 doorCodes=2 zip=91326 endYear=2016 pageLayout=list sortBy=distanceASC startYear=2008 listingTypes=used transmissionCodes=MAN searchRadius=200 maxPrice=19000 mmt=%5BINFIN%5BG37%5BG37%7CSport%5D%5D%5B%5D%5D) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 01:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is java different than JavaScript? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 00:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait... Every time I asked if I could get boards cut to length they said they don't do that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 21:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check the channel that your WiFi is on, especially the 5g.  It should be as low as you can make it on that one.

I've been having some WiFi issues too but I think it's my router than the phone.  I'll go to friends houses and the problems go away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 21:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? You don't know SQL?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 00:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nima - Tool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 00:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I remember right, this song has the most radio plays of all time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 00:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are lots of bio tech here, but there are just a lot more bio tech workers than permanent, stable jobs.  

The business seems to be leaning towards contract employers such as Lancaster that is basically a express personnel but for scientists.  They pay 40% less than the company you physically work at and that place doesn't have to worry about payroll, hr, etc.

The business is also cyclical where it goes well for a few years then lay offs galore.  

It's hard to plan things when you don't have a good sense of job security.

That's why after Amgen shut down, my wife is going into software development </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 16:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I'm one of them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 05:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm STILL looking for PAX Prime tix that are close to face value.  pfft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 05:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea what you are talking about.  My bed is AMAZING.  Granted I paid thousands for it, but it should be good for a decade or so.

Things you never skimp on in life:  Stuff that comes between you and the ground (bed, shoes, tires, camping gear, etc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 02:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scalping.

Fuck those guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 01:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also been reposted a few times all within a month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 00:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I figured.  In CA, AZ, TX, etc I'm sure there are plenty of good ones.

But If I'm in MN, ID, KS, etc you'll never really know what you are going to get  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 23:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Name recognition, good quality food, a bit more than McD but not restaurant prices.

Your little taqueria might be better, but I won't know a good one from a bad one just by looking at it.  With the chains, at least it's consistent every where you go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 23:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the company's principles.  It's their box, they can do what they want with it.  Besides, since this is supposed to be in the south, it's good marketing to your customer base.  Kind of like when politicians suddenly have a slight accent when speaking down there.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 08:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Magneto has been known to use the iron in your blood to his advantage.  

So yeah, he didn't need any visible metal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if you got a newer version of the same car that would be probably 10k more.  

However, if you drove your car until it breaks irreparably and invest that same 10k over that same time frame (I'd guess 5-10 more years at minimum) you would have a lot more money than you do now. 

Cars are very bad investments.  So it's up to you how you spend your money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 03:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, LotR wizards aren't the same as Harry Potter Wizards is what I'm saying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/YxgsxaFWWHQ

/u/mindofmetalandwheels explains it better than I could </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 00:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that was the point of the post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 00:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tankless water heater bro...I have to have a clock visible to know how long I've been in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While true, a head to head battle might lean toward Magneto.  

Think about the guiding aspect.  

Gandalf would know that he may face Magneto in some fashion in the future, as such, he could make it so that Magneto never existed in the first place by having the Nazi's kill him as a child before he even developed his powers.

Knowledge  powers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gandalf isn't just a run of the mill Wizard, he's a low level angel.  Hence why he can stand up and win against the Balrog (another low level angel)

Ethereal powers  mutant powers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently Christopher Lee didn't like that scene, so guess it didn't make the theatrical cut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 09:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> some phones will say H+ when it's actually H+.  not sure if this one does though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 05:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are exploiting the fact that poor people want to help other poor people more than rich people.  

So they say you can keep all this money free and clear or give a portion to this other poor family that might have it worse than you.  Then sit back and watch the drama with some clever editing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 05:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 05:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://youtu.be/QPKKQnijnsM

This has some references but it's a few years old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> poor people sympathize with other poor people more than rich people do.

Even THIS is being capitalized on. http://www.cbs.com/shows/the-briefcase/about/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ceo to AVERAGE pay (not lowest) is around 380x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 90 min of food puns and it's still great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 00:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [here you go](https://girlmeetsfreak.files.wordpress.com/2012/03/from-dusk-till-dawn-560-330.jpeg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 00:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [here you go](http://lmgtfy.com/?q=Wild+Wild+West+Official+Music+video) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 22:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked at a movie theater when these 2 were released.  We closed up on Thursday and then we screened both wild wild west THEN south park.  Left the theater around 6am still laughing our asses off and amazed at what we had just watched.

We went from a silly, almost stupid western (I enjoyed it, but it's just like...meh and this before steam punk was really even a thing) to the most brazen self parodied cartoon of all time.  We were fans of South Park, but we still weren't prepared for how over the top it was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 22:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/r0Iok7W.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 22:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1.5 MM (3/50^th of an inch) margin of error on that shot placement on the ball.  

That's some precision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 21:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to /u/ineedhelpoften 
If the rumors are true, I ACTUALLY respect Konami for shooting themselves in the foot.

Basically, Kojima violated workplace policy and fucked the model for The Quiet.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 05:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, all good pointers

* I've had people figure this out, but it's good to mention early
* I think I have a good handle on that
* This tends to happen naturally with this crowd (at least the ones I know.

* Yeah, this one I think will be the hardest part
* Might be good to do if it needs to be a shorter game.
* I think I'll start by having some of the more benign roles in there to get people aware of how this game works.

Does anyone know a list of premade roles for around that size of games outside the ones in the rule book?  I'd like some boiler plate setups and mod it from there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 24 player Ultimate Werewolf ideas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a group of people that want me to come in and moderate a few games of Werewolf on Wednesday.

I needs some cool ideas for game setup/roles/etc, and also tricks for moderating such a large group of people 1/2 of which I don't know.  I've only done 10-15 people at most.

I would assume table/seating arrangements are key to keep an eye on who people are indicating at night so I don't get it wrong.  Also folded paper with their names written on them so I can write  their roles down if I randomly hand out the cards.

Let me know what role make ups would be good. I would assume that we would have 2-3 games total since we only have a 2 hour window set up for a surprise gaming/birthday lunch for one of the people.

I'm assuming 1/2 of them haven't played before so I'll need a not-to-complicated game to start, then add in more interesting cards/factions in the later games.

Looking forward to the suggestions (or where to find them) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 22:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly right. Know what you want, know that you can get it, then JUST DO IT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 22:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only superstitious if it doesn't work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 21:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda.  As long as you know the pills will work, it usually will.

Attitude and perspective have healed people with seemingly terminal diagnosis and also killed those with survivable conditions.

Whether you think can or can't... You're right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 21:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two things:

1. The richest person isn't the one who has the most, but needs the least.


2. It's only silly if it doesn't work.  I follow a modified version of this thinking and it has worked for me.  

The key is to **KNOW** that everything's going to work out.  It may not happen exactly as you planned, but everything works out.

I found the absolute perfect wife after the worst girlfriend.  I just pictured my perfect person for me, made a theoretical checklist in my head, and I KNEW she was out there.  My friends all chuckled and said "good luck with that".  6 months later we met and she added things to that list that I didn't think were possible, all in a small city.  Married 18 months later, 2 years since and this entire time we've never even had an argument.

We needed to move but wanted to buy a house in the new location.  Lots of hoops and paperwork later, we miraculously qualified for a loan and had the down payment all saved up in 3 months.  The bank wouldn't use my main income.  It's the perfect house with everything we wanted, because we KNEW that we would get it. 

The job she got that made us move and buy the house was getting shut down next year, a week after we got the keys to said house.  We KNEW that this wasn't a big deal.  We explored several options over the next 6 months.  None of those panned out.  Then a friend said to check out this free, women only, year long computer programming boot camp.  They only take 24 people, but it's worth a shot.  I read the qualification requirements and KNEW she would get in.  They had 900 people look at the program, 500 applied, 60 interviewed, and she was one of the 24 that got in. The jobs that this camp trains you for starts at 50% more that what she was getting with her biochemistry degree.

There are tons more examples that I could give that this kind of thinking works for me.  All these that I've mentioned have been in the last 3 years.

This could be a really long string of luck, but I've always seemed to get what I want.  I just know that I'll get it and it'll work out, eventually.  As such, I'm perfectly happy all the time.  What's to be mad about when you know everything will work out?  It's like a lite version of [ataraxia](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ataraxia)

I'm not say that nothing bad ever happens.  Shitty things happen all the time.  I've gotten sick, been hospitalized, needed surgery on a few occasions, but I knew I was going to be fine.  The difference is your perspective.  If you have a good outlook, even in the worst scenarios, things tend to work out eventually.

You also have to be proactive in doing the things you need to do to get what you want.  You can't just lie in bed and think about having buckets of money.  You do have to actually go out there and get it.  I could think about winning the lottery all day long, but I'll never win if I don't go out and buy a ticket.

In the end this can all be scientifically disproven and I've just been getting lucky over a long string of time, but this is the closest I'll ever come to any form of religion/theology.  Just like all religion, you shouldn't knock it if it's working for those that follow it and aren't hurting anyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until they make a proper dual clutch sequential transmission for these cars, it'll always feel that way to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, even lower miles than mine. Manual or AT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 06:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my step brothers half brothers first app.  Not bad for not first app.  Thanks for checking it out though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 02:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to brush up on what your fallacies are.

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.knowctrl.knowfallacy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 00:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they have a 2nd line or alternate listed anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 19:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just go to the carrier store and have them look up the esn.  They can call the owner and tell them which store it's at </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 23:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This deal just keeps getting better all the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 20:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Master blaster? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 08:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never was into Pokemon...my brother in law recently took a high ranking finance job there, so I'm sure I can get all the poke things I would ever want, but still just...meh.  I was too old for it at the time.  But Final Fantasy 1, 5-15 are my jam

I got my brother one, and only one pack of booster cards back in the late 90's for his 10th birthday.  Apparently it had a "Charizard" in it...what ever that was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 08:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://puu.sh/iUXE4/d1b06a1338.jpg doesn't look like it. 

WHY WASN'T I NOTIFIED THAT THIS WAS HAPPENING!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 05:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depending on the places you are going, you can cache a section of the map in Google maps.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 03:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I found an amazon seller that sells the US versions for like $15-$20 more.  Still wont have a warranty, but it's better than double the price.

It's a real pain in the neck to sift through all the china dealers on Amazon and eBay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 00:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> one more thing on buying the cameras.

Everywhere I've looked, it's a bunch of asian stores selling on Amazon or eBay.

I've read that these guys sell "hacked" versions of the cameras with English menus.  You can tell by the instructions and packaging that it comes in.  There have been reports of these cameras having spyware or "phone home" abilities that compromises your network allowing people to get in that you don't want to.

Where do you get the official products in the US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, good info. Thanks.

Off to the internet to get parts and wiring in order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 21:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right on.

Thanks for all that.  One clarification though.

I have an older i7-920 that's overclocked that I don't really use much.  I'm sure that I can get this to be the dedicated NVR without issue.  What I'm wondering is can my main desktop that I use all day for work and gaming be used for the NVR without slowing it down.  It's a i7-4770k @4.4ghz with 16GB of ram, and 5+TB of storage available.

It'd be nice to just tab over to the security software and see the live feed when needed instead of going to the other computer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 08:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could say that Leeloo and the "darkness" were the hero and the villain.  They certainly never meet.

The rest of the characters are just helping one or the other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 08:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out on Blu-Ray finally if you haven't noticed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 05:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that is stronger yes.  Perhaps it's better for this application because it's shorter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be Peter Dinklage incognito at sdcc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's used in semiconductor industry.  There is all kinds of nasty stuff used there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teflon is carbon and fluorine bonded together, which is the single strongest bond in organic chemistry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with you on that.  Once autos (robot drivers) are commonplace, I hope getting a driver's licence is way harder and you have to demonstrate more than just basic vehicle operation and rules of the road.  That way the limits for humans would be raised or eliminated. 

Currently, just because you have a licence doesn't mean you know how to drive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm perfectly comfortable cruising at 100-110 or more in my car on a clear road.  I wish we had autobahn style interstates in the US.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure thing.  What cameras do you have?  How much space do you use?  Is it a spare computer or just part of your main desktop?  How well does the motion tracking alert work?  Any trouble getting remote viewing/playback to work while away from the house?

I don't get good WiFi signal on the outside of the house where I would want to put the cameras, so I'd have to invest in another WiFi extender.  Or I could just get a poe switch and try to run cat5 to the locations as well.  

Trying to weigh the cost vs convenience of both options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All but 10 years in the pnw.  To me, Redmond is a small town, but it's gotten a lot bigger in the 25 years of been around </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 07:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2BKdbxX1pDw

There are seperated dual laned roads that go right through town with on ramps and off ramps that are are 45mph in my home town. It's ridiculous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 07:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't you mean /u/GiantBatFart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 07:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> speed limits are far too low in far too many places,  both in UK and US </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
