<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6084</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 06:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are correct. I wish I could, but titles can't be edited. You are free to edit "emobsymbiotically" to "embosymbiotically" though, if you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slightly OT: How do you land the stunt jump from that ramp? I gave up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full study in Nature:

[Eye-like ocelloids are built from different endosymbiotically acquired components.](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v523/n7559/full/nature14593.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A rare single-celled sea organism has components that resemble an eye, including a "lens", "cornea" and "retina". A new study indicates that each of the components were acquired embosymbiotically from different sources. The creature could answer some long-standing questions on the evolution of eyes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 07:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize this isn't /r/science but I'm gonna put the peer-reviewed study here:

[Imitation Improves Language Comprehension](http://pss.sagepub.com/content/21/12/1903) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that to unintentionally mimic the accent of someone they are talking to, if they have a different accent, is a normal human trait. Psychologists believe it comes from an inbuilt urge to empathise and affiliate with the person you are talking to. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 05:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in the mid-1970s pranksters recorded a series of prank calls to a bar in Jersey City, asking for an "Al Coholic" or "Mike Hunt" etc. The recordings and the barman's responses became an underground hit, and may have inspired a running gag on The Simpsons. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 22:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that on Canusa Avenue in Beebe Plain, Vermont and Stanstead, Quebec, houses on one side of the street are in the USA and on the other in Canada. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 20:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 04:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the source:
 Serge Abrahamovitch Voronoff (Russian:   ; c. July 10, 1866  September 3, 1951) was a French surgeon of Russian extraction who gained fame for his technique of grafting monkey testicle tissue on to the testicles of men for purportedly therapeutic purposes while working in France in the 1920s and 1930s. 

(edit) and:

 By the early 1930s, over 500 men had been treated in France by his rejuvenation technique, and thousands more around the world, such as in a special clinic set up in Algiers.[15] Noteworthy people who had the surgery included Harold McCormick, chairman of the board of International Harvester Company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in the 1920's a French surgeon became famous for his practise of grafting monkey testicles on to male testicles. Hundreds, including the rich and famous, underwent the procedure for its supposed rejuvenating effects. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 04:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I choose to believe that about half way through, mother duck realized that those guys were helping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facial features: What women perceive as attractive and what men consider attractive. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 00:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's a handy map for that.](http://popvssoda.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL there is a mountain in Tibet that has never been climbed, despite several plans to do so. Locals say of Mt Kailash that a climber would have to "turn himself into a bird and fly to the summit." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 04:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 04:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post a study with its real title in a peer-reviewed journal and it will get *buried* on /r/science, it's just the way the world works.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 03:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, I don't see anything in common between the official [Rules of submission](https://www.reddit.com/r/science/wiki/rules#wiki_submission_rules) and what /u/nallen has written at the top of this post.

As an avid reader and frequent submitter to this sub I want to know what the rules are.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK so make the rules unambiguous then. It *still* says, in the post:

 linking to a page that contains a video is not allowed.

I'm not being pedantic on purpose, but rules are rules, let us know what they are, and we will follow them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 01:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry but this is simply false. Here is the text of the new rules:

 (since we don't allow videos, linking to a page that contains a video is not allowed.)

either you need to edit it or explain why we can't post links that contain videos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that mushrooms can create a slight breeze even when the air is calm. They release water vapour, cooling the air and creating a convective current that gets the air moving, carrying spores away from the parent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 01:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 22:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has always been like this. Or at least since I have been on /r/science. The top comments are always variations of these themes:

- "There is nothing new about this. This has been known for some time."

- "Correlation does not imply causation"

- "Sensationalized clickbait title"

Most of the meaningful discussion happens when you scroll down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree but sometimes a truly interesting study that belongs here is the meat behind a garbage title.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite a few headlines in science stories from the mainstream press would violate these rules. So if someone wants to post to /r/science they should adjust them accordingly, rather than use the same headline verbatim? (I agree with the notion, for the record.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 20:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the full study in Lancet Psychiatry:

[Does tobacco use cause psychosis? Systematic review and meta-analysis](http://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanpsy/article/PIIS2215-0366%2815%2900152-2/abstract) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Brazilian waxes originated in New York, not Brazil. Seven Brazilian sisters started to offer the service in 1987 from their salon in Manhattan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 20:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smoking may cause schizophrenia. It is well known that schizophrenics smoke at a greater rate than the general population, but a new study indicates that smoking may play a direct role in the development of the condition. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 19:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that it was once customary for Indian women to be burned alive on their husband's funeral pyre. A British general outlawed it, saying: This ... is your custom... But my nation has also a custom. When men burn women alive we hang them" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 08:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in addition to being fluent in English, Greek, Latin, French, Italian and Spanish, Thomas Jefferson also studied Arabic, Gaelic and Welsh, and remains the most multilingual President of the United States. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 05:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 05:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people like to quote this story as evidence that everything is determined by your DNA. It's a great story but whenever this comes up I'm reminded of the [Texas sharpshooter fallacy](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Texas_sharpshooter_fallacy).  Our genomes can predict what happens to us a lot, sure, but a lot of the other coincidences about names etc. came by chance. Indeed, the new field of epigenetics shows that DNA is *not* necessarily your destiny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 20:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is his name Dale Cooper? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 08:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scottish:

 Was a ginger. And a cunt. I didn't like him.

Australian:

"He was a ranga and my best mate."

Just to clear that up. (edit: formatting)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Nelson Rockefeller, once vice President of the United States, died at age 79. of a heart attack rumoured to be caused during sex with his assistant. The New York Magazine quipped: "Nelson thought he was coming, but he was going" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 05:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Hungry yet?](https://www.google.ca/search?q=deep+fried+haggis client=ubuntu hs=SaI channel=fs tbm=isch tbo=u source=univ sa=X ei=zYadVf7ADMvDggTVpL6QCg ved=0CB0QsAQ biw=1630 bih=905) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Irn-Bru, on the other hand, [was once prohibited by the FDA.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Irn-Bru#United_States) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 21:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he switched to soccer at least his diving skills would have come in handy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 20:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> St Louis is getting hammered! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 20:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  http://map.norsecorp.com/

That site is mesmerizing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The paper is [here.](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.1002195)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Genomics will soon produce exabytes of data a year, surpassing the data storage needs of astronomy, Twitter and YouTube, and posing challenges for computing infrastructure. A exabyte is a billion gigabytes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 09:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all. I'm quite sure all of these things were taken into account, that's what a study like this does. It would not be accepted in such a journal as PNAS without doing so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 07:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 90's were best 's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 06:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shh, don't say that, the mods are strict here and this is a great post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that a 2008 poll of 250 children for a report on hospital design found that clowns were universally "frightening and unknowable". It was recommended that clown images were not used in waiting rooms, etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 06:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 05:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad someone else noticed this, I can't think of any other explanation. If anyone is interested I posted about it elsewhere ITT but it was downvoted. It is [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/science/comments/3ccozd/women_have_not_always_lived_longer_than_men_the/csuh6e1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 05:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a lot of nonsense in this thread about maternal mortality and war, but if you read [the authors' own abstract](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2015/07/01/1421942112), it's very interesting that they seem to attribute the "mortality gap" to a reduction in infectious disease death rates. We all know that antibiotics have had a profound affect on health:

 The remaining excess male mortality may be explained by underlying traits of vulnerability to cardiovascular disease that emerged with the reduction of infections and changes in diet and other lifestyle factors. 

In other words, infectious diseases killed men and women equally prior to the 20th century, but since then, people lived long enough for the lifestyle factors of men relative to women to make a difference in mortality rates in middle age and beyond. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like there may well be some indication of what you are talking about in this study's data. The first figure in OP's article (not the one with the US soccer team) shows a strange outlier of more men than women people dying in their early 40s, say 40 to 45, who were born from 1860 to 1879, compared to the other age cohorts. It's the dark blue part of the graph, and stands out quite a bit.

People who were born from 1860 to 1879 were 40 to 45 from 1900 to 1924. i.e. a large proportion of them were those ages during World War I. Given that we know WWI was catastrophically deadly, and that men were presumably fighting at or over age 40, *and* that this study used data from people in developed countries, I would not be surprised if that dark blue outlier in the chart is an artifact of World War I.

It may be addressed in actual paper, but I don't have access to it right now (paywalled). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 02:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Sigh*

Look at the figure in this write-up of the paper - access to the paper itself isn't needed, it is paywalled. The values on the y axis are the male-to-female mortality rate ratios amongst various cohorts for deaths from age 60 to 90 **at those ages**.

Let's take the age 60 for example, as the text does. It clearly shows that a greater ratio of men to women die **at age 60** for those born from 1900-1935 (red and pale blue) than those born from 1800-1839 (grey and black).

This data has nothing to do with life expectancies **at birth**, which I agree, would be skewed by maternal mortality rates.

Edit: Because a demonstrably false post reply is still number one here. Go to the comments of /u/Snoozeybutton or /u/grewapair for more informative comments, guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 21:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's coming back in the next Mass Effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Seinfeld re-runs are sped up relative to their original versions in order to accommodate more time for commercials. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 21:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the Spice Girls' "Wannabe" is the catchiest pop song in the UK since the 1940s, according to a study. People recognised that song the quickest. Second in the study was "Mambo No 5" by Lou Bega. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 11:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 16:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also notable from that table:

- 3 shots fired by police in England and Wales in 2012-2013
- 2212 people killed by police in Brazil in 2013

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in ancient Rome, one of the most common cooking ingredients was called "laser", from the silphium plant. It does not exist today: it was so delicious that it was harvested to extinction from its natural habitat in what is now Libya. We think that it probably tasted something like garlic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 08:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that butchers in Australia have a secret language called "Rechtub klat", in which words are spoken backwards. (i.e. "Rechtub klat" = "Butcher talk") It is mostly used so that they can comment on customers without them knowing about it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 05:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in 19th century England, a man by the name of Jack Black was an expert rat catcher. When he caught rats of unusual colour, he would breed them and sell the well bred rats to nobility. Even the Queen kept a pet rat or two. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 05:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 22:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Sneak 90] Bypass rule 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 17:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is currently the most read story on all of the BBC News website. Says so on the right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 20:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP scientist's family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists discover the deepest cave-dwelling centipede. The Hades centipede, named after the Greek god of the underworld, lives as far as 1,100 meters below the surface. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it can happen with Twin Peaks it can certainly happen with Star Trek. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google searches for the term "housing bubble" in the US and Australia over time, compared. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 21:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that a cat named Simon served on a Royal Navy ship in 1949, and received a medal for raising morale, killing off a rat infestation and surviving cannon shells during his service. Hundreds attended his funeral when he died from infected wounds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 18:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Monsanto once tried to genetically engineer blue cotton, to produce denim without the use of dyes, reducing the pollution involved in the dyeing process. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 01:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 21:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's up with [this out of place frame in the gif](http://i.imgur.com/yfwWkpL.png)? Subliminal message in the post-it note? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superfast lasers create a hologram you can touch, feeling "like sandpaper". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 03:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Farmers don't need to drive to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that during WWII, the Gestapo's most wanted person was New Zealand born Allied agent Nancy Wake. Among her numerous exploits, she killed an SS soldier with her bare hands, to prevent him from raising the alarm during an undercover raid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Racehorses are continuing to get faster, a new study indicates, in a surprise to those in the racing industry who believe that racehorse speed has reached its limit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 10:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the child's game "Simon Says" is played throughout the world, often with the original "Simon" but also "The King commands" in, for example Norwegian or Portuguese, or "Ship Captain's orders" in Japanese. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 04:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 18:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cricketers are taught this technique from a very early age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that there was an exhibit of paintings done by a chimpanzee in Paris in 1964. However, people were told they were by a real human artist called "Pierre Brassau". The exhibit was critically acclaimed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 07:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 04:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I thought too. And if you're in another galaxy, why not some Johnny Cash to make you feel at home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Manhattan's Central Park contains almost 170,000 different kinds of microbes - a diversity similar to that of wild environments around the world. Also, apparently 2000 of them are unique to Central Park. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 05:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 22:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  long **after** the events of the original trilogy

This is actually slightly surprising, in a good way. I thought it would be a sidequel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 21:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK but what about the Trivago Guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The full genome of a bacterium has been sequenced with a USB-powered sequencer that can fit in the palm of your hand. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 10:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is the paper they are talking about](http://www.sciencemag.org/content/early/2015/06/10/science.aaa2657.abstract), there was no link in the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newbie question: To get into the lore, should people play the earlier games, or can they jump right into Witcher 3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 08:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title says it all really, I've never played any of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the distress calls of baby mammals share elements across species: a study in the Canadian prairies showed that mother deers rushed towards recorded cries not only of infant deers, but also those of fur seals, dogs, cats and humans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 05:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 04:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  researchers tested the testosterone levels of the indigenous Tsimane people in central Bolivia before and after they cut down trees. Their results showed a 46.8 percent increase in testosterone levels following the wood cutting, a full 17 percent higher than the testosterone bump caused by playing soccer.

This is a fascinating study for sure, and no offence to the Tsimane people, but it would be really interesting if the results also apply to people in the developed world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 01:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found this on twitter:

https://twitter.com/sluggahjells/status/609489420769738753?lang=en </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A pickup truck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Computer scientists are training robots by making them play Minecraft. Robots trained with Minecraft then perform better at a real world task: helping people make brownies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 20:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malaysian mountain stripping: 2 Canadians, 2 others get prison time served, to be deported. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
