<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5580</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> i recently saw ant-man and this is what the fight scenes reminded me of </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 13:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/YfchQpxeGyo

yeah go ahead and laugh, also before anyone breaks out the attacks, i'd like to point out i enjoyed ant-man, it was very charming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what movie made you aware of chris pine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for me it was star trek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 05:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whats wrong with my train_subject5580 viewing order

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 05:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whats wrong with my train_subject5580 viewing order </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> presenting the train_subject5580 viewing order! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 01:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 06:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> take them to the theater </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 09:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> every star wars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You underestimate my power! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you mean? And btw our flair is relevant to each other </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [META] I want episode VII to feel unique, and original </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 08:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so if this is a tv movie, technically it shouldnt even be on r/movies, it should be on r/television </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Idea on how to make a fourth trilogy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 03:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start with episode XIII and make XIV, and XV, so that way makers of a fifth trilogy will have the challenge of making episode X-XII, think about it, george Lucas had a blank slate for the prequel trilogy, he just had to make the ending tie into the beginning of the original trilogy, what I'm saying here is to link together both a hypothetical episode X to a hypothetical episode XIII </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> star wars related shower thought- what does a drought on kamino look like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 10:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDIT: that is, what does it look like with no rain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> is star trek V: the final frontier canon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 09:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just wondering </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 07:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they might be on to something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some other poster asked if episode 7 will have wipe transitions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 05:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> i notice in movie prequels theres always more of something </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 07:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for example

in the star wars prequel trilogy theres more lightsabers

in the flintstones in viva rock vegas theres more of those shells they use for currency

and in monsters university theres more of those scream canisters

anyone think theres a connection, or am i just mental? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 11:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> deleted scenes you say? the same person who deleted all referances to lasagna probably deleted that one scene from episode 3 where yoda starts his exile to dagobah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> is there lasagna in star wars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 11:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think IT is known as a "mummy dressed as snow white" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what do you mean "too much"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ''just like'' isnt something to judge someones opinion over, if you read professional critic reviews, clearly they enjoy them, also think about the insults the cast gets everyday, chris pine getting called wooden, zach quinto getting called homophobic slurs, and zoe saldana getting called a slut. you can not stop me from enjoying them dont even try!!! you can respond back to me but dont talk me out of not enjoying them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i just like the cinematography, tthe cast and i like the sense of wonder, so unlike you im able to enjoy a movie, i dare you to top that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 00:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i like it for every reason it gets criticised, so my review would be the polar opposite of a haters review </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 00:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm saying that they did </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> when episode 7 comes out, will the saga films be released on individual blu rays? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 13:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im only asking because im hoping that disney doesnt change the movies any further. and if they do they should put in that new fanfare for the lucasfilm logo. but keep the movies otherwise the same as the blu rays that came before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 11:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you know its funny, i tell people that the reboot cast gets persecuted everyday, implying they should sympathize with them. im worried that zach quinto gets called homophobic slurs, and zoe saldana gets called sexist things like 'slut' and 'whore'. and chris pine gets called names im sure but i dont know what </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 10:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im not going to even bother anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 09:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> har har har, lensflare joke, you mustve spent alot of time coming up with that, you should audition for SNL, youll be the next eddie murphy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> this is why im overprotective about the jj abrams star trek movies x-post from r/movies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 09:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> this is why im overprotective of the star trek reboots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 08:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ever since i saw this snl skit back in 2009, i was freaking phsyched to see the new reboot, and then this snl skit came and shat on my excitement:

http://www.traileraddict.com/star-trek-xi/snl-weekend-update

now after i actually saw the movie, ive been saying to reboot haters that i hate them, i wish they were all dead etc. etc. but now im thinking its not worth it, ill never convince the haters to stop hating the star trek reboots, i am literally sobbing at my defeat! ive told haters about the rave reviews, jj abrams charity work, NOTHING, they still hate the reboots. every attempt ive made to convert the haters FAILED!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> is it ok if i like the jj abrams star trek movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 08:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you know the drill, im sick of hearing the criticisms, yada yada yada </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 08:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also jj no being a fan has nothing to do with the quality of the movie, i dont care that he likes star wars more, i am trying to keep reboot haters like you persecuting us reboot fans! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 08:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this proves my point that reboot haters will never change, i bet you and your wife will conceive a reboot haterling, and raise him to be a hater just like you,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 08:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> obviously you dont read **professional** critic reviews, and clearly the majority of **PROFESSIONAL** CRITICS, enjoy it, and seeing as youre not a professional critic yourself your criticism means nothing to me, ill continue to enjoy it along with other fans, and you can do nothing to stop us, i speak for reboot fans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> whats the use getting excited about star trek beyond? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 07:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all the reboot haters will hate it regardless if a fan writes it or not. ever since 2009 ive been telling the haters that it was good and i like it, and ive been seen as a bully, they should be kissing their asses!!! they saved their franchise!!!! i swear to god if i hear ONE MORE TIME that it doesnt follow gene roddenberrys utopian vision of the future i will scream and commit suicide!! thats right i hate reboot star trek criticism THAT much. they will probably never change!!! theyll marry other rboot haters, have children and raise them to hate the reboots then we'll have anothergeneration of reboot haters!! ITS FUCKING BULLSHIT!!!!! i just wnt people to be grateful, but nooo the reboot haters are too busy wishing they couldve sucked leonard nimoys geriatric cock before he died. i hate star trek reboot haters, hate them hate them HATE THEM, i hate the parents who birthed them and the children theyll raise!!! i would read trekkers reviews but i prefer going to professional critics (you know people who go to movies nearly daily) oh god if all reboot haters died of cancer that would be so awesome. i mean look at this video! and youll see who REALLY doesnt get star trek (hint:it isnt jj abrams or bob orci)

https://youtu.be/YRWUeUK6kKQ

there! now you see that jj has a heart, which is an alien concept to reboot haters. im sick of hearing criticism about the writing, im sick of hearing criticism about the cast, im sick of criticism of jj abrams!!!! so bottom line if you dont like it, why didnt they come to YOU to make it, so fuck all reboot haters to damnation of mankind!! i like the reboots DEAL WITH IT!!! i liked the stories, i liked the new look, and i liked the cast. oh god that would be so awesome if star trek reboot criticism was outlawed and made illegal. i would be so happy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 07:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same here,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 06:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh god that singer, after that barney the dinosaur one that was it for me, ive seen enough. and then the catdog video comes around, and im like "holy fuck, no! they didnt," it was one of my favorite cartoons of all time, and that inspired me to make this post, to check to see if my fears were confirmed, and since they are i havnt a reason to watch it, i have a feeling there will be a day, like i swore to myself that id never see the human centipede (the first one) and low and behold me and my parents watched it together. ill never see the next two human centipede movies, just like ill never watch the scientifically accurate catdog video (i hope) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 02:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats one of my favorite anime episodes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 11:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> uuuuhhhh yeah im not watching this video then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 10:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what does "technically yes" mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 23:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this not a fun time for train_subject5580 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about powerline from goofy movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 13:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does powerline have Marfan syndrome? Because he lacks meat on those bones, and he's unusually taller than most other characters in the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 14:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a bummer, he was a good actor too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what movie made you aware of natalie portman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 07:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for me it was star wars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 02:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> man, i SERIOUSLY need to check legends more often </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what other sports are there in star wars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 02:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> besides podracing, i know in episode 2 when obi-wan ran into that 'sports cantina' i guess ill call it. there were sports playing on the screens, i just never learned the names of said televised sports, and i would love to know their names </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 06:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> darth maul looks good with his beard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 12:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i just got served </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
