<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6818</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used although accounts to upvote his posts.  This exposed him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/mylifesuxnow  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am at a level of overwhelming stress and need help. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am just at a point that I feel like I am losing my grip with alot of things.  They are from financial to superficial all the way to losing family. I don't know where to look other than resting in my mindfulness and meditation.  Is there any advice or reading I should do to strengthen my resolve?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite quote from Forest Gump? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this movie and love the "Lt.  Dan...  Ice cream!"  part. What's your favorite quote?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Non-redditors of reddit, Why do you not reddit and how much of that sweet karma do you have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya..  We are just looking for a faster pace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a side note...  We have the best Kings roster in 10 years! Kings fiends get ready!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE feel like we now need to start shaving some players? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that we are officially done signing, I feel like we brought alot of players. How does our depth chart look?  Lineups and play time?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is ridiculous....  No Hollins,  no ship.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His legs are getting old..  So he relies more on skill and ball IQ. Slows down the game and makes intelligent passes. Having a backup passer is better than a mediocre scorer. Add in vet experience and personal relationship with the coach... Better option IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed.  Unless Seth surprises the world...  Andre miller was my choice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 01:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because we can change it...  Duh!  We did it reddit!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those who taught English abroad, what were the pros and cons? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 23:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't unfortunately  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 20:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The package should be released today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Financial aid for transfers due today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 19:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talked to the FA Office and they told me that transfers are expected to be released today.  Just an FYI.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about a government funded start up.  Maybe even funded by the UN? Have the facility guarded by Un patrol who most of the time isn't really active.  

ROI is less resources used on wars, diseases and fighting poverty as well as maybe having the economy grow and eventually adopting the dollar? 

I might be reaching a little bit.  I'm thinking more of a humanities effort than a business model.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would it be cheaper to build facilities in Africa to manufacture these food options and be more productive than it is to send what we already are doing?  Let's say 50 years down the road?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it's better to proceed at our rate of "technological evolution"  and maybe be wrong that global warming doesn't exist than it is to  not "technologically evolve"  and be wrong that it does exist?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point.  I guess the prices to manufacture would go up due to transportation. Would it be possible to create government run farms out there? Would it be cheaper in the long run to run facilities over there to provide food than it would be to transport food?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Understood but it is for the general public here. We know markups are ridiculous for fast food companies. What is the cost to manufacture food products like this? Is 10 cheap?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can McDonald's manufacturer and sell food for a dollar but we are struggling with starvation in countries like Africa? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Global warming and why some don't believe it exists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea...  That's kinda how prefixes work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to /r/mylifesuxnow  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 22:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was edited.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 19:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The song ruined your dad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While inhaling the fumes!?  Why not eat that lead based paint while you're at it!  Just sit under this table with your eyes closed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Understood.  Most venues will have a camera stand dead center to film the concert.  That's always my go to. 

PSA: please don't be those people who literally make it a mission to push through crowds.  If you left your friends...  You lost your spot.  Be considerate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 15:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Decent idea if people didn't snatch phones at festivals...  Especially while hiding it as high  as possible. 

Find a landmark and converge.  Don't leave unless you expect it to be difficult.  It says message them. Why don't I just message them and tell them to meet me somewhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I built a time machine today... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coop becomes a Barber... Commence with mass suicide please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downvotes because ops a racist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 04:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel for the women..  They were like WTF is he doing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 04:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kings...  You're welcome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dank meme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 02:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/nba where down voting happens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 11:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I could do that but there would be a lot of dead bodies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone post the link to the GOAT Sim shattering the backboard at the pan am? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 05:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: Breast cancer kills over 420 people a minute. Let's evaluate those killers that you have. PM me pics for your annual screening. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 04:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 04:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But a stick bundle nonetheless  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 04:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toggaf a si PO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 03:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a bad area.  Real bad. Not as bad as MLK but I would advise looking almost anywhere else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 03:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 00:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck...  My penis is so conflicted between stupidity and hotness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 23:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure these are the guys who puck the Bucks bottom 3 last year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no reason why someone approaching 7'0" should move like this.  I swear he was a PG in a previous life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great shirt to clean the garage with </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 19:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 19:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Siberia...  It is actually advised and encouraged  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 10:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sheep farmers are lining up all over for this new life changing invention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who do you think is responsible for the JFK assassination?

What are your feelings on government intervention on the global warming crisis? 

Pepsi or Coke? 

How much would could a woodchuck chuck? 

Chicken or the egg? 

Stay-cation or vacation? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess so.  I'll think it over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who upset you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fasho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol just a question Bro relax.  Just a funny question that came to mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 08:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol this guy's always out of pocket hahaha I'll still give him my upvote  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 02:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off...  10 million for a veteran 4x all star and championship with the cap raising? Not a bad deal.  Some people wanted Lee..  And Matthews. 

Rondo has an ego.  It sucks but it's true.  He looks semi humbled with what happened.  If you listen to Rondo talk about his contract,  it was the Kings decision for 1 year.  He was asked to prove himself.  He has a chip on his shoulders.  His risk is no different than Rudy's risk. I can gamble that. 

Acl tears suck. Will Rondo be *rondo* again...  Idk.  He is one of the best passers in the league.  He hasn't been paired with great teams. Mavs were a horrible match up and Celtics damn near had no one. He has multiple shooters now, dominant front court,  killer backup pg and a great coach. 

Remember how sacramento is.  We are a small market team so we are forced with rookie talent who just wanna play for a team and fading veteran talent who...  Just wanna play on a team.  Remember CWebb talked shit about sac when he was coming here. He still says the greatest experience of his career. Rudy same. Ron Artest even praised sac.  We land spurned vets who have been trashed and we build them up when vulnerable and they stay for the long hall.  We kill them with kindness while others buy their teams. 

Check my post history...  I was against it.  No one here has changed my opinion on him.  Only Rondo did. I believe we will see a great Rondo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 02:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big role.  Koufos would be 2nd string.  Rudy wouldn't play 4 he'd stay 3 or Smith runs 3. Either way he was looking at significant minutes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 00:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Appeal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do athletes spank each other? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 00:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: I see alot have fallen onto the camaraderie explanation. Unfortunately, I feel unsatisfied. Why not just pats on the back?  Why not aggressively shake and rub another's head? 

I played multiple sports but I never found the need to slap anyone's ass or felt that my morale or my teams went down as a result of a lack of ass slapping. 

What are the origins?  Who first smacked their teammates ass? What have been the results of teams smacking and not smacking but instead showing another form of team chemistry?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 00:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had to have...  Bigger role + more work + rebuild = no

Smaller role + less work + championship = yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 00:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? We probably went for Luc because Smith already said no.  Clips were in the running since the beginning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 00:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard Chandler parsons is still at DeAndres house </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 21:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha how does Tim Duncan pass lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 21:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hipsters don't call themselves hipsters...  Found the phony  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a word or phrase that you would use not actually knowing entirely what it meant? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 08:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just hiked hidden falls in Auburn.  Last week I did twin bridges. Good places and well worth it
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just do it, worse case you get in, best case you do. Honestly just send the letter there is literally no reason to not. I would stop thinking it and just do it and see how the dice rolls. Also I understand because my school did something similar and I had to drive it up. Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 48 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ty ladies a fucking fool.  We will sign him in 3 years when he decides to try his rebuild and we bench his ass for vet min.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny...  Christians don't care now either... As a matter of fact it's allowed in the Bible now according to them.  God says it's okay. "well doesn't it for a fact say against this?"  


"No...  We interpreted it wrong the first time... "

Clowns.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 00:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd hate to be Vlade with those legs haha...  They have to be annoying to sit down with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 22:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was joking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 17:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Internet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 17:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea...  I think Karl and Cousins handshake wasn't the best </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 17:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dodged a bullet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 09:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WOAH! That was fucking rid....  Never mind I just came
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 09:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Catch ya later alligator </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 09:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better than the sacramento shorts... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 08:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's something unofficial...  He's all over to not be helping Vlade..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 08:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dead for three days...  WTF are you talking about....?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 08:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what is Peja to the Kings FO? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 08:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has been spotted numerous times recently and I kinda blow it off. Now Belinelli mentioned that he "Knew Peja from NO" when asked about Vlade. I know Vlade and Peja are good friends and now that Vlade is leading the game...  What's Pejas official role? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 07:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough...  Upvote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Source]  "Rondo on first name basis with coach. Possible new team buy out.  Cousins okay with this. Rudy's Gay." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 03:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dave and busters.  4.6 star elegant dinner.  Make sure you dress up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 03:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah tyson crandler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 03:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You come up with the craziest shit lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 03:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have some nuts for you...  It is OK to trust me ^^^^^^^catchyalateralligator  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop attacking please  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Father's of Reddit, how many of you have virgin daughters? Daughters of Reddit, where does your dad live? (NSFL) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: ayyy

Edit9: lmao

Edit12: the 4 the Dank gild. 

Edit2: am gril btw :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck *THIS* GUY!!!!  /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 21:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their name is the Lakers...  California is in a drought and they are the Lakers...  Guess it represents the roster appropriately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep my philosophy...  I believe every year we will win a championship...  I figure I have to be right eventually...  Right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh...  I'd rather be delusional </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We dont have an overpaid aging superstar who clearly cares about only money. The Buss's are just as dysfunctional as our FO. Still find it funny that I called that the Lakers would fall in draft as well. 

Remember that we are losers for wanting Rondo* but when Kobe was eating lunch with Rondo last year...  He was the best available point guard?  It was the same when we were getting Deron Williams. Shitty guard and a wash up has-been...  Mavs get him and he's a hero haha.  Laker are shitty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly this. Building a billion dollar stadium is worthless if you don't have a team that plays well. I could make his argument by showing the Barclay center.  From what I heard, it didn't really change much.  Put a stadium in a small city with a winning crowd and people pay. 

I love grabbing a drink and talking about the game...  But where do I go besides Petes after Arco? Mels? 

This will be nothing but good for a city, who in all honesty, doesn't really have much other than the capital. 


Billion dollar stadium with shitty team = Bad

Billion dollar arena with great team = great 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 19:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We destroyed an eye sore of a mall that was rivaled in attendance to the country club mall... Eradicated a place where homeless people loitered and didn't really do much.  Building a new arena will attract so many more businesses and advertisement downtown.  It will create jobs.  It secures a team being here and with a possible hockey team coming..  

It creates an environment that says "We wanna win".  Our skyline needs to develop and this may be a necessary piece to luring investors. Gridlock will suck but like anything...  We will make it work. I cant forsee anything to bad about this besides what may happen to Natomas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 19:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shhhh it's no talks no more...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 19:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a reminder for the upcoming season... We are gonna make a run while the Lakers still rebuild. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 19:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 19:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 19:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair...  Vlade had alot of cap room and a decent FA pool  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 17:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Malone was found to be one of the refs from 2002 western conference finals.  Since on the resume he said he was honest and had integrity...  We realized he lied.  When Vivek brought in Vlade to negotiate bringing him on, he recognized him as one of the refs.  He had ptsd and canned his ass.  Fuck the Lakers.  I enjoyed you guys having Jeremy Lin. Steve Nash look great too.  So did Chris Paul.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 17:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a GM (though I'm sure I act like I am...  Sorry guys) and I don't know what their job demands...  But I personally feel that Pete made it look as if he has no idea WTF he was doing. Only thing good he did IMO was Gay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 09:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Story of your mom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 08:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh. Life g'oes,  o%n!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 08:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I did.  I learned something by making a bad joke.  That is what Reddit is for.  A community helping each other grow through chiding and mockery.  You helped me grow!  Thanks much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 08:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might just be stoopid. Fuck it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 08:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have the letter N...  You forgot to add one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 08:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're full of crap. Shitty story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 08:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your mom's old but I definitely wouldn't call it a sock...  More like a fishes mouth...  Including the smell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 08:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBD is just your run of the mill mid size festival. Far from Coachella but is definitely a crazy experience from a regular concert as in overall experience. 

As for it being your first festival,  I'll warn you that festivals IMO are like giant testing trays so you can sample alot of music.  Because they aren't solo concerts,  you lose alot of experience with a said band.  My rule is that if you like them at a festival,  you have to see them in a touring concert.  Different experiences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 07:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I've done this alot recently ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 05:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 04:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This shows how shitty ESPN is as a source </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone who plays reggae breakdown this song for me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 21:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 19:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dudes an ass hole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How do Festivals like Cali Roots and Coachella get away with public pot smoking? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 07:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 05:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 04:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh go down south and you will see cold...  It's weird here,  some people are super friendly and others aren't. But I would say alot tend to their own business and don't necessarily include others. See people post all the time about finding friends do. Depends on what shit you like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 04:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea...  It's tmobile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 04:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good pickup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 04:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that we are signing  Bar. I'd rather Rondo starting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You ever overhear the neighbors talking about the block party but have no idea what they are talking about...?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet your home owners association meeting are a fucking hoot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sunflower in fair oaks will be her main stay vegan eats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 20:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just Google cuckold...  You're a bitch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 09:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well fuck...  That was lackluster at best </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 09:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I get that... So what's the joke?  IS THAT THE JOKE!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 09:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What am I missing..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 09:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wutm8?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 09:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you had to have been there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 09:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or because it's summer and hot...  And I drink it to cool and regulate body temperature </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 09:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soooo....  Heard ya wanted to earn some monies...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 09:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait...  What?  We cook our food...  That's why sometimes it's hot. I would say temperate and geographical location is huge in this.  I like iced water in the summer but like cocoa in the winter.  I would say there are equal amount of hot beverages as cold...  Generally same as food.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 09:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They show them by floor level </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 09:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easily the shittiest shark costumes around </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 09:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate it when you take off a girls panties and they smell like *Autumn Harvest* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 08:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huehuehue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 08:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 08:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8===D 0: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
