<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7865</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Websites can now block users based on genetic traits such as sex, ethnicity or susceptibility to disease </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Two Bored 1970s Housewives Helped Create The PC Industry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Quest to Get Every NES Game in 30 DaysWithout the Web </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple grows its electric car team but still wont admit the project is real </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grit in the Google machine: why technology needs the friction of politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As US relations thaw, hopes grow in Cuba for a faster, freer internet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 10:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given he's the first with this specific condition to receive the treatment, his age may have actually been a factor in why he was chosen - if something goes wrong, he has a much shorter time to live with the consequences that someone younger. It's not like he's the only person who will ever get this treatment! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit time machine: See what was on the front page when you joined </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DIY Surgery: The Future Of Medicine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 23:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see what you mean, but I'm not sure people often get the chance to see others' handwriting often. Apart from the occasional shopping list I'm not sure anyone has seen mine in a long time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 19:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Writing in cursive is an important life skill  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Service robots get multiple positive forecasts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 13:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VRs First Big Hit Could Be This Simple Soccer Game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 22:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you considered contacting [Watchdog](https://ssl.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b006mg74/contact)? Might involve a TV appearance but could do the trick  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Despite new information, Pluto will remain a dwarf planet, cosmologist says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deus Ex would be perfect for virtual reality: Mankind Divided executive game director </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deus Ex would be perfect for virtual reality: Mankind Divided executive game director </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Virtual Reality is the Future of Religion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Pill Will Let People With Celiac Disease Eat Gluten-Filled Meals Of Their Dreams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hoverbike could be a reality in three to five years, creators say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The mysterious way your body changes with the weather </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers show new Ice Age may begin by 2030 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hitchhiking robot embarking on coast-to-coast tour across US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ReWalk Robotics's New Exoskeleton Lets Paraplegic Stroll the Streets of NYC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The paradox of the under-performing professor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Lib Dems is now led by a Harry Enfield lookalike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 22:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There was a double grape in the snack pack I bought for lunch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 11:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oddly with WSJ articles, if you access them via Google they aren't paywalled.

Here you go:

Technology Will Speed You Through the Airport of the Future

Car-parking robots, tracking beacons and facial recognition systems aim to make travel relaxing

Like a good matre d, the airport of the future will recognize you, greet you by name and know exactly where to put you.

Airports around the world are beginning to move in this direction. At Londons Gatwick Airport, beacons identify you by your smartphone and give GPS-like directions to your gate, pointing out food or shopping along the way. In Germany, robots at Dsseldorfs airport park your car and return it curbside after you land, linking your itinerary to your license plate. Researchers are developing robots that will be able to check your bags and deliver them within minutes of landing.

Facial-recognition systems speed you through passport control in places including Dulles International Airport near Washington, D.C. Some airports use facial-recognition systems to track your movements around terminals. Gates in some airports are automated with doors that flash open like a subway turnstile when you scan your boarding pass or flash your smartwatch.

At the airport of the future, directional signs will be only for backup. Check-in kiosks will be tucked in a corner. Human agents may be even more unnecessary.

The idea is to cut costs, speed up travel and make airports more hospitable. In theory, travelers will be more relaxed, with time to get work done, shop or enjoy entertainment since the airport will track their time and location and tell them where they need to be. Travelers may fret less about sitting down at a nice restaurant when a flight is delayed, rather than camping at the gate.

The airport becomes fun again, says Terry Hartmann, vice president of transportation and industry applications for Unisys Corp., which makes the technology for some of the new airport features. You feel you know whats going on, you interact with the environment and travel is an enjoyable experience.

Of course, planes will still have cramped seats and airlines will still run habitually late. But flyers wont need to arrive 90 minutes early if they know lines and walks are short. Travelers worried about the airport being too invasive can opt out by turning off their Bluetooth connections.

In June, Unisys announced completion of the initial testing phase of a facial-recognition system at Dulles to help U.S. Customs and Border Protection identify imposters attempting to enter the country. New passports have a chip imbedded with data including your photo. The facial recognition systems, also in use in the United Kingdom, Portugal, Australia, New Zealand, Germany and other countries, compare the travelers face with the passport and assign a score. If the match scores high enough, the passport control officer can be more certain of identity than todays system of eyeballing people entering the country.

Manually checking that the person in front of you is the same as a photo five years old is a challenge, Mr. Hartmann says.

At Gatwick Airport, systems estimate queues in real time at security and immigration checkpoints. And some countries have automated border control setups where the facial recognition system automatically clears someone to enter the country without seeing an officer. The U.S. hasnt gone that far partly because not enough travelers have the required chip in their passports.

San Francisco International Airport has 350 beacons installed in Terminal 2 and is testing an app that can give visually impaired passengers audible directions. American Airlines has signed on to a beacon rollout to help customers find their way, starting at Dallas-Fort Worth International Airport.

Virgin Atlantics lounge in London and Cathay Pacifics lounge in San Francisco have beacons that can recognize members when they walk through the door and offer information like food and drink menus. Miami International Airport has been doing limited trials. One potential use: tracking when someone enters the baggage carousel area and when they leave, showing how long they waited for baggage.

By 2018, 44% of airlines world-wide plan to use beacons, compared with 9% that have experimented with the technology currently, according to a survey this year by SITA, an aviation information and communications company. Geneva-based SITA is owned by 430 air transport companies and develops technology for the industry.

In Germany, Dusseldorfs airport is growing in passenger traffic but it doesnt have real estate to expand parking. The answer: a valet parking robot.

From the airports website, travelers make a reservation and enter flight information. Then they drive to a spot in the garage and lock their car. The system reads the license plate and decides where it will park the vehicle. A robot nicknamed Ray, which looks like a giant forklift, picks up the car by the wheels and moves it. At night, robots reshuffle the garage so cars that will be returned the next day are easily accessible. The system tracks if travelers flights are delayed or canceled and has their cars ready when they arrive.

The robots have operated for nearly a year and boosted garage capacity by 32%, says SITA managing director Christian Jahncke, who oversees the robot project. It has had one ding in one of the 40,000 cars handled. One problem: Sometimes the robot sets off the anti-theft alarm. Eventually the screeching stops. High-quality cars are very sensitive to being picked up, Mr. Jahncke says.

Close-in valet robot parking costs 29, or about $32, a day. That compares with 24.5 for premium parking the same distance from the terminal without valet service.

Each robot costs about $250,000, and Dusseldorf uses three so far. In all, Dusseldorf has spent about $1 million, far less than building a new garage, says Mr. Jahncke.

SITA is looking at whether it could make a robot to check bags, says Jim Peters, the firms chief technology officer. Travelers would self-tag, or have a permanent-use bag tag that identifies them. Robots would pick up the bags and maybe even deliver them, speeding up the process and reducing manual labor costs. Managing your baggage and not making it a pain is a part of the airport of the future, Mr. Peters says. The number of airlines offering self-tagging bag drop, but without robots, has increased to 17% from 9% last year. That is expected to rise to 74% of airlines by 2018, according to the SITA technology survey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Technology Will Speed You Through the Airport of the Future </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 11:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple News is seriously good and might become your only news app </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 18:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a very cool idea - a lot of potential for epic pranks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair point - I also wonder if the road surface would have any effect on stopping distance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fish feed shortage could provide missing link in the bid to make insects the food of the future </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Verizon to Add Vice Content to Its Coming Mobile Video Service </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Mad genius' no more: the genetic link between creativity and psychosis is pretty weak </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Solar Cost Less than Half of What EIA Projected </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Future Dutch roadways made of recycled plastic will snap together like LEGO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Evidence Life Could Have Come From Space </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Agave Hold the Secret to Drought-Resistant Farming? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservatives Choose More Unwanted Pregnancy and Abortion over Better Birth Control for Teens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's a very fair response, although it often seems like some people let articles, tv etc form opinions on every aspect of their lives! 

I quite agree about the job issue, I think perhaps more articles about how people can transition to new jobs unaffected by AI (or even create them themselves) would help. Obviously no article would be a perfect solution, but this sort of approach, even if it is very basic, would help people realise it wasn't all doom! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Pay has launched in the UK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 10:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welsh Government Responds to UFO Questions in Klingon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 10:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Graphic] How worried should you be about artificial intelligence? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 10:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Universal basic income is not the solution to robots taking our jobs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two more critical Flash flaws discovered in Hacking Team data breach </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 12:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transhumanist Party presidential candidate to drive Immortality Bus across the U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 12:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sleep On The Side Of A Mountain In These Vertigo-Inducing Pods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 12:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Digg Cofounder Jay Adelson On The Reddit Mess - And Why It Isn't Digg All Over Again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 12:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sharks have been discovered living inside an active volcano </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 12:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M9 crash report man 'feels guilt' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 12:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [podcast] Can technology make meat sustainable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 12:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Virtual reality technology expands to a blitz of uses, including football </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 12:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 17:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case anyone is interested, that's equivalent to $8.39 a gallon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can always spot the imposters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would work, but he'd need to be absurdly posh and be saying to a friend as affectionate 'banter'. 
Source: am British. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 14:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends what industry you work in, but in general that doesn't sound unreasonable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we might well develop systems to create life from sequenced DNA to enable robots to terraform planets and that sort of thing, but this would be robots essentially carrying out tasks programmed by humans, so I'm not sure if it would count as robots re-creating life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might just be being an idiot, but what exactly do you mean by a 4D object? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How technology could kill the art of lying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New wireless charging technology can simultaneously power 30 mobile phones or five laptops at distance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 12:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside Amazons Warehouse, Human-Robot Symbiosis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 12:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook's new friends icon takes the chip off the womans shoulder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 12:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sensor technology can improve accuracy of prostate cancer diagnosis, research shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 12:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An unpatched security flaw in Adobe Flash, discovered then kept secret by Italian cyber-surveillance firm Hacking Team, is now being used by malware developers to hack victims computers following the leak of over 400GB of data from the companys servers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 12:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anthropology grad here. Put it like this, you're going to get reeally good at explaining what anthropology is to people in suits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huge, Alien-Hunting Telescope Could Become Hubble's Successor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Desperate man with dying phone jumps on Broadway stage to revive it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> See the wearable tech of the future </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 16:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 14:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of us are!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why news editors can't ignore online comments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 13:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Subtle nuances: Language tiff nearly derailed world heritage designations for Japan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 13:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robosapiens  merging with machines will improve humanity at an exponential rate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 13:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 18:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK officials discussed resettling 5.5m Hong Kong Chinese in Northern Ireland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 01:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 15:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A man can dream... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 15:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, Steve is a friend of my Mum's - I never expected to see him mentioned on Reddit! 

This is an awesome piece, thanks for sharing it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hacking the brain: can DIY neuroscience make you happier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 14:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists announce major breakthrough in the understanding of memory formation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new cloud tax law goes into effect in Chicago today, aimed at seeking out more revenue from popular streaming platforms such as Netflix </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super-Muscular Pigs Created by Small Genetic Tweak </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These headphones let you switch between styles in a snap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cuban Babies Are Now HIV-Free </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Males and females process pain using different cells, a new study with mice suggests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Man Who Wants to Turn Our Clothes Into Modular Gadgets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toyota's Mirai will go 312 miles on a tank of hydrogen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dentist saved my tooth, but wiped my memory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 10:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Gene-Editing Technology Has Scientists Excited </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can Technology Ease The Burden Of Caring For People With Dementia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservative research confirms sixth mass extinction has arrived </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 20:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> E3 2015 signals the beginning of overdue change for big budget games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 18:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK's Legalization of CD Ripping is Unlawful, Court Rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 18:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASAs Space Launch System  the essential next step in space exploration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 18:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is facial recognition tech really a threat to privacy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 17:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Space technology: how to clear up space junk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 17:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. I only have a Wii U and was gutted by the lack of content. 

My SO has theorised that they aren't doing any more games for the Wii U after the announced ones, and are moving Zelda U to NX. I bloody well hope not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bitcoin technology will disrupt derivatives, says banker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oculus unveils Half Moon, a VR Rift controller to reach out and touch the virtual world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google creates Sidewalk Labs to redesign city living with technology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To make its prototype augmented-reality goggles a product, Magic Leap will have to scale up silicon photonicssomething heavyweights like Intel have struggled to do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple iPhones could soon be built in India </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quantum technology probes ultimate limits of vision </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Technology to Prevent Drunken Driving Could Soon Come in New Cars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The World Custard Pie Championships, as seen through a GoPro </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 18:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 14:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Craziness. Reddit makes the world feel weirdly small! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 00:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hang on, is this the Swan in East Peckham? I thought it looked familiar - it's my parents local! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 19:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with this - it looks like a country pub in north Kent or another of the neighbouring counties </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently I've switched genders in a lot of parallel universes! 

Very cool though, thanks for posting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should try, if only to give the person who decides a good laugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to love that pub - it was all no-nonsense tasty stuff. What a shame its gone all hipster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I particularly cannot cope with the horrendous word 'Brexit' that the Guardian keeps using. If I have to see it repeatedly for the next 2 years I might have to seek out its inventor and bludgeon them with a spoon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple To Launch New Flipboard-Like App, While Newsstand Goes Away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fairly certain its a British passport </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The secret history of Wes Andersons Rushmore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Revolutionary technology to improve bedside tumor diagnosis in patients </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 17:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Solar Impulse makes unplanned landing in Japan, breaking solar flight record </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 17:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earth organisms survive under low-pressure Martian conditions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 13:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Article] Why Dinosaurs Would Have Never Built Spaceships </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 13:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Christians Should Embrace Transhumanism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 13:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Virtual Reality Gets Huge Boost Thanks to Googles Jump Platform   3D Printing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 13:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Technology Ruin the Expat Experience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 13:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AI Supercomputer Built by Tapping Data Warehouses for Their Idle Computing Power </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 13:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslim Invents First Space Tech Prayer Mat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 13:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google's new finger control technology is straight out of a science fiction movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 13:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Genomic sequencing technology advances make food poisoning outbreaks easier to control </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 12:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China Unveils World's First ATM that Can Identify Faces </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 12:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 13:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zoltan Istvan of the Transhumanism Party is, but he's not exactly one of the major players </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Theres a fork in the road today": Edward Snowden on the future of surveillance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 17:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Hollywood Is Learning To Tell Stories In Virtual Reality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 17:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK Watchdog Says YouTube Viewers Must Know A Video Is Sponsored Before They Click </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 17:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drone Giant DJI And Top VC Firm Accel Partners Launch A $10 Million Drone Fund </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 17:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DARPAs legacy: Open source simulation for robotics development and testing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 17:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quantum computer emulated by a classical system </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 16:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IIWTL: I'd get one of these geodesic walking pods custom built, hook it up with Internet and tour the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 16:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter Needs to Change, But Only if It Stays the Same </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 13:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robot Journalism: Algorithms are More of a Tool than a Threat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 13:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You could soon be taking a robot pill that delivers drugs with sugar needles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 11:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man breaks Guinness hoverboard record after standing on a drone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 10:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 13:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be run by a dude called Fit Nes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 20:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The changes were observed using a European Space Agency satellite, the CryoSat-2, which is designed to sense ice remotely.

According to the article, the GRACE was just used to measure gravitational changes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
