<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9503</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowden's Plea to Top Technologists: Build an Internet for the People | 'Everybody should be safe all the time, else we let others choose who will be safe or not,' whistleblower tells meeting of independent internet engineers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red States 'Feel The Bern' as Populist Message Resonates Far   Wide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 19:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get ready for the American Spring. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 00:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American Spring </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 00:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the No-Management Trend Could Disrupt Everything | "If the market can work out a template for running companies this way and there are a few more big success stories, sentiment could tip quickly like it did with free food. Companies with less structure will have a major recruiting advantage." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 23:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The "Sharing Economy" is the Problem. The Cooperative Economy is the Solution. | Extracting wealth is exactly what these sharing economy corporations are so good at doing. They belong with the old, extractive economy but they're trying to pass as part of the new, generative economy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 02:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minute-Zero In The Gender Pay Gap | Women never ask me the big one up front: How do I negotiate a better salary when I still want to be known as a team player? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 06:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A remarkable and poignant account of a self-aware young woman and her indomitable sister. Beautiful, sad, heroic, despairing and hopeful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everything Is Yours, Everything Is Not Yours | At age six, I ran away with my sister to escape the Rwandan massacre. We spent seven years as refugees. What do you want me to do about it? Cry? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 04:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Older. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Law of the Land has caught up with the Law of the Lord | While many religious leaders and institutions collectively echo Chicken Little, so many more of us  marginalized and abandoned because of our prayerful hope that love does, actually, win  are breathing deeper and lifting a toast to God. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 02:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Editing the Software of Life | A protein called cas9 could be engineered to easily cut through DNA at precise locations. The key word was easy. If genome editing was once akin to performing dental surgery, it had almost overnight become more like squeezing toothpaste out of a tube. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 01:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 18:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phrasing it as 'talk, talk, talk' dismisses it as useless, whereas some kinds of talk can involve reflecting, realizing, challenging.  Racism is not going to diminish without talking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Makes Work Meaningful? Ask A Zookeeper | If meaning is the thing that makes us work well and with satisfaction, even if it means spending Christmas morning cutting up lettuce for a tortoise, its not the sort of thing that can be served up in a corporate mission statement. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 00:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 23:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Talk, talk, talk.

Reflect, realize, challenge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 19:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A powerful reflection on the ways black survival has depended on white comfort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cost Of White Comfort | Comforting white people is hardly the priority right now. The priority is to change the way that black people are treated in America, especially by police. Which requires white people to do a lot more than just feel bad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 19:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 22:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an in-depth interview with a man who has a deep grasp of the tenacious and widespread persistence of the effects of the institution of slavery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bryan Stevenson on Charleston and Our Real Problem with Race | There are many people of color who are just as reluctant to talk about these issues as people who are white because it's uncomfortable, it's disruptive. But we are all going to be burdened until we deal more honestly with this legacy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 22:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A blinding noise | Cooking oil bursts into flame at around 370 degrees celcius. In fahrenheit, thats roughly 700. When human flesh is exposed to those temperatures, it bubbles and has a scent a lot like pork. I smelled absolutely delicious. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 18:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waiting For Kindergarten | I slept outside for 16 days to enroll my son in Fairview-Clifton Elementary School. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 18:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> black man walks into Silicon Valley and tries to get a job </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 08:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I chose a life without breasts after cancer | I want to talk about it so that its not shameful. I want people who have had cancer to bring their experiences into the world, into a dialogue that is miserably lacking and poorly representative of the real experience of cancer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 01:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oskar Groening   Our Own Guilt for Crimes Committed Collectively </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 01:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an interesting perspective from a folklorist who studies traditional culture, exploring the ways in which these symbols continue to affect us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yes, youre a racist and a traitor. | In America today, the most prominent, prevalent, and pernicious of these revisionist movements is the Lost Cause narrative: the idea that the Civil War was a romantic struggle for freedom against an oppressive government trying to enforce cultural change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where Should Innovation in Education Come From? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ingenious: Robert Sapolsky | The primatologist and neurologist talks turbulenceteens, stress, and the information age. | The teen brain, for all its famous downsides, is a necessary stage in human developments slow dance, an incubation time for social intelligence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 00:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ingenious: Robert Sapolsky | The primatologist and neurologist talks turbulenceteens, stress, and the information age. | The teen brain, for all its famous downsides, is a necessary stage in human developments slow dance, an incubation time for social intelligence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 06:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 05:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A historian of race explains the meaning of the Confederate flag in the context of history and reaches a damning conclusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 04:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great perspective from a Southerner who loves the South. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the Confederate flag really means to America today, according to a race historian | You cant filter out the racism and leave whats pure and historical, because that purity doesnt exist. Some things are so primitively stained or tarnished by history that that can never be set side. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 04:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Truth Does Not Change According to Our Ability to Stomach It: A Southerners Perspective on the Confederate Flag | Pride in the Confederacy is irresponsible, it is dangerous, and it is dishonest. Lay aside the revisionist history you were fed in the sixth grade, and open a book. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 04:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Freedom of Panorama is under attack | On 9 July 2015, the European Parliament will vote on whether to abolish our right to freely take and share photographs, videos and drawings of buildings and works of public art. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 04:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Greatest Good: What is the best charitable cause in the world? | Effective altruism, a burgeoning movement that has been called "generosity for nerds." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 22:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aneurysm | from Henry Marshs Do No Harm, a memoir where one of Britain's foremost neurosurgeons gives an intimate view inside delicate and dangerous surgeries. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 05:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans Must Go on the Offensive or Risk Losing Ground | Polls report huge support for some values and policies of the left: Medicare for all, major steps to address climate change, governmental back-up so everyone has enough to eat and a place to sleep. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 01:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Zero-Armed Bandit | A metal chest topped with 23 toggle switches is left inside a Las Vegas casino. A note says the box contains a bomb big enough to level the building, which will explode unless a ransom is delivered by helicopter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 18:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Johann Hari: The War On Drugs | The evidence is clear: A system based on stigma and punishment and hatred doesnt work. A system based on compassion and care and love does work. It turns peoples lives around. So now we have a choice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Life Of The Doctor As Writer | When I walk into a patients room, if Im doing my work well, I listen for their Once upon a time. I am about to be the disruption in their story, and since I am an oncologist the disruption is usually pretty rough. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 19:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Ive Learned About Government, Big Banks And Consumerism | "The moment you step outside the way people are supposed to work in the U.S.  either because that model doesnt work for you or because youve lost a traditional job  you get cut off from the countrys support systems." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 07:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I Defaulted on My Student Loans | It struck me as absurd that one could amass crippling debt as a result of going to college. Having opened a new life to me beyond my modest origins, the education system was now going to call in its chits and prevent me from pursuing that new life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 19:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How my father gave me a terrifying lesson at 10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Algorithms of the Mind | What Machine Learning Teaches Us About Ourselves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 03:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 03:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm finally getting around to reading [Dreams from My Father: A Story of Race and Inheritance](https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/88061.Dreams_from_My_Father?ac=1) and am enjoying it a lot.  If you haven't done so already, check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Consciousness Began When the Gods Stopped Speaking | How Julian Jaynes famous 1970s theory is faring in the neuroscience age. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 22:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Layers Of Reality| Discursive conversation. Carroll, a theoretical cosmologist, talks accessibly about the laws of nature and the limits of knowledge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 19:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cunning Minds Of Fish | Close study shows fish to be much cleverer than previously imagined. They appear to co-operate, cheat, console, punish  overturning long-standing assumptions that intelligent social behaviours are limited to primates because only primates have big enough brains. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 17:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Biologist-Turned-Buddhist and His Philosopher Father on the Nature of the Self and the True Measure of Personal Strength | You first need to have an ego in order to be aware that it doesnt exist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 18:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, Im a Teacher Now  10 Reflections From the First 10 Weeks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 04:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 17:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ginger Campbell's Brain Science podcast has interviews with neuroscientists and is worth listening to.  She makes it a practice to ask each for their advice to young people starting out in the field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Right And Wrong Questions About The Iraq War | The right questions are: How did you assess the available evidence at the time? And, most important of all: How will the experience of Iraq shape your decisions on committing American force in the future? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 22:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Our Genome and Technology Are Both Riddled With Crawling Horrors | At least when it comes to our technology, perhaps we need to be more willing to embrace the cruft (the messy accumulated material that often is part of kluges) we see in the things around us. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 02:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It Is, in Fact, Rocket Science | The oversimplification of discovery makes science appear far less rich and complex than it really is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 21:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Flight | En route from London to Tokyo, a pilots-eye view of life in the sky. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 19:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do we want people to work more? | Imagine if everyone in America managed to afford a house in a safe neighborhood close to a good school and that featured convenient commuting to job opportunities. That would be a much more egalitarian society. But it would also be much more growth-friendly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 19:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baltimore looting tweets show importance of quick and easy image checks | Anyone who has ever asked me for tips on content verification and debunking of fakes knows one of the first things I always mention is reverse image search. Its one of the simplest and most powerful tools at your disposal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 07:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a Knock on the Door Can Change Public Opinion (2014) | Were talking with them privately, one-on-one, out of earshot of anyone else. And this person encouraging them to talk about things that really matter to them. Well, how often does that happen in life? Almost never. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 17:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 21:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe not all commenters have taken the time to read the article.  It's a worthwhile read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Making A Brain Map That We Can Use | When it comes to complex functional systems, the laws and regularities and connections that matter are themselves higher-level; they don't bottom out in laws framed in terms of neuronal units any more than in laws framed in terms of quantum mechanical processes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 06:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is it okay to discriminate against women for religious reasons? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 06:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atonement | A troubled Iraq veteran seeks out the family he harmed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 05:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why American Workers Without Much Education Are Being Hammered | The median earnings of working men aged 30 to 45 without a high school diploma fell 20 percent from 1990 to 2013 when adjusted for inflation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 01:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Before the Law | A boy was accused of taking a backpack. The courts took the next three years of his life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 01:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atonement | A troubled Iraq veteran seeks out the family he harmed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 06:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists Perturbed by Loss of Stat Tool to Sift Research Fudge from Fact | The journal Basic and Applied Social Psychology recently banned the use of p-values and other statistical methods to quantify uncertainty from significance in research results. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 06:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to efficiently capture carbon dioxide out of thin air | The amount of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere has reached the point where simply reducing emissions will not be enough to tackle climate change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 22:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To have and to hold | Serious thinkers have given surprisingly little thought to the family dynamics behind the early stages of capitalism. Novelists are a better guide to this subject than classical economists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 22:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Strange continuity | Filmmakers intuitions are a gold mine for people like me who want to know how perception and memory work. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 22:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet the School That Hates Rules | Free play is key to child development and happiness. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 18:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buddhist Economics: How to Stop Prioritizing Products Over People and Consumption Over Creativity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 04:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I Teach My Students to be Brave | At my spoken word camp, I watched a 15-year-old girl bring us to tears with her raw openness. That is why I teach. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 20:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best, Brightest  and Saddest? | Want the best for your child, not for your child to be the best. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 02:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Smarter Way to Teach the Teachers | Teachers learning needs are as unique as their students. Why, then, is their professional development so awkwardly flat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 00:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stoned Muscle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 22:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Organ Transplant Reform: The Time is Now | How is it possible that supply fails to increase to meet demand, resulting in annual dialysis for over 400,000 Americans (which also costs $70,000100,000 and is paid for by taxpayers), long wait-lists, and often death? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 03:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Sell Bottled Water During a Drought | Take the simple and change it into something convoluted and arbitrarily elitist  then repackage it to the consumer, put in a nice bottle, and sell it as a benefit they cant possibly live without. #disrupt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 02:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microaggressions, Trigger Warnings, and the New Meaning of Trauma | My sympathy for your suffering ended when you demanded I change my life to avoid bringing up your bad memories. There is no I must never be reminded of a negative experience expectation in any culture anywhere on earth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 21:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barney Frank drops a bombshell: How a shocking anecdote explains the financial crisis | "The fact that we waited six years to get some semblance of a decent economic recovery traces back directly to the failure to alleviate the foreclosure crisis." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 20:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barney Frank drops a bombshell: How a shocking anecdote explains the financial crisis | "The fact that we waited six years to get some semblance of a decent economic recovery traces back directly to the failure to alleviate the foreclosure crisis." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 20:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The City-States will veto Red States in the Culture War </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We Live in an Age of Irrational Parenting | Its hard to think of a safer time and a better place than the United States of 2015 to raise children  but we act as though the opposite were true. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 19:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Is the Matter with Wall Street? | Changes in economic policy in a much more Keynesian, Democratic direction are not just in the interest of the 99%. They are in the interest of the 1%. And of the 0.01%. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 19:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Children Need Chores | Doing household chores has many benefitsacademically, emotionally and even professionally. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 05:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antiwork - a radical shift in how we view jobs | We seem to have a nasty, and very persistent, cultural neurosis in the form of an archaic cognitive frame for work and leisure. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 04:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attribution Is Hard | We can stop treating the internet like the Old West. Both providers and the public can learn to deal with network technology in a more realistic way with standards of safe manufacture and responsible use. And until we do, its all going to stay broken. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 19:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Magnitude of Inequality | Wage inequality is just the tip of the iceberg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 03:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Better Than This | In depth story about what it took to get out of an environment where parents, teachers and principals were asking What makes you think youre better than anyone else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 01:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 21:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a cast of characters: Pitts and McCulloch, Bertrand Russell, Norbert Wiener, John von Neumann.  Of Pitts and McCulloch the article says:
Thanks to their work, there was a moment in history when neuroscience, psychiatry, computer science, mathematical logic, and artificial intelligence were all one thing, following an idea first glimpsed by Leibniz--that man, machine, number, and mind all use information as a universal currency.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Man Who Tried to Redeem the World with Logic | Walter Pitts rose from the streets to MIT, but couldnt escape himself. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 21:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why You Should Tell Your Children How Much You Make | Our spending isnt a secret in the first place; children see plenty. But watching us whip out plastic cards in the store or in front of the computer, completely out of context, may give them the wrong impression entirely. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 23:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 05:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This deserves a wider scope than /r/atheismplus.  Please cross-post to a subreddit with a more subscribers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What You Absolutely Must Understand About How Poverty Impacts Education | "For the first time in at least 50 years, a majority of U.S. public school students come from low-income families." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 23:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> School girl in Fiji [OC] [1280x960] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 03:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giving Students a Voice in the Classroom | By gathering feedback on key constructs like student engagement, grit, and student interest in the class subject, it offers a new perspective on those teaching skills that are often difficult to measure. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 17:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Computer Becomes Unbeatable At Poker | Heads-Up Limit Holdem, a popular form of poker, has been essentially solved by a new computer algorithm which has discovered through trial and error the optimal strategies, including bluffing, for all possible distributions of the cards. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 06:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hear, O Internet. | Optimizing the Internet for one purpose de-optimizes it for all others. | Apparently knowing how to find one another interesting is not as easy as it looks. | Every time you call us "consumers" we feel like cows looking up the word "meat." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 18:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Things People Say When Youre A Blonde Engineer At MIT | Sometimes I feel as if in saying that I attend MIT, Im telling a blonde joke. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 18:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Work-Life Balance in Finland: Americans on a Different Planet | Although I see Finnish teachers take coffee breaks throughout each day and often head home just minutes after their last classes, they are undoubtedly hard-working and committed professionals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 05:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ursula K. Le Guin on Being a Man | A journey to where the semicolon meets the soul. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 23:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YSK that insulting someone you're arguing with is not only impolite, it's counterproductive, unless you have no interest in changing their view. See link in comments. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 22:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worth reading:  [How to Criticize with Kindness: Philosopher Daniel Dennett on the Four Steps to Arguing Intelligently](http://www.brainpickings.org/2014/03/28/daniel-dennett-rapoport-rules-criticism/)
 How to compose a successful critical commentary:

 You should attempt to re-express your targets position so clearly, vividly, and fairly that your target says, Thanks, I wish Id thought of putting it that way.

 You should list any points of agreement (especially if they are not matters of general or widespread agreement).

 You should mention anything you have learned from your target.

 Only then are you permitted to say so much as a word of rebuttal or criticism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fixed vs. Growth: The Two Basic Mindsets That Shape Our Lives | In the fixed mindset, imperfections are shameful - especially if youre talented - so they lied them away. Whats so alarming is that we took ordinary children and made them into liars, simply by telling them they were smart. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 21:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Margaret Hamilton, the Engineer Who Took the Apollo to the Moon | "I worked on all the Apollo manned missions and a couple of Apollo unmanned missions." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 19:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tasers, Drones, and Cold Chicken | Inside the multibillion-dollar business of keeping foreigners out of America. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 05:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let the Other 95% of Great Programmers In | Barring some cataclysm, it will always be true that most great programmers are born outside the US. It will always be true that most people who are great at anything are born outside the US. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 20:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YSK How to use ABS brakes properly, and other lessons from the BMW Performance Driving School </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 23:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You Suck At Driving](https://medium.com/re-form/you-suck-at-driving-33d6a9a4be4c) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Homo Economicus A Psychopath? | A study in Japan shows that Homo economicus makes up only a minority of the population, but a minority with a wide range of unusual personality traits, including a touch of psychopathy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 04:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Deprogramming Kids From How to Do School Could Improve Learning | Discussing their learning with them, switching grading policies and assigning more inquiry-based, hands on lessons all helped Holmans students feel he trusted and respected them. And they rose to the challenge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 17:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Unbearable Whiteness of Protesting | "Dont hold up a Black Lives Matter sign in Times Square if youre going to clutch your purse when a black man steps into the elevator." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 17:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wall Street Moves In For The Kill | We are at a pivotal moment in the struggle to restrain the financial industrys toxic blend of recklessness and political influence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 18:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its Time to Intelligently Discuss Artificial Intelligence | I am an AI researcher and Im not scared. Heres why. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 03:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New Republic: An Appreciation | 'TNR made a habit of "reflecting briefly" on matters that were life and death to black people but were mostly abstract thought experiments to the magazine's editors.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 03:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I Will Prepare My White Son for the Interactions He Wont Have with Police | I am the mother of a white boy--an effusive, dynamic, gentle, kind toddler, who was born with so much privilege. He will need to hear a very different version of the talk than these women gave their sons. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 03:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Silence of the Lawyers | Most lawyers know perfectly well that criminal justice in this country is in disgraceful condition, that it makes indefensible distinctions between white and black, rich and poor, first class and second class. Its just that we prefer not to talk about it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 22:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not my place to say, but | "I realise that I am a white woman and all I can do is stupid comedy, but police brutality against black people is absolutely my business. Its everyones business." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 18:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Death Becomes Him | Caleb Wilde is a sixth-generation funeral director who wants to reacquaint us all with the uncomfortable, eye-opening realities of death. Itll make us more human, he says. If it doesnt kill him first. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 17:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Learn from the losers | The world is biased in systematic ways. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 05:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From 1,000,000 To Grahams Number | 10 to the googol-th power is relatively minuscule. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 05:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rioting Elites and a Nation Built on the Rule of Lawlessness | Contrary to what Barack Obama says about the U.S. being built on the rule of law, the country routinely resorts to official violence and illegality. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 16:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 02:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is he complaining about evolution?  And where does he show his misunderstanding? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Co-operation | Biology is thought to be all about competition - and that supposedly means constant struggle. This emphasis has had an insidious effect on the public mind and has encouraged the belief in individual selfishness and in confrontation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 17:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Letting the Neocons Lead | Granted, the situation is now such a mess that it is hard to decide what the best course of action is. But rational policymaking would surely rule out the advice of the people who created the mess in the first place. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 04:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 04:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR How the performance revolution came to athletics and beyond and the implications for education. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Better All the Time | Most American schools basically throw teachers in at the deep end of the pool and hope that they will be able not only to swim but also to keep all their students afloat, too. Its a miracle that the system works as well as it does. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 04:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Invisible Stars Who Make Hollywood French | As an American, it is my duty to think of the French, subjects of endless jokes, imitations, and envy in my culture, as weird and dramatic, sensual, snotty, magnificent, intensely full of joie de vivre but simultaneously carrying a collective darkness. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 19:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a Treadmill Became a Political Plaything | I am willing to put my infamous treadmill up for sale. All profits will go toward supporting marine-biology research so that the House science committee can rest easy knowing that they can once again eat fat juicy shrimp without using government funds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 19:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Germans Work Fewer Hours But Produce More: A Study In Culture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 18:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ferguson and the Self-Fulfilling Prophesy of Violence | A massive and intimidating show of violent threat by the state against its own people can produce exactly what it supposedly deters. Deep and prolonged conversation, listening and positive action are not on that official table. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 18:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Old people resting in Kyoto (OC 1975) [1443x790] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 22:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOPs Secret Weapon | Many liberals and progressives believe that talk of love and caring is mere psycho-babble. As a result they cede to the Right the values issues rather than providing an alternative set of values in which love and generosity and caring for the Earth would take center place. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 03:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Billion Dollar a Month Club: A Runaway Transfer of Wealth to the Super-Rich | A Financial Speculation Tax might be the best approach to stop the wealth transfer carnage. We have to do something. The splitting of our society is nearly beyond repair. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 16:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 17:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ###Submission Statement
One of the greatest films wasn't pure farce after all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost Everything in Dr. Strangelove Was True </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 17:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How #BeenRapedNeverReported Became a Movement | According to Canadian studies, only 33 out of every 1,000 [rapes] are ever reported and of those only three lead to conviction. That means 99.7 per cent of attackers walk free. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 16:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Infuriating Facts About Our Disappearing Middle-Class Wealth | 1. Each Year Since the Recession, America's Richest 1% Have Made More Than the Cost of All U.S. Social Programs . 2. Almost None of the New 1% Wealth Led To Innovation and Jobs... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 16:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin to Western elites: Play-time is over | At this conference he declared the game to be over, explicitly violating Western taboo by speaking directly to the people over the heads of elite clans and political leaders. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 03:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ten Things You Should Know Before Voting (Or Deciding Not To) | 1.) Ebola is a bogyeman. 2.) ISIS isnt an "existential" threat to the US. 3) Immigrants arent taking jobs, hurting the economy, or ruining our values...7.) Absent constraints, capitalism enslaves and impoverishes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 17:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corporate Destruction of Free Markets Rules Us | "(Adam Smith, they neglected to add, favored public works, public education and social safety nets like decent wages and public welfare as needed.)" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 17:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Speech for Sale: How Toxic Slime-Fests Can Shrivel Voter Turnout | "If money is speech, then speech is no longer free - its for sale. This year, were seeing what the Courts absurd edicts are costing us." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 17:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Empathy Deficit Disorder | Some Democrats have it, but the disorder seems especially widespread among Republicans. These politicians have no idea what people who are hard up in America are going through. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 20:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Do We Keep Thanking the Troops? | The war on terror is going into its 14th year. Its years past the time when anyone here should be able to pretend that our 18-year-olds are going off to kill and die for good reason. How about a couple of concerts to make that point? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 16:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Myth of the Free Press | The mass media blindly support the ideology of corporate capitalism. They laud and promote the myth of American democracy--even as we are stripped of civil liberties and money replaces the vote. They pay deference to leaders, no matter how perfidious their crimes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 16:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Message to the 21st Century | If these ultimate human values by which we live are to be pursued, then compromises, trade-offs have to be made if the worst is not to happen. So much liberty for so much equality, so much individual self-expression for so much security, justice for compassion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 21:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Koch Congress' Could Make Oligarchy Official | At risk are the rights of all Americans, especially women, workers, voters, veterans, as well as the protection of our rapidly warming Earth, since the Kochs end game is to defend their wealth by continuing to pollute politics and the planet for free. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 05:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Coming Financial Crisis: A Harbinger of World Renewal? | Will our elected leaders finally accept the need for an entirely new economic approach that breaks away from the primacy of growth and profit -- or will their hand be forced by a resurgence of mass public protest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 18:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Imperative of Revolt | There is no effective organized opposition to the rise of a neofeudalism dominated a tiny corporate oligarchy that exploits workers and the poor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 06:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On a Top-Heavy Planet, Nordic Nations Show Path to Healthier Wealth Equity | Income gaps and wealth concentration go hand in hand, new global stats make clear. With one exception. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 06:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On a Top-Heavy Planet, Nordic Nations Show Path to Healthier Wealth Equity | Income gaps and wealth concentration go hand in hand, new global stats make clear. With one exception. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 06:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frida Berrigan on Operation Kid Freedom: Making Our Communities Safe for Children to Take Risks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 20:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Project Wild Thing: a film-maker's campaign to reconnect kids with nature | Children don't play outside anymore. David Bond wants people to spend as much time outside as they do in front of screens. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 20:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Threats Against Anita Sarkeesian Expose the Darkest Aspects of Online Misogyny | Making social media less hostile and abusive environment is an eminently reachable goal --- for companies and sites that care to expend the effort, that is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 18:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hysteria Over Ebola Fuels Racism, While the Real Disease Is Capitalism | Ebola is a disease worsened by poverty. Western inaction has worsened the crisis in part because there was no money to be made before the disease reached epidemic proportions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 17:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ten Facts about Being Homeless in USA | Over half a million people are homeless. One quarter of homeless people are children. Tens of thousands of veterans are homeless. Domestic violence is a leading cause of homelessness in women. Cities are increasingly making homelessness a crime... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 20:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How We Punish People for Being Poor | Low-income individuals are being sold auto loans at twice the actual value of the car, with interest rates as high as 29 percent. Families who turn to predatory payday loans can end up trapped in an inescapable cycle of debt at 400 percent annual interest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 20:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How We Punish People for Being Poor | Low-income individuals are being sold auto loans at twice the actual value of the car, with interest rates as high as 29 percent. Families who turn to predatory payday loans can end up trapped in an inescapable cycle of debt at 400 percent annual interest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 18:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 23:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ###Submission Statement
An in-depth look at life in the oil fields of North Dakota.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Trip to Kuwait (on the Prairie): Life Inside the Boom | Toxic flames that burn around the clock; intermittent explosions caused by lightning striking the super-conductive wastewater tanks that hydraulic fracturing makes a necessity; an abundance of meth, crack,   liquor; and far, far too many men. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 23:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
