<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8959</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Amazon logo isn't an odd grin. It's an arrow from A to Z. I just figured that out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The wave particle duality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hating things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop reading user comments on CNN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ability to deeply smell menstruation from distances of over a mile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A semen encrusted pair of my wife's underwear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Birds with Arms](http://www.reddit.com/r/birdswitharms) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's racist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My penis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Homey don't play that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enter the dreams of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The inability to comprehend someone disagreeing is precisely why I can't... no, I won't support it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you certainly helped my case lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We can save our dreams on computer hardware to watch again and again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KFC refusing to reform after videos leaked of chickens being tortured. Paul McCartney got involved, PR nightmare. I haven't visited a KFC in a decade as a result and I'm now vegetarian largely because of what the scenario taught me about corporate restaurants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You picked pouting over a sarcastic comment over reasonable response. To each their own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's nuts. I know the alphabet, basic words and a few sentences and I'm learning numbers now. It's a major major part of the woman I love, I feel it's important to show her I understand that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get an English teaching degree. Move to OPs home town. Find his or her school. Befriend the English teacher. Get them to fall in love with me. Send them abroad and take over teaching the class myself. Teach proper tenses of the word "launch" every single day of class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bulgaria, similar language to Russia in structure and sound to me but she swears they are vastly different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I married someone from Eastern Europe. She didn't give me a choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Traveling from DC to Norfolk some years ago, I sat next to a man who was absolutely brilliant. Physics professor I believe.  We discussed chess, fantastic theories etc. Was really cool. He was attending his sons wedding, I was there for work.

A strike at my company caused me to have to reschedule my return flight, early by 3 days. When I boarded the plane, I was seated next to the same man. His son had broken his arm and they delayed the wedding and he scheduled an early flight home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supporting feminism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Surges in 2016 Republican Presidential Nomination Poll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good call edited to address that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, I do not support him. I'm pointing out real possible damage he could represent to Democrat opposition. Personally, I feel Republicans are up shits creek in this election and they know it. I would say, short of some catastrophic attack against US that allows GOP to ride the "Obama failed us" train into the White House, they stood no chance before Trump and now they stand even less of a chance of winning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You have 1 trillion dollars and 30 years to prepare. Who is the strongest superhero you can possibly destroy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: To address question, you have access to the fictional universe of your target. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Be ashamed to die until you have won some victory for humanity.'

-Horace Mann </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly? He's so under the radar he's difficult to criticize by personality while also being a minority. This blunts a great deal of criticism towards Trump as being racist, it practically negates a major attacking point of the Democratic nominee. Also he is an incredibly intelligent man. I don't agree with most of what he says but I can certainly acknowledge he is very smart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite quote and who said it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 01:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so glad you shared that with me, but I didn't ask for your opinions on the state of the Union. I asked a specific question to a specific group of people. As a Democrat, let me tell you your immediate jump to insulting others before hearing them out is a hypocritical display of intolerance of intolerance and makes us all look bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This in no way addresses the question I asked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Reward] Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 19:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be incredibly interested to see potential running mates. Ben Carson or Condoleeza Rice could genuinely clench it for him which is hard to imagine as reality to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 19:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is amazing, I never thought of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Redditors currently supporting Donald Trump, what about him appeals to you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hackers Remotely Kill a Jeep on the HighwayWith Me in It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every breed of spider develops wings and flight mechanisms similar to houseflies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 15:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the best advice you have for training or studying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 15:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has any serious discussion taken place to study the use of hallucinogens in resolving OCD? If so, who is leading this discussion? If not, do you believe it's something that may happen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 14:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marijuana </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "In Netanyahus Israel, there is only one way to react to a deal that the rest of the West greeted with at least some measure of cautious optimism: fear and paranoia." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 06:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who's the greatest entertainer you have personally seen perform live? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 04:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What made it so good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 04:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm jealous of this submission. That is all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 23:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was down voted for proving a fact people don't want to know? That's a completely intelligent response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Media largely ignoring new report linking fracking to serious illness in humans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 06:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 06:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gray goo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 04:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Germany made it to North American shores] (http://www.washingtonpost.com/local/sunken-world-war-ii-german-u-boat-and-freighter-found-off-coast-of-cape-hatteras/2014/10/21/5374c262-5938-11e4-8264-deed989ae9a2_story.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hitler never orders his forces to march on Russia in WWII, instead turning all of his military on the United States. Who would win? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 21:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ender Wiggin commands the modern day military of Mexico. Can he defeat the US in an all out war? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 05:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the Disney movie 'The Rescuers' originally contained a frame from a softcore porn hidden in a scene </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 05:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 03:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So allowing innocent people to protect themselves makes them safer? This sounds like rocket science to me, it just doesn't make sense... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Chattanooga: How to make military personnel safer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 03:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I believe it may be scientifically impossible to mention a dream I had to someone without that person cutting me off to tell me about their dream. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 03:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 23:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tims more agile. I think he would kill Eric by outlasting him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 22:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound like a dum-dum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 22:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone should mail bashed rats to the Emmy offices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could Miracle-Gro work on certain body parts like it does plants? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm offended by things I see in certain subreddits but there's a man holding a gun to my head, making me read them. What can I do to solve this dilemma? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 19:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 17:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zone Theory helped me to become a happier, healthier, more confident man. I recommend it to everyone I meet. Buy it now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tim Heidecker vs. Eric Wareheim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 16:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cage fight to the death </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who were once wealthy but lost it all, what happened? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 05:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 22:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Bullying" is subjective. If I believe these  policies are bullying towards me, does a black hole open up and devour the solar system? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 22:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You said 3 twice. 3 + 3 = 6. You have 60 characters not including spaces in that sentence. 60+6 = 66. My name is train_subject8959. 66 + 666 = 9/11 Towers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 20:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, I don't understand you. I don't own a fedora. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After I die, how long should I wait before concluding there is no God? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 06:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the input, everyone. I appreciate those that shared some valuable information it's incredibly helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 06:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very helpful, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WYR spend the rest of your life hearing Black Eyed Peas 'I Gotta Feeling' on an infinite loop in your brain or permanently lose your vision? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 06:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question for business owners in Colorado - what is a good resource to learn the costs and processes for starting a business in the state? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 00:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NOT a grow/dispensary job. Looking for any advice in general for the process of starting a business in the state. I'm a resident and have been working on my business plan but I do not quite understand the licensing for the business and would love any input I could get. Thanks. (Also I apologize if this is not an appropriate post, it seems the most logical place to ask, that's all. Thanks !) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit folks who work for large companies, have you ever seen a customer revolt impact your bottom line? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did it happen? What was the long term and short term impacts to your company? What if anything did your company do to address the problem(s)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Freedom of Speech does not mean we support everything people want to say. They have the freedom to say words. Not any words, it doesn't say freedom of all speech does it?"
-The answer I predict we're going to hear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Incredible Hulk is rampaging through Westeros. Can anyone stop him? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they're not practicing any illegal trades, I don't think any subs should be "deserving" of a ban. That's exactly how it starts, convincing people that unpopular people or ideas needed to be eliminated. Then you start moving people towards viewing your beliefs as popular and all others as "dark". The rest is elementary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit set to cull 'dark side' communities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supporting censorship is funny. Yay for shutting down things I don't agree with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. It's not funny. A woman is practically dead. However, the silver lining is that I just saved a shitload on my car insurance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 18:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't imply that at all. I stated "If America was truly a Christian nation". You, in a clear mistake on your part, blurted out "BUT WE GREATEST WAT IF WE NO HEAR!?" That's almost funny if it were not so sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My wife has stage IV breast cancer and it's not looking good for her. Once she's croaked, do I mention this ordeal to women I'm trying to pick up or should I just pretend the marriage never happened? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 17:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If America really was a Christian nation, we'd get our asses kicked. We'd have no military due to fearing sex and we'd get annihilated in battle by turning the other cheek. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 09:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Phoenix vs. Silver Surfer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 07:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If your partner starts putting on some unsightly pounds, casually make comments like "Are you seriously eating another donut" or "That's a pretty disgusting tire you're growing around your midsection" so they'll gradually recognize the weight gain without you offending them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 21 year olds are considered old in BMT. Many reach sergeant before they can legally consume alcohol in the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone under the age of 21 coordinates a surprise global attack on everyone over 21. Who wins? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 17:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 16:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's 1950? Edit: being down voted for this is indicative of a sexist mentality that disrespects stay at home dads or coparent situations with two working adults. Sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You have one trillion dollars and 5 years to plan. Could you defeat Superman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 07:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Tired of parents grounding you? Tell your school counselor they're molesting you. Instant results. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 04:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could the Flash run around the world faster than Superman can verbally count to one million? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 04:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wall E </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 23:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any idea how they expect this to happen? Pretty sure that would be impossible by sheer population advantage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Operation Jade Helm 15 and the hysteria surrounding it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A genuine liberal supports gun rights. A packaged CNN liberal does not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 21:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One example I know of is Third Eye Blinds Semi charmed kind of life which addresses heroin addiction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a story or song people perceive as funny or light hearted but actually has dark or tragic origins? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 21:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 11:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brevity, for Christs sake. You know who preaches? Preachers. And in my experience, preachers tend to be wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Master Splinter becomes bloodlusted upon discovering his distant Womp Rat family has been slaughtered by Luke Skywalker. Can he defeat Luke and have his revenge? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 05:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 04:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 04:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is attacking the threat. Why waste time or effort acknowledging all the players "beneath" him? Strategically, he's doing what any candidate that wants to win would do. Hit the strongest opponent as soon as you can, as hard as you can and don't stop hitting them until one of you stop moving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 03:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want him to be. At this point one of two things will happen. He'll continue gaining popularity in the party and win the nomination in a surprise victory OR the GOP will ostracize him which he won't forgive and we get an independent Trump in the general, bleeding conservative votes and sinking whichever idiot wins the Republican primary. Either way, invest in popcorn now because that stock is about to skyrocket. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump on Jeb Bush: "I don't see him as a factor" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Guys, when a girl says "I like you as a friend", she's testing you to see if you fold. Immediately show her your penis to demonstrate your courage and dedication. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When will the world run out of lightning and what should we do to prepare for it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 07:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legolas vs. Captain America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 05:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> City street fight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot imagine any scenario where the APA/war machine collusion was limited to only this. My gut tells me this is a speck on the tip of the iceberg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: American Psychological Association colluded with U.S. interrogation programs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'C-E-O P-A-O T-K-O' would be a nifty tabloid headline tomorrow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How concerned should we be about the sixth extinction predictions that have been popping up in the news? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 01:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 23:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. Completely and sincerely. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Ozymandias was given 20 years to prepare, could he successfully destroy Silver Surfer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird, he was seriously being considered for guardians of the galaxy too... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 05:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fine, but I'm interested in whether or not anyone had demonstrated vulnerabilities yet. Seems like people would be tripping over one another to reveal flaws in either OS.

EDIT: I distrust practically any and all tech in the US right now for the record but I do believe money is more important to them than US interests at this point. I definitely don't trust them but I also can't set either company sacrificing global market share to satisfy American intelligence agencies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 05:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Predator would encounter pregnant Arnold from junior. Faced with Arnold JACKED by motherly protective hormones, Predator would suffer absolute devastation at the hands of Mother Arnold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 04:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting take on it. Has it or Android 5.1.1 been demonstrated to not be secure? Serious question, I'm genuinely curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sauron has regained The One Ring. Can he kill the Incredible Hulk? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 04:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is the most outrageous government tirade against iOS 8 encryption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 04:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Batman is sucked into the Looney Tunes universe. Can Bugs Bunny defeat him? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 01:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The FBI is attempting to link encryption with ISIS terrorists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aladdin wishes Galactus is destroyed forever. Can Genie do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 09:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disney film Genie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On second thought, maybe I shouldn't have done this one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 09:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We need to go deeper... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 06:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Xpost from r/iasip) Here's Charlie from Always Sunny as viewed through the Deepdream algorithm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AMA Request] Graham Hancock, archaeologist, author and alternative historian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 21:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **My 5 Questions:**

1. What is your opinion regarding the massive skeptic movement taking place in science right now?
2. What first interested you about archaeology?
3. What advice do you have for someone that wants to follow in your footsteps?
4. What is your favorite album?
5. What one book would you recommend everyone read?

**Public Contact Information:** If Applicable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 07:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paul and Obama did not run primary against one another. Clinton and Obama did. You're no less wrong than you were initially. You might even somehow be more wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
