<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7067</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DailyTech - Editorial: Reddit Allows Itself to be Hijacked as a Hate Platform For Racist Bigots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 13:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 09:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  First of all, we are talking about the standard of proof. 
Nobody claimed it was a civil trial. 

 Further:  Tom Brady and the Pats had every opportunity to put on a defense when they told their side of the story at the time of the investigation and again at the hearing.

 They did challenge the evidence. Vehemently.

 They could present any witnesses they would like, Wells would have LOVED to hear from them and so would Goodell.

 Wells is not a prosecutor, he was an investigator. He had no agenda other than to figure out what happened. Goodell is not a prosecutor either, he works for the NFL. The Patriots are part of the NFL and Kraft helps pay his salary.

 No lawyer worth his salt, if they were unbiased, would believe for one second that Brady was unaware that the balls were being deliberately underinflated.

Don't read the comments.  The ignorance is real.  I vomited in my mouth at "[Wells] had no agenda..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 09:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a lot of people like this, autistic or not.  I still don't get how she's different than a "normal person."  She seems like a normal girl to me, is it necessary to label her autistic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 09:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I can in good faith be skeptical about autism, but man is it hard to tell what it is, yet other people watch something like this and see ALL the signs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We would get along this girl and I, except the meth part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone can play the game of snippets and edits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool it there breezy, I can't for the life of me understand autism.  Both the girls in the video seemed normal to me, can you help me empathize with what autism is?  Honestly Jenna looked to me to be a bit introverted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find autism VERY difficult to understand and empathize with.  I've watched this video and many other on autism, but like this video they both seemed normal.  Nothing stood out as out of the ordinary other than one was introvert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you, i'm starting to think autism is made up, they both are normal to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
