<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3438</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not really sure, it's probably 480p. I'm watching it on TV and it's a non HD channel. 

But yeah the lighting is dimmer and not as sharp, which suits Alien which is why the idea came to mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What movies do think look better in non-HD? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching Alien right now in regular format and it seems it suits it better than HD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 21:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The masks that they have on when they rob the bank </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 20:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will never be good and that's not bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He scouted all the locations and got a lot of the casting done, but it was ultimately too expensive to finance. 
 
The whole script is online if you're interested, I believe they're trying to make a miniseries based on the script. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 21:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Napoleon by Stanley Kubrick would have been the movie to end all movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 09:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you said no romance but Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind will rip your heart out and stitch it back together again.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 01:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like the 1920's all right......Nobody gave a shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 17:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you look the guy pouring has nothing but foam in his cup......"It's gonna be a while" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm trying to create a mega list of the best movies to watch stoned! Tell me your favorites! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 22:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any movie, no matter the genre, that you enjoy while getting baked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been really getting into Epics lately, Give me some epic movies that I've never heard of. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 03:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Movies similar to Lawrence of Arabia or Dances with Wolves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 07:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forrest Gump for sure..
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
