<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject541</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 10:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how we do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Redditor makes a phone call. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 09:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ello there! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I typically sit in the drivers seat of my car. However, today I got in the passenger seat. This was my altered view. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 19:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bulldogs always look so sad. It's weird cause their body language says otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 19:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I went to the Bay Area I paid $16 for a pack of cigarettes, a bottle of water, and a lighter. This was at the 5th place I stopped at because all the other ones were more expensive. Granted this was downtown San Francisco, but still. I've never seem more homeless people in my entire life and I don't live in a small city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct me if I'm wrong, but couldn't you just buy a relatively cheap computer off Amazon or really anywhere, for probably less than $500 that would be literally 1,000's of times better than this? 

I would assume their budgets would be hundreds of times this, why couldn't they spend a few hundred once on a replacement? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are at least 5 Family Video/Marco's Pizza in my immediate area, and I know of 3 more closeish, so I'm pretty sure this could be one of many </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 07:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm way late to this, but my assistant manager at a place I worked at a few years ago came very close to having a heart attack, luckily they caught the blockage in time to do a triple bypass. 

Now, his insurance was very good so out of pocket he only had to pay like $8,000 or so, but he got an itemized bill from the hospital, and there were some absolutely ridiculous charges on there... one that immediately springs to mind was $300 some odd dollars for administering baby aspirin (like $30 per pill). 

I literally almost shit my pants looking at that bill. It was insane. The total amount, had he not had insurance, would have exceeded $500,000. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck that. I'd have told my parents to get bent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 02:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was gonna have something to do with tanking or something, threat referring to aggro. This was still good though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 02:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very few things I hate more than the douche that suddenly slows down to 15 in a 45 without warning to start turning, and *halfway* through the turn on goes the signal. I'M ALMOST IN YOUR TRUNK BECAUSE THE PURPOSE OF THE SIGNAL IS TO WARN PEOPLE AROUND YOU THAT YOU'RE **ABOUT** TO TURN. IT'S A LITTLE LATE NOW CUNT. 

I want to punch these people so hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's an annoying yet harmless habit you know you have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 22:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 22:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even know what that is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 22:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 22:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Salami and provolone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm just a guy, but I'll actually answer more than 3 questions and in less than 12 hours! AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 20:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 01:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no way he's ever gonna be able to pay that off either. 

But these dingbat politicians think this is perfectly acceptable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 23:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and I'm pretty sure it was Chantix </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
