<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8210</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None found though description of the person who it may belong to is found [here](http://www.newrepublic.com/sites/default/files/migrated/bazooka_joe.jpg).  Not sure about the blackheads though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bazooka Ammunition Found in Fairfax County Storm Drain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd have to have a screw loose to enjoy hell.

As crazy as it is, when one gets back to the "real world" some wish they could get back to the lunacy.  Hard to explain, I don't understand it, but I sometimes wish I was back in Iraq.  Not that I "enjoyed" it per se, but there was nowhere near as much drama or bullshit that you find here in the "real world."  It's comforting but maddening at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bazooka Ammunition Found in Fairfax County Storm Drain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bazooka Ammunition Found in Fairfax County, VA Storm Drain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem!  Thought 4,000 was outrageous enough and when I checked the article, saw it was a lot more than that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP, you mistyped and forgot a "0" in your title.  I recommend deleting and re-submitting with the accurate, and more ridiculous, number.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

Lieutenant General Sir Adrian Paul Ghislain Carton de Wiart VC, KBE, CB, CMG, DSO (5 May 1880  5 June 1963) was a British Army officer. He served in the Boer War, First World War, and Second World War; was shot in the face, head, stomach, ankle, leg, hip, and ear; survived two plane crashes; tunnelled out of a prisoner-of-war camp; and bit off his own fingers when a doctor refused to amputate them. Describing his experiences in the First World War, he wrote, "Frankly I had enjoyed the war." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Sir Adrian de Wiart served in the Boer War, WWI, WWII, and was shot in the face, head, stomach, ankle, leg, hip, and ear. He survived 2 plane crashes, tunnelled out of a POW camp, and bit off his own fingers when a doctor wouldnt amputate. About WWI, he wrote, "Frankly I had enjoyed the war." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 22:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 1/2 years ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The criminal justice system is designed to fuck people like this man.

Which of the charges below are "designed to fuck" with this guy?

three counts of assault in the fourth degree

one count of disorderly conduct in the second degree 

one count of theft in the third degree 

one count of resisting arrest 

one count of interfering with a police officer

I'm assuming you'll at least say the bottom two because, well, reddit is all about anti-authority and everything.  Nevermind that he was apparently whacking customers with this thing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 20:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> please don't procreate

Already did. You're grounded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 19:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it really fucking matter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 19:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've got [plenty of posts](https://www.reddit.com/user/RedditHypocrite) where all you're doing is bitching and moaning in TIL posts about the content/subject.  If it bothers you that much, remove it yourself from your own "default" or just be a grown up and move on.

If however you just like to troll and complain, then fist yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great.  Thanks for admitting that and letting me know that anything you post is unreliable.  [I wish you luck in your future endeavors.](http://i.giphy.com/fAGln5qp01U9q.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Edit:Going to take your advice though. I shall ignore you now 

So what you're saying now, is that you can't be trusted as you're not a man/woman of your word and are a liar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So people shouldn't talk about places they've never been to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The action did not in anyway indicate me being upset. 

OK

That is in your mind, think what you want.

I will.

Also, rules and etiquette are two separate things. 

Nothing in etiquette against reposts either.  There is against those who complain about them though.

Poorer arguments on top of poor assumptions. Nice.

You get butthurt over reposts.  On reddit.  That's pretty much all anyone needs to know.

And lead by example in this specific case. 

Again. This is reddit.  You take this too seriously.   

 If you wanted me to ignore the post because it was repeated and i am being immature by stating it here, you are setting yourself up in the same area by replying to my 'repeated' comment. 

OK

You are just moving in circles not even realizing that you are calling yourself immature. 

Your deflection attempts are amateur.

A sad life, if you have nothing better to do in your break. 

Coming from the guy who gets butthurt over reddit reposts.  And then reposts comments.  And again, the amateur deflection is just that, amateur.

And i applaud your originality in the style of your reply and coming up with this form of circular arguments. Bravo, the man with all the originality of the world is here!

Thanks!

Edit:Going to take your advice though. I shall ignore you now :) Again, fuck you.

OK! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Learn the rules](https://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/wiki/index#wiki_rule_.233.3A_no_news_or_recent_sources.) before spouting off at people "buddy."

This rule does NOT mean that posts that contain links to news articles over 2 months old are not allowed.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  which in itself is a poor assumption

Actions speak louder than words.

How about you getting riled up on a repeated comment which you deem insignificant anyway. 

Oh I'm not riled up at all.  I'm merely mocking you while taking a break during my work day.

You should have followed your own advice and ignored my comment then!

So you're not going to be a grown up and just ignore things and instead lead the charge to get OPs to remove re-posts even though there is no rule against them?  [Sounds awesome!](http://i.giphy.com/4bMAaXendmGWc.gif)

Lead by example.

Seriously?  Lead what?  Redditors?  Yeah.  OK.

But you had to reply.

Yes.  Because you people amuse me.

Looks like you are just a hypocrite. 

OK

Or would that be Captain hypocrite to you? 

Lacking originality.

I would rather have another deserving post taking up space than a repost of something posted not even a day.

That's why they have up/down vote buttons.  Guess what?  Not everybody saw it the first time around.  Just because you did doesn't mean anything.  Downvote and move on.  You're not some white knight saving the reddit universe.  

People repost after 3-4 months. Cool. Heck, even after a month.

Good for you.  As much as your narcissistic self won't like hearing this, you don't set the standards for others.

But that day itself. That is shitty. 

So what?  I didn't see it the first time around.  I know I'm not the only one.

Obvious stated or do i need reiterate for you?

Is that even a sentence?

Edit: Seems like OP got the message. Fuck you :) 

Still lacking originality.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  News and any sources (blog, article, press release, video, etc.) more recent than two months are not allowed.

Did you read the entire rule?

News and any sources (blog, article, press release, video, etc.) **more recent than two months** are not allowed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A repeated comment and a Repost are not the same things. 

Both are insignificant.

You got your thoughts mixed up.

Nope.

This is a concern.

Seriously?  It's reddit.  Calm down.

That is a title post. 

Thanks Captain Obvious.

The more people point it out the more likely OP will be to rescind the post. 

Or you could just, you know, be a grown up and ignore it.  There is no rule against re-posts after all.  

Though, looking at your stance, i can understand if that explanation sails over your head.

My stance is that you need to step away from the computer and experience more of the real world if a repost upsets you this much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has already been brought to the attention of the OP.  Did you search the comments to make sure you're not making a repost by stating this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newly Discovered Dr. Seuss Book Released This Month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newly Discovered Dr. Seuss Book Released This Month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newly Discovered Dr. Seuss Book Released This Month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 15:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the hell does it matter?  That was 11 hours ago.  Do you think that the same exact people, no more/no less, are the only ones that will see this one?  I for one didn't see the one that was posted last night.  And not knowing it in the first place, I certainly wouldn't have gone browsing TIL to locate it either.

Stick with licking the windows [Corky](http://s3.amazonaws.com/rapgenius/filepicker/bZmcvSCTTXSaNvOpj4f3_57761.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 14:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

In September 2012, Matt Smith stated a desire to see an episode of Doctor Who directed by Sir Peter Jackson, the director of the Lord of the Rings trilogy. Jackson responded positively to the suggestion by saying "name the time and place".[35] In March 2013 he maintained his desire to have an involvement in the show, stating that he would happily accept a Dalek in payment. Steven Moffat stated in August 2013 that Jackson was serious about his desire to direct Doctor Who, and also said that, if it were to happen, there was a good likelihood of filming taking place in New Zealand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Sir Peter Jackson, director of the Lord of the Rings trilogy, had a desire to direct an episode of Doctor Who and stated that he would happily accept a Dalek in payment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 14:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 14:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

The Velo-Dog (also known as a Revolver de Poche) was a pocket revolver originally created in France by Charles-Franois Galand in the late 19th century as a defense for cyclists against dog attacks. The name is a compound word composed of "velocipede" and "dog". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The Velo-Dog was a pocket revolver originally created in France in the late 19th century as a defense for cyclists against dog attacks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 14:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL A man accused of swinging a toy light saber at customers in a toy store used the light saber to break one of the wires on a Taser when police officers responded to the call. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

On 5 November 1950, the Joint Chiefs of Staff (JCS) issued orders for the retaliatory atomic bombing of Manchurian PRC military bases, if either their armies crossed into Korea or if PRC or KPA bombers attacked Korea from there. The President ordered the transfer of nine Mark 4 nuclear bombs "to the Air Force's Ninth Bomb Group, the designated carrier of the weapons ... [and] signed an order to use them against Chinese and Korean targets", which he never transmitted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL In 1950, orders were given for the retaliatory atomic bombing of Manchurian PRC military bases if their armies crossed into or attacked Korea. The President ordered the transfer of nine nuclear bombs and signed an order to use them against Chinese and Korean targets, which he never transmitted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New video shows eruption of riot at West Baltimore intersection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New video shows eruption of riot at West Baltimore intersection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why China Wants a Jeb-vs.-Hillary Race </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Florida Man, 68, padlocked mom in home while going out for crack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man, 68, padlocked mom in home while going out for crack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man, 68, padlocked mom in home while going out for crack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photos show Donald Trump in military uniform, with athletic teams before dodging the Vietnam draft with bull---t injury </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well no kidding.  Why?

Because neither side really gives one damn about vets.  It boils down to what the opposing politician's party is.  All this "respect for the vets" talk is cheap political nonsense that they don't believe as much as you'd like to think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gay Man Fathers 10 Kids With Nine Different Women In 13 Months </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the poor would lose their cases against the rich because it was felt they had incentive to lie for being poor

The more things change, the more they stay the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your titles use of pronouns is so unclear/incorrect

In proper English

Oh Jesus Christ, shut the fuck up.  This is reddit and not a college thesis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Improve relations?"

Screw 'em.  [$625 million dollar + in aid?](http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2012/08/30/us-foreign-aid-by-country_n_1837824.html)  Yeah, sorry, the tax payers of the U.S. would be better served with that money staying put here in the states. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah this is already on the hot page currently sitting at #5. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I think Trump is the shiny object for the media right now.  He's so ridiculous that they have no option other than to give him the coverage because he's not acting like the stereotypical politician.  

Technically he's a contender.  In reality he'll eventually fizzle out.  Personally, I believe he's got some ulterior motive going on that we don't know about yet that will help him make more money.  That's what he is, and always has been, about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernie Sanders is the Donald Trump of the left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, this applies to any politician though.

Q: "What color is the sun?"

A: "Let me tell you about a time when I was in the third grade and realized my American dream......" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to see a stage setup similar to Hollywood Squares.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the type of crap that annoys me.  What it boils down to is not whether or not someone is a veteran but rather what party the person doing the attacking or being attacked is in.

These outbursts about giving respect to vets has gotten very old, very fast.  If any of these politicians give one damn about our vets, I don't give a fuck what party the politician is in, they would step up and take action to actually help our vets and not use them as a political tool.  The reason veterans are veterans anyway is because the politicians couldn't do their job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 01:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need to help politicians rediscover life outside of Washington,

If they need help doing this, they shouldn't be in office.  They are supposed to be representing people outside of Washington anyway, the people who elected them there.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 01:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Presidential hopeful Sen. Marco Rubio (R-Fla.) slammed President Obama for **allowing the United Nations Security Council to vote on the Iran nuclear agreement.**

Kind of how things work Marco.  The U.S. can't tell everyone what to do and expect them to listen/follow all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 01:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prison guards are the scum of the earth.

Based on what?

Any group that hides behind closed doors

Would you prefer they, and the inmates they supervise, were in an unsecured facility?

and claims to represent "the law" and thus above the law is a red flag

How exactly do you come to the conclusion that people claiming to represent the law are then "above the law?"

Billions in profit for the prison unions and millions lobbing against the public interest every year. 

Are you referring to public or private unions?  And in each case, how does it go "against the public interest?"

They are are a cancer on our free society. 

Who do you feel should supervise/monitor the inmates?



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 23:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That article read as if it was part of a high school newspaper.  The author is aware that there are already exceptions for the First Amendment right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

On August 4, 2003, a fire destroyed a Jim Beam aging warehouse in Bardstown, Kentucky. It held about 19,000 barrels of bourbon. Flames rose more than 100 feet from the burning structure. Burning bourbon spilled from the warehouse and set a nearby creek on fire. An estimated 19,000 fish died of the bourbon in the creek and a river. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL A fire destroyed a Jim Beam aging warehouse that held about 19,000 barrels of bourbon in 2003. Burning bourbon spilled from the warehouse and set a nearby creek on fire. An estimated 19,000 fish died of the bourbon in the creek and a river. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shooting closes portion of Route 80 in New Haven </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 15:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The term "cornicione" refers to the raised rim of a pizza. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 14:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 13:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

Soon after the Japanese attacks on Pearl Harbor, the college requirement for pilots was dropped. McMahon immediately enlisted and entered flight training in Dallas, Texas. Afterwards he completed fighter training in Pensacola and obtained his carrier landing qualification. While he was still in flight school, McMahon became an instructor, a role in which his ability to project came in handy. His flight instructor status lasted for two years until he was given orders to report to the Pacific Fleet. However, before he entered combat, atomic bombs were dropped on Hiroshima and Nagasaki which ended the war, and facilitated the cancelation of his orders.

Although the war ended, McMahon continued his service in the Marine Reserves as an officer. Once the Korean War began, McMahon's active duty status was reinstated. His primary role during that war was to fly Cessna O-1 Bird Dogs as a spotter for batteries and Navy and Marine fighter bombers. He flew a total of 85 combat missions and earned six air medals. He retired in 1966 with the rank of colonel.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Soon after the Japanese attacks on Pearl Harbor, Ed McMahon enlisted in the Marine Corps and entered flight training. Though unable to enter combat in WWII, he flew 85 combat missions in the Korean War and earned 6 air medals. He retired in 1966 with the rank of colonel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 13:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 13:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad these people didn't put this kind of energy into something that actually matters and could make a difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whistleblower prison guard paid the price for reporting abuse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 13:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whistleblower prison guard paid the price for reporting abuse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JFK Airport to Open ARK, a Luxury Animal Terminal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JFK Airport to Open ARK, a Luxury Animal Terminal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Father Killed After Son, 19, Runs Stop Sign in Queens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Father Killed After Son, 19, Runs Stop Sign in Queens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Father Killed After Son, 19, Runs Stop Sign in Queens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Father Killed After Son, 19, Runs Stop Sign in Queens N.Y. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man Charged for Treating Cancer Patient with 'Baggie of Dirt' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man Charged for Treating Cancer Patient with 'Baggie of Dirt' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Donald Trump was up to while John McCain was suffering as a prisoner of war </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure how long they've had it.  I stumbled upon it only a few months ago myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sea turtle released off Florida Keys tracked by satellite </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sea turtle released off Florida Keys tracked by satellite </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sea turtle released off Florida Keys tracked by satellite </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man accidentally shoots and kills himself on his 21st birthday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 18:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> preferences about body hair differ

This was never refuted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 17:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you speak for everybody? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 17:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every single thing listed is a personal preference. Nobody can speak for everybody.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 16:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here](http://cdn-static.denofgeek.com/sites/denofgeek/files/styles/insert_main_wide_image/public/rick-astley.jpg?itok=m74SoPZy) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Curb stomp in American History X. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She resigned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys who shave their body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 04:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They lack common sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 01:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes. The old, "But they said it too so it's OK!"

This is a big deal now likely because A) it's Trump and B) in 2000 we hadn't been in an ongoing 13 1/2 year war. 

Regardless, stupid statement no matter who says it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 01:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rick Astley- Never Gonna Give You Up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 01:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moist Cooter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 01:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facebook </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 01:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8675309 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 18:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom's basement doesn't have windows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 18:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 18:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It" being OP's mom? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 17:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The moon landing was fake/staged." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 17:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't pull out. Kid 9 months later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 17:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gin and tonic using Bombay Sapphire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 17:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bitch and moan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 17:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My gun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 22:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He works for Google so he will find out if you are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 15:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So no evidence then. Just a guess. 

Additionally, in regards to your question about accepting things at face value, this is the exact reason I asked a question. Because I won't accept a claim at face value without factual evidence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 13:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You still haven't shown how they are obviously paid for. I'm not asking for a "how to" on marketing. I'm merely asking a simple question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 13:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To discuss?  What's the harm in that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> obvious paid placements

Just because it's on there doesn't mean it's "obvious" it was "paid" for.  In regards to the JD one anyway, haven't read the other.

Mentioning that a company gives away a bottle of JD, to its employees and not customers, is certainly not going to do anything to promote a product.  "Oh wow, they give away stuff to their employees?!  Let me go buy some!"

Additionally, let's take a look at /u/jrcollin138's submission history.  Over two years, at least, of posts/submissions and he/she lives in Connecticut.  I can't imagine someone building up an account for a couple of years just waiting for the right moment to make that JD post.  

Stating that it's an "obvious paid placement" comes off as /r/conspiracy.  Amazingly enough, some people just find things out and find them interesting. 

In regards to the Conan one, what about it tells you it was a paid spot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 01:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure but I guess if it was to buy time you could.  The key here to that question I believe is that this took place in China and, just guessing, but I would think their rules/regulations are a little more lax than places like the U.S. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chuck E. Cheese's is pretty badass.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coffee cups that are missing the bottom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tie my shoes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you OP.  

Rest assured that you've made one fan of the balloon knot happy today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a hair across your ass or something?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not piggy back off of hot page posts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stand naked in my front yard and perform "The Sprinkler" dance while urinating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That one time someone posted a question asking what my pet peeve was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for Kenndoane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sleep with a student </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Working </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The doctor performing a vasectomy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "No" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/brony </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheetos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fifth grade.  Some other kid was in a school play and after changing into his costume he had left his regular clothes in the restroom so I put them into the toilet.  No idea why that sticks out in my mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Artificial heart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1)  People freaking out about it are brainless morons who need to get outside more.

2)  Not at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

Rice was associated with a variety of charitable organizations during his career, primarily on behalf of children, some of which have carried on into his retirement. He was named an honorary chairman of The Jimmy Fund, the fundraising arm of the Dana-Farber Cancer Institute in Boston, in 1979, and in 1992 was awarded that organization's "Jimmy Award", which honors individuals who have demonstrated their dedication to cancer research. Rice is also active in his support of the Neurofibromatosis Foundation of New England. Rice's involvement with Major League Baseball's RBI program (Reviving Baseball in Inner Cities) resulted in the naming of a new youth baseball facility in Roxbury, Massachusetts in his honor in 1999. A youth recreation center in Rice's hometown of Anderson, South Carolina is also named in his honor.

Rice's most notable humanitarian accomplishment occurred during a nationally televised game on August 7, 1982, when he rushed into the stands to help a young boy who had been struck in the head by a line drive off the bat of Dave Stapleton. As other players and spectators watched, Rice left the dugout and entered the stands to help 4-year old Jonathan Keane, who was bleeding heavily. Rice carried the boy onto the field, through the Red Sox dugout and into the clubhouse, where the young boy could be treated by the team's medical staff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Jim Rice, of the Boston Red Sox, rushed into the stands in 1982 to help a young boy who had been struck in the head by a line drive. Rice carried the boy onto the field, through the Red Sox dugout and into the clubhouse, where the young boy could be treated by the team's medical staff. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't aware ethics were a problem in regards to reality shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You and me both.  Recently, while visiting the Museum of Natural History here in D.C., there were 5 people standing in a row taking their selfies in front of one of the dinosaur skeletons.  One of the most ridiculous things I've ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

The Old Order Amish are among the fastest-growing populations in the world. They prohibit the use of contraception and have low infant mortality rates. The average Amish woman can expect to have at least seven live births. Other Plain sects with the same or similar doctrines can be expected to have similarly explosive growth.

Despite this, the Pennsylvania Dutch, which includes Amish, Old Order Mennonite, and Conservative Mennonites are expected to become a smaller percentage of the population as the sects respond to high prices of farmland by spreading out all over the United States and internationally, and the English population spreads out from Philadelphia into suburban and rural areas. Donald Kraybill believes there are Plain sect communities in 47 states. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The Old Order Amish are among the fastest-growing populations in the world. They prohibit the use of contraception and have low infant mortality rates. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

In some cultures of Cameroon, there is a special ceremony featuring cat-eating that is thought to bring good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL In some cultures of Cameroon, there is a special ceremony featuring cat-eating that is thought to bring good luck. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

the mug shots on Red's parole papers are actually photographs of Morgan Freeman's son, Alfonso Freeman. He can also be seen in the scene where Andy arrives at Shawshank.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the mugshot pictures on Red's parole papers in the Shawshank Redemption are actually photographs of Morgan Freeman's son, Alfonso Freeman. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brokeback Mountain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Selfies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Cruz: If you think Washington is going great  then I aint your guy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rick Santorum Suggests Planned Parenthood Is Just As Racist As The Confederate Flag </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China meat smuggling crackdown stokes risky underground trade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Couple Arrested After Infant Found to Have 20 Fractures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3rd Teen Dies in Driver's Ed Crash; 4th Teen Leaves Hospital </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3rd Teen Dies in Driver's Ed Crash; 4th Teen Leaves Hospital </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 03:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HAHAHA!  Love seeing this after the shitshow provided by the anti-Pao clowns who figured she was the one behind all of the changes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 03:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That part was changed afterwards. 

Looking at the history of the article on Wikipedia, it looks like it was changed three times today if I'm reading it correctly.  Not the first time that's happened.  I posted something in TIL once and later in the day, I looked at the wiki page again and the sentence that was my TIL post had been removed/edited by someone on wikipedia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on the response, guessing the seller is also a redditor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's what I'm curious about in this situation. The issues surrounding Planned Parenthood are not new, at least in the world of politics and it seems to heat up every once in awhile. Did anybody do any actual investigating into their practices previously or sit back and do nothing but pay lip service to the media? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And has nothing to support his claims either.  And really, does he need to remind everybody every time he talks that he's a veteran?  I am as well but that certainly doesn't mean I'm an expert into the Iraqi government system and I certainly don't talk about my service much either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's what I'm curious about in this situation.  The issues surrounding Planned Parenthood are not new, at least in the world of politics and it seems to heat up every once in awhile.  Did anybody do any actual investigating into their practices previously or sit back and do nothing but pay lip service to the media? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump: I don't know why I'm meeting Ted Cruz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ted lining up to ride Trumps coat tails. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So was electing Senator Cotton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A House committee and at least two states have opened investigations into Planned Parenthood following the release of an undercover video that shows a Planned Parenthood executive graphically discussing the process of aborting a fetus in a way that preserves its organs  and the costs associated with donating those organs to medical researchers.

Sounds to me like Planned Parenthood was doing what they should do, provide information about services.  

AND it looks like the government will do what they shouldn't do, blow more tax payer money on non-sensical hearings for the sole purpose of politics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we want people to know the dignity that comes from work

I'm surprised the word "dignity" is in Walker's vocabulary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

Sybil Ludington (April 5, 1761  February 26, 1839), daughter of Colonel Henry Ludington, was a heroine of the American Revolutionary War who, mounted on her horse, Star, became famous for her night ride on April 26, 1777 to alert American colonial forces to the approach of the British. Her action was similar to that performed by Jack Jouett or Paul Revere,although she rode more than twice the distance of Revere and was only 16 years old at the time of her action. She was an aunt of Harrison Ludington, a Governor of Wisconsin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Sybil Ludington was a heroine of the American Revolutionary War, famous for her night ride on April 26, 1777 to alert American forces to the approach of the British, similar to the ride of Paul Revere. She rode more than twice the distance of Revere, alone, and was 16 years old at the time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

The boombox quickly became associated with urban society, particularly African American and Hispanic youth. The wide use of boomboxes in urban communities led to the boombox being coined a "ghetto blaster", a nickname which was soon used as part of a backlash against the boombox and hip hop culture. Cities began banning boomboxes from public places, and they became less acceptable on city streets as time progressed.

The boombox became intrinsically linked to hip hop culture and, as Fab Five Freddy puts it, was "instrumental" in the rise of hip hop. Certain models like the JVC RC-M90 and the Sharp GF-777 were known as the boombox kings, having the power to drown out other ghetto blasters; they were frequently used in music battles. The Beastie Boys embraced the boombox as a signature, The Clash always had a boombox with them, and Schoolly D carried around a Conion 100cf in the UK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The wide use of boomboxes in urban communities led to the boombox being coined a "ghetto blaster. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

The 1968 Mothers of Invention song "Let's Make The Water Turn Black" tells a true story of an adolescent acquaintance of composer Frank Zappa who habitually saved his own extracted mucus on the pane of his bedroom window. An episode of Seinfeld entitled "The Pick" deals with the social stigma of publicly picking one's nose. Harry, a character in Requiem for a Dream mentions enjoying picking his nose in the first chapter of the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The song "Let's Make The Water Turn Black" tells a true story of an adolescent acquaintance of composer Frank Zappa who habitually saved his own extracted mucus on the pane of his bedroom window. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for nevebe003 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **THE** inventor?

Edwin Binney (18661934) is best known for **his invention (along with his cousin C. Harold Smith**) of the Crayola crayon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

The photograph was extremely popular, being reprinted in thousands of publications. Later, it became the only photograph to win the Pulitzer Prize for Photography in the same year as its publication, and came to be regarded in the United States as one of the most significant and recognizable images of the war, and quite possibly the most reproduced photograph of all time. Three Marines depicted in the photograph, Harlon Block, Franklin Sousley, and Michael Strank, were killed in action over the next few days. The three surviving flag-raisers were Marines Rene Gagnon, Ira Hayes, and Navy Corpsman John Bradley. The latter three became celebrities after their identifications in the photograph. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The photograph of the flag raising on Iwo Jima became the only photograph to win the Pulitzer Prize for Photography in the same year as its publication. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

In 1979, Scott Spiegel wrote, produced and directed a short film entitled Attack of the Helping Hand, which featured a "Hamburger Helper" oven mitt as a killer glove.

Further detail about the short film:

[Attack of the Helping Hand](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Attack_of_the_Helping_Hand) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Hamburger Helpers Helping Hand was featured in a 1979 short film entitled Attack of the Helping Hand, which featured a "Hamburger Helper" oven mitt as a killer glove. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant text:

Previous attempts to use video games to halt, or even reverse, cognitive decline related to aging have generated mixed results. The latest attempt, led by neuroscientist Adam Gazzaley from the University of California, San Francisco, kept it simple by targeting a single cognitive skill: multitasking. In a study published Wednesday (September 4) in Nature, Gazzaley and his colleagues demonstrated that a handful of training sessions behind the wheel in a 3-D racing game could improve multitasking performance, and that such improvements lasted up to six months.

Gazzaleys group developed the game, called NeuroRacer, to test the multitasking abilities of subjects ranging in age from 20 to 70. NeuroRacer requires players to steer a car around a winding track with a finger on their left hand while signaling the presence of randomly appearing road signs of a particular shape and color with a finger from their right. The researchers found that initial game performance declined linearly with increasing age.

After playing the game for just 12 hours over a four-week period, 60- to 85-year-old subjects improved to the point that they outperformed 20-year-old subjects who had never played it before. The observed performance improvements lasted for six months following the initial training.

Certain cognitive abilities that were not specifically targeted by the gamesuch as working memory and sustained attentionwere also improved among the older subjects. NeuroRacer doesnt demand too much of those particular abilities, Gazzaley told Nature. So it appears that the multitasking challenge may put pressure on the entire cognitive control system, raising the level of all of its components.

Gazzaley cautioned against over-hyping his teams results: Video games shouldnt now be seen as a guaranteed panacea, he told Nature.

Other scientists are taking a wait and see approach. The science is still too early to know how much it can help, Douglas Gentile, head of the Media Research Lab at Iowa State University, told The Wall Street Journal.

Emil Toescu, a neuroscientist at the University of Birmingham, agreed. The technology is not yet sufficiently proven to recommend itself for immediate adoption by older people, he told The Telegraph. But, on the other hand, a moderately complex gaming experience is always good fun, whatever the age, and it cannot do damage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Training for several hours with a racing video game improves the multitasking abilities of 60-85 year olds for up to six months. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Town, State

Odenton, MD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police: Chickens seized from Odenton man euthanized </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chickens seized from Odenton, MD man euthanized </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iowa community drops plan to shock official for fundraiser </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Burlington police warn public of high-risk sexual predator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> South Carolina Sen. Lindsey Graham said the deal equals a "death sentence for the state of Israel."

Holy crap I'm so sick of hearing about Israel.  And let's see some evidence to back up these claims.  Just saying it doesn't make it true.  Graham and McCain are just a couple of war mongers at this point anyway.  I can't believe anybody actually takes them seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeb Bush was first out of the gate, more than 24 hours before the deal was actually signed. He boasted on his YouTube channel: History is full of examples of when you enable people or regimes who dont embrace democratic values you get a bad result...its called appeasement.

Iran-Contra (Reagan)

Osama bin Laden (Reagan)

Saddam Hussein (Reagan)

The Taliban (Reagan)

To name a few.........

Let's go give some more weapons to freedom fighters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posting in /r/shitpost when the link was already posted here yesterday. Go figure..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry you're gullible enough to fall for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With that in mind, here is a rough (and only partial) inventory of the stuff **mankind** has left on the moon: 

Read the fucking article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's what you call taking a troll for a ride.  

No surprise he was a troll from the outset.  They like attention and want to feel like they are getting under someone's skin.  However, when they run across someone who is bored as hell at work with a couple of hours still to go, they're going to get someone to bait them along.  

I posted that TIL yesterday, his response was last night.  I went back into the TIL to have fun with one of the many trolls.  It's really not that complicated and as much as I'm sure you'd like to believe it, no, he didn't "b8" me.  I was bored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rick Santorum: Scott Walkers wife could make him soft on gay marriage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Texans, in particular, feasted on colorful conspiracy theories that, thanks to the Internet, went viral -- including one that involved a supposed plan to convert old Walmart stores into death camps and another about a plot to round up and remove political dissidents. There also was speculation about the name, Jade Helm, and a secret link to China. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Volunteer watchdog group dispatches to western states to monitor 'Jade Helm' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 00:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's busy fisting your mom.

And dude, really?  I posted this thing four days ago. Shoot me your Paypal email so I can send you $.25 to go buy yourself a life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump campaign ad appears to feature German Nazis marching under White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
