<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9063</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Be more dog - Korin the cat sits for bacon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 11:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 08:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awesome film! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 13:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you wash your hands after you're done though? That's the real man question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 10:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cute, very cute. But it's a Mac. Better teach her to play on a real machine. She seems pretty disssssapointed in your choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dustin Diamond "Screech" from "Saved by the bell" not charged with murder over stabbing incident despite internet rumours. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 01:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 17:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well its something you would do really isn't it! Silly girl and her silliness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 16:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And she's better than me at poker...... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 16:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm OP is a girl, she's my wife..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 11:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very helpful, it's not actually for me but my wife so I will get her to read all your helpful posts and see what she thinks of them! Perhaps soon I will post some of her first work! 

Again thanks a lot guys never before has a sub been this helpful to me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 22:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woman, you're clumsy.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want to start doing simple 2d computer based animation - any tips? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 10:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there, I'm interested in starting up animation as a small hobby, I was just curious as to what programs would be useful in starting myself off? I'm looking for any program that might have lots of pre-set templates that would be able to help me in studying the basic concepts of animation with an easy pre-cursor to more advanced things.

Sorry if this sounds like a silly request, have no real background on animation programs, the only thing I've really done in the past is stop motion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harry Potter/Blackadder - Crazy Hagrid Mash Up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 02:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 20:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was wondering where In this post someone would mention the blatant mis leading title about being left at the altar. Original news post on reddit suggests it was a week before. Not at the altar as this post says. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 10:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was only a phone camera, get off my case :( lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 23:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah this video didn't capture it very well but local reports from people suggested it did touch down ever so slightly out of sight from where i was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
