<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1529</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ISIS Transforming Into Functioning State That Uses Terror as Tool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ISIS Transforming Into Functioning State That Uses Terror as Tool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US officials target social media, encryption after Chattanooga shooting: Did "IS" propaganda inspire the Chattanooga shooter? There's no evidence to back the claim, but some officials are already calling for access to encrypted messages and social media monitoring. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US officials target social media, encryption after Chattanooga shooting: Did "IS" propaganda inspire the Chattanooga shooter? There's no evidence to back the claim, but some officials are already calling for access to encrypted messages and social media monitoring. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senator Lindsey Graham will probably have to change his cellphone number. Thats because Donald J. Trump...brandished a card showing the South Carolina senators phone number from the stage at a speech on Tuesday afternoon, reading the digits aloud and encouraging people to dial. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senator Lindsey Graham will probably have to change his cellphone number. Thats because Donald J. Trump...brandished a card showing the South Carolina senators phone number from the stage at a speech on Tuesday afternoon, reading the digits aloud and encouraging people to dial. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Forget About the New BRICS Bank: The New Development Bank, which opened today in Shanghai, has been overshadowed recently by the AIIB. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scores of Native American demonstrators protested at the US Capitol on Tuesday against a proposed $6bn copper mine in Arizona at a site that members of the Apache tribe say is sacred. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simulations lead to design of near-frictionless material </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A scientific research team spent seven years tracking the movements of skyscraper-high waves in the South China Sea. Scientists are trying to understand how these waves, which rarely break the ocean surface, develop, move and dissipate underwater. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook Inc cannot challenge search warrants New York prosecutors used to get information from its site on hundreds of users suspected of Social Security fraud, a state appeals court said on Tuesday, in a decision likely making it harder for New Yorkers to keep their digital lives private. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With Tuesdays Speech, Donald Trump Continues to Blow Up the 2016 GOP Primary Field </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate Republicans Said to Mull New Tactic for Easing Dodd-Frank </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Press release from conference with abstracts](https://www.alz.org/aaic/_downloads/tues-8am-women-risk.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Older women with mild memory impairment worsened about twice as fast as men, researchers reported Tuesday, part of an effort to unravel why women are especially hard-hit by Alzheimer's. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The European Court of Human Rights condemned Italy on Tuesday for failing to provide legal recognition to same-sex couples and said the country should introduce some form of civil union for gay couples. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The European Court of Human Rights condemned Italy on Tuesday for failing to provide legal recognition to same-sex couples and said the country should introduce some form of civil union for gay couples. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The bullies who run Kosovo: Hashim Thai and the rest of the Kosovar political elite are frustrating investigations into murder, kidnapping, and trafficking in human organs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama on Iran deal critics: They were wrong on Iraq too: The administration has presented the negotiations with Iran as a choice between peacefully preventing a nuclear Iran and going to war with the Islamic Republic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama on Iran deal critics: They were wrong on Iraq too: The administration has presented the negotiations with Iran as a choice between peacefully preventing a nuclear Iran and going to war with the Islamic Republic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new report on child welfare that found more U.S. children living in poverty than before the Great Recession belies the fanfare of the nations economic turnaround. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new report on child welfare that found more U.S. children living in poverty than before the Great Recession belies the fanfare of the nations economic turnaround. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans chose different path when John Kerry's war record was questioned: As the presidential candidates defend John McCain and other US veterans, the 2004 attacks on secretary of states war record tells another story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans chose different path when John Kerry's war record was questioned: As the presidential candidates defend John McCain and other US veterans, the 2004 attacks on secretary of states war record tells another story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Clooney seeks to expose those who fund and profit from wars in Africa: The Oscar winner has launched a project with US human rights activist John Prendergast to investigate the flow of money in and out of conflict zones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The EU fell short Monday of an agreed target for the relocation of 40,000 asylum-seekers across Europe. Interior and justice ministers secured pledges from member countries to take about 32,000 refugees and pushed a deadline for completing the pact until the end of the year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.N. Security Council on Monday backed Iran's nuclear agreement with world powers but the Islamic Republic's Revolutionary Guards attacked the resolution, underlining powerful opposition to the deal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The House will take up a bill this week blocking funding for so-called "sanctuary cities" that resist turning over immigrants to federal authorities. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israeli Ambassador Courts Black Lawmakers Ahead of Iran Vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine cant survive on its own: The United States could provide the help they need. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Los Angeles County public housing agency and two Mojave Desert cities have reached a $2 million settlement to resolve allegations they discriminated against black people by discouraging them from living in their communities, the Department of Justice announced Monday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 23:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP GOD DAMN IT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean they miss the very best and the very worst... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 07:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah well sorry about that, hope it didn't reflect poorly on LGBT as a whole. There are some thirsty-ass creepers I've dealt with too. Really sad, most of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israels ongoing opposition to the nuclear deal signed with Iran has put it at odds with almost the entire international community and the tension was clear to see during yesterdays meeting in Jerusalem between prime minister Binyamin Netanyahu and visiting British foreign secretary Phillip Hammond </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 02:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hungary plans to close its permanent refugee shelters in towns and cities and set up temporary camps outside urban areas instead, the latest response to a surge in migrants crossing its borders. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 21:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hungary plans to close its permanent refugee shelters in towns and cities and set up temporary camps outside urban areas instead, the latest response to a surge in migrants crossing its borders. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 21:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> France Foils Plot To Attack Army Base and Behead Senior Officer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 21:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> America's best program for the poor may be even better than we thought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 fundraising shows power tilting to groups backed by wealthy elite </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Protesters wave Confederate flags as first black president drives by in a motorcade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "A trove of thousands of Saudi documents recently released by WikiLeaks reveals in surprising detail how [Saudi Arabia's] goal in recent years was not just to spread its strict version of Sunni Islam  though that was a priority  but also to undermine its primary adversary: Shiite Iran." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 11 Planes Struck by Lasers Approaching Newark Airport </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rudeness in the workplace isnt just unpleasant: its also contagious. Encountering rude behavior at work makes people more likely to perceive rudeness in later interactions, a study shows. That perception makes them more likely to be impolite in return, spreading rudeness like a virus. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe on Thursday pushed through legislation in the lower house of parliament that could see troops sent to fight abroad for the first time since World War Two, despite thousands of protesters overnight chanting and holding up placards reading "No War, No Killing." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016's Campaign War Chests Are Just Jewelry Boxes Next To The Super PACs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian President Vladimir Putin said on Thursday calls for a U.N. tribunal to be set up to prosecute suspects in the downing of a Malaysian airliner in a rebel-held part of Ukraine were counterproductive and premature. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian President Vladimir Putin said on Thursday calls for a U.N. tribunal to be set up to prosecute suspects in the downing of a Malaysian airliner in a rebel-held part of Ukraine were counterproductive and premature. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Europes dirty little secret is Greece will never pay back its debt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netflix CEO tells subscribers to brace for higher-priced plans in the future </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Turns to U.N. to Outmaneuver Congress: Washington is working on a new Security Council resolution making the nuclear deal legally binding on the next president. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Turns to U.N. to Outmaneuver Congress: Washington is working on a new Security Council resolution making the nuclear deal legally binding on the next president. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. authorities working with law enforcement officials abroad have shut down the Darkode online forum used by cybercriminals around the world and charged 12 people linked to the site, the Justice Department said on Wednesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. authorities working with law enforcement officials abroad have shut down the Darkode online forum used by cybercriminals around the world and charged 12 people linked to the site, the Justice Department said on Wednesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Phone app can identify behaviors linked to depression, study shows: The average daily phone use for depressed people was about 68 minutes and about 17 minutes for non-depressed individuals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Phone app can identify behaviors linked to depression, study shows: The average daily phone use for depressed people was about 68 minutes and about 17 minutes for non-depressed individuals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Italy takes step toward legalizing pot: Even members of Prime Minister Matteo Renzi's party voted for the measure, a first step toward full legalization. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greek Parliament accepts austerity; protests erupt on Athens' streets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
