<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2003</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 15:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *You won't believe what this app did for me! [Click here](http://#) to find out now!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 15:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you could have said he was... barred from entry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 15:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm trying to imagine what it must have looked like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 15:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, this is the country which owned practically half the world but decided to let them have independence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 15:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 15:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 15:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's my wife.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 15:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um... pass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 15:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more of a guideline though. amirite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 15:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By the hacker named 4chan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 15:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you fart in front of your close girlfriends? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 15:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a summoner and I object to your association of my kind with nerds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Copyright laws would be ineffectual.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Esmerelda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many children do you really have? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quackstar - Coming This Fall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I now have the ability to bend awesomeness out of movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jalopnik editor takes notice of his plight and is on the case: http://www.reddit.com/r/teslamotors/comments/3e0fa9/saleen_is_trying_to_get_an_injunction_against_me/ctaxlga </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> u/FredTesla speaks out against shady practices of a penny stock company, ends up being sued by its CEO for "defamation" and now faces bankruptcy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good screener for warrants/options with expiry dates 5 years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a way to find all warrants/options with expiry dates of 5 years? Thanks very much in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good screener for warrants/options with expiry dates 5 years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a way to find all warrants/options with expiry dates of 5 years? Thanks very much in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good screener for warrants/options with expiry dates 5 years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a way to find all warrants/options with expiry dates of 5 years? Thanks very much in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 10:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Shit." 

\- all wars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Friend knocked out this gem today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 10:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The transition is incredible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 10:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 10:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just message the moderators. They'll be more than happy to help you remove it. Same principle as companies complaining to host sites about pirated software. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm 30 Years Old and just realized that nobody knows what they're doing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 10:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 10:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [When he returned to base](http://www.livememe.com/ccrlkkh) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I thought this only happened in the movies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 10:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I thought this only happened in the movies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 10:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That little jump at the end </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 10:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That little jump at the end </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 10:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Is Feminism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 09:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Incredible Self-Defense Technique </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 09:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Incredible Self-Defense Technique </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 09:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Incredible Self-Defense Technique </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 09:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 09:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> isn't that dirty? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 09:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're saying this from what source..? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clever trick to get ketchup out of the bottle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Winnie The Pooh? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the European Union has an entire legal chapter dedicated to ensuring the quality standards of cucumbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I found the Lion Turtle [no spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am currently working at a fund. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great! Do you think freezing fresh veges would have the same benefits as buying frozen bags?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apples cash pile crosses $200 billion for the first time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha alright thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chopsticks (r/beamazed) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> get a gigantic mirror. cheap, easy to maintain, makes the room bigger. I was in a tiny toilet yesterday which couldn't have been 6' x 6', but there was a ceiling to waist-height mirror which made the room look dramatically more spacious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see, so what if I don't vary the veggies? Say I only stick to carrot, peas and corn because they're affordable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going for an interview for Senior Equity Analyst at a value-oriented firm. What questions would they ask? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that I'll be expected to lead a small team of junior analysts, and teach them the ropes. Will be reporting directly to the head and other fund managers. I'm quite confident in my analytical abilities with regards to value investing, but just thought about prepping for any interview questions which might catch me off guard. 

Fund managers of value investing firms, what would you ask?

(firm is more of a long-term good business Buffett type, not net-net or event-driven type) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it unhealthy to eat frozen Mixed Vegetables (those frozen bags of carrot, peas   corn) as my only source of vegetables? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more for the convenience than anything; I find I cook at irregular intervals and as such when I do cook, it's easier to just boil a bag of frozen veges that will never spoil than to prep veges that spoil within a week. I heard that frozen vegetables retain the same amount of nutrients as fresh. Is this sustainably healthy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The difference between normal people and Redditors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trick Dog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trick Dog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trick Dog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A show about kn0thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bot using Markov Chains (a kind of AI algorithm) pretending to be human, strikes gold </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 11:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 10:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> duh. CFA. no question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 09:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Here's a great answer by /u/holdoffhathcock:  https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/3djsya/soldiers_of_reddit_what_is_something_you_wish_you/ct68lra?context=3

You have to memorize a truly, truly exhausting amount of information and be able to make calculations on the fly. You'll probably carry a calculator wherever you go as well as a little notebook full of tables. Some guys glue their notes to the stock of their rifle.

Look at the problem of putting a bullet on target at 300-400 meters, which is a little bit longer than a city block. At that distance, it's more or less point of aim point of impact, which means you don't have to do any adjusting, just point and shoot, pow. Past 500 meters, things start getting fun, and past 800 is basically magic. At that range, you're not pointing your rifle at the target. At that range, you're aiming at the air above it and somewhat off to the side. A bullet doesn't arc up and down like a basketball.

Gravity pulls down on the projectile as soon as it leaves the barrel. Air resistance pushes against the projectile, slowing it and sloughing it off to the side. The density of the air does the same thing, and makes the curve more lopsided and steep. How high above sea level you are has a huge effect on the path of the bullet, at higher altitudes, the projectile will travel farther and faster. Humidity has to be accounted for, for the same reason. Temperature, not only the ambient temperature but the temperature of the propellant in the ammunition you're loading. A bullet that has been warmed in the sun is going to hit about 20 inches higher at 1000 meters than a cold bullet. The rifling spins the projectile, at a 12 inch twist it will make a full rotation once for every 12 inches of travel. This means at 1000 meters it's going to spin about 3600 times, and the spin makes it drift to the side, sort of like a curveball if you like baseball comparisons. Are you aiming uphill or downhill? Aiming downhill you'd probably guess you need to aim a little lower, and you'd be right. But you also aim low while firing up-grade.

That's all math, that can be accounted for and adjusted for pretty simply with practice. It's wind. Wind is the motherfucker. A soft breeze will push you way off target when you're shooting out past 500 meters. But, when the projectile travels past 500 meters, the air it travels through isn't going to be the same that whole way down range. Think about the way a bird floats on swirls of hot air, and imagine trying to make a bullet travel a straight line through a whole series of those. Maybe where you're standing the wind is 3.5mph traveling north. Well, 300 meters out the wind is pushing in the opposite direction. 500 meters out it's blowing harder. 800 meters out there's dead air, and at 1200 meters there's a draft off the side of a tall building. There's no way to account for that, so you learn to scan your environment and make educated guesses. Watching the way dust and trash blows down the street, and watching the way laundry flutters while it dries on a balcony. Watching the direction grass and trees are bent in the breeze. You have to visualize this bizarre corkscrew of wind patterns that you want to shoot through.

You're still not done! Have you fired your rifle recently? Because a clean cold bore shot will come out slightly different than a warm shot, after the inside of the barrel gets coated with copper from the path of the bullet. You're constantly zeroing your weapon, finding out how it digests different loads of ammunition at different temperatures. And again, the temperature of the bullet is going to affect the path.

So we'll take a shot at 1250 meters. Pretend we're using an M24 with M118LR cartridges that came from a cool, dry place. You know your zero, you crank the bullet-drop compensator as high as it will go, to 1000 meters, calculate the ballistic correction for the extra 250 meters, which is probably going to be another good 9 feet, so you'll hold off using the dots on your reticle, which means you're aiming with the little dots below the crosshair instead of dead center. Slightly off to the side to compensate for the spin you know is happening, and what you guess is sort of going to happen when the wind throws it off balance. You're ready, you pull the trigger.

In the space between pulling the trigger and the propellant igniting, which is 22/1000th of a second, the average walking pace puts a person an inch away from where they were when you fired. If they're running, they move about two inches. For simplicity's sake, let's pretend your target isn't moving. 1250 meters is far enough for a bullet to float above the ground for several seconds, which means the earth rotates underneath the projectile and causes it to hit off-center even more than if it weren't beaten by wind, cutting through the air, fighting humidity, and everything else.

After all that, it's going to be an absolute miracle if you hit your target on the first shot. You're probably going to miss. Luckily, you have a spotter who can watch the path of the projectile and tell you exactly what adjustment to make before firing again. You're almost always going to fire two or three times at extreme distances before you actually hit what you're aiming at.
But "sometimes one shot, sometimes one kill" doesn't look as cool on a t-shirt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I found the Flat Earth Turtle (xpost r/beamazed) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book Review: Billionaire Howard Marks' 'The Most Important Thing Illuminated' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 05:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diver loses his flipper while freediving 100 ft into a well (turn on sound to hear his gasps for air) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pixar's new animated film </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pixar's new animated film </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 18:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *ahem* **The** Victor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Square Inc. - A detailed case study about the conflicts between business and finance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't burn your hand on the stove. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL SquareEnix is worth less today than it was right after Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within bombed at the box office </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What are you better at your job at than your boss? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woah dude! (x-post r/BeAmazed) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The future is here (x-post r/BeAmazed) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swing Batter Batter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swing Batter Batter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whale (x-post r/BeAmazed) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Day on the Job as a Data Analyst </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunset Garden in Fluorescent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does living next to a power transmission tower significantly affect your health? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First day as a financial analyst... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 11:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 10:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't really have to. With that much platinum available it would become feasible to develop fuel-cell batteries for electric vehicles. What I'd do is partner with a bunch of car companies in an equity-for-materials exchange (e.g. Tesla) where I became the supplier of the platinum and they give me stock instead of cash. Refuse to partner with anyone who doesn't give you favorable outcomes, while leaving enough on the table for friendlies to profit. With the cash you'd encourage R D into fuel-cell technology with the goal of putting a fuel-cell vehicle in 20% of American homes by Year 10. 

Keep in mind you already have the reputation of being the first company to harvest materials from a gigantic space asteroid, that's guaranteed to give you brand equity. Pump a few stories each year in the media on fuel-cell battery progress, get the first electric vehicles rolling off the assembly line in 5 years. Pretty sure all the stock in companies you exchanged your asteroid for will skyrocket. Continue development into heavy vehicles, promote a CO2 free future agenda, and continue expanding on your 20% monopoly. You'll probably be a trillion dollar company in 30 years. 

As far as how a government could profit, you'd do the same except that your target would be a net 1% increase in GDP instead of stock ownership in car companies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 10:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Started out as a baby. Now I'm 6 feet tall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is this supposed to cover? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 09:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 08:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is in every conceivable way. With small businesses you're starting from the bottom up with an arbitrary goal, without any meaningful way to quantize what you set out to achieve. You're basically running on hope. With a big business, or at least an SME in a dominant local position, you can say with reasonable certainty that we'll make X dollars on Y date. With a small business you're at the mercy of the business gods, e.g. big retailer moving in and draining demand, economic crisis sapping the pockets of your would-be customers, fire started two blocks down blocking the street, bad publicity from unrelated event halfway around the world, Paypal blocking your account for 90 days, etc. Ever heard stories of Greek mortals trying to defeat the gods of Mount Olympus? It's not an inaccurate representation. With business, it's more about luck and persistence than it is about actual finance.

You hear a lot about the heroes who survived; you never hear about those who died in vain. Dead men tell no tales. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What are you better at your job at than your boss? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 06:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> zeroth world problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just one question... why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 09:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just one question... why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 09:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 19:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch this video: http://youtu.be/GqA42M4RtxE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 19:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually, Kidney.org would be the kidney. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 19:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that the part responsible for the seizure? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 19:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Believe in yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 19:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! I use WebMD too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 19:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit would be Alzheimer's  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time for Lobster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 18:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 18:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it's kickasstorrents.com, which asks you to download an .exe file to "access" torrents.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 18:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the best time, bot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which famous quote would sound the funniest in broken grammar? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 17:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sniper talks about the math that goes behind a sniper shot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 06:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 05:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Sir, you need a big cart." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's set in Vietnam.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But did he see why kids loved it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to take advantage of economies of scale and buy them in bulk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 20:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Outsider CEOs

Its Earnings That Count  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This 360 video has me smiling like a little girl watching the train for the first time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 20:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 20:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a longtime Apple shareholder. Apple's only major asset right now is the iPhone and associated assets like brand. iPad/Mac doesn't really have room to grow. Apple Pay isn't going to kill anyone anytime soon, and its contribution to bottom line for the medium term is negligible. Apple Watch isn't going to be the next paradigm. I say this with the authority of someone with a decade of tech experience.

At this point you can kinda expect growth to be powered exclusively by the iPhone and buy backs. I'm giving it about 9% EPS growth going forward. Unless there's a new development I'd say the 17x P/E is a pretty accurate valuation. 

Google on the other hand is killing it, with sustainable 15-20% EPS growth going forward. They're pretty much like Visa or MasterCard in the FCF department. They also rely on only one thing to power earnings, but Search is such a huge moat I don't worry about it. The only problem is the high P/E of 28. That puts it pretty much on par with AAPL as an investment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 20:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...about what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 20:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you still here?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 20:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gesundheit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 20:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In what way is this passive aggressive? I'd honestly think I just met a friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 19:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 19:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 19:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my house we just apply toothpaste.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 19:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize people just tolerate you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 19:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't let your dreams be dreams </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 19:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless people don't actually do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 18:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You finished the storyline, game assets, game mechanics and music score for an 80 hour game in 2 years?

Do you even work bro? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 13:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any tips for a non US Big 4 audit to get into the US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [](/stonerdog) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No he's mysterious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know what hungry meant until I saw this.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it listed under endangered species? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's literally a pound of melted sugar. What did you expect? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's better if you don't know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean like a barbecue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 08:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the problem is that these sites have computers programmed with click bait titles to garner the highest ad revenue. Guess which headlines get the most attention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 04:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's understandably upset. He's a pigeon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> u/nite_ scores 5x LG G4 smartphones worth $2,400 for 5 cents on Amazon Prime Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 04:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 03:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're just dense. Not sure which is worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a tiny house for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saudi has a decade worth of positive current balance. And they're extremely aggressively trying to move away from oil into tourism. The only thing that would destroy them is ISIS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe Mark Zuckerberg is cheating on his wife with your girlfriend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody cares coz you're rich.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Induction Pans, how do they work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not how it works </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Picture of Mass Relay by NASA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dunkin' Donuts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 03:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 03:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw no problem. Remember, the world doesn't revolve around us. A pessimist would say that means the world is uncaring. An optimist would say that our problems aren't really that big in the grand scheme of things. Take life slowly one step at a time if big steps are too much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 03:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Request] Neural pathways forming in her brain as she watches the train](http://i.imgur.com/hlrvyFg.gifv) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Tree Friend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you think your day is bad... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy gets fed up with engagement photos, reenacts them with a burrito </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 19:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy gets fed up with engagement photos, reenacts them with a burrito </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 19:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found this gem on Facebook today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 19:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little girl sees train for the first time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 19:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washing Machine Execution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suddenly ALL the guys on the rig want a piece of the stuff and he's running a petroleum jelly-stock exchange. He's all smiles making $5 a day (!) and his kids finally get to go to school again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see, thanks a lot! This was exactly the kind of answer I was looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I mean bourses? like BATS, but listed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a scientist not an accountant. Traitor! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found one which looks pretty attractive  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-CEO of Reddit, Yishan Wong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK thanks for the correction. I guess what I meant was how does one analyze exchanges? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 10:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fine, I find that passionate people make better investors than professionals. Yeah I'm doing that now, just want to get some feedback from others who have done the same. At this point profits seem to mainly depend on: i) volume/activity, and ii) tracking the stock market in general. So when it's up it's up, and when it's down it's down. It can't be as simple as that, so I wanted to ask if there is anything I might be missing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 09:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Magikarp used Flail! Mewtwo fainted! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Real Enemy of Reddit isn't Ellen Pao </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 09:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors after realizing that Ellen Pao had been against banning subreddits all along </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 09:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you look for when analyzing   investing in stock exchanges? (e.g. NYSE, NASDAQ, DOW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 09:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking the main one is frequency of activity. Anyone else researched exchanges? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting an IUD contraceptive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 08:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 08:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember to time it just as the F-16 passes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 07:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's actually a good reason for this. The medical logistics system is extremely fractured and messed up. It may seem like there's one cohesive system with programs like Medicaid in place, but it's more of an umbrella of a thousand little fiefdoms (hospitals) than a single kingdom (government). Each of these hospitals closely guard their costs so that they can remain competitive, while suppliers individually negotiate with each hospital to secure the best prices. It's a cutthroat world in medicine; if your prices were known publicly while others kept theirs secret, you would quickly go out of business as suppliers and customers picked and chose. 

As a result, literally nobody, not even the government, can pinpoint the actual average market price for a particular strain of medicine. That's why you get very different prices for the same medicine between different states; you can even see huge spreads between hospitals in the same state. Add to this the fact that medical aid isn't exactly a price elastic market - if I break an arm, I'm not going to go to a hospital in the next city just because it's cheaper there. 

Since the insurance companies don't know the average prices, they have to model their risks based on the price quoted by the highest hospital. As a result, insurance becomes very expensive; so the hospitals adapt to the insurance environment by billing the maximum amount possible. Billing the actual costs isn't feasible if they are to recoup what they pay for insurance; and it isn't feasible for insurance companies to provide coverage at the level mandated by governments by modelling risks on median costs. This creates a vicious cycle where hospital bills and insurance prices become grossly inflated, but nobody wins. Add to this the fact that provision of medical aid is mandatorily and vigorously encouraged by the government, and you have very little incentive for the market to withdraw to a lower price level. 

tl;dr: it's not a problem with any particular individual; it's just the way the system is. The only way to correct prices is to publicly publish prices in all hospitals; good luck with that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3000 Feet Deep </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 07:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Humvee Parking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 07:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Humvees are Awesome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 07:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enjoying the City Skyline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 07:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is not CGI; this is real-life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 07:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Medical students at the University of Florida, Drexel University and the University of Wisconsin have designed a Prostate Exam Simulator, i.e. a Robot Asshole </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 07:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prostate Exam Simulator at Drexel University </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 07:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to talk to customer service </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 07:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
