<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8652</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And SJW sounds like a  good thing to be too.  Social Justice....  yeah, that's an evil thing to want.   Who would want that?     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is still a bug that has not been fixed.   It is a problem that has to be effecting a large number of users who assume when they see the forbidden message that the problem is that Reddit doesn't want them submitting, period.  So they give up and go do something else.  I know how to work around it, but it is annoying as heck.  

Please look into fixing it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 12:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is still a problem.    I've explained in other comments in this thread exactly what causes the problem and how it could be easily fixed.   

This is really annoying.  And while I know how to get around it, I'll bet it is effecting many users who just think Reddit is them that they are not allowed to submit, period.  

Please look into fixing it.    Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Despite animosity, Moscow's Muslims change the city: At least 1.5 million Muslims in Russia's capital form the fastest growing and most ethnically diverse demographic group. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 11:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suicide blast leaves several dead in Afghanistan market: At least ten people killed in northern Faryab province after a suicide bombing in Alamar district's main market. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 11:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress inches toward functionality: According to the 'Healthy Congress Index, both chambers are seeing more action in committees, instead of behind closed doors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 11:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With 'Go Set a Watchman,' Atticus Finch shows complexities of racism in America: The national conversation about Harper Lees new book comes during a moment when the country is grappling with its history of race in renewed and troubled ways. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 11:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Central African Republic risks becoming 'case study of a failed state', says report: International Rescue Committee warns that the international community must move beyond humanitarian aid to address the root causes of conflict in CAR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 11:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philippines to raise 10m signatures for popes climate petition: The worlds third-largest Catholic country is plagued by natural disasters and church leaders say they will mobilise believers to join Pope Franciss campaign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 11:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Florida Gun Shop Now Muslim Free Zone" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 11:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman breaks car window to rescue child trapped in 43C heat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 11:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The new Francophone Scrabble world champion doesn't speak French </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 11:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-Vax Parents Looking To Sue Anybody They Can After Teen Daughter Gets Herself Vaccinated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 11:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 10:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/Coontown alone already is almost as large as Stormfront on it's own.   Include all the Chimpire and other associated subreddits, and they are much larger than Stormfront right now.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How One Tweet Can Ruin Your Life: Jon Ronson, TED Talks (2015) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 09:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RichardFordBurley on why the "precautionary principle" ought never to apply: "it asks for the impossible, proof of absent harm, when all we can provide is absent proof of harm. It's an insurmountable obstacle". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 09:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another Sloppy Anti-GMO Rag: GMOs, Norway, and the Precautionary Principle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 09:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  national hero

International hero.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asthmatic Father Dies After Police Hogtie Him Face Down on Disorderly Conduct Charge: Even the pettiest encounters with police can and often do end in pointless death. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the NYC Lawmaker Leading the Charge Against Uber Getting His Information on the Company From Random Google Searches? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The media created Donald Trump  and now he can't be stopped </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US officials target social media, encryption after Chattanooga shooting: Did "IS" propaganda inspire the Chattanooga shooter? There's no evidence to back the claim, but some officials are already calling for access to encrypted messages and social media monitoring. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three Spanish journalists missing amid Aleppo violence: Three freelance journalists from Spain have disappeared in Syria, according to a journalists' federation. They were working in the area around Aleppo, where government and rebel forces have been fighting for control. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Professor who posted about hanging queers on Facebook no longer employed at Kingston college </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Residents love marijuana plants sprouting on Vancouver traffic circles but police not amused </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for asianbabes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 08:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for Vados2009 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for ManCaveCooking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for ialsolikebutts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 06:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for Oati1995 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for PestControlServices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for pressclubus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for manwiththeplan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for bookkeeping123 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for satanandhitler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 05:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chocolate Cake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 14:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 14:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were many fully secular people involved in the Civil Rights movement as well.  It was not a religious movement.   A good number of religious people were involved,  but the movement itself was not religious in nature.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mayors at Vatican to demand 'bold climate agreement' from leaders: Dozens of environmentally friendly mayors from around the world will be signing a Vatican declaration Tuesday urging their national leaders to approve a "bold climate agreement" that keeps global warming at a safe limit for humanity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 14:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evacuation ordered as new wildfire burns near Kelowna, B.C. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 14:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bruce Springsteen - "You can look (but you better not touch)" [Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian women beat the U.S. to collect first-ever Pan Am basketball gold </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Greek government submitted legislation to parliament on Tuesday required by its international lenders to start talks on a multi-billion euro rescue package. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two killed as blasts, gunfire rock Burundi presidential vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea says not interested in Iran-like nuclear talks with U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A smugglers haven in the Sahara: The route to Europe for many African migrants passes through the underworld of Agadez, Niger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eugene Robinson: Attacking Donald Trump seems to only make him stronger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Race to the bottom: These two photos illustrate perfectly how ugly and pathetic white supremacists are </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diner owner not sorry for yelling at noisy toddler: It made her shut up, which made me happy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SpaceX Falcon 9 explosion likely caused by faulty metal brace, Elon Musk says: Metal component failed 'five times below its nominal strength, which is pretty crazy,' Musk said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump vs. the Republican Party: Who will be left standing? -- 'Celebrity politics' are not rational, but they seem to be winning the moment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every Muslim has the potential to be radicalized: How Franklin Graham became the religious rights Donald Trump -- Graham responded to the Chattanooga shooting last week in the most crass   offensive way possible. Sound familiar? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders moment of truth: What hell need to do to prove hes the real deal -- He's electrified the Democratic Party, but how will that translate into actual change? The ball's in his court, now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ethics Panel Extends Review of Mike Honda: The committee is looking into allegations that the California Democrat's staffers mixed official and campaign business. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Conservative Leader Who Doesn't Want to Lead: Jim Jordan's colleagues have pushed for him to be a chairman, whip, even Speaker. For now, he's the GOP leadership's most important intraparty foe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why History Gives Obama the Benefit of the Doubt on Iran: U.S. presidents of both parties have often shown better judgment in knowing when to accept diplomatic solutions than in choosing to go to war. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 2016 U.S. Presidential Race: A Cheat Sheet -- Ohio Governor John Kasichs announcement Tuesday means the Republican field is now complete. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for Reginald49 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 11:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 10:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vegetarians are very evil.    As a /r/Food and /r/Health mod have seen amazing evidence that proves that they only consume Soylent Green.    And, as we all know, [Soylent Green is people](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9IKVj4l5GU4).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for arihantj84 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are people in that thread splitting hairs so fine that several of them would claim Obama isn't even Obama because Robot Space Lizards don't have Earth names.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for ernestwilliams16 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for bestguitervideo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for sunfusionsolars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for powerandlightkc </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for igeaneuro </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for mjohn8541 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for obesitygroup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for theperfectplayground </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's from 1977.   Probably was recorded on some guys boom box tape deck sitting off the side originally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 07:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I'll just leave this here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xCd43ntfxB0). 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for comfortade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 06:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for ulybnistv </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 06:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for normandantzig </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 06:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for silkasmr </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 06:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for airzen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 06:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 06:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is one of the best musicians on the planet.  But your later point still remains, he doesn't know what he's talking about at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the AMIA Massacre   Mysterious Death of Alberto Nisman Still Haunt Argentina: This weekend Argentina remembered one of the worst massacres of Jews since WWII,   the mysterious death of the special prosecutor just as he was about to accuse the countrys leadership of a coverup. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 06:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 06:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P6MOnehCOUw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 05:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a mod of /r/Apple I can tell you with absolute certainly that Tim Cook only cooks meat-based products.  He is from Alabama after all.  :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 12 Nutty Dungeons   Dragons Media Mentions From the 1980s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 05:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 05:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once you become a engine mechanic of such advanced skill and ability, where you can tune up any car on the planet, the only way out is....  

One you know how to grill the perfect hamburger, that tastes greater than all the other hamburgers.... 

It's just nuts.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 05:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three can keep a secret, if two of them are dead.  -  Benjamin Franklin 

So, naturally....  Ben has been going on a killing spree.  I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 05:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course it's the National Review.   They won't bother to research what Ted Cruz, Jed Bush or Rick Perry pays their staff though.  That's for sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 05:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A very long time.  I was the one who implemented that back in the day.   /r/History does it for six or eight hours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does Sanders pay his staff interns, or are they paid for out of the Senate's own internal Operations budget?    If the later, then Sanders has one vote out of 100 when it comes to what staff interns are paid.   

If it's from a budget he controls, then he would get a to determine how it's spent.  In such a case, I would guess it would be something he farmed out to a Chief of Staff or something, which hopefully Sanders will be correcting the situation shortly.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scalpel?    Use a weed whacker.   It's faster.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're mistake is admitting those things.   True Jewish Zionists always deny it.  Always.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That certainly explains what Nixon was.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's /r/conspiracy.   Monday is Tuesday.   Tuesday is Friday.   Friday is ElephantDay.  Just forget about asking about ElephantDay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss Birdman.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "So, is there anything in your life that might be embarrassing if it was discovered after you came to work for Disney?"

Sadly, these guys wouldn't understand the question really.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Positive development.   Baby steps forward.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And AATA is so interested in how the guy found the thread.   Well, that's easy using Reddit search.  Find out where AATA is mentioned by anyone who is not AATA with [this search of reddit](https://www.reddit.com/search?q=AssuredlyAThrowAway+-author%3AAssuredlyAThrowAway+-reddit%3Asubredditreports restrict_sr= sort=new t=all).    

And that's without the added power of looking directly at AATA user overview or using Google. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for christineflo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gilda Radner as Miss Emily Litella </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for SimpleSalad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 03:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for itsmebord </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 03:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for Alexa121 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 19:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for MaryMunoz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 14:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 13:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All praise Chutulu

Probably means Cthulhu.  But I'm wondering.... Is this like "We salute you, our half inflated Dark Lord!"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Science meets sci-fi in new ILM retrospective: "Star Wars" actor Mark Hamill narrates a new special -- "Raiders, Raptors and Rebels: Behind the Magic of ILM" -- with interviews of George Lucas, Joss Whedon, Robert Downey Jr. and more. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the AMIA Massacre   Mysterious Death of Alberto Nisman Still Haunt Argentina: This weekend Argentina remembered one of the worst massacres of Jews since WWII,   the mysterious death of the special prosecutor just as he was about to accuse the countrys leadership of a coverup. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for moonlight_14291 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 09:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for tranhungnghiep </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 09:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for vibachkieu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 09:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for livescore92 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 09:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for ngoknb </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 09:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for vutung106seo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 09:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for KiraTran94 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 09:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for alimap1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 08:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for alimap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 08:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for tklongabc </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 08:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for thichhocnauan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 08:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for harryinternet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 08:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for quantrinhahang </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 08:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for daylamkemaau </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 08:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for bachkhoahanoi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 08:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> KKK and Black Panthers hold rallies at South Carolina Capitol, supporters clash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 08:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mitsubishi apologizes to WWII Japanese prisoners of war </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 08:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Francisco techies are hiring this Wiccan witch to protect their computers from viruses and offices from evil spirits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 08:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 08:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all becoming clear now.   Obviously a guy who was in *Head of the Class* was turned evil by Howard Hesseman.  Diabolical!  Johnny Fever was prime evil!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 06:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elos, your comment here is mostly gloating.  Yeah, you got him.   I removed him now too.   But come on, just send us a mod mail in the future instead please.   We can deal with it neatly then. 

Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 04:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, this thread got me to remember [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P6MOnehCOUw). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah..... Well, you can use facts to prove anything which is even remotely true.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 02:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it matter?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 02:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the summer time.   A lot of people when asked by pollsters say "Sure [hahaha], I'd vote for Trump.   Pass me another beer".   When it actually comes time to really vote, even in a simple primary or caucus, people sober up real quick.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 02:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Making it through his POW experience was a bit more than just a passive thing though.   I'm a left wing liberal, I disagree with McCain on a lot of policy stuff.   But more than 99% of people would just give up and just die instead of allowing themselves to be treated the way the North Vietnamese treated McCain and many of his fellow prisoners.   Survival wasn't a passive thing on his part, nor was it simple.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 02:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> McCain lost his teeth to a ball-peen hammer.  He has a personal relationship with torture that other people just don't have.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 02:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More of an 6.7 in my opinion.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 01:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I removed  the thread about this guy from /r/Bestof yesterday.  It was reported over 90 times.    Which is a lot of reports.   Most heavily reported threads never get more than 5 or 6 reports.  Sometimes a rare one makes it to 10 or 12.   But I saw 90 reports and removed it.    

And now it gets even worse.   

This guys problems are really turned up to 11.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for rashith </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 00:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Chattanooga Shooting, Congress Pushes Against Military Recruitment Centers As Gun-Free Zones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Appalling True Story Of What Happened At A Texas Frat When They Thought No One Was Watching </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charlie Hebdo editor: Magazine will no longer draw Mohammed cartoons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taiwan elections - A contest between women: Taiwan is set to have its first-ever female president in 2016 as both the ruling Kuomintang (KMT) and the opposition Democratic Progressive Party (DPP) have named women candidates to contest the presidential election. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hollande: France ready to build 'vanguard' to strengthen euro -- French President Hollande has called for an overhaul of the way the eurozone is governed, saying that a "stronger organization" of the 19-member currency bloc could help win back people who've sided with euroskeptics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State believed to be responsible for deadly Iraq car bombing: The Islamic State group has claimed responsibility for the attacks, according to messages posted on Twitter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> India bribery scandal: Mysterious deaths, massive coverup? -- A murky Indian corruption racket involving test-rigging is threatening a top politician  and killing witnesses. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Horizons probe zooms into Pluto's plains: The American space agency's New Horizons probe has returned further images of Pluto that include a view of the dwarf planet's strange icy plains. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Korea spy kills himself amid hacking scandal: An employee of South Korea's National Intelligence Service (NIS) spying agency has been found dead in his car after apparently taking his own life on a mountain road, police say. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The way forward: The judge helped a quadriplegic man become a lawyer. Could he help her recover from a catastrophic fall? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump belittles McCains war service, sparking stern Republican backlash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Does Your Uber Driver Think Of You? -- Uber passengers are accustomed to rating drivers. But with Uber feedback, judgment goes both ways. A couple of simple steps can show you your Uber passenger rating  if you really want to find out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big News: Tiny Parks Coming Soon To A Parking Spot Near You </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/conspiracy, you just [never change](http://i.imgur.com/Ta3AY.jpg).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for vanessaspagnol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 12:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 10:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are going to actually assert that thread is real?   It's a text-file created on free text file hosting service (similar to imgur is for image-files) is posted to /r/conspiracy by a mod of /r/conspiracy.   It's obviously fake and was created from whole cloth by the same account that posted it.    

You can't figure this one out on your own?   I really have to explain it to you?    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 10:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/Bestof allows any subreddit to opt-out per mod request.    

They can have a permanent opt-out forever.   Automod will enforce that.   

Or they can request removals piecemeal on a per-submission basis.   

/r/Bestof always respects a mod teams rights to not be highlighted at /r/Bestof.  

Likewise, we don't allow the subreddit to be used for witch hunts or in efforts to get somebody down voted.   If a submission to /r/Bestof is highlighting a comment people would normally want to down vote, we'll remove it.   /r/Bestof is meant to be a positive experience and the /r/Bestof mod-team won't allow it to be used as an attack platform.  

We work with other teams and the admins to keep the *Best of* experience positive for everyone.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 10:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't create anything.   I stepped up to defend some people who I thought were doing the right thing.    There is a difference.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 10:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember LouF.   

I also remember /u/zephir (now zephir_baned_baned and zephir_banned_baned).   He used to show up in /r/science and /r/Physics and complain that Albert Einstein time traveled into his home, stole his work and physically assaulted him and a bunch of other butty stuff.     I think he is a [time-cube](http://www.timecube.com/) crazy.   I never really could figure out what he was trying to say cause it hurt my brain to read his comments.  

Anyway, the mods of /r/Science and elsewhere have been repeatedly banning him for years.  

He seemed to have made for this [Billy Madison scene](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LQCU36pkH7c) to come to life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 10:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget the guys at /r/conspiracy, who have more than 300K subscribers.  They [never brigade anything](https://www.reddit.com/r/conspiracy/comments/3dtg7h/israel_affiliated_mod_utrain_subject8652_shows_up_in/).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 10:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The admins have directly said alts would count in the max-number of defaults one can mod.  So, /u/karmanaut and /u/bechus both count in the total number of defaults Karmanaut can mod.   If you have information about anyone modding more than four default subreddits, you should alert the [Reddit admins](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2Freddit.com) about it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 10:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R_A posted [this image](http://i.imgur.com/J2Ks9uw.png) in [this comment](https://np.reddit.com/r/SubredditDrama/comments/3dt2ix/drama_in_rdocumentaries_after_mod_nukes_nearly/ct8fknb).   Of course the guys from /r/conspiracy will now explain to us how none of that is antisemitic in the slightest.  

I'm sure they will explain to us how they aren't a brigade either.   As we all know that bipolarbear0 made them do it.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 09:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry about that then.   Please forgive me.    There are a few weirdos who follow me around with different accounts at times.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 09:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't even remove the thread I supposedly removed.   Of course, it was all me.   Yeah, right.  Whatever.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 09:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woman and their mind control powers.  I'm sure she rigged the Lotto numbers and controls the stock market too.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
