<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3651</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comb jellies, close cousins of jellyfish, once had skeletons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original Study: http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2015/07/15/1504467112 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fossil fuel emissions will make carbon dating less reliable. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 15:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One interesting possibility is that trans teens will be less depressed if they know it's not a case of being in the "wrong body". From the conclusion:
Transgender youth are aware of the incongruence between their internal gender identity and their assigned sex at early ages.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transgender youth have sex hormone levels that match the gender they were assigned at birth, according to a new study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 14:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Angelina Jolie tested positive for BRCA1 (a gene involved in breast cancer), the publicity influenced other women to seek out genetic testing, a new study finds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 21:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gut worms protect babies' brains from inflammation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 21:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 14:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the animals...they're trying to tell us something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that cheetahs cannot roar. Instead, they chirp like birds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 14:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robots pass the classic "wise-men puzzle", showing a new degreee of self-awareness. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 14:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coaches can be a strong influence in preventing football injuries, new study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 14:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dairy products boost effectiveness of probiotics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 14:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that girding your loins is pretty easy. It involves lifting the hem of your tunic and then tucking it into your belt or tying it in a knotbasically turning a dress into a pair of shorts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 16:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 00:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 00:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The study is mansplaining combat, and it's wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 00:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact: Spanish speakers actually modified the Aztec word "ahuacatl" to "avocado" because the former sounded too much like "abogado", the Spanish word for lawyer. TLDR: Avocado=Testicles=Lawyers. The Aztecs http://www.smithsonianmag.com/arts-culture/why-the-avocado-should-have-gone-the-way-of-the-dodo-4976527/?no-ist
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are only ~172 million water buffalo in the world. 95.8% of them reside in Asia. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Water_buffalo#Distribution_of_populations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Implying Christians do not *already* like anal sex and bestiality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> False.

http://m.snopes.com/man-arrested-for-alligator-sex/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is an incredibly interesting insight into a blessing that always bothered me a bit. Nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incidentally, all of those Talmudic cases also have very practical, law-based applications. For instance, the section on breast size is trying to determine at what age a woman is considered an adult for the purpose of court prosecution, especially in capital cases. 

In the US, once you're 18 you are an adultregardless of your personal development. Even though we know some 15 year olds can consent to sex and make their own decisions, we call them children. And even though we know some 20 year olds can barely consent and are easily swayed by peer-pressure, we consider them adults. 

The Talmud tries to avoid these pitfalls by defining adulthood for the purposes of consent and prosecution by physical development...the onset of puberty...at which point, the Talmud needs to define puberty.

Fascinating...not ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Russia has a larger surface area than Pluto. Russia has a surface area of 17 million km2, compared with 16.6 million km2 for Pluto. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you've ever met someone with colorectal cancer or Crohn's Disease, this actually makes a lot of sense. I think it's sort of awesome that they thank god for something that actually matters...the physiological processes that make our bodies work. Sure beats those hymns thanking god for mountains and forgiveness and stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Curiosity rover finds evidence of Mars' primitive continental crust </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL warm-blooded fish exist. Opah (or Moonfish) use their warm bodies to thrive even in frigid ocean depths. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 18:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nah, that was me. sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL cats only meow at humans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 17:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
