<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject933</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 02:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also have depression so I understand where you are coming from. Have you considered some sort of support group or group therapy? It may help if you surround yourself with people who are trying to get better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 02:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After watching Gone Girl, I sat in silence for five minutes while in the pitch dark.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 03:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chances are she won't admit to it if she has been gaslighting. From my experiences, gaslighters will never admit to being in the wrong: this is how they achieve the gaslighting, by denying the evidence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 02:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People take pick-up basketball way too seriously </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 15:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you need more mature friends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 15:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but you menfolk can be sensitive about these things. 

Oh forbid that a man actually has feelings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 05:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That I was suicidal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 05:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad avoids anything sex related. He starts yelling and making a big scene when a sex scene comes on if we are watching a movie. 

So the answer is no.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 04:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once dated a girl who truly was not a very affectionate person. I often had to ask. People are not mind readers. Sometimes, you have to ask for what you want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 19:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right back at you, sir
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 19:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An abusive relationship is similar to traveling deep in the ocean. You start to become lost in your own world, therefore, you begin to rationalize things. 

I would often make excuses for her behavior: "She didn't mean it this time, she was just having a bad day, she's not like this all of the time". 

It does not matter what your friends and family tell you; also, chances are she has isolated you from their reach. You begin to sink deeper and deeper in this ocean until you suffocate. You either realize what's going on or you're stuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 19:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly this. I was at a point in the relationship where it didn't matter what my friends or family said. I was the one who actively chose her, every time. Thankfully, it hit me one day and I realized that she wasn't going to change. So I got up and left.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 18:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hayley Williams of Paramore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 18:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Video Games is such a beautiful song </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 02:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I don't and I really wish I did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 02:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trunks. I used to like boxer briefs but designers make the legs so long now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 01:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was emotionally abandoned as a child. Therefore, in order to survive my own emotions, I emotionally abandoned myself. Consequently, I have some deeply rooted abandonment issues. 

In my relationships, I have abandoned lovers in fear of them abandoning me. I've also been abandoned. 

I have been trying to work on this. I tend to repress my emotions so I blotted out the memories of my mind. I figured it out when the memories started coming back subconsciously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 01:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In what ways did your ex abuse you? If you want to respond in PM that's fine too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 01:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand your concept of marriage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 21:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Threads like this really give me hope. Most of the people who shape the perception of men are not men. I do not understand how people try to define masculinity and argue how men never suffer oppression, if they are not men. 

When will society open its eyes?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 15:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About an hour, but that normally includes showering, eating breakfast, packing bags, and sometimes ironing clothes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 15:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we are truly best friends, then I would love him regardless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 15:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't grow a full beard until 22. I really think it has to do with genetics. 

On the contrary, neither my father nor my grandfather can grow a full beard. Therefore, I must have some distant relative's genetics on my mother's side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 04:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beauty and the Beast because of Beast's character development </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 04:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/AskMen/comments/2rfmix/who_was_the_last_person_who_held_you_while_you/

Take a moment to look at the responses from this thread a few months back that asked men to share who was the last person who held them when they cried. Many of the answers are their mother during their childhood. This is unacceptable. 

Until society, including other men and women, learn to validate men's emotions, we will continue to have the mental health struggles. Men are humans, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 15:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the part that you are missing here is the threatening sacrifice. In other words, my emotions were manipulated to the point where if I said no I would have been attacked emotionally. 

From your comment reply, you said this as if some women feel as if they must sacrifice to please their partner. All relationships have sacrifices. However, I was forced to sacrifice for my emotional safety. That type of sacrifice is never okay in any relationship. 

No one should have to fear the consequences if they want to say no to sex. And I did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 15:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always carry a shovel. In other words, always be prepared to dig yourself out of a situation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 04:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I told myself I wasn't going to tell this story in fear that my ex would find my Reddit account, but I will not allow her to run my life. 

My ex girlfriend and I decided not to engage in sexual activity until we were married. I had my beliefs and values about sex. However, I always felt the pressure from her to do whatever I could not consider sexual intercourse. 

One night, she was staying the night at my place and we start making out. Clothes start to come off and at this point, I knew we were close to the heat of the moment. I also knew my values and I did not want to go further than those. However, there was always some sort of emotional consequence if I didn't do something she wanted. She would criticize me by saying I was either being selfish or too passive or not manly enough. There was one occurrence when she started crying because I wasn't being sexual enough with her. 

So, I knew I had to do something to please her. I had to give up my body or face her criticism. So, we do some sexual things. The body doesn't lie though. I did not even become aroused. She thought it was because I didn't like her. I knew that I had to either do what she wanted or face some emotional punishment. As soon as it was over, I laid on my side of the bed and felt so helpless. I have never felt so powerless. 

And that was how I was sexually coerced. It fucked me up pretty bad and it still haunts me to this day to know that she had that much power over my body. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 18:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think everyone struggles with confidence at some point in their lives. No matter how many compliments I receive, I still have my moments of insecurity. 

Ultimately, I think in order to love yourself you need to know yourself. Figure out what you enjoy and what you don't enjoy. You can love yourself by being around people you enjoy and doing things that you enjoy. 

OP, how well do you know yourself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 16:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finding the hole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 02:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Experiencing mental illness/delusions  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 19:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Need to Know by Wale </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 19:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hispanic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 21:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are two of my favorite Coldplay songs. I guess you do not enjoy their acoustic stuff as much  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 21:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Princess of China takes the cake  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 20:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "But he gotta get rid of these hoes for me" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 15:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Families who kick their child out because he or she is gay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 15:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's important to feel needed. However, I have noticed from my ex-girlfriends that most of them think feeling needed is very important. 

My last ex-girlfriend often complained that I didn't need her in my life because I wouldn't show my needy and tender sides. She thinks that I don't need anyone. I'm just a very self reliant person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 15:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a time when my family's opinion dictated all of my decisions; now, that is not the case. I will say that once your relationship progresses into something more serious, family matters become a little more important. That's if you strongly value family. If you don't value family as much, then you will be fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 15:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $250 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 16:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playing basketball and a guy on the opposite team was trying to save the ball from going out of bounds. He tried to forcefully throw the ball in bounds. Hit me right in crotch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 20:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was younger: baseball (12 years) basketball (8 years) soccer (2 years). 

Now, volleyball.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 20:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My volleyball teammates and I make jokes about when people say it's a girls' sport. I'm a volleyball player too, but indoor. What position do you play? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 17:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always believed that I would have OCD for the rest of my life so it's interesting to hear that from your perspective </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 17:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OCD is not an adjective. Please do not ever say that "you're so OCD" or that "you're OCD about something".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 17:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're telling me that you don't have OCD anymore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How often do you have nightmares? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 16:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say that I have nightmares at least twice a week. Tell me about your nightmares. How often? What do you do when you wake up from one? Do you remember your worst one?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 18:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Your Atmosphere by John Mayer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came here to say this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 02:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a friend who has OCD and has been a strong contributor to this subreddit. He has been such a support system for me, I honestly don't know what I would do without him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many people do you know with OCD? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 23:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Among all the people I have encountered in my life, I have only met two people who have diagnosed OCD. How many people do you know personally who have OCD?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 21:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some girls just want attention  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the biggest situation that your parents helped you overcome? Or what do you wish that they helped you overcome? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 20:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe your parents had to bail you out of jail. Maybe your parents helped you out with a significant amount of debt. Maybe your parents dressed up as your favorite superhero for your birthday. 

Whatever it is, I want to hear the ways in which your family helped you when you needed it most. If they didn't help you, what moment did you need them the most?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 20:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasting my time with a girl from Tinder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
