<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6760</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 11:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the detailed reply. I'll follow your instructions. However, I'm not sure what you mean by "side bar." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 11:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like smaller tablets. I guess I will have to go for a large tablet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using Kindle for reading text books and studying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 17:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been using a Kindle Paperwhite for a few months. I love to read on it. I would like to read text books and study on it too. The problem is that most text books come as PDF files, and the formatting goes awry if you convert it to *.mobi. You can of course read PDFs directly, but navigation is cumbersome. Considering these, I have two questions.

1. Does anyone know of a better way for PDF to mobi conversion?

2. How can you convert essays/large articles/websites into a format to read on Kindle.

Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany return home as heroes, fans pack the streets of Berlin - photos | ProSoccerTalk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 15:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> #Love: Virtually No Sex - Techcrunch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 06:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> " How to Terraform the Moon" - Is this article about terraforming the moon scientific? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 05:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 15:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will need to read up about the gamma factor and the Lorentz transformation before replying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 14:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a query about the experience of astronauts in the ship. As per my understanding, the time taken the ship is 2.5 years to reach the galaxy from the point of view of a stationary observer on Earth. Considering this, I don't know how "long" the journey would take from the point of view of the astronauts. What do you have to say about that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Hypothetical travel to a nearby galaxy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 12:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been reading up about the speed of light and time dilation etc. So if suppose we build a spaceship to travel very close to the speed of light and go to the Andromeda Galaxy (2.5 million light years away) and return back, would Earth be older by 5 million years when the spaceship returns? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 11:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are people like that. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 11:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The original link does not mention any specifics. I wonder if someone knows more detail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-13 08:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god, this looks more realistic than the CGI in Hobbit movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
