<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6494</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 15:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reignwolf was amazing, never heard of him before lolla last year (I was waiting for MK) but he's a truly amazing performer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 15:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fall out boy is touring over the summer with Paramore, I think they're in Texas around the lolla dates, so I think it's unlikely, though id love to dream they'd be there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 15:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Panic would be amazing to see at Lolla. They've only gone once  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 14:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm underage so it's a little difficult to get a supply of alcohol let alone enough to get drunk  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 13:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it still asexual if I really really really feel sexual attraction though?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 05:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much, could you explain what some of the sexual dysfunctions are? PM me or comment it doesn't matter  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 04:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is definitely something ill have to try? Do you suggest doing it myself or waiting until I'm with my SO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 04:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very, very, VERY well  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 04:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that I know of, the only think I could think of it accidentally watching someone give birth on a health channel when I was 4 or 5, I don't remember it, but my parents said I cried for weeks. I still never want to have babies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 04:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I guess it hasn't been such a relevant part of my life until now, im in my first sexual relationship so I guess the problem has never arose  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 04:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know one is fine and one makes me pass out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 04:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a therapist that I have been seeing for a few years now, (mainly for anxiety and depression) do you think she could be able to help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 04:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone I know uses some kind of drug. From coke to caffeine. I don't  know If it's a small town thing, but here drugs is an everyday occerance  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 03:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arctic Monkeys, their new album is brilliant  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 03:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is very much being afraid of something inside of me, I am not freaked out by my gf at all, but when I put a finger inside I get really nauseous. It's very weird and hard to understand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 03:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I never think I've gotten far enough in to be painful  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 01:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to stop reading this AMA to masturbate  on pornhub. Thanks for the great AMA  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-25 15:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From Michigan, it's sweeping high schools everywhere up here, it's hella crazy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 03:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg type of soup she was using. I imagine someone pours soup into their vagina!!!! But thank you, my girlfriend has mentioned that she has sensitive skin,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 03:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg type of soup she was using. I imagine someone pours soup into their vagina  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 13:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She says it doesn't bother her but I can suggest it, maybe she'll like that better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 01:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am shaved. it could just be irritation i havent really payed attention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 04:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ive been taking lexapro for about4 months now and have noticed a little weight gain, but not a drastic weight gain. have you asked your doctor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 05:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you so much for taking the time to write this out! i as of right now identify with the whole "Who the fuck cares" because i mean ive had a boy, ive had a girl, i guess ill see where i takes me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I would love some advice. Here is my story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 05:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am 15 and know i have a long time to figure myself out. I am in no rush to identify myself sexually. Growing up i just assumed i was straight. i was attracted to boys and as i grew up and puberty hit, i definitely looked a boys a different way than girls. I've had two boyfriends and have had very fulfilling relationships with them. I had never really questioned my sexuality. As i entered high school i met a girl and we quickly became very close as friends. Throughout our relationship something has happened to where we have a FWB type thing going on. We make out with each other all the time and really have an emotional attachment to each other. I've been noticing how sexually interested i am in her as well as romantically which has been very confusing for me. This is the first girl i have looked this way and though we could get into all the details about our relationship and my confusion (she is also "straight") i just want to know if this is common in the bisexual world or if anything is possible. Thanks for the help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-25 06:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUCKING NOPE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attachment Therapist Terrorizes Child. Attachment Therapy (AT) is illegal in many states for being too cruel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 06:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> i need your advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 08:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i am a recovering self harmer, i was really addicted to cutting when i was 13-14 and have been doing very well with recovery...so far, but, i have made a friend who i have become very close to in the past year who is currently self harming. I thought i was completely recovered but seeing her cuts talking to her about it is extremely triggering for me. i had a feeling she was cutting so i texted her and she said everything was fine. i asked her if she was lying and she said yes. i immediately went to the razor and cut again...for the first time in a year. I love her to death, she's my best friend...but i dont want to go back to self harm. what should i do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 06:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reignwolf and The Drowners! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 08:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So funny  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 08:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shut up and have faith that some people Aren't creeps :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 08:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The tri cities. Bay city to be specific.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 19:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if youre down to hang out with teens i dont have a problem! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 19:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! I'm 16 but would love to meet up! I'll make a new thread soon so we can have a group </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 19:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should all make flags. I'll post mine once it's finished  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 19:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 19:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol supa creep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 19:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotcha, I'll remember  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 19:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should have a big meetup  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 19:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How old are you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 08:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> girl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 07:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> almost 16! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 07:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> michigan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 07:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 07:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awesome! how old are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 07:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a mix. The Cure it headlining this year, its alot of well known as well as obsucure bands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 07:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm super excited for alt-j and icona pop, but the big ones like Phoenix and Steve Aoki are going to incredible  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 07:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awesome! you going all 3 days? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 07:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its a 3 day music festival in Chicago. its pretty amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
