<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9683</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 21:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay, would it help you if I changed it to "Slade Wilson(w/ Mirakuru)" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 21:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I refuse to disagree with you, my brother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 21:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I googled synonyms of supernatural and got superhuman, so I would say Mirakuru is supernatural.

andnbsp;

**Supernatural**: unable to be explained by science or the laws of nature : of, relating to, or seeming to come from magic, a god, etc. 

I'm pretty sure Mirakuru falls under "unable to be explained by science or the laws of nature", at least to the real world, which pre-The Flash TV, Arrow is basically in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 20:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yea i did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 20:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I'm confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 20:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers... just speculations] Hal Jordan?? maybe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 20:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this video(scene), Oliver says "Those 5 years that I was away..I came across things that just...defy..explanation." 

Is it possible Hal Jordan became the Green Lantern before or around the time Oliver was away from Starling City? Is it possible he means the Green Lantern, because so far the only supernatural thing we've seen, is Slade (with the Mirakuru ofcourse). What do you guys think he meant? Do you think the producers had a plan when writing this scene.

andnbsp;

Mind the title of this video... its an Olicity channel xP https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hcX3qFIvLGQ

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 19:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Nice Math](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QRIYLV292Rs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 19:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll rate the seasons in terms of rappers.

* Season 1 = J Cole / Great for a start, had some flaws but overall enjoyable
* Season 2 = 2Pac (or Biggie or Eminem) / The greatest of them all, Manu Bennett's performance was amazing, and the character development in past and present day was astounding
* Season 3 = B.o.B / Definitely had it's good moments, has it's haters, and has it's lover, good overrall, not perfect, but good... like Banana Bread compared to Cheesecake... good but not quite there

andnbsp;

Edit: I shouldve used desserts instead of rappers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Any chance of seeing this woman as a new Oliver love-interest in a Russia flashback? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 19:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure how the universes work in the CWverse, but this lady is apart of the Soviet Air Force... so maybe we'll get to see her in Arrow, if she even exists in this universe. http://dc.wikia.com/wiki/Valentina_Vostok_(New_Earth)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 23:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn reddit doesn't like fan-fiction :(

andnbsp;

If it helps, it's not a cheesy romantic fanfiction. Olicity will not be the core focus of the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] I have a theory on the upcoming flashbacks for S4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 23:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think there will be Coast City, I think he will be getting on a ship that sends him somewhere else... possibly Russia, or if he does go to Coast City it will be very brief.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 23:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is the guy on the right? Looks like a mix of Pied Piper or Cpt. Cold or something, but I know it's not them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 23:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His first was actually getting Roy all roided up on Mirakuru. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 11:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually writing a Flash/Arrow fanfiction, I plan on making her meet the real White Canary, and not be so pleased with her ways, and change her name back to just "The Canary" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 10:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he's joking about how similar Green Arrow is to Batman.

andnbsp;

Unfortunately, he doesn't know that they share villains.

* Merlyn (Green Arrow villain)
* Deathstroke (Green Arrow/Batman/Teen Titans villain
* The Huntress (Anti-hero, not a villain really of Green Arrow, but brought into the story because.... Black Canary, Birds of Prey, etc.
* Brother Blood (Not even a Batman villain, Teen Titans villain.)
* Brick (Green Arrow Villain)
* Cyrus Gold (Solomon Grundy pre-zombie, is a Green Arrow villain post-crisis)
* Deadshot (Not specifically a Green Arrow villain, but has faced him in Animated TV Shows, and his daughter lives in Star City)
* Ra's Al Ghul (Not specifically a Green Arrow villain, but Merlyn is affiliated with the League of Assassins, so it was fine to introduce him into Arrow... in fact if it wasn't for Merlyn, the League would probably never have been involved with the story, except some snippets of Sara Lance here and there.)
* The Clock King (Green Arrow villain.)
* Cupid (Green Arrow Villain.)
* Brother Eye (More of a JLA villain... which Green Arrow is a part of.)
* Count Vertigo (Green Arrow and Batman shared villain.)
* Firefly (Batman villain.)
* KGBeast (Not a villain.... yet. But a Batman villain.)
* Dollmaker (Batman Villain.)

___

andnbsp;

Consensus: The only true Batman-exclusive villains on Arrow are Firefly, Dollmaker, and Deadshot, we have yet to see Anatoli Knyazev's story, assuming they'll cover the whole Russian Bratva thing in the flashbacks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 10:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They could get a different actor sorta, like if they did some future/alternate timeline grey-haired Slade like in the comics/video games/cartoons.

andnbsp;

I doubt they would... but it would be cool, to mention him in the future, or tease him in an alternate universe on The Flash, of course, they could still show a guy in the suit and mask, you don't need Manu Bennett for everything Deathstroke concerned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 18:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not that funny :\ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 17:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get what you mean, if Olicity was like Diggle and Lyla, I think it would be received well by shippers and the rest of us.


Because you get 

* the badassery of a crime fighting couple
* some romantic/emotional scenes when the day is done, not mid way though the episode
* and some humour... like "No glocks on the dinner table." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free Karma for this Drunk dude at an ATM? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 14:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers (just a theory I guess] Will we ever see more Joe West and Cecil moments. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 14:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's about time Joe West got some action, since I'm sure Arrow will never give Quentin Lance anymore :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 14:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like Arrow is gonna go completely downhill now. No more Slade, barely anymore Roy, probably no Hal Jordan, and more Olicity.

andnbsp;

:( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 10:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terra and Beast Boy.... a better love story than ~~Twilight~~ Olicity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 09:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Name is Daniel Brickwell, for 15 years I was stranded in a basement with only one thing... a greasy Xbox controller. Now I have return to my city, not the raging teenager I once was, but the ....raging adult that will wreak havoc on Starling City. But to do this, I must become someone else... I must become something else.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 09:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 09:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget the motto.

andnbsp;

Not God...Grodd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 09:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   a human "U wot m8".

Those already exist.... they're called "Kids on Xbox" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 09:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was someone else...she was... something else...

andnbsp;

andnbsp;

andnbsp;

andnbsp;

Previously on Hannibal Bates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 09:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No he's not. Our show is dying :( and they're probably gonna end it in 2 more seasons. Whereas The Flash will go on for eternity.

:'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 03:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes... the Hōzen.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 03:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grodd I hope, he's actually joking, at least reference him, find out his name, or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S1E4 and S1E21 Minor Spoilers] Just wondering if this had any connection. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 11:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Wells was...i guess lecturing Cisco about the Cold Gun going missing in Episode 4, he said "You know how I feel about weapons, Cisco, they do not belong in S.T.A.R. Labs"

andnbsp;

Then in Episode 21, Grodd said "Father. hate. gun." when he made Joe West throw away the handgun.

___

Just thought I'd share (\^‿\^). Something to keep us thinking throughout the summer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 10:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kelly Frye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 10:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! Jokes on you, I've only seen about 2 of your synopses. So I have all summer to enjoy them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
