<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2704</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 19:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or its one of our stupid birds flying the coop like they often do in spring  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 12:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kevin Bacon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 09:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried that myself made things horrible comfort wise. Though I'm by no means a professional.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Lowering A Motorcycle. Pros? Cons? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 08:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everyone, I've been thinking about lowering my bike recently. I bought it last March and rode it all summer as it was. (standard height) However that being said. I am 5'2 small female and ride a Kawasaki ZX6R 2008. Its quite tall, I have to tip toe on stopping and sometimes it makes me feel really uncomfortable. I know that lowering a bike will change it geometry and make it different while cornering. But say lowering an 1'-.5' would it make a big difference? Or should the bike just be left in stock suspension. Something I've been thinking about for a while. Considered it all summer while I rode it. Though now its off season and I've been thinking about spring a lot and lowering the bike. So whats this community's general consensus. Any advice would be much appreciated. Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 11:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emily, Sarah,  Jessica,  Khalessi, crystal, John, Chad,  Bob,  George,  Jesse  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 00:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm online in Ontario, Canada.  Downloading a game from the store as i type.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 23:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No but the right shoulder pad armour on my mage was floating around her body in every cut scene  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 18:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you make these or buy them? I was thinking of doing something similar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 02:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry but why not have sex instead of fapping?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 13:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 11:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Headlights are wrong for a 2008 zx6r. Looks more like an 2005 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 11:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tick or treating  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 06:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figured as much. I might breed her when shes big enough  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 17:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check etsy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 04:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Salmon, with jungle and albino apparently  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 20:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She will be 2 in august  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
