<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6760</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 07:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like a med student. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 07:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. I was on my uncle's lap. He pulled his hands in my shorts and fondled my genitals in front of my Mom and Dad. Everything was so casual. No wonder I'm under therapy for PTSD/depression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 06:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my dark secret. I was molested in front of my father and mother by my uncle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 12:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am watching a lesson on the same on Coursera.

The course is "Introduction to Astronomy" (Duke University) by Ronen Plesser.

This is best described in the 5th lesson (Where is the sun?) of the first week (Positional Astronomy).

I will try to post screenshots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How do you imagine the ecliptic (in astronomy) from the POV of an observer on Earth through the sidereal year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 11:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have gone through the various resources (WikiPedia, YouTube, Reddit) about the ecliptic but still find it hard to imagine it. Is there any better way someone can explain people to imagine the ecliptic from the point of view of an observer on earth looking up at the sky over the course of the sidereal year? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 05:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your thoughts! I belong to the LGBT community too and I have met some TGs. I think I will ask them too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 05:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant the blisters caused by wearing ill-fitting shoes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 05:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would women in general be willing to admit to your hypothesis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 Have you any idea why women buy new, badly made shoes despite them causing severe shoe burns? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 04:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 16:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must confess. I do both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 07:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The link above redirects to this reddit post. Can you please check? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 05:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His character is so adorable. Not completely sold on his in-ring work though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
