<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1095</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 12:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *DC/Vertigo*

**Convergence #1**

**Convergence Nightwing and Oracle #1**

**Convergence Titans #1**

**Convergence Question #1**

*Dynamite*

**Masks 2 #1**

**Reanimator #1**

*Image*

**Savior #1** Raised religious, but the solicit sound like another "What if there was a superhuman among us" type comic.

*Marvel*

**Ant-Man #4**

**Captain Mavel #14**  Black Vortex (I hate having to add more comics to my pull due to cross-overs)

**Darth Vader #4** Decent enough so far

**Deadpool #45** "Death" of Deadpool. What's $10 (minus 15% pull list discount) for a "milestone" comic?

**Hulk #14**

**Miles Morales Ultimate Spider-Man #12** Started at #1 so why stop now?

**Spider-Man 2099 #11**

*Boom! Studios*

**Sleep Hollows Origins #1** Followed the show somewhat so decided to check this out

*Valiant* 

**Imperium #3** As always I enjoy Valiant and this is no exception

**Rai #8**  I need to re-read it all, but have still enjoyed it.

I really should start limiting my budget. . .Looking through the replies only a couple have as much or more than me, which is probably not a good sign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 11:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't a single one of these minus Saga in trade form. . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crossed question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 10:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comixology is having a massive sale on Crossed. I was wondering which runs are worth getting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 09:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well to be fair many states just require you to be 18 to be able to serve alcohol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 10:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they put as much work into their movies as they do their comic books (as in I can't find a single issue I dislike) then I can't wait for their movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 04:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is kinda how everyone jokes Batman's power is that he **is** Batman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 19:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea thats the Beowulf I am thinking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 07:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention overwhelming the wallet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 06:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did Beowulf ever show up? I kinda sorta remember reading a Beowulf feature in the New 52 DC presents that involved Camelot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 05:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spaceman by Vertigo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 23:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And in Eureka7 there is a character named Stoner. . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 23:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully Del Toro can be a producer at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 10:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope you are not alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 10:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Post Convergence isnt New 52 anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 05:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were also Futures End One-Shots of most titles, but very few linked up at all to the main weekly and for the ones that did it wasn't anything significant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 05:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it may still be a possibility since isn't DC dropping "New 52" post-Convergence? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 22:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about plastic man? Could be like a rival Kirby or something. . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice League 3000/Futures End question. (Potential Spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 22:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So did anyone else notice similarities between Locus and Fifty Sue? Their powers seem very similar. . .

On a side note: The last time we see Sue she has entire DNA vault in her possession. So would it be possible at some point she decides to join back with Cadmus? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 22:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It did sort of have a set up for Justice League 3000. We get the explanation of how Cadmus is having DNA of most Superhumans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 20:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Gemworld ever gonna have a new series? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 06:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **NEW 52 FUTURES END #48** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 05:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A decent setup of what is to come. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 05:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want Babs and Jason to be a thing :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 05:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was my first Doctor Who Comic and I surprisingly enjoyed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 05:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **DOCTOR WHO 9TH DOCTOR#1** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 05:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was an Anderson Psi-Division mini series IDW finished not too long ago. I really enjoyed that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 20:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't bother me one bit. I guess I will check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 16:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the Vertigo Quarterly went for this much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 15:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this series? I've been thinking of playing catch up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 15:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't see that coming regarding who Wells is/was. . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 15:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea man, when you hit that Speed Force...it is like you become a part of something greater than yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 14:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...but Sandman links up with Lucifer. . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 14:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2nd to last issue...can't wait to read it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 04:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gonna pick up issue 15 forward tomorrow. Thanks for the heads up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 23:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I read an article a year or so back stating they had to redesign the Batsuit somewhat because there was an issue of mobility. . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 19:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoyed it and they did a good job character building. I lucked out and my LCS still had one copy left, but I am not sure I added to my pull list so I have to get there early tomorrow. By the looks of it you can still get it at IDW's website. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 10:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evangelion was one of the first Anime I watched :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 10:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ended up getting Wonder Woman, Batgirl, Batwoman, and Supergirl from this sale. I enjoyed them all, but Batwoman had several 2 page spreads that at times made reading difficult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 10:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure to check out Lucifer. Also a good series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 10:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Batman Eternal #52

* Convergence #0

* Names #8

* New 52 Futures End #48

* Blood Queen vs Dracula #2

* Project Superpowers Blackcross #2

* Citizen of the Galaxy #2

* Neverboy #2

* Amazing Spiderman #17

* Cyclops #12

* Return of the Living Deadpool #3

* Spider-Gwen #3

* Uncanny Inhumans #0

* Doctor Who 9th Doctor #1

* Lady Death Apocalypse #3

* Puppet Master #1

It is gonna be an expensive week ╮(╯▽╰)╭ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 09:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umbral is a favorite by Image.

Citizen of the Galaxy by IDW #2 gets released this week and I really enjoyed the first issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 04:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hoping Shadowman is a main player in this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 21:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I found out that you can take college courses, while in high school, for credit towards both, I was a little pissed off. It would have saved not only time, but also money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 17:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is mostly single issues, but they are pretty fast in releasing volumes. As for the Scribd service, I am not sure how they have them on there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 07:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoyed Rai, Eternal Warrior, and Shadowman. The latter have concluded, but Rai is ongoing. Honestly, I havent found a Valiant comic that I do not like yet and I've started most of them. Check out Scribd for a near complete collection of Valiant comics in digital form. Occasionally Valiant will have a Humble Bundle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 08:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just waiting until the Tula Lotay Art Book drops on April 1st. I really enjoyed the comics she has been a part of and would love to get something like this of hers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 08:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I don't mind digital, Marvel Unlimited is an excellent resource. Even if it is single issues at a time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 08:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the end of 2013 Google play had a **massive** sale of N52 trades, which is actually what got me into comics. Like 3 or 4$ each. Just keep checking there each week to see if anything is on sale. One time they had The Walking Dead Compendium (Yes the huge collections) 1 and 2 for less than 10$ total. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 08:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitly the Death: Deluxe Edition. Excellent stories about Death of the Endless (Sandman Mythos). It is such a good deal for all it has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 08:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhhh this may explain why Supergirl Vol. 2 is not on the play store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 12:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it on Netflix or Hulu yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 12:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figure it is a 4:1 shot a BvS trailer (even just a teaser) debuts with the Avengers 2 movie. I mean would DC really give up such an oppurtinity to advertise on one of this year's biggest releases? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 12:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sure wished I did, but I am one of those souls that must read every series from the beginning even tho I consider jumping in at N52 not a bad start. Considering I started with comics in December 2013, I don't think I will ever catch up.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 11:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am trying to decide between Wonder Woman, Supergirl, and Batwoman. Might go ahead and do all three, but the other titles such as American Vampire and even Fables and Ghost are hard to choose from. I might just have to go by a pages/cost ratio to decide.

Either way, I **highly**  recommend the Death: Deluxe Edition. I have the physical copy and it is still a such an amazing deal on such a good story collection (even if you are completely new to Neil Gaiman's Sandman and the Endless Mythos) that I am considering buying it in digital form, which at just 1¢ a page is a massive steal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Play is having a $2.99 sale for Woman-lead comic books, including Batgirl, Supergirl, Batwoman, Wonder Woman, World's Finest (All N52 Vol 1's) and Death: Deluxe Edition (My personal favorite). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 11:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 11:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering Image is way faster than DC/Marvel in getting their trades out after the last issue in it, I am not surprised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 08:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second Outcast. Apparently the series Weaveworld is pretty good, but have yet to read it despite picking up the first trade (good luck finding this one, it was released in the 90's). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 08:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't really been following the tourney....but why no Valiant series? Is this just the Big 2 plus Image and Dark Horse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 08:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is beyond tragic. My LCS does 15% discount with free bags. I occasionally order from Midtown, but I like to keep going to mine because I like the people and enviroment.

 Is your store at least going to attempt a digital retail conversion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 08:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much this. Half the time I forget about a spoiler by the time I get to reading a comic. Of course, half the time I don't get to the comic until Thursday or the following weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 08:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just read Vol. 6, which had Ramadan in it, last night and i really enjoyed it. The story was interesting and I sort of want to read into middle eastern lore after it. The fact Iraq was/is still a war zone is a humbling fact 20 years after this issue was published. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 08:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have it on my pull list, but can't get until next week:(  Been loving it so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 08:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like /u/bliffay said it originated from the Lil B fanbase. He is a somewhat underground rapper (I don't he is signed and is still independent) and has a huge presence on the internet. I remember he released a 100 track mixtape once for free. I don't really follow him tho. . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 07:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally, it seems, Vertigo is getting consistent love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 07:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have about 5 issues to read of this series, been buying them, but havent read them yet. . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 07:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to order this. I've been following this series via trades and have absolutely loved it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 07:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is on my pull list, but I can't pick it up until next week. I have to save my money for a Tula Lotay Art Book that is releasing April 1st and I suspect the shipping is gonna be a bitch. Enjoyed the first issue and can't wait until I can read this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 18:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with you on this. Tyrese, I think would make a decent GL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 09:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My LCS usually gets me the variant cover for titles that I have on my pull list. Occasionally, I will get them from Midtown comics and they will generally have them ready for pre-order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 08:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Valiant relaunched a couple years back (they were around in the 90s) and practically all their titles are excellent. If you want comedy, Archer and Armstrong or Quantum and Woody are great series. If you like mythical/magical, Shadowman is decent. Eternal Warrior is about one of the most prominent characters in Valiant and is contained in two trades. Can never go wrong with X-O Manowar with it being pretty much Valiant's flagship title. 

On current series not yet in trades: Ivar, Time Walker is fun and you don't need to know too much about the Valiant Universe, but it definitly will help make connections. 

Keep an eye on Humble Bundles, I managed to get a good chunk of Valiant trades for not very much. Or perhaps check out Scribd since Valiant has a good amount of digital issues in this service.

Also /r/valiant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 03:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Shadowman should at least have one or two vols in the middle of Quantum and Woody so you have some background for the heist, even if it isnt a real crossover. . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 19:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wounded Rhymes, easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 06:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the free digital version. It lets me sell off issues I don't want so I can buy a couplw more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 16:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lykke Li features always brighten my day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 15:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's done a couple collaborations with rappers. One of my favorite is Gifted with Kanye and Santigold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 15:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was stuck holding a beam that would otherwise crush Aunt May. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 09:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lykke Li easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 04:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do LCS get from me putting down my Marvel Code redemptions at their store? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 20:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I rumble when I yawn and cant hear anything half the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 05:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly so much so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 03:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I highly recommend this series. The artwork is great and the story actually moves along at a good pace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 18:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sandman

XMen Apocalypse

Star Wars 7

AntMan 

Suicide Squad

Fantastic Four

Avengers2

Deadpool

BvS

Green Lantern

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 18:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didnt Dwayne Johnson confirm he is Black Adam? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 09:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much on the trade release. Image gets it right in this regard. I hate having to wait for the next DC trades after so long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 09:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free Digital copies with the purchase of physical copies.  

Make more Netflix Series.

Live Action JLD.

Give Klarion a better run.

1 event maybe 2 a year.

Crossovers not nearly as much or as long.

Not make trades come out several ARCS after the fact. Kinda like how Image does what? Like a month after the last issue in a trade.

DC Unlimited.

Make Humble Bundles for at least older comics.

Make sure Elektra actually lasts for a decent run.

Make flagship issues longer with "shorts" in the middle. Like a Batcow short story in Batman.

More easter eggs and no more white borders. We need more art to look at while reading.

And an all New Crossover between the universes.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 17:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ivar Timewalker is an excellent series that is only a couple issues in, if anyone is wanting something easy to jump into by Valiant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 17:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must have missed the news on a Bloodshot movie. Sounds awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 17:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Save 20$ for their next humble bundle. Im still only about halfway through the ones they have had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 05:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine the gap will close, but once we get closer to the movie in December it will grow again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 04:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This album is always first in my library whenever I get a new device. The first line is so unexpected and the album just continues to deliver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 02:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This seems like a pitch for an excellent Dave Chappelle skit, if that show still existed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 02:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing Pixel Heroes on android. All the nods to pop culture is entertaining.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 02:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last issue was so hard to understand. The art is still pretty good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 03:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it was the 07-08 school year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 02:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he was class of '14, I don't think he would have had the pleasure of knowing Moretta, sadly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 00:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The integration was in 1955 and was the first in all of Dallas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 00:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the Non-Catholic/Secular Private schools we also have St. Mark's and Hockaday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 00:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would Mr. Moretta have to say about this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 00:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ursuline is also the Sister school of Jesuit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 18:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anyone can figure out the BB suit it'll be Tim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 18:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was my first thought. Of course I mostly DVR because I work at night, however, it is nice the days I dont work to watch the shows live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 07:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we get a quality post tag? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 00:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But then again the title does say Unlimited Budget... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
