<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6494</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 23:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/mFEd4rB.jpg 

This is no makeup, Id love any suggestions! But I'm definitely looking for a pretty wearable brown lip
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 02:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely love a few of their songs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 16:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm being Mary Poppins! Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 00:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that I recall, they're LE and I will admit I wasn't paying much attention, anyone know if they're the same price?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 20:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely love it! I'm not one who normally wears nudes or mlbb shades but I absolutely love this!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 19:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they do, it is honestly much better, it's...less cheap looking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 19:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish they would switch it! I like it a lot this way  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 18:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry my old packaging example is scratched up, but I picked up sweet cream last night and I was surprised that the packaging was different! It's blacker, and sleeker, I really like it! The cap to the lipstick hasn't changed at all, but overall im happy they changed it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Wet N Wild lipstick packaging! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 18:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 19:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, multiple orgasms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 19:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure I have 10+ lipsticks just for putting my lip of the day in my purse and forgetting to take it out!' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 23:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone's got a different type  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 13:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I didn't understand why you were jugs saying "no"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 12:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually a little underweight, I have a very round face which could probably make someone think I'm chubby  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 06:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope!  I just found this subreddit today! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 06:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To each their own! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 05:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cutie pie 100000000000/10 I love you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 05:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha thanks! I was in a play,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 05:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 18/f just found this subreddit, I'm curious, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 05:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are some more recent pictures I'm interested in what you have to say! 

http://imgur.com/Z1iiVZW
http://imgur.com/IDXji1P
http://imgur.com/8Me63hO
http://imgur.com/Qjj3gVl
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 05:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 18/f be honest, brutally honest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 05:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are some pictures, I tried to get a range of different styles or whatever 

http://imgur.com/4iHkhSJ
http://imgur.com/Z1iiVZW
http://imgur.com/IDXji1P
http://imgur.com/8Me63hO
http://imgur.com/Qjj3gVl
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 04:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't see the rules on mobile, I saw that there was a 16 year old on the front page so I assumed it wasn't just 18+. Just thought this would be a fun experience. Sorry that made you feel like you had to be sassy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just finished a run as Jane Porter in Tarzan the Musical. They got this amazing shot and it would be so amazing too see it drawn! All styles welcome! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 01:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 00:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 22:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 20:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rant: all the Ulta stores within my immediate area (about a 3 city radius) are completely disgusting when it comes to their displays and testers. I recently went to try and look for a nice black lipstick (to no avail unfortunately) but was dumbfounded by the mess that was specifically the NYX and Benefit areas 

Rave: my new 24 Hour Color Tattoo in tough as taupe. I'm still trying to get a hold of creamy contour. But I absolutely love it so far!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 20:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I've ever heard that song and NOT cried  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 07:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they posted on their Instagram at it's July 31-August 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 23:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please let this be true  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 22:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already seen 2 people caught smoking pot and it was confiscated, and it's not even 4 on the first day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 03:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm new to makeup! Id love to try all those products since I don't own any of them, and always have wanted to but I mean... A teen girl doesn't make enough money for all that   :((( I would love it if you picked me!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 14:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live by central so I SHOULD be going there, but I go Glenn because of their theater program  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 00:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely, the homeless people seemed to spike in the past two or three years and now they're everywhere, the polish festival is going on right now and they're just wandering around it piss drunk. The city is getting more dangerous at night. But other than that the downtown area is super cute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 19:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell yeah, I don't think I've been there yet and not seen a homeless man sleeping on it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 04:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An hour away from Ann Arbor here in Bay City! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 23:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was the most obnoxious, loud mouthed, inconsiderate girl I had ever met,  we've been dating a year  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 16:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tri-city area in Michigan, maybe he reads reddit and just stole it, because I mean what are the odds that this thread is on the front page of r/askreddit AND the town radio host happens to share stories about bad break-ups that include getting a membership to the KKK  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 16:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude I just heard my local radio guy that happened to him on air, this better be the same fucking guy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 03:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does it mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 00:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather be a little slow and safe than aggressive and reckless when it comes to driving  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This can't be true right? Found is Seventeen Magazine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 04:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 17:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sucks! I wish it would have worked out better for you :( it's annoying know that no matter how many people tell you a foundation is great, every person's skin is different and we all need different things. I wish there was just one mega-foundation that worked for everything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 03:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the clarification!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 01:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could I be mistaken and thinking of photo ready instead if colorstay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 00:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure you used the Whipped ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 00:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to refer to myself as "cancer patient pale" if that give you any idea. The two lightest shades are very pale, one with yellow undertones and one with pink, I use the pink undertoned one which would be the "second lightest" but I think it is very pale, if you can I would try it on in stores but I don't think you'd be dissapointed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 13:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rave: Tarte Amazon Clay 12 hour Foundation. I have an unbelievably oily face and this is the only foundation I've discovered that's able to control it. It is my exact shade and doesn't make me break out, plus I can't even feel it when it's on my face. Truly the best item of makeup I own to date. 

Rant: Revlon colorstay whipped. It's got glitter in it??????? Who wants glittery foundation!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 02:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Product List 

NYX Mosaic Blush 
Random Brown Eyeshadow  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
