<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2415</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 05:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it depends on where you live, but that seems crazy! From what I've looked up I've seen somewhere around $10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 05:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely get that. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 04:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm combo/oily myself, so that's perfect! Do you have a reason that you prefer it? Thanks(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 04:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds great, thanks! I'm an NC25, do you have any idea what shade I would want to pick up? I'm horrible at choosing the right shade. Thanks again(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] Foundation for a broke girl? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 03:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello lovelies,

I am absolutely in love with MAC foundation, but have finally admitted to myself that, as a highschool student, I cannot afford it. (Yes, it was a sad day.) Do you guys have suggestions for what I should switch to, being on a LOW budget?

Thanks! xx

EDIT: Powder suggestions are welcomed as well(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-13 22:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOVE THIS! Absolutely gorgeous(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-13 05:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here! Doing this for the sanctity of my (future) marriage and to get closer to God. There are some more personal reasons as well, but that's what brought me here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-13 05:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you... Ten days can do amazing things to you(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 00:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the story of my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 06:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 04:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. His name is Peter Joback, and I don't find the appeal... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 04:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Samantha's Christine!! But Peter... I don't know... definitely not my favorite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-10 23:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew it! Haha, that's hilarious!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-10 05:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why I click on that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-10 05:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would've instantly freaked out before taking the picture... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 06:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Morpheus is currently down, so maybe! That would be awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 04:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad. I thought it was a retort to the "No." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 04:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see now. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 04:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah... Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 07:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...an apostrophe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 06:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop. Reposting. This.

Please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 06:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah. I had no idea that they were literally knots. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 06:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woow!! I wish I was that creative! This is amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 06:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I would have really freaked out not having heard that!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 21:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 21:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 21:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome and gross. Haha okay. I usually gets vitamins and what not from Walgreens because they're cheap, but I was just wondering because I couldn't just find B. They were mostly B-12 and B-Complex. Do you have a preference, or don't know?

Thanks for the quick reply(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 21:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which vitamin Bs do you take? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 20:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As you've seen, treatment is available, and you should be okay. Sorry for that scare. I hope you're doing okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 20:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> STDs are not funny. Even when easily treatable, they are diseases and definitely not fun. Sometimes it's too late to treat anyway. I think he'll be okay, but it's definitely a cause for concern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 20:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You did an amazing job!! I think it honestly looks better than the original... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 20:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for that(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 20:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is, I don't really have a reason. I read about all these people who suffer so much from it and it made me decide to try and quit. It's like I know it's good for me, but I haven't gone through much of anything making it bad in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 20:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just getting turned on in general. My body says I want to, and even when my brains says I don't, I relapse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 20:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the support(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 20:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just Wanted to Talk to You Guys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 06:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey fapstronauts. So I've been feeling really lost and alone on my journey lately. We're 60,000 strong and yet I feel really alone in my chalenge. Maybe it's because I don't post enough with you guys, but also because 1) there's noone I know personally to relate to with this and 2) I feel kind of like a minority here being a 15 y/o girl. My weakest temptations are the ones that make me fall, and then I sometimes don't even feel bad. Any words of advice or inspiration? Mostly, I just needed to vent a little. 

NoFap, thank you for existing. Someday my life will different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 05:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if there's something wrong with me, but that speech at the end made me want to cry. Thanks for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 05:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely think it's harder as a teen with hormones, our brains not being fully developed, and whatnot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 05:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fifteen as well. Good to hear from other teens(: If you scroll down the page you'll see nine buttons, one of which says reset badge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 05:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a singer, that would be my dream come true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 00:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The overall quality isn't quite what you'd want on a headshot. I also avoid windows because they provide really uneven lighting, which is really bad for headshots. Accent your eyes, they're gorgeous! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 00:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The camera angle is too low, and the attention draws to your clothes as opposed to your eyes. Smile also looks a little fake and ... awkward. Overall, it's a good picture of you, but not a great headshot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 20:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the repost of all reposts,... but I still think it's hilarious. Have an upvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 05:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Figured that out recently, and I have. Thanks, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 05:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds awesome. In the past, my mildest urges have gotten me to relapse. Hope I have that kind of self control someday(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 03:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agreed. It was like her jaw was nailed together. Also, she needs to put her chin down. It was like she was drawing a picture with her head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 22:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, she did a great job!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 07:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best of luck to you. It's not an easy journey, but it's an amazing one. Make sure you set up a badge so you can track your progress with us(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 07:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so happy for you(: Do you remember when your urges kind of died down? Just curious. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 07:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agreed. I don't post too often, but I check the page everyday and usually comment quite a bit. Even if I just look at the top post really quick, I feel like I have so much support around me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 07:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that would make me cry, and fap anyway... But hey, it looks like it's worked for other people(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 07:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So cute!! I love that look! I usually see it with blue, but the pink with blue eyes looks GORGEOUS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 03:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I Have a Dream" and "I Dreamed a Dream" are very different songs... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 02:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'll try that(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 02:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried that, and it didn't even kind of work... Thanks for the advice, though(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-31 05:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that we can't, it's just that if we don't notice, we're gonna get an ass full of toilet water. I know a lot of girls are way too bitchy about this. Most of the time I notice and put it down myself. Most women figure that men just have to aim closer, but women may fall in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-31 05:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! Good luck on your journey, it's a hard one. Be sure to set a counter so you can view your progress! Also, have an escape plan. Plan something very specific to do if you feel the urge to relapse. As someone whose relapsed a handful of times, this is *very* helpful. Again, good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Google, do you know a good cure for a head ache? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-31 03:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sex. Sex. SEX. Yeah, my cure for a headache used to be to masturbate. I'm feeling pretty calm now, but if any more websites suggest sex (or masturbation for me), then I'm afraid I might do just that.

Has anyone else come across this problem? Any tips? Good way to get rid of a headache?

Thanks guys. I'm so happy I found this subreddit. I know I'm only on day 3 now, but I have a feeling it's gonna stick this time(: Love you all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 06:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found it. It's right by the small lake. Hope that helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 04:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 04:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just spent a few hours playing around with this house. It's amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 02:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not alone... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 00:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I agree. This is a little insine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 00:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look fantastic! Glad to see you happy with your appearance. You're gorgeous. Keep posting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 00:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 00:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She does say that she can't live up to me a lot, but I don't know what to do about it. I can't stop being myself to make her happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 00:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, but she won't go to counseling. And I've been to enough to where if I can be in a good, calm environment, I would be fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 00:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. It starts with an M. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 06:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was diagnosed over two years ago. I don't talk about it anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My sister is tearing my family apart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 04:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today's my mom's birthday and she's sitting downstairs crying. My sister thinks her life is over because she isn't in honors classes and is sixteen years old. My dad is too old to be dealing with teenage drama (he's almost 62). My sister hates me because I am happy, confident, and know what I'm going to do with my life. If I want her to be happy, I can't. She throws these huge temper tantrums, and everyone hates each other because of her. Not to mention, I have clinical depression, but I'm afraid to talk about it since she's already so messed up.

I don't think any of us can be happy until she leaves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-27 06:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is one beautiful dog!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 05:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having a pause button. I'll be sitting in class thinking, *wouldn't it have been nice if this morning once the alarm went off, I could have just paused and gotten all the extra sleep I wanted?* Or pausing just to finish my homework. This seeps into my thoughts all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 03:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhh.... Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 03:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still don't get it... Care to enlighten me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-25 20:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did anyone else read that as hashtag one? I'm ashamed of myself... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Shocking News in the Paper this Morning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-25 17:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-25 05:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It didn't help that it said Texas in the title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 05:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was so hoping that this was a gif. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 23:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true, and I am feeling better now, thank you. Hope you are aswell(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 23:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but I've been through treatment before. There is a history of substance abuse (alcoholism) in my family, and I'm too afraid that I'll get addicted. I stay away from that kind of stuff. It's just not right for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 07:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly... Thank you so much for the support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 07:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, I never thought of it that way. Thank you so much(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 06:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, really. It's more depression as the disease than depression as the effect of something. It's hard to explain, really, so that's a completely valid question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 06:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I know, there really isn't much to say, but it's comforting just knowing that someone is reading this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm Sad Today... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 05:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing went wrong... I don't know, I just feel bad. My heart is kind of sunk, and I don't know why. Depression just sucks. It's always looming in the distance, but it wasn't too far away today. I'm normally not to stuck in my depression, or at least haven't been too sick for the past few years, but today, I feel bad.

This is a lame post, I know. I just needed someone to talk to. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 03:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even... Wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 00:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're amazing!! Keep it up, you really have a talent there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 20:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are my favorite person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 07:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally understand. Either way it's a good look(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
