<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject337</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 20:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 20:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to turn it off when he mentioned Carmen Sandiego and Oregon Trail. Too many memories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 20:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you just... You did.

You ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 20:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember all the campaigns to remove the "is"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 20:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My tweets and instas get posted directly to my Facebook wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 23:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I haz? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 23:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is how I crack my toes. But, this girl is also doing it on rocks instead of carpet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 23:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was Frederick county bad too? I'm pretty sure it butts up next to or very close to Loudoun County, so I assume they got just as much snow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 21:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember my junior or senior year in high school they purposefully added extra days off for Spring Break in case of too many snow days. That way they could make us come back early from break or something.

This state just doesn't know what to do with anything that falls from the sky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 20:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Mine wins - "Good to swim in but hard to swallow"](http://i.imgur.com/ZpXGoJE.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 19:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh Dominion. I haven't missed you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 19:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My kid brother apparently had to sit in the gymnasium with a bunch of other kids because the teachers couldn't get to school that day last week.

 #closeFCPS was trending ~~nationwide~~ worldwide on Twitter. #closeLCPS was up there too.

OP's picture is more like how it was when I was in school here many years ago. "Oh, we might get some snow at some point. CLOSE THE SCHOOLS!!"

edit obvious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 16:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be interested in being a mod too. I can think of some good ideas and directions for the sub.

And I know CSS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 05:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. I used to work at a supermarket bakery and every day we would throw out food that had hit it's "Sell By" date. It was all cakes and bread loaves and bagels and the likes. This food was still good to be eaten for days. I tried to get the store to donate it to the homeless or shelters, and they said it was a health liability thing. I could see the issue being the same or similar for people who root it out the dumpster.

Didn't stop me from taking a bunch of that food home though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 19:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone needs to call the guys over in /r/theydidthemath and figure out how many packs of cigarettes this is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My parents still tell this story to anyone I bring home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 16:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 15:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That last one is perfect. Sex then pizza? Yes please. I need to remember that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 15:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get like that too. I can't think of what anything is called and trying to remember just makes the pain worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 22:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we go with comments that have significant text, I'm an expert in catching Minecraft sheep.

My very top comment is just an imgur link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 20:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This:
http://i.imgur.com/90pVdrH.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 19:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to hide my obsession with clash for a while. But then my clan started warring all the time, and I needed another 1.2mil gold for my th upgrade, and I could no longer keep it a secret. Now I just hang my head in shame and mumble out a "sorry" when my friends notice me off in the corner, playing CoC, avoiding social interaction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 17:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should look at /r/Goatsintrees  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 17:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never thought about until now, but yes, the putting on a t-shirt is super hot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 17:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we're not getting the whole story here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 15:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geese. I once saw a goose pick up a baby duck by its neck and shake it around until the duck was dead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 15:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not know that I could make it go to sleep with that button. I just use hot corners. Learn something new every day... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 07:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found the fattie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 07:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actual serious subreddit. One of the greatest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 07:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only a matter of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 07:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait. What? How long have we been able to tag? Did I miss a blog post or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 16:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awwww sweet!!! I'll walk down there now! Under Mark, I assume?

P.S. You're making my Monday morning a million times more tolerable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 15:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free breakfast from my favorite fast food place? Yes please!

608 North Main Street, Blacksburg, VA 24060

Lobby

Bacon AM crunchwrap, bacon waffle taco, coffee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 00:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The L in "inhale" looks like a hairy leg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 15:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please can someone make this happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 21:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wine glass works nicely too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 21:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we're talking about my dream from last night, about 5 bottles of oddly-named liquor, in all blue, silver, and white bottles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 19:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit at work has made me really good at laughing without smiling or opening my mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 16:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Animals technically don't have a gender when it comes to grammar. You don't say "That's my dog; his name is Spot." You say "It's name is Spot" to be grammatically correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 15:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on the license plate on that GMC, he's in VA, so I'd bet he works in DC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 08:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I come here. Voices of reason to calm my freaking out.

Patience is not my strong suit, but I'll try my hardest to keep calm until we can talk about it and hopefully work it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only a week in and already having issues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 07:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He moved away a week ago. Since then, we've had one phone call that lasted about 10 minutes. I get maybe 1 text from him a day, if even that. I mentioned today that I've barely heard from him. He says he's been busy. I tell him it would be nice to hear from him more than once a week. I explain that I don't need to talk to him every single day, but I don't want us to become strangers because we never talk. We agreed to talk about it more tomorrow on the phone, as he's with his friends tonight.

It's only been a week and we're already fighting about the distance. If I'm going to only get to talk to him once a week, that's not enough for me. I know myself, and I know I need more than that. I'm hoping we can find a compromise. I'm hoping he has a good explanation.

Did anyone else experience this at the beginning? Is this a red flag for later on? Before he moved he had this attitude of "we'll make it" and "don't worry, we'll be fine" and all that. Now it's like he doesn't think that's the case anymore. If he cared and wanted it to work, wouldn't he be putting in more effort? He says he's been busy with his friends. Can't he find 15 minutes to get away and call me, or 30 seconds to send me a text message? Why am I feeling less important than the people he sees every day? I'm starting to think maybe he's not as serious about it.

I'm suppose to drive up to see him this coming Friday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 06:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/thingsforants  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 08:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm home alone. I didn't go to my family's this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 21:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thought about juggling two lives has definitely crossed my mind. You know, never spending weekends with my friends here and whatnot. I suppose we will just have to take it as it comes and hope for the best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 20:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's hoping :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 20:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, your post is making me tear up, because your situation sounds extremely similar to the one my boyfriend and I have just thrown ourselves into. We weren't together for as long beforehand, but he moved away as a career move and I stay here for mine. We are both extremely career oriented people and this is just how it has to be right now. I have too much going on here to be able to move right now, and he needs to be in a different location for his job. We're also about the same distance away as you and yours (about 4.5 hours), so saying that you get to see him nearly every other weekend makes me happy.

But the thing that really got me is your bullet point 4. SO said something like this to me the other day, before he left. He said that we're both such ambitious people that we have the potential to be an amazing power couple one day. But we have to work on getting there first. And if that means being apart and still together, then so be it. It's a bittersweet thing.

Thank you for the feels. I'm on day 1 of my LDR, so your post was very encouraging for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 20:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't wear makeup normally, so no I'm not equating the two. I don't feel that I need makeup to look or feel good about my appearance. And I just happen to like my body better when it's in-shape and looking healthy. Everyone should always strive to have the body they want, regardless of what that body type is. Be happy in your own skin. I'm happiest when I'm slender.

I don't see what's shallow about wanting my own body or appearance to be a certain way. I'm saying nothing about how I prefer anyone else's body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 19:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP, I'm waiting on delivery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting my first quadcopter for Christmas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 18:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all! I've been thinking about getting into flying for a while. I've lurked on this sub a bit, and watched plenty of YouTube videos with various copters, and learned about the parts of them and all that jazz. I decided to (kind of) take the plunge and asked for a quadcopter for Christmas. Well, I found out that I'm getting a Syma X5C. So I'm wondering, did you all start out by learning on a smaller, less expensive copter? How long before you felt you were ready to invest in a nicer one? How hard is it to actually get good at flying? Any wisdom you have to share with someone who's never flown anything remote control before?

Thanks!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He moved away yesterday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 18:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a feeling I'm about to be a more frequent poster in this sub.

First of all, thank you to all of you who offered kind words and encouragement on my last post. Yesterday was the day. He left my apartment and I immediately called my best friend who came over with wine and Christmas movies, which was awesome.

I feel like crying and throwing up. I barely slept last night, my appetite is all but gone, and I'm still doubting that I can even do the long distance thing. SO is so confident that everything will be fine and we'll make it, so I'm hoping his confidence will rub off on me in time, and I'll gain some better faith in myself.

I think what worries me the most is that the move is indefinite. I have a career where I am now, and he has no plans for returning. He's starting a career in this new location. How is it suppose to work if we have no plan of being reunited at some point in the future? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 21:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't know that she does any of these things for him. Maybe she keeps herself slim and attractive because she likes herself that way. Not all women look good in order to impress a man. Some of us just take pride in our appearance, regardless of anyone else's opinion on the matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you're bored and flip through your apps without finding one you want to open, it's the digital equivalent of opening the fridge and not finding anything you want to eat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 21:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What can I send to my prisoner pen-pal for Christmas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 15:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 20:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cannot be unseen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 20:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a garbage person, but the 20" monitor sitting on my desk at work was found next to my apartment dumpster. Works great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 22:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Stop trying to make [insert some stupid word here] happen. It's **not** going to happen" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SO moving away soon. How do you guys do it? [f25] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 07:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bf is moving away this weekend. We haven't been together long, almost two months, but we've talked about it and we want to try to make it work. He's also not moving very far away, only about 4 hours. I've been pretending it's not happening and then this evening the whole thing just hit me like a bag of bricks and I broke down. I've never been in a LDR before and I have no idea how I'm going to deal with this. I don't know how I'm going to balance my life here with him being away. I feel like I'm going to lose all my friends because I'll be trying to visit him every weekend I can, or if he comes here I won't want to see anyone else. To me right now, it feels like a breakup. My best friend keeps telling me it will all be ok. Bf keeps reassuring me that we'll be fine, and I know deep down that we will be. I just don't know how, or how hard it's actually going to be to make it work.

Sorry I'm kind of venting right now, and my thoughts are all jumbled. I just needed to get this out and hopefully gain some insight into what I can expect, and maybe some advice to help me stop freaking out.

Thanks for reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 01:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of that rant was unnecessary. I can't believe I actually read through the whole thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 01:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It always makes me think I'm mildly psychic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 19:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it dropped the second one it was so adorable, I lost it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 17:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's good! Keep getting yourself out there. You'll find a good group of people to stick with eventually. It took me a while too because I don't make friends easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 17:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last movie I watched was Sabrina, so I guess I would be marrying Linus Larabee. So, married life would consist of me sitting around at the pool all day and not having to work because my husband is super rich. I'd be ok with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 17:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you checked out meetup.com? Not sure of your location, but if you're in the states, there are all kinds of meetup groups on that site. I host a group and we have random people show up sometimes and they like it and they become part of the group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 17:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he texted me after I gave him my phone number, and then continued to text me and hang out with me. I think that was a big hint.

I know, most boring story here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 17:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cousin and I did this driving up the east coast once. It was at a point in time when I was a broke college kid and didn't have a data plan. Lots of snapchatting ensued. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 16:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying really hard to come up with a TF2 reference... Someone help me out here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 21:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://creepypasta.wikia.com/wiki/The_Expressionless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 21:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one is the my favorite. Found it. Done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 18:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best place for Pho is the DC/Northern VA area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apparently the game thinks my level 5 town hall stands a chance against this monster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 18:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cereal Killers vs some Chinese team - Dec 11, 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 18:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Imgur](http://i.imgur.com/GAAwTJa.png)


Victory 51-17
War record 4-0

We came in strong with nearly every member of Cereal Killers attacking at least once.


Cereal Killers | Attack Totals | Other Clan
---|---|----
28 | Attacks Won | 9
38 | Attacks Used | 20
80.9% | Avg Destruction | 63.8%
-| - | -
 |**Best Attacks**|
12 | 3 stars | 2
5 | 2 stars | 4
5 | 1 star | 3
- | - | -
 |**Attack Stats** | 
1.34 | New Stars per Attack | 0.85
1m 56s | Average Attack Duration | 1m 52s
- | - | -
 | **Featured Battles** |
G_Shine | Most Heroic Attack | some name in Chinese
none | Most Heroic Defense | ssc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 20:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dafuq? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 18:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downloaded and playing. I'm not good at this.

Did you have coding experience before you built this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 17:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the only woman in my office. Having the bathroom all to myself is glorious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 23:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is location a reason to be cautious? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 23:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PayPal is fine. I just wasn't sure what the normal method was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQ] $300 to sign the lease of a last minute apartment change. Pay back $350 from my Dec 16th paycheck. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 20:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi. I originally was planning to move in with roommates who already had an apartment secure and I wouldn't have to pay a deposit. But, I found a different apartment that is worlds better for me to live in (less rent, no roommates, only a block from work, etc). I need to sign the lease by the end of this week, but I don't get paid until Tuesday the 16th. Normally it wouldn't be an issue as I make a decent amount of money, but with Thanksgiving, my last paycheck was only half of what it normally is.

I will pay back as soon as my Dec 16th check goes in direct deposit (9am on the 16th), $350 or whatever amount is deemed appropriate. At this point, getting this apartment secured is more important than the money.

I'm in Blacksburg, VA, USA. I don't know how the members of this sub handle money transfers as this is my first time here, but I'd be willing to pay for overnight mailing of a money order, or whatever else is easiest.

Thanks for reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
