<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9001</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 08:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What events transpired during your stay in Asia? Did you have any interesting or meaningful experiences? What did you spend a decade doing there? I'm glad you turned your life around by the way, and now you have a badass backstory!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 07:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The importance of parameters... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 05:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People actually do that. I'm one of them, it's always been a habit. It's said to build your immune system because you're ingesting a tiny amount of germs each day and your body builds resistance to it :D I can attest to that, because I rarely get colds or the flu and such even when everyone around me is sniffly and miserable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 17:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of do, mine consist of immense pressure in my eyes and it hurts to move them, sometimes I get sharp pains behind my right eye.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 22:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a small voice, so I constantly get talked over. It's disappointing when you have something to say and  realize that nobody's even looking at you, or even listening to you because someone else apparently had something more interesting to contribute to the conversation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 19:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg I stayed up all night playing video games, lol my insomnias really bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 04:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicunts sounds like a kickass band name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 04:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are not alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
