<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4675</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 23:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've surrounded myself with people who have mental illnesses and broken families. I don't know why, but I find it comforting. If you ever need to talk,I'm around. And I swear I'm not a creepy guy sitting in a basement 0.0  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not judging, but as a the child of a teen mom, I must ask-Why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 23:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, my mom had me at the ripe ol' age of 16. I had a lot of hard times in my life because of that, so I have to ask, why not out your children up for adoption? I would have asked to be put up for adoption if I had any sense of what was going on when I was a newborn, and I know it would have been the better choice. So, why not? Am I just generalizing my experiences? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 23:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a number 6...


SIXES FOR THE WORLD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any other teenagers suffering from anxiety and/or depression? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 23:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I'm the only one outside of my friend group at school, sometimes, which sucks. It'd be nice to know that there are other people my age who have these problems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 19:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I do. Generalized Anxiety Disorder, but mostly social anxiety. 

Usually, hanging out and talking to him works, but, as I said, I can't today. What people don't usually get is that he was my best friend before we were together so I've always depended on him, ever since we were really little.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 19:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an anxiety disorder, so my being upset could be for many reasons, or no reason at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
