<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1361</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 05:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure why this is in r/funny.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 05:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reeeeeeeeeepost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 05:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oral hygiene, it can save your heart! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 05:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Self cleaning antibacterial kitchen surfaces, robot maids/butlers, shower walls that don't get that soapy scum mould on them, microwave meals that taste like properly cooked food... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 04:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They would all be dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 19:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For accusing someone of giving inaccurate information, you sure didn't read the OP too well yourself. The OP is the girlfriend of the deceased and she is asking others to wear helmets to protect themselves.
Yes, the guy may have been riding badly, but I think the accusation of karma whoring is a little OTT to be honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 15:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She certainly has the superiority complex! But then again she is 6 and I think a lot if kids that age are fairly egotistical! I am going to see if I can visit with G T school and check out if they have a late application process. Thank you :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 15:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 15:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would it make a difference that this is a charter school, set up with the purpose of helping these children excel? I am not worried about whether she is the shining star, a leader, or a follower, I just want her to be happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 06:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 04:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for replying :-) 
Did you find it hard to socialise with your peers? What would you suggest for encouraging her to make friends of her own age? School admitted today that they bribe her to play with her peers with extra math work? :-)
(as in, she loves math so much she always wants to be doing some!)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it worth sending my daughter to a school specializing in Gifted and Talented children? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 03:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My daughter is 6 years old and will turn 7 in December. 
She is currently reading at around a high 2nd to 3rd grade level. Her math is at high 2nd grade level. Her current Kindergarten teachers have identified her as G T and suggested today that, although her allocated school for grade 1 is very good, she might be better off attending a school for G T pupils for her to achieve her maximum potential.
She has pretty much all of the characteristics of a G T child, she is obviously very bright, but she finds it hard to bond with peers, preferring to talk and work with adults. 
She completes the bare minimum of work necessary if she is not given extended guidelines to follow on quantity and quality as she 'does what the other children are capable of'. When given extended guidelines she can produce high quality work easily. 
She has little to no interest in playing with other children unless the play revolves around fact finding or discovery, e.g. she spent today playing with a group of boys finding and describing insects outdoors.
She also has all the wonderful emotional insecurities and anxieties of a young child trying to process thoughts beyond her emotional years. She has a huge fear of the unknown, and becomes very anxious when she does not know someones expectations of her. Change leaves her very insecure and I think she over analyses a lot in seemingly simple situations. 
I would hate to see her become lost in the education system, but I also worry that placing her in a G T school may ostracize her from peers in social settings. 

Do I give her a year at the public school and see how things go, or do I try to get her enrolled in the G T school?

As an aside, there are two other children in her current class that will be attending the G T school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 02:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My exact thought! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 02:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened to the other thread? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 02:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sjogrens syndrome? ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 00:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually free if it is for a child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 21:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks :-) I have been referred now to the National Jewish team. Hopefully one of them has some experience with EDS. I just want to get out of this bad pain cycle! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 23:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the first gif where he has actually appeared attractive to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Mint Chocolate Chip Easter Cake [2,560px × 1,920px] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 05:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 03:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have emailed them to see if any of their doctors have experience with, or patients with, EDS. They look great! Thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 03:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :-) I will check him out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need a recommendation for a rhumatologist in the Denver area. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-28 22:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am need of a recommendation for a rhumatologist or rhumatology specialist in the Denver area. 

Preferably nearer to Aurora or Parker, but I don't mind travelling further out. 

Preferably with knowledge of Ehlers-Danlos Syndrome.

They also need to take Cigna/GWH insurance.

I hope someone out there can help!

Thanks in advance x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-22 04:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We did this and it made a HUGE difference to us opening up to each other sexually. And we have been together 13 years! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 20:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love you :-)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 01:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Handcuffs, lube, dildo :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-15 01:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have two young children. Nothing is weird anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's only 9.30am... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 16:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 06:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ziggler vs Jericho :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Went to the Raw World Tour last night in CO. This is my favorite shot of the night. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 04:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 05:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just watched Pitch Perfect again. Sigh :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 05:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally hot. Going to a WWE house show in two days. Hoping to see him and a few other wrestling hotties :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-03 21:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would make more sense to show the weight in grams. I guess younger children can visualize the size of a tsp better? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-03 17:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not certain, but from the amount of sugar in each bag, it would appear that they have been labelled as x number of tsp, but they have used a tbsp to measure out the sugar. I have seen this mistake before in a kindergarten class doing the same comparisons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Anderson. Oh my, those eyes! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-19 22:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 00:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> me too. I thought it was normal to wake up in pain every morning! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-18 03:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soooo apparently I have a degree of color blindness... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 04:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant to add that the CBT course above is the one used by the NHS in Cornwall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 04:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Online CBT course here -

http://www.cci.health.wa.gov.au/resources/infopax.cfm?Info_ID=46

Usually through your local NHS is a 6-8 week wait for high risk cases, slightly longer for lower risk, but it depends on where you are.

Private CBT is *very* expensive.

I hope this helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-22 18:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually win and throw the tp roll at him in consolation :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-22 18:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats not good :-( I hope you find your way back again soon xxx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-22 06:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am between picture 6/7 at the moment.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-21 22:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soooo space is fruity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-21 20:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-21 17:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can see if you can get it in, but there might not be room today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-21 03:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well done on getting out of the house! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-21 03:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 23:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I hope you manage to get even a little done :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 23:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 23:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you mean! I usually am quite good with my day to day lists, but I have had 0 motivation or energy to even write them recently!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 21:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay, scribblenaughts :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-13 14:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your sister looks EXACTLY like my daughter! I did a triple-take! :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 18:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn onions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-14 02:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hehehe someone edited it to "...and I like pizza'. I was too slow to get a screenshot before it was changed back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-12 01:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tend not to go far if there is a chance of snow, but now I have put blankets, coats, gloves and hats, and some bottles of water and snack bars in the trunk :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-12 01:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stay safe! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-11 17:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hehe thanks :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-11 17:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-11 15:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have Google reviewed them. I also sent a message of thanks to their head office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-11 15:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I certainly have! Annoyingly they were all in the car the day before, but we took them out to take my husband to the airport and I forgot to put them back in the trunk! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-11 04:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-11 04:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankfully it was the battery. Apparently it had been slowly loosing fluid and then with the sudden drop in temperature it just gave out. I hope your applications go well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-11 04:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was the one on S Gibraltar Wy and S Himalaya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-11 03:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope your leg is ok :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love you people of Denver :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-11 01:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stupidly went out to run some quick errands today assuming the snow would fall when the forecasters predicted.

The snow hit just as my daughters gym class ended. Unperturbed I parked up at King Soopers in Centennial to do my groceries and when I came back out laden with shopping and two hungry and chilly kids, my car battery was flat. Dead. Kaput.

So, now I have a car going nowhere, no coats or blankets, and two cold and scared kids.

I tried a few friends on my mobile, but no one was in or answering their phones, then my network dropped out.

I got out of the car (in a t-shirt and jeans) and looked under the hood to see if there was anything I could do.

The guy parked in the space in front of me got out of his car to check what was up. He too had a flat battery and was waiting on a friend to come and give him a jumpstart. 

When his friend arrived, they tried to start my car first, but it was completely flat and we thought maybe the alternator was gone. They offered me a ride and a coat, but I didn't have anyway to get the car later, even if I called a tow.

I spotted an old Brakes Plus sticker on the car and called them from the superstore (they let me use their phone!) as I knew they were just across the block from where I was. The guy on the phone was very sweet and when I explained I had the kids with me and no coats etc, he offered to come over to the car park to see what he could do.
He brought his own jumpstart pack, but the car was still completely dead.

He drove us over to the garage waiting room, gave the kids candy and drinks, me coffee and obviously most important - access to the restroom! He then went back over to the car park to fit a new battery and drove my car back to me at the shop.

The people I met today were so helpful and kind, I just had to come and say Thank You Denverites for being so lovely :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-03 21:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to take some painkillers and woke in the night not remembering my name, where I was or who was in bed with me. I convinced myself I was a gay man. I am a straight female and the person in bed with me was my husband. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pumpkin Family </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-31 03:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-27 15:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NSFW, tripod and timer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's snow time! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-25 17:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-15 18:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great link, thanks!

The 1st advert kind of made me chuckle with all the native/transplant conversations on here :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-10 23:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last few days there has been an unmarked cop car picking up speeders in Aurora. On Quincy Ave, between S Picadilly and Gun Club. Usually with a marked car a few hundred feet up the road. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the amount of talk on Reddit about the election, how many of you are registered to vote, and how many of you will actually vote this year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 15:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a UK citizen living in the US, it feels that the hype and discussion around the election involves far, far more people than those who will turn out on or before Nov 6th. So Reddit, are you going to put your voice and choice to use? If not, why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-02 02:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Done :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-23 05:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, but only because I was driving out to Byers for the Dirty Girl 5k Mud Run :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-19 07:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aurora, Colorado :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
