<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject888</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 03:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "A while ago..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 03:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ayy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 03:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing has been released that will actually be on the album, as far as I know. Have you heard ["Go?"](https://youtu.be/vIi57zhDl78) I realize it's a collaboration, but still:  It is evidence of her experimenting sonically. *shrug* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grimes — REALiTi (Experimental pop) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 01:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 00:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. I have found that the medicinal/therapeutic effects also depend on the quality/type of weed, but mostly my mind-state before and during consumption (i.e. if I'm feeling negatively or overtly anxious it's probably not going to be much fun). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else here use marijuana to ease emotional pain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 22:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 08:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I’m sorry…. Hopefully a new build will be out this week to move your experience in a better direction.

On the upside, just be glad you’re not using the just-released Surface 3…apparently 10074 is rather unusable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 06:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize they’re of entirely distinct ethnic origins, but your mother and Björk bear some striking visual similarities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 05:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhhhh.... Ever read much into the Holocaust? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 03:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I my personal experience, tiles are too visually inconsistent--they provide similar functionality to "true" Start menu pinning, but in a package that I just have never warmed up to.  Hopefully somewhere down the line basic Windows 7-style pinning will come back into play, but until then, they'll remain excluded from my Start menu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 02:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
