<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2415</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 04:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> love this!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 01:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have gone with a warmer shade of pink, but otherwise, GORGEOUS! I love this look so much, and you are beautiful(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 04:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look great! Happy birthday(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 01:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was expecting a "You've sure got her back" type joke somewhere on here... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 01:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, happy cake day then! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 22:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The eyes look very nice(: I would add some color to your face (blush) and lips, and bring out those eyebrows a little more. You look great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 22:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 22:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might want to post this to /r/motorcycles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 22:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm confused... Today is your cake day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 08:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly what college is for. People that complain about a college degree not getting them a job went to college for the wrong reason. It is meant to enrich your mind, and in turn make you more skilled at your craft and hopefully more valuable to a workforce. Good for you(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 05:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, girl, you're talented!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 05:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is gold! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Made You Quit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 06:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had been on this subreddit for just under a month, and then one day I just wasn't motivated anymore. I realize that masturbating wasn't affecting my confidence or anything, I just decided that I wanted to stop. Now I can't get motivated again, and I thought if I heard some of your reasons why, I would find motivation in that.

Thanks for sharing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 03:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not alone... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 03:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, my area code is 972 as well! I don't know why I found that so interesting... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 00:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WOOW!! You look gorgeous! I'm officially obsessed with this look! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-28 02:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mean is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-28 02:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Just gonna put this here...](http://i.imgflip.com/1bh6.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-28 02:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May I just say, you are gorgeous!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 04:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 04:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first musical in high school was Grease. Couldn't agree more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 04:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love Never Dies.

No way in Hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 03:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, your welcome, I suppose. Honestly, the story is so amazing, I wouldn't normally care. The only reason I point it out is it was actually a vocabulary word of mine (being in high school and whatnot) and couldn't resist.

Thank you so much for your contribution to reddit. Your posts will never be forgotten. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 03:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. My. Lord.

My heart just wept... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 02:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is amazing, and I appreciate what you've done here. I am so sorry for this, but I couldn't help myself...

... you're trapped between the split in the ice *floes*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 02:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else start suddenly playing the soundtrack of *West Side Story* in their head? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 07:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you have another job while performing this job? If so, what was it? and if you didn't, what would you do while on your period? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 06:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else find this incredibly sad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 00:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh... Haha, I hummed this to myself and though, "well, I don't recognize this tune from anywhere..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 04:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that is a very good look on you!! I'm usually not a fan of bangs, but your face was made for them(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 02:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe, but that's just not how I look at it. I don't think He *did* it for me, He just helped me feel confident and strong enough to push myself to my fullest ability. But I completely understand why one might look at it that way. I just believe that there have been so many people that have helped me get to where I am today, and He had a portion too. Thank you for your support. It gave me a smile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 02:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, thank you, and I understand how you would think that. I think I wouldn't have had the strength to push myself so much if it had not been for His mental support.

But still, thank you very much(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 22:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 22:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fixed post... http://www.reddit.com/r/Christianity/comments/1cre0b/what_the_power_of_prayer_did_for_me_this_week/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the power of prayer did for me this week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 22:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi /r/Christianity,

I am a fifteen year old girl who is on her high school's drill/dance team. This week, we had tryouts for next years team to see who would make varsity and who would make Starlettes (JV). I am just about to graduate from my freshman year (so in tryouts, I am considered a sophomore), and since the beginning of this year, I have been a Starlette. I knew I was a better dancer and deserved to be on varsity, but I waited patiently for my turn to move up. Once tryouts came along I knew it was my time to shine.

But still, I couldn't do it alone. I knew that even when I had put forward my best effort, I still hadn't moved up during the year like some other girls had. I was confused and scared and had no idea what I was doing wrong. So I prayed. I have been praying for about a month that I would make the varsity team, with the help of St. Vitus (the patron saint of dancers) and St. Genesius (the patron saint of performers). God gave me the strength to work my hardest in the upcoming weeks to tryouts.
Well, yesterday was tryouts, and I made varsity! Yay!! And not only that, but as a sophomore, I made the highest score out of the whole team, plus a $100 scholarship. WOAH! My director told me that the judges were wondering why I hadn't tried out for officer (the highest authority position), yet I hadn't even been on varsity yet.

**Yes, I do acknowledge that it was my hard work that paid off, but I got the moral support from God. It wasn't like He told me *Okay, now do 100 jackknives and then sit in you splits for a minute, each side.* That was me. But I think He helped guide my patience and my focus. He inspired me to work toward this goal that I ultimately received.**

This is surreal. I honestly cannot believe I am so extremely lucky that such a thing could happen to me. This is almost unheard of, and I am so unbelievably happy. To add on, just two years ago I was fighting an extreme depression and battling thoughts of suicide, but God saved me. If I had given up then, I wouldn't be here now. Thanks to His guidance, I have never been happier. My life is going amazing, and I am so thankful to Him. Just ask, and He will do anything for you. You are His son/daughter and He could not love you more.

**TL;DR:** Trust in God. He will give you the strength to carry on, even when it gets tough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 22:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry. I guess I did misunderstand. I just got very defensive when I thought you were undermining my mistake. My apologies for lashing out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 22:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excuse me?

Being a part of a drill team is an extreme dedication that is hard to explain. You spend every hour of every day trying to be perfect, a goal that can never be truly reached. It takes so much concentration and strength. I put everything I have into this, but I couldn't do it alone. I have no idea what this has to do with me being a young person. Sure, there are many other things that are much more severe that the Lord has helped people with, but this is what is important to me. I am extremely embarrassed that you would suggest that people would "rip it apart." I'm sorry, but you made me feel like my accomplishment amounts to nothing.

Think before you speak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 03:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dem lashes... aw my gawd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 03:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! You look beautiful!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 03:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that's amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to keep your waterline from smudging all over your lower lids? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 03:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello lovelies,

I normally don't do my waterline, but when I do (for my drill team), it is a hot mess. (FYI: I use the twistable pencils aka crayon eyeliners.) Every single time it smudges everywhere. No matter what I do, it ends up all over my lower lids and looks horrible. Can anyone advise me on what to do? I'm sick of wiping my eyes to get all the ugly blackness off of them):

Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 03:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 06:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone tell me what he said? It was deleted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 06:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 04:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That poor girl... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 01:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah. Sorry about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 00:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is this on this subreddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 00:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. I was writing the word "label" trying to spell it as "lable." I could *not* figure out what I had done wrong. I also have gotten stuck over "santa" vs. "satan" quite a few times. That one is a bit more concerning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 00:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this!! I am currently enrolled in a Catholic high school, and I have much respect for the Islam faith. I understand that we have our differences and my beliefs differ from that of yours, but we are very similar and just want to love God. I'm so sorry that you're beautiful faith has been associated with such horrible acts that you and the vast majority your fellow Muslims are not responsible for.

Go in peace and love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 00:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's definitely enough proof for me. Dammit reddit...

Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 22:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe Kids Bop is the Canadian KidzBop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 03:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Sexy zebras. When I was in eighth grade, I had a friend so used this phrase instead of "cool" or "interesting." Now it's my username. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 08:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was it like when you saw yourself for the first time all doctored up? Was it a relief, or strange to see a new face? On that note, how similar do you look in comparison to before that son of a bitch decided to fuck with the wrong woman?

Thanks so much for answer *so. many. questions.* you truly are amazing and I wish you an amazing life here on out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 01:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I've heard that they can be perceived as gay, but honestly, I think they are amazingly attractive. They hug and show *just* enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 06:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant username? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 06:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boxer briefs are so goddamn sexy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 06:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also cleanse my face in the shower. It's so convenient and refreshing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 06:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the hardest habit to break, and you're not alone. I believe that it's okay to break once in a very few time. Just remind let this be a release, not a relapse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 00:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently selling that on eBay. Price went from under a dollar to over ten dollars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 22:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it makes you feel better, most women think men should have to ball sacks. We only pretend to know what's going on, and it's easier to pretend because the male anatomy is somewhat less complex than a woman's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 22:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I use the ultra thin liners for when I have a super in and have to wear a thong. (Note:  I'm on a dance team.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 22:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, when it first kicks in, you know. It's easier to tell when you get it when you wake up, but when it's during the day, personally, my thighs get sweaty and my uterus feels like it's being used for a scratching post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 22:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely get turned on more easily. The right song can send me into a dizzy fit on sexual tension. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 22:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could say cool, I would say annoying... Haha, Glad I could help!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 21:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fairly accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 21:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me personally, I've only had mine for about four years, but I have adjusted to knowing how my period works and understand it better. I am more of an instinctual person and have paid very close attention to how my body works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 21:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going to lie, I don't know / haven't study much about what exactly is going on down there. I do know that the first few days is a lot of what seems like tissue and blood. The rest of the time is still the tissue, but not so much blood. To get a more accurate description, you would have to ask a professional, but I know for me, I never have only blood, but I do sometimes have only uterine wall.

EDIT: (Currently on my period) You can have just blood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 21:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I hate waking up to a dirty pad. I usually wear a pad in addition, but alone, it grosses me out too much. I never use a tampon for more than twelve hours. I usually switch them three times a day (partially because I'm too lazy to do it more): when I wake up, in the afternoon, and before I go to sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 21:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fenêtre. It means "window" in French, but I think it sounds beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 07:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all. I actually find you quite beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 07:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already posted this comment, but I'll just copy and paste it down here for you.

Too be honest, it can be hard to tell sometimes. For most women, you wake up in the morning and their tampon is still white, so they can move on. For other women like me, the bleeding stops, but the uterine wall still sheds for a few more days. In the end, a woman's uterus feels fresh and renewed, and your body kind of tells you when it's over.

To sum up, womanly instinct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 07:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn you... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 07:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too be honest, it can be hard to tell sometimes. For most women, you wake up in the morning and their tampon is still white, so they can move on. For other women like me, the bleeding stops, but the uterine wall still sheds for a few more days. In the end, a woman's uterus feels fresh and renewed, and your body kind of tells you when it's over.

To sum up, womanly instinct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 07:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bloating going away. Every period I get, my belly puffs up like a bubble. When it's done, I realize I have a great figure. It is a *huge* confidence boost.

I also have to add that you feel a lot less gross and, well, *are* a lot less gross when your uterine wall isn't coming out in bloody patches. I would add the cramps finally going away, but mine usually only stick around for the first half.

**TL;DR** You don't feel disgusted by your own body once it's over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 06:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daaayum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 06:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would've posted something in French just to see if anyone noticed... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 06:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, there's a reason we have subreddits like /r/confession ... If this were real, it wouldn't be posted here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 05:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took it in today and decided to let then go ahead and replace the hard drive. It was in really bad condition, and none of the files could be read. Thanks again for all your help(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-05 06:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much!! It really helps to understand the situation. I tried to repair it, but the b-tree problem arose and claimed that the disk could not be repaired. When I pressed my ear to the bottom of my laptop, I heard ten clicks, followed by two, four second vibrating noises. I assume that's he clicking sounds you were referring to, so I shut it off for the night.

Thanks again!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My mac claims to have an Invalid B-Tree Node Size... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-05 04:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was using my laptop last night to listen to music, and I realized the music had become slow and choppy, so I decided to turn it off. When I turned it back on, it took a very long time and it popped up with a screen I had never seen before. (I'm don't really have an adept knowledge in computers, so please bear with my somewhat vague explanations.) It allowed me to navigate to something that told me I have an "invalid B-tree node size." I cannot access my files or desktop now. What does this mean? Can I fix it, and if so, how? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 02:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to question the date, but then I realized that I'm just an American... *facepalm* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 07:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but I have come across people that have thought less of me when I have told them I am Catholic. In Catholic high schools, there is a large group of people who are atheist and I tend to socialize with the people a lot, just by chance. When they found out that I was not an atheist, some avoided me or just appreciated my company less. I guess it's just a level I can't relate to, but I still worry that they think I'm a nut or something.

I'm not crazy, I just think I have a loving Father waiting for me on the other side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 02:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I saw the title, I was not expecting gore makeup... Nonetheless, she did an amazing job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 21:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **DON'T PRETEND YOU DON'T KNOW THAT WE GAVE YOU THE EIFFEL TOWER!!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 21:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I have this? This pack looks AMAZING! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 07:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at a time like then, when they take over our subreddit... 

**TO /R/FRANCE!!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ARE YOU FEELING THE FREEDOM, VOUS TROUS DU CUL FRANÇAIS?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 07:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 07:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **NON!! C'EST PENIBLE!!**

**THAT'S THE ONLY FUCKING FRENCH I KNOW TO INSULT YOU WITH YA DAMN COMMIE!! DON'T MAKE US TAKE BACK THE EIFFEL TOWER!!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 07:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **NOT TO MENTION THE EIFFEL FUCKING TOWER** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 06:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moisturize, moisturize, moisturize!!

I know that it can sound contradictory, but moisture is an oily face's best friend! When your skin becomes dehydrated, it overcompensates for the lack of water with *oil*. Benzoyl peroxide can also have a drying effect on the skin, so you can use it, but with moderation. Drinking more water can also help.

As an oily girl too, I hope this helps!!

P.S. **MOISTURIZE!!** 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
