<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4359</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 16:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably not as devastating or terrible as some... but I found out my mom regrets marrying my dad whereas my dad does not. He's not a terrible person per se; just very stubborn.

I knew their marriage wasn't perfect but to hear her actually say that was a bit disheartening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 16:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very lucky. As much as there's a lot of shit going on in my life, I've been incredibly lucky that my hard work paid off when it needed to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 16:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I don't understand either. I thought this was a cute post. And a lot of people clearly agreed since it got to the front page.

Edit: You don't like this because of FB qualities. Point taken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 16:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a pretty pattern. Man that fish is a better artist than I! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 02:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the thumbnail alone I saw the inside of the ears as red eyes and the face as an open mouth. I was so confused why this was on awwducational </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 16:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm not a racist but it's time for dinner"

"YOU HYPOCRITE" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 16:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put that cookie down! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 16:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Very poor choice of words." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 16:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I admire you for being the bigger person. I think I'd be consumed with rage and bitterness if someone did that to me. Hope you find a great guy that deserves you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 15:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "lol sry bro, got so many prompts and must have clicked yes by mistake." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 15:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry you had to go through that kind of shit. Just reading your comment broke my heart; I can't even imagine how difficult it must have been for you. But looks like you have great kids. Best of luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 12:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being dismissive of people who hold jobs that pay less.

I went on a blind date with a guy who was really full of himself. He was also a hard worker so I could kind of see why he was so proud of his achievements, and I tried to be understanding. But then he said something like "you know how bus drivers are, they're uneducated and grumpy." That drew the line for me. Didn't even want to be just friends with the guy afterwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 12:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wanted to finish Cthulhu: Dark Corners of the Earth but I was too much of a wuss. Survived the Attack of Fishmen chapter, didn't have the energy to continue. I think I would've had more fun if I had my friends over to play it with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 12:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. That Let it Go song made me sick of the movie even before I watched it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 09:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What defines "nice"? This is probably an extreme example but I'm sure Hitler was a pretty nice person to people who blindly followed him. 

IIRC Louis mentioned that implying that they weren't nut jobs when they were going on about their daily routine. They did have a "normal" side to them, loving their family and enjoying little things in life, but it pales next to what they believe and how they act on such beliefs. 

My heart goes out to former WBC members, but I find it hard to believe those who stay there and choose to spread hate can be deemed "nice". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 08:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty amazing how most people in the ROK are skinny to slim when they offer fattening food like this. I have the Korean genes but I wasn't born with that kind of "eat whatever the hell I want but stay skinny". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 08:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the sight of something can make someone feel "neugul" / nauseous. I agree food itself should be described as "neuki" / greasy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 07:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper fresh out of a photocopier, all warm.

It's kind of disconcerting when it's in tens or hundreds of pages and I have to work on it, but it still has a peculiar smell I find pleasing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 07:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How *you* doing? (a la Joey) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 07:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the faction idea, but yeah I wouldn't buy monthly subscriptions either. It'll probably make me feel like I *have* to play the game as much as possible as opposed to just making me want to play whenever. That's too bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 07:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "love don't make things nice - it ruins everything. It breaks your heart. It makes things a mess. We aren't here to make things perfect. The snowflakes are perfect. The stars are perfect. Not us. Not us! We are here to ruin ourselves and to break our hearts and love the wrong people and die. The storybooks are bullshit." - from Moonstruck.

Not particularly cute but something about this resonated with me. Love makes us unreasonable, at times insane, and the lines seem to capture that perfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 07:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One time back in university years I thought this server at my fave restaurant was pretty cute. I left him my number in a post-it with my check. Never heard back from him so I stopped going there for several months out of embarrassment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 07:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, watching it would be fun. I'm not particularly good at PvP so :p

I guess Skyrim Online doesn't have this? I haven't tried it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 07:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love this as well except I'm not sure how it could be a competition. PvP? Things would come down to the issue of who has better items and not skills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 07:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually it doesn't exactly apply to other people who hold the same position as I do. I was extremely lucky.

I'm isolated from the rest of my colleagues (who work together in one room with cubicles, where I once worked as well) and even though technically I could, I would feel too self-conscious to do whatever I want. Right now I share my office with one colleague who is not my supervisor so anything goes. I receive assignments via email or phone calls so people giving me work rarely see me in person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 07:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, shit vs. the shit doesn't make much sense to me either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 07:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how that phrase was coined but I always imagined a giant cookie merrily rolling on the road... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 07:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can pretty much do anything I want at the office as long as I get my job done in time. I've watched movies, played the League, blogged, taken a nap, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 06:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely love that series. I really have to commend him for tolerating them and trying out their way of life even though he (like the rest of us) cannot comprehend what drives them to be so hateful. I would've been really tempted to just quit midway. I don't have that kind of patience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 01:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really love the retro style! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 00:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking love naan. I don't usually use expletives in expressing my love for food but goddamn I love it so much. Yours looks superb! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 10:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not British but this looks like a "u wot m8" situation... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 10:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Look at me. You will pick me. You will serve me for eternity." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 10:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I thought too, like using the flag as a cape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 10:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was afraid this might have a bad ending. Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 10:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goddamn I hate it when people do that. For some, common decency just doesn't seem to exist. :( But it's good to see that this hasn't discouraged you from helping others. I think I would have called it quits easily myself. Though I don't smoke, I know a lot of people who would benefit from this and I thank you for continuing to help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 07:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they're okay too. I don't like every song they make, but a lot of the songs in All the Right Reasons were pretty decent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 07:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually this makes me happy for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 07:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here 2, also Canadian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 07:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I didn't know that. Thanks, I'll check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 06:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a giant dick now thanks to radiation poisoning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 06:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry you had to deal with those assholes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 06:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching my grandpa's coffin being rolled into the crematorium.

Obviously I didn't see the oven. We said our goodbyes before the gate that led to the oven chamber. But I didn't expect them to bring out the remains before our eyes and then show us the grounding procedure. 

That felt surreal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 06:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine a slightly smaller one with a little surprise from John Doe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 06:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Descent. The last woman probably didn't make it out of the cave. ... Probably. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 06:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's kind of like sharks that would bite you to death and then say "oh, dude, sorry, I thought you were a seal. I'm... I'm so sorry." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 06:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teleportation spell from Diablo II. I'll have to wave my arms like crazy though if I want to get to work from home, given the fact that I can only teleport to a location within my sight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 06:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love this, except I wonder if I'll remember that I loaded the old save file? I don't think I can take most out of learning from my mistakes all that much if I forget... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 02:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also I'd rather not feeling anything, so this sounds like a winner for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 02:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I hear networking is really important in BDSM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 16:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way things turned out after Scar was put in charge was tad disappointing. The typical good people (Simba's.mom,.etc) suffering is predictable but even Scar and the hyenas had little to eat. Thought he was smarter than that. HE IS JEREMY IRONS. COME ON DISNEY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 16:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you enjoy it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 16:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Paul! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 16:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's an excellent point worth digging into. But in the end he set his weapon loose to wreak havoc and tried to profit from it. I wouldve been more sympathetic about Syndrome's good boy gone bad personality otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 13:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me me me me me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 00:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad I'm not alone in having hots for Bear Grylls. ♥ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 08:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the varying degrees of Cheese shades. Must they all squeeze themselves in there together? 3 They just know how to be cute, don't they. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 05:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like everyone here I think you found your look! It looks awesome. Also thanks for donating that luscious lock of yours. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 06:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They operate on a reservation basis? Must be really popular. Thanks for the info. Will check it out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 06:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't surprised by this. I knew something was up :'( Hope things turn out for the better for both of you. I'm sure he's a fighter inside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 06:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's beautiful! Such detail. Consider submitting it to the Fight Club FB fan page. More people need to see this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 04:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Dude are you sure this is how it's done?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 03:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to say "can't wait for her to settle in and dominate the house" but it seems like the job is already done. Thanks for bringing her to safety! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 01:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back when the Internet was still a new thing (Windows 95-98 era, I think) I saw that my computer was in danger, infested with malware and this nice company offered a program for just 49.95 to get rid of them.

I was like ten. I was afraid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 01:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally. Same goes for carrots, onions, pretty much all vegetables.

I still hate beans though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 01:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, makes sense. I myself am pretty much addicted to coke zero so I'll take the offer nine times out of ten. Non perishables or things you use on a daily basis at a large quantity, also understandable.

I guess I should've clarified in my original comment that I was thinking more along the line of clothes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 17:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure Canada is still in Top 3 of the most polite countries... If not, then I do apologize in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 17:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Yeah. When we're done with it!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 17:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got my mom (in her 50s) into the trilogy and it's become an annual thing for us. Back in university we'd pick a week in the winter break and do the LOTR marathon.

Of course by watching I mean talking over all the scenes because we know what happens and just want to nitpick the detail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 17:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not very NSFW but I used to take screenshots of the Sims 2 and make comics. Also created clothing items. I'm pretty sure this was the major factor in bringing down my undergrad GPA. I should be ashamed of putting so much effort and time into doing something like that but I was happy doing it. Good memories... just had lasting repercussions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 17:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buying things whenever you see "up to __% off" or "2 for 1" sale.

If they had been meaning to buy those particular products, sure, but buying stuff just because it's on sale is pretty silly.

I give this as an example because I used to be like this when I was younger... What a fool I was.

Edit: typo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 17:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wha...? This is some Disney teen movie stuff right here. Who does that? Jesus christ. Sorry you had to endure that :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 17:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it's not like Frey needed another reason to be called a scumbag... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 05:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brownie points for being a cat person. Not that he'd need any... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 15:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember installing Prince of Persia 2 from larger floppy disks (5-something inch ones). There were like ten of them! Now I can carry around 64gbs in my cell phone charm... All that progress in less than 30 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 12:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You captured each movement so perfectly! *resist making a pun*

This would make a really great sticker series 3

Edit: Just found out you only ship within the US :( Too bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 12:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must make a calendar of her... She's beautiful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Used to work for Honest Bender's Orphanarium... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 12:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 05:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do want to see more of Futurama. People say the Simpsons has gone way past its prime and should have ended a long time ago but I still find the series endearing and funny. I'll probably feel the same way about Futurama if it is rebooted yet again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 05:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What are you, gay?" The phrase it self is totally dull but the context was flawless. A close second would be the one about how the spirit is willing but the body is spongy and bruised. :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 00:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awww they're made for each other. I can't wait for them to conceive a twisted hell spawn!

Man each time I post a comment here I'm typing things I thought I never would... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 00:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow I'm late to the thread and probably (and hopefully) you feel better by the time you read my comment but fuck that woman. Even if she was a super model she wouldn't have any right to say that kind of thing to anyone. I'm sorry you had the misfortune of crossing paths with that kind of nut job. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 00:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My usual course of action in this case is to murder the wife... welp this is a sentence I thought I'd never type. Thanks CK2! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 00:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol it seems like that's when Tom swung by Korea. He also starred in the Korean SNL and did some weird shit. Gotta love a hot guy with a sense of humour and Oxford accent 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 11:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously though. I want to know as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 11:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MY GOD first of all the cherries look great! The kisses decoration is so well-done. It's something I'd never pull off. Well done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 05:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man once I get a taste of that I'll probably want exclusively that burger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 12:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm relieved it's about excitement. He'll be thrilled!

I just hope he doesn't sell the tv to get you a present a la the gift of maji haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 12:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know... I would think the person was trying to befriend me if someone stuck an arrow in me and set me on fire... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 12:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "How come you have to shower so often? WHY ARE THEY PUNISHING YOU"

unless she likes water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 09:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello from a fellow Canadian! I only got to stay five days or so in Montreal but I loved food there in general! Wish I could visit your shop... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 03:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you make the costume yourself? It's spot on! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 03:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Is it me?" *raises one eyebrow* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 01:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad she met you! Hope she gets to run around soon and play with your kids. That'd be an adorable sight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 16:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure you say that NOW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 01:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't realize I'm part of that 1%! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 01:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chocolate beans! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 01:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so sorry you lost him... And he was so young :( But I suppose he'll stay young in the kitty heaven forever, teasing other older companions. RIP beautiful Mr. Boots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 01:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is she Siberian?? She does look like a princess! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 01:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must. Resist. Petting. the Monitor... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 01:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet mother of God a Tuxedo 3 She's gorgeous. And I love it when a cat and a dog become friends. Consider posting pics of her in /r/cats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 00:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the detail on Slurm! Each figure looks like it would make a great keychain or necklace. wish i had this kind of talent! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 14:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the last part In Moe's voice automatically </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
