<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1095</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 16:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kinda wish he was like the Vertigo Lucifer, but how would they have pulled off Mazikeen. ╮(╯▽╰)╭ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 15:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just the mini series. I've been wanting to check out the Books of Faerie myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 02:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like that one guy from the Mighty Boosh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 15:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Diamond the only vendor source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 07:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look for small clues, like someone constantly sniffling or rubbing their nose, people taking short breaths. . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 01:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone hook me up? Either as a third party or with a contact for a LCS that can help me out? My LCS's havent heard about this and there are a couple TPs i wouldnt mind getting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 14:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish they had extended the sale by just one day T.T . . .I would get paid the day after Batman Day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 05:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm tempted by the buy 2 get 1free online with the discounts....just wondering if instocktrades is still cheaper. . .gonna have to mess around with some numbers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 06:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait. . .so you harass her until she fucks at work?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 05:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is about what was left on the loan yes. In the middle of paperwork currently to determine how they will setup a payback plan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 01:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In response to your Edit 2.0:

I mean they do make test kits to find out what powder is what. . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 00:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With $27k , I can pay off the attorney general and still have 8k to put towards my other loan that is close to default. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 19:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a question or a declaration? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 19:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They bring crime, litter, SWINE FLU

So just like your average american? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 17:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is all the red meat he eats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 09:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work the morning T.T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 09:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harley Quinn's series just finished its first arc, so the next issue will be a good jumping on point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 07:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea it is kind of an ego killer when you realize that you passed the halfway mark of your late father's life. Shit sucks when you realize you are no where near where he was at this point in life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 19:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops seems I was just thinking of the Baby Formula vs Breast feeding controversy of Nestle Mexico. . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 19:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe it was Mexico. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 17:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it has a slight reference in Justice Leeague 3000, but so far is stand alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 09:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heads up, get ready for some pretty big feels with this title. I actually cried a little in volume 3, and got kinda sad in some of the others. Still need to read the last  5 trades and the select single arcs trades.

The Deluxe Death Trade that collects all her stories in one is a decent related title at a good price. And After volume 4, it would be a good time to start the Lucifer trades if you are interested in how his story continues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 22:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple of my favorite from the New 52 are Sword of Scorcery vol1. , Hawkman and Justice League Dark. 

If you end up liking the darker side, there is the Sandman Series from Vertigo (which is like a Mature part of DC)

Last piece of advice, instocktrades.com has trades at an awesome discount price for most comics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 22:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea started the East of West and recently Saga thanks to the Image humble bundle a month or two ago. I need to go back through EoW again to remind my self whats going on also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 21:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started late with my **Justice League 3000** pulls so I just got the first two last week (a local LCS wanted $20 a piece so did Midtown for reg. Price) and read all 8 just the other day. It is an interesting story and how it ties in to Future's End is interesting when they mentioned they have 97% of all metahuman DNA from the island 1000 years ago. Happy to be current on it.

Ordered Outcast #1 from Image with those two, since it sold out everywhere I looked. Decent take on Exorcisms and looking forward to the explanation of his blood burning the possesed.

Read through the other day the Batman Manga Death Mask. It was an interesting story with a little background of Bruce in Japan.

Currently working on the first Hellblazer arc in Original Sins TP and enjoying it so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 07:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should be next banner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 06:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly the movie with Keanu Reeves was my first encounter with anything Constantine. I know almost quite literally everyone denounces the movie as being a Constantine film, but I love it none the less. My first comic ecounter was the New 52 JLD and Constantine trades, I tried catching up with the single issues, but never really put much onto it so I just wait for trades.

Just started Hellblazer vol. 1, and am still in middle of first arc, I find it intetersting, but am going through it slow since I'm reading a couple different books at the same time.

My vote for next title is Lucifer vol. 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 06:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fag is common brit slang for cigarrette. The first time I ever heard it, yea same reaction, but that was long before I read Hellblazer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 20:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the Xx_'s are due to the name they want being taken, so that is accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 08:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI, Goobers is a chocolate covered peanut candy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 02:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping he appears in Future's End at some point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 02:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a horror comic, also by Image, it sold like crazy everywhere near me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 02:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For my it was between that or Outcast for my pulls. I chose Outcast and am going to wait for a trade on Wicked/Divine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 02:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Nightwing vol. 4 is still in the mail :x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 02:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watched first season of Arrow this past week on Netflix. Unfortunately season 2 isnt on it yet and my local libraries dont have it yet. Anyone know when it is supposed to come to netflix?

I've been meaning to pick up the New 52 trade of Static Shock. Does he show up anywhere outside his series?

That Marvel 100th Anniversary issue of Spiderman was fun. Kingpin in a tech-venom suit, like woah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 02:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering they've had leaks, I don't see why they wouldn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 01:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You dont think NSA intercepts their own messages?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 03:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is just that there is not only THC in weed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 19:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Django Unchained TP- Gotta have some Django

100th Anniversary #1: Xmen - Really enjoying these anniversary issues.

Deadpool: Dracula's Gauntlet #2 -first one was decent, but not sure how I like having 3 weeklies on my pulls

Elektra #4 - Really good series so far.

Savage Hulk #2 - was disappointed regular hulk was cancelled and the #1 Savage was ok, so I'm giving this one more try

Ultimate FF #4 -

Batman Eternal #15 - too far into it to give up now.

Harley Quinn invade Comic Con Intl. San Diego #1 - I'm a sucker for one shots.

Teen Titan #1 - Gonna see how the new one is.

The New 52: Future's End #11 - Loving the story so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 09:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Django Unchained TP- Gotta have some Django 

100th Anniversary #1: Xmen - Really enjoying these anniversary issues.

Deadpool: Dracula's Gauntlet #2 -first one was decent, but not sure how I like having 3 weeklies on my pulls

Elektra #4 - Really good series so far.

Savage Hulk #2 - was disappointed regular hulk was cancelled and the #1 Savage was ok, so I'm giving this one more try

Ultimate FF #4 - 

Batman Eternal #15 - too far into it to give up now.

Harley Quinn invade Comic Con Intl. San Diego #1 - I'm a sucker for one shots.

Teen Titan #1 - Gonna see how the new one is.

The New 52: Future's End #11 - Loving the story so far.






































 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 08:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing until at least this Wednesday, it has been up for at least a week already so not sure how much longer it will be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 07:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? Well if I am to afford at least the weekly's in my pull list this week Imma have to cook my lunch/dinner at home for work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 07:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing one is the older version and not the reprint. . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 05:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is just that doesn't Constantine and Zantanna have a sorta of history together? I think she would be better to have a show on NBC if their shows end up doing well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 05:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to see Doctor Occult or Tim Hunter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 65% off Select DC trades- InStockTrades is having a second wave of 65% off select trades and collections. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-13 21:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 18:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard you can ask for honey butter on a chicken strip sandwhich. Never tried tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 02:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being mutilated as a baby

Fucking disgusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 20:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of shit phone you have? I read it just fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 05:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sleeping until I have to go to work at night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 04:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Purfume: Story of a Murderer or Spirited Away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 02:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 02:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is the southern equivalent of Disney workers saying "Have a magical day" or something that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 14:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't prove that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 06:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of y'all being taller and longer than I only justifies my confidence issues, at least in my mind :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 18:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out the Sandman Series by Vertigo if you are wanting a Darker feel from your comics...shoot I started reading them when I was 22 last year.


Incase you didn't know a good place to find a lot of trade collections is instocktrades.Com  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 18:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking it was this, just wasn't 100% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 17:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So jealous. What collections are these exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 04:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dark House is leaving soon and was Decent enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 02:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Credits are part of the run time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 02:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it is exactly 3 hours with the 15 minute previews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 06:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is this one thing. . .what is it called. . .Reddit Platinum? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 05:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shoot I work in a cinema and dont really understand what the difference is, but if someone had brought that to my attention, I would have gone to the booth and verified that the current playlist matches the projector's settings. I mean the correct format is right there in the name of the movie file.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 05:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he was a fan of the Sandman comics series. There is the short story in one issue where the Dream of cats tells this cat it is talking to that basically if enough people (or cats) dream the same reality at the same time the true reality can be changed. It was a rather sad story actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 05:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was high the first time I watched Paprika, so naturally I didn't fully remember the ending. Be me, a rather overweight guy, showing it to current crush and everything getting super awkward when the fat guy gets the hot girl at the end. . .the moment was so cringe-worthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 01:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a little hard to follow, I'm giving a couple more issues to really decide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 15:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Batman Eternal, Future's End, Sinestro, JLD, and maybe Harley Quinn #0 Director's Cut.

Others: Trees, C.O.W.L., Doop, Amazing Spider-Man, Savage Hulk, All New Ultimates, Ghost Rider, Deadpool vs Carnage, (Damn seems all my marvel pulls are this week imma be broke T.T) and need to get MPH from last week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 15:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad I'm not the only one captivated by Trees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 00:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> East of West easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 22:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they extended their service area to the suburbs on the edge of Dallas, I would actually use the service. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 21:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hellraiser. I guess I just waited too long to see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 21:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was funny before I did pot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 13:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you say before taking it off if she never takes it off in the .gif?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 13:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I have a hard on for inconcievable bugs? It doesn't matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 10:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you are on xbox. . .just saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 09:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well. . .arent there tofu steaks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 09:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we need to break down the military budget into what % of it is actually used for military research and not just straight arms productions or troop employment/deployment then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 05:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it is a Driver's License it does apply, but if it is just a straight up ID, I'm not sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 21:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched Unbreakable, with Bruce Willis and Sam L Jackson, for the first time the other day. Was a very interesting look at the question: What if there are superheroes, but they dont know it yet? I highly recommend it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 21:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Current Runs from last week: Batman Eternal, Future's End, Harley Quinn, Ultimate FF, Elektra,

Currently slowly working through the First Lucifer Trade from Vertigo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 23:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm preparing myself for the Hobbit Trilogy marathon that is sure to happen in december.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 21:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I talked to a police officer the other day at my work and apparently there is a sort of underground prostitution ring on myspace in various cities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 19:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the response was worthwhile others would let you know by the way they respond. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 19:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has been off and on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 19:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it hurt us after the leak wouldnt it have hurt us before the leak? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 05:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shoot it wasnt too long ago that tardigrades were all over reddit. I learned what a water bear was due to it being a meme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 02:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive been wanting to get into the Books of Faeirie honestly. But I am up to book 6 of Sandman, but been having trouble finding it locally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 02:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldnt mind a DC one, dunno if you have any Vertigo but that would be dope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 23:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didnt see that being who was placing the hits on Harley. Decent enough surprise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 04:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And thats why i live in the burbs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 04:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didnt know it implied sexual orientation that phrase as Big Boi said in his song Back Up Plan:

I was young, full of cum, down for the skeet skeet, not dumb . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 07:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like the mirror isnt exactly haunted, but begs the question that it attracts mentally unstable people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 05:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree, but I tend to be liberal with my judgement of short films. The last one and "O" are the weirdest. "F" tho is indeed wtf worthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 00:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its just no matter what theme I set those couple things stay green.

Edit: looks like it is only the black theme with the green everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 23:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit...I wouldnt have updated if I knew it would be like this. . .it feels so wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just updated to HTC Sense 6.0 on my M7 and have a couple issues. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 23:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything is green. Like the letters on the keyboard when I type, the loading bar in the internet browser, and who knows what else. I tried changing the theme to all black option, but that only fixed the HTC news reading list.

Is there some way to change it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 20:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I give up. I cant find a mutant with the name: O______ R___ . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 12:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So do you get a family discount on the nights she works? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Camdoja - Empire Made of Fire (Official Video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 20:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 20:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll only have enough PTO by then for one weekend (〒︿〒) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 20:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of the Outkast experience is also the dungeon family being apart of it, IMO.C-Bone was there so I got a little more than one third if anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 20:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would think, but I'm so conflicted. I've already met and seen Big Boi in concert, so that's one half the Outkast experience. And then there is rumors this is Li's last album round. Considering I'm from Texas it's an additional 3 hours to ATL than Kansas City. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need a new album to go with my MGMT, Lykke Li, and Lorde playlist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 19:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for an album that is solid all the way through that would compliment the discography of those three. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
