<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4879</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long does it take for exams to be marked? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 05:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering when I will get my exam marks back, i wrote them yesterday, and this morning. they are humanities exams. one of them was for a seminar, if that's of any relevance. thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the difference between cooking something at 200 degrees for 40 minutes or 400 degrees for 20 minutes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 00:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Phone restarts whenever i try to view photos i have taken </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-30 02:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whenever i open the camera app, and navigate to my photos, my phone screen goes black for a few seconds, and i hear a click, and it restarts. everything else works fine, only a few months old. running 4.4, not rooted, hoping someone knows the source of this bug, and whether or not its just kitkat being glitchy, or something is wrong with my phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-24 22:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reminds me of the clover field monster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 04:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awesome, thanks for all the info!

i hate to bother you with more questions, but i was wondering if you knew any ontario companies as well? 

I'm trying to apply to as many companies as possible, I'm really hoping to plant this summer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 03:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im a student, but I'd like to treeplant at least for the next 4 summers, potentially even after I graduate. are there any companies you can recommend applying to, as a first year planter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 04:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whats the advantage of planting in the west? and is it possible for first year planters to get jobs out there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 05:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sweet, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
