<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4065</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 23:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The house that bad storytelling built.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 23:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nicholson's Wolf, he gets turned in Vermont. 

I Am Legend the last human city is in Vermont. 

The Shining, Nicholson had worked in Vermont (I might have the detail wrong on this one). 

Those are some less obvious ones. Of course there's the Bob Newhart show and Me Myself and Irene.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 23:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh. I do SEO and reputation management for a living, and have been watching this for a while now. I advice clients on how to handle these things, and it was a good move. Of course my advice also includes to be more humble, transparent, and honest in communication. I wonder if he got that message too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 00:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks really fricken cool. Anybody know anything about Kupa? I've never heard if them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 01:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a post to r/tablets about one by Kupa that fits your description. Great stats including 8gb of RAM, removable battery, and modules to add other items. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 02:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wishing the best for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 02:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cluster headaches. 

Fuck that shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 01:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 15:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to hear about your struggles. Sounds like you have a lot on your mind currently. Make sure you are doing something good for yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 15:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My marriage is falling apart. 

But really looking forward to the next Star Trek! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 15:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not in front of my computer, so this is from my failing memory. You have to click browse (or something like that) where it allows you to search for either games in progress or lobbies. At that point there's an option to open a new lobby. 

Hope that helps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 12:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When in the lobby as the leader, edit settings and change server to local.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 04:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worst dialogue ever, that's why.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 03:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Minor detail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 00:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you post link when done? I'm at ikea now so can't watch yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 19:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't argue with that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 12:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's kinda like saying you worship Christ, but Satan is your second god.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 12:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I do too! It'll be nice to see all the Patriots fans squirming in their seats at work. They always seem to feel their the only team that deserves to win. I'm sure they will be blaming the refs. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 03:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We saw butt fumble, now we have the ref tackle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 03:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My understanding is heat death is like the Big Crunch (opposite of Big Bang) and cold death is when energy speeds to far for significant heat, thus freezing everything. 

Mr Nye? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 02:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom, is that you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 01:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that the leading theory is that the universe will either end with cold death, or it will continue as-is, and heat death has been eliminated as a possibility.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 00:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck the Patriots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 13:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just change one letter, be project herpes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-18 16:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use Firefox, search for a YouTube downloader in the add-on section.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-18 01:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in New England. I started watching football when Marino was the man and took the team to the Super Bowl. Watching him was a lot of fun, and became a fan. I was about 9 years old.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-17 16:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super good movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-17 14:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't hurt me.  Have I finally found my super power? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 16:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I third this. We should shoot for quality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 02:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the empty seats look nicer on TV.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-14 00:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you did there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 14:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's never had a top defense. He's over rated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 18:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll check out superuser, thanks. ID rather not go through all the re-encoding hassle for this many films though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 18:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'll check the codecs. I have a feeling those are fine as it starts to play often then just stops, but I'll see. Good to know yours works. What do you use to rip blu-rays? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tablet for large movie files </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 12:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the first Asus Transformer, but it won't play, or crashes, when I try to play some of the larger movie files I have (1.5 - 4gb, generally .mp4), which are obviously often HD.

What tablet specs should I look for in determining if it can play these files? Any specific recommendations?

Thanks Reddit!
Endif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-10 17:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you forgetting about the Fourth Kind? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 03:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I consider it horror, and definitely my favorite. 

Also like The Ring, and Blair Witch Project.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 03:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad. I think the series could be a lot of fun with a better director.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-08 03:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to be an Ireland defender, but let me give it a shot.

McCown was 2008, which Parcells was in charge of. Feel free to disagree, but if we are going to evaluate Ireland I feel like the last 2 years are the ones to look at.

When I look at last year's draft, I think it may end up being one of the best that any team had in 2012, especially considering rookie free agents.

Here's why. Our picks:
1st Round  Ryan Tannehill (QB, Texas A M)
2nd Round  Jonathan Martin (OT, Stanford)
3rd Round  Olivier Vernon (DE, Miami)
3rd Round  Michael Egnew (TE, Missouri)
4th Round  Lamar Miller (RB, Miami)
5th Round  Josh Kaddu (OLB, Oregon)
6th Round  B.J. Cunningham (WR, Michigan State)
7th Round  Kheeston Randall (DL, Texas)
7th Round  Rishard Matthews (WR, Nevada)

So we had 4 draft picks as solid contributors this year (Tannehill, Martin, Vernon, Miller). That looks pretty good!

Add Lane and Thigpen and that's 6 solid rookie players in one off-season.

I think you will be hard pressed to find many teams that got 6 starters from the draft. If I compare this draft to an Ozzie Newsome one, who I think is great, the Ravens best draft may have been 2008 where they got Joe Flacco, Ray Rice, and Tom Zbikowski (now with the Colts). That's 3 players out of 10 picks. I don't know who their rookie free agents were, but we know those are rare anyway. The rest of the Ravens picks aren't even on their team anymore, just Flacco and Rice. Two important pieces and that's a successful draft.

I guess what I'm saying is that I think Ireland has become the fall guy, and people have really high expectations in a draft (most guys don't work out, just a fact). I wanted Ireland fired after 2011, but the more I thought about it, the more I feel he really does deserve to continue. Parcells is the guy we should be mad at, he didn't pick a good coach or QB, so we were doomed. Now Ireland is in charge, and so far so good. Let's just hope it continues.

Anyway, agree to disagree I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-08 00:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, decaf!

You just said he sucked the whole time, so what do you expect in return? A second rounder for a guy you readily admit sucked (your word) sounds like we got the better end of the deal.  I'll take that deal every day. 

And I haven't down voted any of your posts or comments (that i am aware of) and am willing to make that public to prove it. 

Deep breath now!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 07:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blocked in US.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 04:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still happy with the trade. A 2nd rounder is good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-06 20:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's a girl. Even if a reason were given it would be impossible to truly understand. And in typical female fashion, she kills you for not understanding. 

You must not be married for asking such a question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-06 03:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure that's Fred Savage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 03:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Think players, not plays.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-01 05:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Food court seman surprise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-01 04:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Virgin Mary. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 14:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serenity now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 12:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck the Jets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 01:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. The drafts Parcells lead sucked, Ireland hasn't done poorly, deserves to continue. Change there now would be bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 00:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn you Binns! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 00:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cause fuck you fist pumper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jets to fire Sparano </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 00:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 00:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still watching. Hate not watching.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-30 23:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck the scheduler! Fuck his wife! Fuck his daughter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-30 22:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boobs are never wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-30 22:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like tannehill's wearing a goddamn parka.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-30 19:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While we're at it let's fuck his wife too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 18:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed that this one is better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 17:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree. Look at the stands of the away games and you'll see teal 13s throughout. 

We are here. 
We are hungry. 
We are not all in Miami. 
We are not all willing to spend hundreds to see a game until you prove we will consistently have a shot at winning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 04:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's going to be a tough year. We better be ready.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-27 18:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever...

GIRLY MAN! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-27 02:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought he did well for his first game, but not like I concentrated on him. 

Smith, Marshall, and him...then add a rook and our secondary may be decent. 

Honestly, with even a slightly better secondary we may have made the playoffs this year, they were burned repeatedly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-24 02:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's the tail that makes it look like a whale. It isn't terrible, but needs some tweaking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-22 01:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A moment of revelation. An exciting discovery. The urge to share.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the last person to notice the Star Trek Into Darkness poster is in the shape of the Star Fleet badge? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-22 00:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-21 22:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 04:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a sequel too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asylum (2008) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 18:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grace (2009) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 18:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 03:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well that was easy. got it set up in just a couple minutes. thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 03:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like it does support dynamic dns, but only from one provider and there is an associated cost.

Do you know of a free script? The IP sometimes changes during the day, so one that would email every time that happens would be awesome.

Thanks,
Endif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get my home laptop IP from work. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 02:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit techsupport,

Here's the challenge I've got. I occasionally connect to my home laptop from my iphone using VNC when I'm at work, so obviously I need to know my home laptop's IP address. 

Unfortunately, my crappy backwoods DSL connection occasionally restarts, and then I get a new IP.

Is there any way to set something up so I always know my home laptop's IP, even when not there?

Appreciate any assistance.
Endif

home laptop:
Sager; Windows 7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Changeling (1980) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-13 03:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 03:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I Am Legend HD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-06 18:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe that I bought a 5gb hard drive in 1998 for $500. I'm so stupid, if I just waited I could have gotten a 500gb for $60. 

Buying computer parts has ruined my life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-27 03:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just ripped a couple films. Worked well, and easy. Quality is acceptable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-27 03:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My condolences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-23 17:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old thread but thought I'd comment. 

As someone with a lot of hours, it's a very strategic game that can be ruined by inexperienced players. I'm not a fan of kicking, however, if you don't communicate and try to follow instructions you probably will be kicked. But it does depend on who you are playing with. Tell people you are new and listening, they should give you a chance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
