<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3014</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 01:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, this is it! Thank you so much! I've been searching for this forever! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 00:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, not those either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 03:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm... That's not it, and I don't think either of those bands would play it. Thanks though! Found some nice new music! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] [Song] Modern(ish) Jazzy song? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 00:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only heard the song I'm looking for twice. Both times it was played on a radio station that plays bands like: AC/DC, Led Zeppelin, The Beatles, The Allman Brothers, Lynyrd Skynyrd and other bands, mostly from the 70's and 80's. I think it has piano, drums, bass, vocals and flute for most of it. Just one man is singing. I can't remember any of the lyrics to it. Please let me know if there is anything else that would help!


Edit: It's not a rock song at all. It sounds like it should be on an easy listening station or something like that

Edit 2: I took a look at some more Jethro Tull songs and the one I'm looking for sounds a lot like Jethro Tull's [Serenade To A Cuckoo cover](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Zh4GZJlQCfY) except with a singer and more upbeat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 21:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you come up with the name "B Story"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 21:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Julian! When did you start making videos on a professional level? Are there older videos that no one has ever seen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 21:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you just didn't know. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 21:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! What is your favorite band? I'm curious to know where you get your musical influence from (if any). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 21:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello Julian! How long was the filming for the Back Then music video? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 21:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly she has passed away. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 21:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Julian. I just wanted to say that when I  watched the Back Then music video, you blew me away with it. I think you have really reached a new level in your filmmaking. I hope you get to where you want to go soon, be it Hollywood, or just the rest of the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 21:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mac or PC? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 21:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Beatles. Yes or no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-19 03:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-13 04:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate when there is an amazing AmA and get there after it's over.(?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I turned 16 seven minutes ago! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-13 04:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today: I Went to the library, got two boxes of candy as a present and had ratatouille for dinner.

BEST BIRTHDAY EVER!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 22:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it were possible, would you ever want to cook in space for the astronauts on the ISS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 22:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has been bugging me for ages...
What is nougat made of!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 22:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think onions should be genetically altered to make people laugh instead of cry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 21:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you could only eat one thing for the rest of your life what would it be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 21:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for doing an AMA Alton! 
My question is: What's your take on locavores ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 20:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello Alton! I am wondering when you knew that cooking was your definite career choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
