<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9737</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 21:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take a break. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 21:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BURN.
Just because she did a little bit of psychology studies (emphasis on the little) doesn't mean she has the right to use it against you during every freaking argument. The stuff learned in high school psychology skims the mere surface of theories, anywho...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 21:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bitch, fart, and pussy are not particularly good words to use around women. Especially girlfriends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 20:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -slow clap- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 00:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New Jersey, USA style: No. We do no tan, drink, and do laundry for shits and giggles. Sorry guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 04:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am currently enrolled in Holocaust studies at my college and if it has taught me one thing, it is that there will always be people who have either never heard of the Holocaust or simply refuse to believe it. Sometimes, governments are to blame or simply a person's family. There is also the location to consider, as well as the ages of those surveyed. Rural people will not "hear" as much as urban; younger do not know as much as the old.. blah blah. Still, this was an interesting read :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 19:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elizabeth: dah fahk is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 19:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is incredible. I hope you have an equally successful year AGAIN :-). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 06:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suggest combing through your history (inside jokes, places you have gone/thing seen) and maybe using this material to customize your gift for her. Maybe search for a customized gift online relating to this stuff, like a bracelet with something cutesy she likes to hear from you every now and then.. small stuff goes a long way in relationships.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 05:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cold hot-water bottles.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 01:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~the princess~~ ~~A NEW CASTLE~~ home insurance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
