<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4918</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 20:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was expecting a bag of roasted chile to bring some fragrance on the plane.  I am disappointed in my hopes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 19:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell yeah!  What kind of parties have a smoker as a prize?  I mean, that's pretty awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 19:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trained as well.  I've never been taught that in any of the fine dining or scholastic settings I've been in.


It's not about getting burnt.  It's about spilling a pudding that is not completely set.  Or dropping the dish.  I personally would fire someone who did that after being asked not to.  Simply because I sell all of mine and only make 8 a day.  Or in the shop that did 300 covers nightly, I would make 20 and sell every one.  If I dropped one, I would have been in a world of shit.  It will get 86'd every night, but not by an employee's fuck up.


I know why someone would say to pick up and roll the dish.  It moves the sugar.  However, if you use the proper technique in dusting, you will never have to move the sugar yourself after you sprinkle it.  It it needs to be moved, you use the forced air of your torch.


Part of what defines a creme brulee is "burnt."  Nothing wrong with a little black.  Those are words that have been spoken by people who are much better cooks than me.  I'll stick to my roots.  There is a fine line when it comes to excellent and ruined.  Don't be afraid that what you think is good isn't up to others standards.  Others standards are just theirs.  If you are making it for yourself, make it how you like it.  That is the beauty of food - you can control it completely if you do it yourself.


As far as getting the sugar right, there is no other way of doing it rather than practice.  However, doing the whole process is a pain in the ass and not cost effective.  So do it over gelatin water.  Bloom gelatin and let it set up in your ramekins.  It will take 5 minutes of inactive prep and cost a few pennies per dish.


Now your torch.  You need to know your torch.  The reason people get burnt sugar compared to caramelized is because they use too much sugar and they try to melt it to quickly by placing the flame to close to it and burn the top layer.  To get around that, place your ramekin on the table.  With a 3 finger pinch, lightly sprinkle sugar over the top in a fine, 1 or 2 grain layer.  Shake the dish a little to move the excess around which isn't stuck to the surface, then tip on its side to tap off all the excess sugar.  Removing the excess is the most important part.  Note that your layer of sugar will not be 100% at this point.


Now lightly melt the sugar with your torch.  While the sugar is still hot, repeat the dusting process again and let sit one minute until cool.  Lightly melt again and repeat dusting.  This third and final dusting is where you're going to want to get the caramel.  Now this is where the practice of the torch comes in handy.  And I can't tell you how to do it without actually using your torch.  You just have to play with it.  But it's really fucking simple.  And even easier to fuck up.  Done right though, it's magic.


Alright.  Now it's time to make a Cubano.  Also.  I didn't ask, someone else did ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 17:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold up here.  Never hold it in your hand. I'll BRB, but while what the posted above said will work, you run risk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 17:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A smoker to subscribe to?  Or a sub?   If you mean sub, i'd say r/BBQ and R/smoking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 02:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well.  Don't be a dick.  If you don't act like a dick and say dick things, you won't get treated like a dick.  Nor will you get told to go fuck yourself.  I tried investing in a slicer by offering you to purchase one for me.  And then you insult me.  You sir, are a dick and can go fuck yourself if that is how you are going to behave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 02:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, considering that I care fuck all about plating, I'm almost concerned with it.  And considering that you can not either create or contribute content, only critique it, I almost care what your input is.  

But here is what it comes down to.  I make better product than you can probably afford to purchase.  So why don't you either A) go fuck yourself or B) go fuck yourself.  I suggest you take option number two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 01:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My good knives were at the shop and the little home slicer I own is BS.  How about you invest in me and ship me a 12" deli slicer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 23:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's what I was just reading on Wiki.  Staple Toronto sandwich eh?  I might just have to fly out there and have one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 22:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OH!  What is this peameal bacon you speak of?  That is a new term to me, so now I'm going to have to learn how to properly make it.  May the gods continue to bless the internets so that we learn of new forms of bacon daily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 20:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want them to succeed, you will have to help them if this is their game plan.  And more than likely, they will need a lot more help from the community than that if it is going to succeed.  Like a landlord that is willing to front up space for 6 months to get ducks in a row.

But in all honesty, good luck.  This is a recipe for failure and would probably ruin their marriage if this is a plan to stick with.  If this is really last ditch, I would suggest they need to dig a different hole to get out of.  Sorry.  But by the sounds of it, this plan will do more harm than good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 20:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I have been told, that would be back bacon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 19:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya know, I don't know the history of the different cuts so much, outside of Italian.  Now I'm intrigued.  I've read a lot and have a decent library, but I guess I need to hit the books just as much as I hit the salt.

To me, while I know that pancetta is technically an older style of bacon than American, I still wouldn't call it bacon.  It's pancetta for fucks sake, not bacon.  It's all in the nuances of language.  That is why when people ask me stuff is anymore I just tell them to shut up and shove it in their mouth :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 19:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And all my friends keep asking me why I don't start a catering company... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 18:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pineapple slaw.  I think this might be the winner idea out of all.  How did you make yours?  

It needs to be charred, no question about that IMO.  Cabbage doesn't seem right.  Mangos or apples would make it to fruity.  Cilantro and pea shoots?  Hrm...  I live in the desert and don't work with pineapple much.  I love it, but it's usually a second thought and in this instance, it would be awesome to have it as a primary ingredient.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 18:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They love me in there.  However, I have been asked to not post ingredient questions, only full on sandwiches.  Here is a gallery of snacks if you'd like to make yourself hungry...

http://imgur.com/a/BYZRe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 18:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/CXR1Bl1.jpg

60 hours in the brine, 6 hours in cold smoke, 3 hours roasted at 200.  I need to make some pizza dough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian "bacon" [xpost] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 18:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 18:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/CXR1Bl1.jpg

60 hours in brine, 6 hour cold smoke, and roasted at 200 for three hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 17:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monday nights at Big Adventure Comics is "The Game Thing."  On open to the community board gaming night.  There are hundereds of games in the collection and dozens of people show up every week.  I think biggest turn out has been around 50 people!  There are people that show up who play chess.

Also.  Talk to folks at Stagg Tobacconist.  They are in the moving process to their new location on Cerrillos, but they are the only place I know of in the area that sells Chess clocks and high end boards.  They would probably know of others in the area too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 09:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do love to share with my neighbors.  In fact, the only reason I cook is to feed other folks.  If you're ever in NM or planning a trip out here, hit me up.  I'll gladly make you a sandwich.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 05:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am planning on it and will do.  This chunk of bacon is week 7 of my "make a different kind of bacon every week for a year" challenge.  So you can expect to see many more pics of tasty from me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 05:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Horseradish.  I've been thinking wasabi or some such nonsense, but I know where I can get farm fresh horseradish right now.  Good call.  And the red onion would pair nice with a lime dressing and pickled ginger.  Yeah...  I can see something delicious coming together... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 04:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 02:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking either a lemongrass or sesame slaw of sorts.  Maybe some charred bok choy?  A straight up Bhan Mi would be good, but I make those already.  Anyone have any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to make a sandwich out of this Chinese BBQ pork. What should go on it and what kind of bread? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 02:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 21:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/ANsz2tQ.jpg

http://i.imgur.com/s2VQu9N.jpg

Salt, garlic, black pepper, Hatch Green Chile, pink salt.  48 hours in the cure and into the smoker it goes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today's adventure in bacon - Hatch Green Chile Rub </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 21:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> smoked, rubbed, and ready for the oven </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 09:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I like making bacon. I didn't know the sub existed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 00:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The crunch of the sugar is the most satisfying part... [oc][1024x768] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 22:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baked penne puttanesca with house mozzarella </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 21:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> pork cutlet, kraut, dill chips, stone ground,and swiss on an onion roll. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 05:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Per request - no tomato, add egg. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 07:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maduros, fried with a little salt. So easy, so good... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 08:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pork Milanese, panchetta salad, onion jam, and pesto on an onion roll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 02:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't make just one sandwich anymore... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 02:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> a little chop chop on the bacon before the pan... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 17:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The sandwich in question... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 22:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another day, another bacon sandwich... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 22:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> one of the best I've made in a while [xpost] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 00:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House bacon, garden fresh bruschetta with Hatch Green Chile, ciabatta toasted in shallot oil, parm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 00:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I would like to help you make bacon. If interested, inquire within... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 20:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just more bacon. Something so easy to do and I hope that I can get a few of you to give it a go. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 19:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> plate? who needs a plate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 18:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> another round of bacon... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 18:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GCGC with farm fresh tomato and basil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 18:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was only planning on smoking some bacon today... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 00:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What a proper blend of cheese can yield... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 23:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wish you could try my Hatch Green Chile Grilled Cheese (the GCGC) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 23:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fruit pops... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 00:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wish you could eat my sandwich. And my fries. GCGC with tomato and triple cooked chips. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 00:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lobster mushrooms all cleaned up and pretty. Any suggestions on what to make? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 17:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even YOU can make bacon! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 17:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grilled cheese with Hatch Green Chile and tomato, maduros, sweet potato fries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 17:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> one must select the proper blend of cheese... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 17:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> xpost, some of you might have missed it. Good read about food economics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 16:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> yesterday's tacos... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 03:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hatch Green Chile and extra cheese </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 03:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> a grilled cheese of sorts... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 03:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> pulled pork, slaw, and pickle on ghetto buns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 23:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> still processing. back for more tomorrow! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 20:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chimayo Red Chile pulled pork with Hatch Green Chile Slaw </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 04:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wish I had an outlet for all of the stuff I find. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 05:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate cleaning lobsters, but it's so worth it... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 05:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tomorrow is a year of no nicotine for me. Here's to hoping I don't fuck it up... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 15:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone interested in trading dried mushrooms? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 15:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> it was a nice walk. 9000' high aspen bolete... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 23:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> looking for a solid, vegan burger patty recipe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 20:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title says it all.  I'm an accomplished cook and yet for the life of me I can't come up with a good bean patty burger recipe.  Or find one online.  The only stuff I can find that turns out the way that we like is a falafel type pattie.  Not that that is bad, but I want something to grill that won't fall apart and not be falafel.  Any help would be greatly appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> it's that time of year again... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 18:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bring on the monsoons, it's mushroom time! Picked in SF forest, 7/30. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 08:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IT'S PORCINI TIME! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 08:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> making bacon is easy! (round two) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 07:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hatch Green Chile and smoked cheddar double slider. With house bacon, pickle, and mustard on a garlic butter basted sourdough roll. [OC][1024x768] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 06:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> red </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 17:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> house bacon, grilled pineapple, bork burger, swiss, BBQ, Hatch green chile and cheddar roll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 16:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> muffaletta burger on ghetto white bread, provolone, house pickle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 00:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> a gallery of tacos you wish you ate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 01:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> a whole host of sandwiches I've made and eaten... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 19:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> another burger with fries... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 06:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Antonio Creek, Valles Caldera NM [OC][1024x768] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 20:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> bacon, mushroom, and swiss burger on green chile cheddar roll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 19:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where it all starts. Gotta love a good stock! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 19:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> how many tacos can we make? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 19:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> spring rolls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 20:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> making bacon is easy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 17:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> kalamata and art hearts off a cast iron comal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 18:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> more random, delicious tacos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 18:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> not the prettiest, but snacks were had! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 22:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> multi cheese sourdough, with pickle and mustard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 18:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> even vegans need sammichs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 18:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> wish i made two </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 20:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> more blt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 22:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> two halves of a burger... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 04:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> i might be onto something... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 18:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> snack time! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 19:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BLT, one of the better I've made... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 22:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> a burger and fries... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 23:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> sandwich! details in comments... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 21:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ribs, chicken, and bacon! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 23:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> house brat, granny smith, brie, quick kraut, grain mustard, sourdough </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 17:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> red chili chicken burrito [OC][1024x768] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 22:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> pig three ways </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 15:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> cured meats and brioche </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 18:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> yesterday's tacos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 19:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> swiss, parm, and provolone tuna melt with Anasazi bean and chard soup. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 02:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> some chocolates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 18:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> grilled turkey on sourdough, risotto croquette, b-nut squash soup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 18:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> eat your vegetables! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 16:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> taco plate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 18:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> tacos pastor [OC] [1024x768] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 16:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> flan - details in comments [OC] [1024x768] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 19:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> slow cooked caraway brawt, 30 day dill chips, overnight kraut, stone german mustard, muenster, sourdough hoagie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 23:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> game night snacks - blood orange creme brulee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 18:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> p-nut butter   chocolate chip cookie sandwich with double chocolate chunk ice cream cream. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 15:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> onion bagel, brined and breaded porkloin, 5 day bacon, heirloom, shallot, mixed greens, french stone ground mustard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-08 19:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hot and sour orange chicken, cukecumber, cabbage, basil [OC][1024x768] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 20:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> chocolate chip vanilla cream birthday treats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 20:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> grilled burgers on rye </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 16:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> snacks! egg, heirloom, house bacon, overnight muffin, swiss, hot honey mustard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 20:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> mushroom/swiss/caramel onion burger with house made bacon, brioche, and roasted garlic aioli. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 08:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> pork milanese </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 17:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
