<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1576</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 02:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have found our new Michelle Bachmann. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 00:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's get back in the saddle and pedal forward.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 00:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you, /u/elzmuda -- there are always excuses to drink, but if you make the decision first thing in the morning not to drink TODAY no matter what happens good or bad, if you doggedly persist in the commitment, then alcohol is not an option.  I like to say that after I decide that I am not going to drink TODAY--alcohol is out of my movie for the day, all day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 00:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lady Lindsey is the last closeted gay male in politics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> State Rep Suggests Abortion Is To Blame For California Drought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 23:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 23:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, it was a widely-held belief that the alcoholic was immoral--if only he would take "the pledge" or "get religion."  The failure to make the choice not to drink was seen as sin.  It really wasn't until the late 19th century (Rush, Trotter 1760-1832) that a practical "disease model" and treatment emerged (Keely) although it was not widely known or accepted.  The modern recovery  movement begins as a radical reaction to the WCTU and the moral choice models--fully accepting the disease model of alcoholism.  Frankly, the anti-AA ideologues are actually preaching a moral choice model--without the moral-ism.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Kasich Strives for Self-Control </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 23:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 22:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many times, these sorts of local heroes become honored judges and courthouses are named after them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christie is least conservative 2016 Republican hopeful, analysis says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 22:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As his bachelorhood goes viral, SCs Graham shares details of his personal life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 22:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker: 'I Ran Against a Woman' and Won </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 22:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker and the Fate of the Union </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, I've been there in my own special and painful way.  Most of us get where you're coming from and we want to provide support along the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I remember that neuro-feedback loop when I was drinking.  When I went back to "moderate drinking" after 15 continuous years of sobriety I thought of course that I could sip fine wines.  I'd buy these $100+ bottles of aged port and I'd have the appropriate crystal glasses.  Of course, being an alcoholic, I'd hide all of my apparatus in crawl spaces and wait till everyone else in the house was asleep and pull out my port and sip my wine--inevitable waking up at 5 AM laying on the floor with empty bottles of port that I must have swilled down.  Did I need any more proof of my powerlessness?  And yet, I went on and on for 7 long hellish years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fine chocolates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Capitol gridlock taking toll on Gov. Brownback, House GOP members say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like EVERYTIME. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a discussion sometime last year, I told my pal, /u/offtherocks, about the great 19th Century English novelist Anthony Trollope who in 1858 published [Doctor Thorne](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Doctor_Thorne) which deals with the multiple episodes in the lives of recurring characters in something called the Barchester Chronicles.  If you are at all interested in literature, I can't recommend them highly enough.  In *Doctor Thorne* the title character treats the alcoholism of his friend Sir Roger Scatcherd who eventually dies from the disease.  

 But be this as it may, be it true or false that Sir Roger was most efficacious when in his cups, there can be no doubt that he could not wallow for a week in brandy, six or seven times every year, without in a great measure injuring, and permanently injuring, the outward man. Whatever immediate effect such symposiums might have on the inner mindsymposiums indeed they were not; posiums I will call them, if I may be allowed; for in latter life, when he drank heavily, he drank alonehowever little for evil, or however much for good the working of his brain might be affected, his body suffered greatly. It was not that he became feeble or emaciated, old-looking or inactive, that his hand shook, or that his eye was watery; but that in the moments of his intemperance his life was often not worth a day's purchase. The frame which God had given to him was powerful beyond the power of ordinary men; powerful to act in spite of these violent perturbations; powerful to repress and conquer the qualms and headaches and inward sicknesses to which the votaries of Bacchus are ordinarily subject; but this power was not without its limit. If encroached on too far, it would break and fall and come asunder, and then the strong man would at once become a corpse.  p.124

And here, Scatcherd on his death bed describing his fears relating to the effect of the disease upon his heir, Louis:

 "With my poor boy; with Louis."

 "If he [Louis] will let me, I will [look after him,]" said the doctor.

 "And, doctor, when you see a glass at his mouth, dash it down; thrust it down, though you thrust out the teeth with it. When you see that, Thorne, tell him of his fathertell him what his father might have been but for that; tell him how his father died like a beast, because he could not keep himself from drink."

 These, reader, were the last words spoken by Sir Roger Scatcherd. As he uttered them he rose up in bed with the same vehemence which he had shown on the former evening. But in the very act of doing so he was again struck by paralysis, and before nine on the following morning all was over.

In the characters and story of Doctor Thorne and Sir Roger Scatcherd I was struck at how sophisticated Trollope's 1858 understanding of the psychology of the alcoholism and the sufferer's powerlessness over the malady.  Also the powerlessness of that caring physician to help his friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-prosecutor is disbarred for his role in capital murder conviction of innocent man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 20:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prosecutor disbarred over role in case of innocent man wrongly convicted in capital murder case. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 20:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rich Republican Donors Get VIP Retreat Treatment | They can even do Sunrise Pilates with Bloomberg reporter Mark Halperin and the former first lady aspirant Ann Romney. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 18:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge Angela Stokes' defense against charges of misconduct has cost Cleveland taxpayers more than $650,000 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2 state officials promoted after hot-tub party trouble </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker Pushes Obamatrade On Eve Of Vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 14:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chis Christie and guns continue to be a lethal rhetorical combination, the kind of noise you should avoid by ducking under a table the moment he begins to flaunt his heat-packin' bonafides. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 14:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Catholic bishops discuss how to best follow pope's lead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 14:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former deputy Attorney General disbarred in Pa and Del. after Rape conviction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Missing' $20 Million at Issue in Lawyers' Divorce </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cambridge University seeking Professor of Lego in new job </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fifa's Jack Warner delivers YouTube response to Last Week Tonight's John Oliver </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama isn't bullying the Supreme Court on healthcare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comcast Accused in Fraud Lawsuit of Scheme to Acquire Discounted Sports Rights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wrongful rape conviction, 17-year prison term 'makes my stomach turn,' advocate says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mom, 92, adopts daughter, 76, in Dallas courtroom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Like Jurassic Park, Jeff Flakes anti-pork gimmicks are also making a comeback </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sisterhood Is Sour: How Republican Women Are Taking on Hillary Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 13:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Michigan law lets adoption agencies decline referrals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 02:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Court Denies Requests to Keep New Net Neutrality Rules From Taking Effect on Friday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 02:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rick Santorum Says Economic 'Stagnation' Will Help Him Win in 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 02:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker Says Supporters Have Suggested Walker-Rubio 2016 Ticket </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 02:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio-built appliances are among the best made in America, Consumer Reports says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 21:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cavs' Dellavedova out of hospital, ready for Game 4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Closing arguments filed in DUI setup case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Karl Rove: GOP Energized by Wide Primary Field, Upbeat Campaigning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bush Says His Views 'Haven't Changed at All' on Unwed Mothers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon wins pricing patent litigation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elizabeth Warren Launches Last-Minute Blitz to Stop Trade Bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tale of Sex, Drugs And a Rookie Lawmaker Grips Israel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton won't back down. Or go away. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 19:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News: Roger Ailes to Continue to Report to Rupert Murdoch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jury finds man guilty of sexually abusing unconscious woman at strip club </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prosecutor: Marijuana legalization would create 35,000 jobs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lakewood helps drivers pinpoint, avoid road construction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cleveland paid legal bills for a former homicide detective to file for bankruptcy to duck a $13.2 million judgment to a man who served 12 years for a murder he didn't commit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SC high court upholds USC/Alabama game death conviction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Big Law bookkeeper testifies he falsified failed-Law Firms accounting records </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Judge Accused Of Firing His Gun Inside West LA Home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fourth Circuit airs internal dispute about whether to criticize the Governments appellate litigating position </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fiorina's campaign-trail attacks leave out her own ties to Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christie Touts Success in Winning Over Latino Voters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Not to Become Brian Williams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 15:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> G.M. Chief Flatly Dismisses a Merger Overture From Fiat Chrysler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 15:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge plans to go into 'uncharted legal territory' to stop Macy's from collecting shoplifting fines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 15:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge to Macy's: Stop collecting shoplifting fines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 15:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Lawyer Who Invented a Way to Take Cash From Accident Victims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 15:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Supreme Court Down the Stretch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 15:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tech's role in bullying has been greatly exaggerated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 13:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jamie Dimon Wants To Mansplain Banking To Elizabeth Warren </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 13:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vote likely locks in Soyuz flights to ISS until 2019 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 13:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Schuitmaker's pandering tax proposal hits bullseye for gun lobby </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 13:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas man, 72, and dog die trapped inside his Corvette dream car when door locks and windows fail to operate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 13:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> City need not return brain of Staten Island teen after autopsy: judge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 13:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brains dont have to be returned to bodies after autopsy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 13:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Motorcyclist catches fire after head-on crash near Beaverton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 13:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christie on pot: blowing more smoke </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 13:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Four-Pinocchio claim that on average, girls first become victims of sex trafficking at 13 years old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 13:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The GOP's Secret Plan To Fix Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 13:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What 10 Republican Presidential Hopefuls Say They'd Do First </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 13:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Jeb Bushs campaign ran off course before it even began </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 01:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mistrial declared in Lawyer Susan Van Note double murder case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 21:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats prepare for filibuster summer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 21:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Creates Tribunal for Bishop Negligence in Child Sexual Abuse Cases | Pope Francis creates a tribunal to subject Roman Catholic bishops to judgment and discipline by a new tribunal if they are accused of covering up or failing to prevent misconduct. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 21:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Appeals court chides judge for dismissing rape case, then testifying against victim's mother </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 20:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Del Taco manager pepper-sprayed in burrito dispute </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 20:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-Justice: Dont fine cities defying camera ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 19:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Tristan Und Isolde,' The Love Story That Changed Opera For Good </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 19:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Googles Larry Page named best CEO in employee survey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 19:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finding misconduct by Santa Clara County prosecutor (now a Judge), the 9th Circuit Court of Appeals overturns a murder conviction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 19:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are Gun Rights Second-Class Rights? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 19:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finding misconduct by Santa Clara County prosecutor, court overturns murder conviction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 17:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 2016 Presidential Race: A Conversation With Democratic Candidate And Vermont Senator Bernie Sanders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Voting Rights, Who's a Person? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 15:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analysis: In Voting Rights, Who's a Person? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 15:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The death of Voice Mail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 14:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nashville's Living History Museum Expands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 14:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'American Sniper' Widow Taya Kyle Backs Rick Perry for President In 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 14:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trinity Industries ordered to pay $663.4 mln in guardrail case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 14:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US military bans discrimination based on sexual orientation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prison Worker Planned to Drive Escapees -- NYMag </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawyer drops suit over 'stupid patent of the month' blog post featuring his patent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prison break lets Cuomo divert attention from capital corruption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Orphan Black' Production Company Must Face Copyright Lawsuit in California </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Latest Congressional Fundraising Draw: Taylor Swift </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bush says Putin has changed; calls for a tougher stance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama to Supreme Court: You wouldnt dare kill Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vincent Musetto, 74, Dies; Wrote Headless Headline of Ageless Fame </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Matthew Dellavedova Isnt First Aussie to Charm Cleveland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Burden Unites the Cleveland Stars Jim Brown and LeBron James </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Life on Life's Terms | Clearing away the wreckage of my past </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 02:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I got sober in 2009 after a 7 year relapse, as I saw it, I had the choice of killing myself and avoiding what was certain to be professional disgrace and a criminal prosecution over unfiled and unpaid federal income taxes or get sober and face the music.  In the years of my relapse the income from my professional practice was on a roller coaster.  Some years, I barely made any income and in at least one of those years I made a million dollars.  The unpaid and unfilled taxes were an abyss that I could not figure out how to address despite numerous false starts--of course, not being in recovery I had intentionally walked away from ready and willing help and support.  Finally I was at "fuck it, I'll just sit here and drink."  

Ultimately I suffered very serious professional and criminal consequences that included federal prison time. Some of the damages to my reputation and professional status (I lost my license) were permanent, but the criminal consequence has been long in my rear view mirror.  

When you own taxes in the US you might find that you owe reasonably $300,000 dollars and then through some black magic the IRS says your $300,000 indebtedness is now $600,000 and then time passes, even with payments and forfeitures, the IRS says you now owe $900,000 which is sort of where I find myself now.  In other words, my sole criminal offense resulting in a short prison sentence has become a life sentence as it relates to intractable debt and IRS collection activities including garnishments and seizures.  

When the collections nightmares first got underway the local agent that I dealt with suggested that I file something called an Offer In Compromise (OIC).  An OIC is a whole lot more than calling the IRS up and saying--here's a few thousand send me a release,  In 2012 I undertook the process and I was very close to accomplishing a deal when mysteriously (a common experience when dealing with the IRS) the rug was ripped out from underneath me. 

Leaving out lots and lots of the details, I determined to find out why.  I submitted a Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) request and I got my entire IRS file.  As a result I learned that the former criminal investigator in my underlying criminal case supplied misinformation which if I had had an opportunity to address I would have been able to supply documentation refuting allegations he made that disqualified me.  

Flash forward, to now, I just completed all the hoops, and I am greelighted to submit a new OIC (now complete) which my accountant believes stands a chance of success based on revised rules adopted by the IRS in 2014.  Also my employer is supplying funds to effect a deal if it can be done.

I write about this to let you know that I too struggle with life on life's terms and I don't drink TODAY no matter how frustrating, confusing, depressing, anxious painful or embarrassing those terms are.  I doggedly persist every day that I am SOBER which means, I still stand a chance.  Five years sober and I am still working on clearing away the wreckage of my past.  

tl;dr  CC has bad, bad tax problems; he doesn't drink; he overcomes obstacles; and, he hope that he may finally be able to clear away financial wreckage of the past.

Note: This was painful to write, but I promised to update a comment about my resolution and determination to deal with this issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Man Before The Guitar: Remembering Les Paul At 100 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did the New York Times Just Make Marco Rubio a Lot More Relatable? | An expos of the Florida Senator's finances shows that, yes, he certainly can understand the problems of ordinary Americans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Is What It Would Look Like If American Pharoah Raced Secretariat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 23:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Christie: My family wants me to run </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 21:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newspaper Celebrates MLBs First Underwater Pitcher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawyer argues Ohio shouldn't get second chance to execute teen's killer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rubio Campaign Goes After New York Times Article on His Personal Finances </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2nd Circuit: Man gets new trial in major tax-fraud case because suspended lawyer lied to get on jury </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 17:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Jersey Supreme Court hands Chris Christie a big victory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 17:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disbarred lawyer is still alive and politically active after prison release for terminal cancer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 17:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump and the Clown Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 15:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vincent Bugliosi dies at 80; prosecuted Charles Manson in the Sharon Tate murders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 15:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superintendent drops charges for cheering at graduation; ACLU sees First Amendment violation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 15:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interview: Joshua Cohen, Author Of 'Book Of Numbers' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 14:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LeBron James Has Nothing to Prove, but Hes Proving It Anyway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jon Stewart to Nicola Sturgeon: You think you're Saddam Hussein? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cleveland Leaders bypass McGinty to seek indictment in Tamir Rice case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hensarling Leads Bid to Kill Export-Import Bank </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snoop Dogg Sues Pabst Over Alcohol Endorsement Deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does freezing defendant's untainted assets violate right to counsel of choice? SCOTUS to decide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Spotify Should Be Very Afraid of Apple Music </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP Swiftly Rejects Obama's 'One-Sentence Fix' to Obamacare If Supreme Court Voids Subsidies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marco Rubio Says He Didn't Flip-Flop On Immigration But Hillary Clinton Did </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Republican Stronghold, Worries About End of Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Truth Teller </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 03:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Huckabee Movie Telemarketing Lawsuit Revived By Appeals Court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 01:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Court won't hear challenge to gun lockup law; dissent sees Second Amendment double standard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 21:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perjury charges filed against 4 police officers after dramatic 'Perry Mason'-type reveal at hearing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 20:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What That Campaign Logo Is Really Saying: A Design Critique </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 19:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fleeing shoplifting suspect in crash that killed a grandmother, hurt 2 others </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I drive a car with license plates that read DRUNK. Weird things happen as a result. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was Fort Lee mayor a long-term political target? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Kasich's Wall Street ties could haunt 2016 bid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lakewood police arrest four adults, five teens after rash of bike thefts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big changes to Workers' Compensation system now in motion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 15:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Billionaire Or Bust: Who Are Rich Backers Lining Up With? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 15:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Burn the courthouse down' close helps win acquittal; attorney Knizley has used it before </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 15:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas Gov. Sam Brownback has signed a bill that cuts off funding for the states courts if they overturn a 2014 law on the selection of chief district judges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 15:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas governor signs law cutting off court funding if courts strike down 2014 law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 15:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austin officer pepper-sprays man in Mounted Patrol incident </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 15:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abercrombies Legal Defeatand Its Cultural Failure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 13:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2015 Tony Awards: Cleveland Play House faithful gather to see hometown Tony win; Oberlin grad Alison Bechdel's 'Fun Home' makes history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 13:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christie says 2015 is 1979 again, and he'll be like Ronald Reagan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 13:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge's former intern releases video, says there was no romantic relationship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 13:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The political power of you </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 13:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On overseas tour, Jeb Bush hopes to prove himself on foreign policy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 13:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-Official Says Chris Christie Broke Grand Jury Law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 12:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Thrill of Political Hating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 12:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV Broadcasters Beat Class-Action Lawsuit Over College Athletics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 02:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abbott   Costello Heirs Sue Over Lifting of "Who's on First" Routine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 02:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LA lawyers withdraw lawsuit accusing hollywood director of sex abuse; pay 7 figure settlements; and, issue complete apologies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 02:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perry Fires Back at Clinton on Voter ID </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 17:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton Traces Friendly Path, Troubling Party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 13:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Iowa, pork, patriotism and presidential politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 01:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sometimes we have to wait 30 years to be discovered: Lee Hazelwood, Producer extraordinaire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 23:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bobby Jindal signs bill letting employers drug test hair, expanding detection window to 90 days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 23:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As he nears a 2016 bid, Louisianas Bobby Jindal hits political bottom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 23:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Campaign finance reformers think the United States would be better governed if the government could thoroughly regulate campaign speech, which is speech about the composition and comportment of the government. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 23:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker Riding With Joni Ernst in Iowa as Rivals Give Chase </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 20:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Secret History of SEAL Team 6: Quiet Killings and Blurred Lines | The unit best known for killing Osama bin Laden has been converted into a global manhunting machine with limited outside oversight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 20:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jury convicts female L.A. officer of assault in deadly arrest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 20:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christie: Congress should 'fix' Obamacare if U.S. Supreme Court ends subsidies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 14:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservatives Ask How They Lost the Culture War Over Transgender Rights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 14:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dem Rep. Luis Gutierrez: I Assume God Speaks Spanish Because He Named His Only Son Jesus | </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 13:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Undercover cop in biker-gang beating rattled on the stand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 13:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> West Shoreway speed limit drops to 35 mph in the fall as boulevard conversion begins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 13:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UPDATE 1-BP executive acquitted of lying about Gulf of Mexico oil spill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 03:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Scalia takes on commencement cliches in humor-filled speech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 03:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-war activist confronts Sen. Tom Cotton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prosecutor Charges Minnesota Archdiocese With Turning 'Blind Eye' To Abuse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 23:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge Murray Snow: The man judging Sheriff Joe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 23:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rick Perry Borrows Elizabeth Warren's Message, but Does It Fit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 21:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Middle East Is Falling Apart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 21:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cop suspected of driving drunk (BAC .24) in fatal wrong-way crash still on payroll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 20:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge jails lawyer who tried to duck jury duty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 20:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marco Rubio and His Wife Cited 17 Times for Traffic Infractions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 19:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tariq Aziz, top minister for Saddam Hussein and Iraqs longtime international spokesman, is dead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 18:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NJ lawyer gets federal sentence for mortgage scheme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 18:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Death-Row Inmate Challenges Second Execution Attempt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 17:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New here? The Baby Steps are a pretty good place to start stopping--now newly revised with a link to the daily check-in. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 17:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [Baby Steps](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) is a post that I published in several versions.  It's made up of information that helped me stop drinking and get sober + ideas suggested from among others, /u/offtherocks.  My pal, /u/Flow_Morpheous_Flow noticed a typo so with the need to make that slight revision I added a link to the daily check-in, too.  

So if you're **new here** I hope you will consider making the [Baby Steps](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) and [the Daily Check-in](http://www.reddit.com/r/stopdrinking/wiki/checkin) part of your Stop Drinking routine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guilty Until Proven Innocent | The Supreme Court let a vicious Arizona law die, and conservative justices are furious. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 14:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LegalZoom files $10.5M antitrust suit against North Carolina bar, cites SCOTUS dental case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 14:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
