<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2003</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a foreigner, how I feel about the US right now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 15:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Proof that nuclear weapons cause widespread generational mental retardation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 14:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I found the most photoshopped image ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 12:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How did mosquitoes manage to survive evolution if they are such useless pieces of shit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 16:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How come Reddit's servers always overloads, while Imgur's servers which are arguably serving much larger images/GIFs don't have that problem? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 07:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WSJ: Tim Cook approved Apple electric car project a year ago, hundreds of employees working on it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 17:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://9to5mac.com/2015/02/13/wsj-tim-cook-approved-apple-electric-car-project-a-year-ago-hundreds-of-employees-working-on-it/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's painful just imagining it... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 17:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oregon House of Representatives subtly Rick Roll the floor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 17:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Rick Astley has been utterly let down by Rickrolling, giving up all but $12 of the royalties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 17:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google celebrates Youtube's 10th anniversary by revealing plans for Google Fiber in 10 largest cities by end-2016. Includes NY, LA, Chicago, Philadelphia   Houston. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 16:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Efficiency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 06:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Efficiency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 06:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The founder of Nutella just died. Today is a sad day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 16:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, TIL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 15:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So who was camera? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 16:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think goes through Obama's mind everytime he goes "uhhhh"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 16:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple has been working on an electric car for a year, according to WSJ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 06:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/apple/comments/2vtghv/wsj_tim_cook_approved_apple_electric_car_project/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He must have previously had a bad experience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 00:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does eating spoiled food which has been cooked still make us sick? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why can't we cook the danger out of spoiled food? Wouldn't the heat kill all the bacteria which are responsible for making us sick? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baidu Maps looks like Simcity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opulence, I has it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look what I found at the thrift store! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coolest Macbook Sticker Ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I found the beached ship from Fallout 3 in real-life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Your mother was so fat..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atlantis Is Real </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This photo of the Red Sands Sea Forts belongs in a movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL there is a site which literally lists down all the written form of sounds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nigerian scammer expert u/Neverwish turns the tables on Nigerian scammers by scamming them into doing retarded things like balancing buckets on their heads, holding handwritten signs, etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He captured more than countries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> u/yerrbo gives a comprehensive step-by-step guide on how to successfully turn AirBnB into a full-time job </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who have been hit by two-wheeled vehicles before, how jealous are you of people who have been hit by four-wheeled vehicles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL there is a 2000m deep layer of salt lying beneath the ocean floor called the Pre-Salt Layer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Vat arrr you sinking about?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Vat arrr you sinking about?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin talking to a secret KGB agent in disguise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> His name is... PUTIN!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man goes Super Saiyan in wind tunnel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> u/intern11 shows how Mark Cuban's meteoric rise from rags to riches was nearly entirely based on luck instead of skill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You are Neil Armstrong just before taking your first step on the moon. With millions listening on the radio for your first words, you accidentally trip and exclaim, "S***!" How do you redeem yourself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ballpoint drawing of the Great Wall of China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Target Acquired (x/splitdepthgifs) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 15:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL an office worker sitting on his bum all day burns as many calories per day as our prehistoric hunter-gatherer ancestors who hunted for food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 15:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Target Acquired (x/SplitDepthGifs) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 15:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today, I beat the system! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 15:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The 'Door Close' button in most elevators is actually just a placebo button. It only functions if pressed continuously, and is only meant to be used this way by firefighters and rescue personnel during emergencies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 15:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL In 1945, a B-25 bomber pilot crashed into the Empire State Building's elevator shaft, snapping the cable. By the time the carriage reached the bottom, a thousand feet of cable had piled up beneath it acting like a spring, which allowed the lone occupant in the car to escape injured but alive. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 15:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> u/Shangoma finds a card autographed by Bobby Bowden selling for $109.95. He buys an identical card for $0.99, sends it to Bobby Bowden who then autographs it and sends it back to him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 15:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Punny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 15:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This picture was sold for 15,000 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 15:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stop being so funny, you guys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 15:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My colleague is the greatest guy since Abraham Lincoln </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 15:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you can't convince them, confuse them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 13:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taking bets for /u/fscomeau dethroning Games of Thrones style </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 03:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dark pool is selling European puts on /u/fscomeau's AAPL calls becoming worthless by expiry on a 1:10 ratio, strike at today's price of $16.50. Par is at $0.38, price was determined using the Black-Schmoles formula; you can trust me. Anyone who is interested, GET TO THE BACK OF THE LINE!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Loopholes That Could Undermine Net Neutrality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 10:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This picture is selling for  15,000 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 06:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many Chuck Norris jokes can you make about Benedict Cumberbatch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 06:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most epic combination of first, middle and last name that would not sound utterly out of the ordinary? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 04:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After reading the AMA with the chocolate expert </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 03:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] The government just announced that it will privatize NASA, and made you the CEO. How will you make it profitable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 17:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditor gives an in-depth explanation why TSLA isn't doing so well in China despite massive investment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 16:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/worldnews/comments/2vgi80/tesla_only_sold_120_cars_in_china_in_january_ceo/cohyvph </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What were the motivations behind sending out Voyager 1   Voyager 2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 16:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scientifically, technologically, politically? Why did we suddenly decide to spend a couple billion dollars to send a craft to the rough edges of space, when we haven't seen deemed it feasible to do it again for the past 30-40 years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's something which you hold a half-empty view of, which the comment below can give you a half-full view? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 10:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A good site full of Warren Buffett's quotes over the years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 09:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IGN giving free copies of Mass Effect Infiltrator on iOS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 06:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Value Investing Analysis 1: SapuraKencana (5218.KL) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 06:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ok I promised /u/Piospro a value investing post, so here's one. The entire post is 14 pages worth of Word, so given the 10,000 charcter limit I'll only be posting the first few pages here. You can read the rest on my blog: http://investingmy.com/sapurakencana-5218-kl/

 Anyway, just to tl;dr, this is a company I feel pretty good about. Feel free to share your opinions.



**BACKGROUND**  
SapuraKencana. What is it?
It used to be solely in the oil and gas services industry, laying pipes for upstream suppliers. The company started out as Sapura Bhd, which was specifically involved in OCSS (Offshore Construction and Subsea Services), before merging with Kencana Bhd in 2012 which was primarily a FHUC (fabrication, hook-up and commissioning) provider.
Basically, the oil and gas industry is broken into 3 different industries  upstream suppliers who do the actual drilling and procurement of oil, midstream suppliers laying the pipelines or providing the equipment for the upstream suppliers (i.e. transportation of oil), and downstream suppliers who do the processing and refining to turn the crude oil into something actually usable, such as petrol or kerosene. Then there are the integrated oil majors, sometimes known as integrated oil or super majors, such as ExxonMobil, BP or Shell, which do all three.
Sapurakencana in this context used to be a midstream supplier, laying the pipeline and transporting oil for the large oil and gas majors in places where they dont deem it feasible to do it themselves. It also supplies oil rigs to these companies so that they are able to drill the oil in the first place. 
However, with the recent acquisition of Newfield Malaysia in 2013, SapuraKencana has effectively dipped into the upstream market by participating in the actual drilling for oil. It is clear with the recent acquisitions that its CEO, Tan Sri Shahril Shamsuddin (Shahril) is trying to transform SapuraKencana into an integrated oil major. In the same year, SapuraKencana acquired the entire tender rig division of Seadrill Ltd, a major midstream player in the US market, in exchange for some cash and a 12% stake in SapuraKencana (which has since been pared down to 8%). This effectively made it the largest tender rig operator in the world. 



**RUNNING THE NUMBERS**  
**Net profit**  
Net profit has shown pretty decent y-o-y growth, rising 60% last year and projected to match last years performance this year. 3Q/2015 results have already surpassed the previous years full year results by 16%. Revenues also increased proportionally, likely coming from the acquisitions. 
Depreciation for the nine months to 3Q/2015 was RM 829,919, while finance costs were RM 513,459. Im going to assume that CAPEX for the next 3 years or so is going to average about RM 1Bn, based on the depreciation figure. Finance costs on the other hand are a bit troubling. As well see later, debt has been rising even after the acquisition.

**Capital structure**  
The company has approximately 6 billion shares outstanding, giving it a market capitalization of around RM 17bn at the current share price of RM 2.80. In comparison, it has a whopping RM 14bn in debt which incurred interest of RM 500m in the nine months leading up to 3Q/2015. Debt:equity is 1.2x; which does not factor in payables, which if included brings the liabilities:equity ratio to 1.8x (high payables is common in oil   gas companies). At this point, the company is levered to the hilt. The fact that it was able to reach this point is impressive in itself, much less any consideration that it might be able to further increase its leverage. Im sure its strong brand in the region had been a key factor in helping it acquire this magnitude of financing in the first place. 
The first question which springs to anyones mind is whether the company can continue to service its interest and principal obligations, in the context of the falling oil price environment. Its unlikely we will ever see $100/barrel oil again, although consensus is that oil will revert back to about $60-$70 in two to three years time. So the question is, can SapuraKencana survive over the next two to three years?

The answer is a resounding, if not quite reassuring, yes. The company has a RM 30 bn orderbook, which at current revenue levels is enough to maintain performance for the next three years, albeit at zero (or possibly negative) growth. Obviously, things are not as straightforward as that, however if the company can continue populating its orderbook at even slightly slower rates, it should be fine. Alliance Bank states that the company would have to maintain its orderbook to sustain its contract burn rates. Even in the worst case scenario, the company is well-recognised and well-connected enough that refinancing debt (albeit at higher interest rates) is always an option.
Having said that, the bigger question and the elephant in the room, is whether the company can redeem its debt in full in a reasonable amount of time. Any debt which remains on the balance sheet will incur interest charges, which represent a fixed share of profits going to debtholders. For reasons yet unapparent until the 2015 financial statements come out, it seems that debt has increased by RM 3bn in the nine months to 3Q/2015 despite no significant acquisitions taking place, not including an additional RM8bn Islamic note signed in Jan 2015 which was not captured in the 3Q/2015 statements. No equity investor in his right mind would buy shares at the current price (9 Feb 2015: RM 2.80) without a serious plan in place to reduce the debt burden. The CEO has said he expects to debt reduce to US$ 3bn in 3 years; however, how he plans to do that while maintaining present growth rates is anyones guess. Debt:equity levels have to reduce within the next 10 years AT MOST  without artificially diluting equity holder  if equity investors which to see a profitable ROI on their investments today. 

In any case, here are some finer details about the debt. Interest payments are currently at about 4% of debt  some sources claim that it is 1-2%, although Im not sure how theyre getting to that. The 4% figure is impressive anyhow, given that corporate debt on the largest companies in the US is going for about 5% average. This is no doubt contributed by two factors: firstly, its brand and connections to the Malaysian government (a bailout in the event of a catastrophe is highly likely), and the fact that it has access to international barrel-scrapping interest rates. A few minor points to note are that: i) the debt is denominated in USD, ii) the company doesnt really participate in any currency hedging, and iii) the recent spike in MYR-USD rates have been beneficial for the company since it reports earnings in MYR.
Another related possible cause for concern is that RM 9bn (possibly increased since Jan 2014) of debt is maturing and payable in 2 years. Thats right folks; it has to front RM 1.50/share of debt within 2 years, something which is only possible via refinancing. While this is no cause for alarm due to the high likelihood of refinancing, remarkably little details have been provided regarding what this debt relates to and why the maturity date is so short for such a staggering amount of debt, as well as why it was structured so unusually to begin with. Is it a bridging loan for the eventual sukuk-tization of the debt? Was it a sale and leaseback agreement for the Seadrill assets? Nobody really knows. Its something to stay incredibly conscious about, thats for sure. 
In any case, heres the bottom line. As weve explored above, the company is in growth mode and is expected to continue its impressive rate of growth through further acquisitions, given its vision of becoming a fully integrated oil major. Since oil and gas companies do not typically have a lot of free cash flow (FCF) after reinvestment, it can only do so in one of two ways: take on more debt or issue equity and dilute shareholders. So far, management has been extremely prescient about the effects of diluting shareholders, and theoretically picking up debt is an optimal way of maximizing returns. However, it is approaching dangerously close to the possibility of default risk in the event of a global economic catastrophe. For instance, if a hypothetical world war were to suddenly break out, the company would definitely fold. 

I wont go into a full breakdown of each segments performance, as my goal with this article is to give you a broad overview of the company with enough detail to fill in the blanks yourself, but not to unnecessarily overwhelm you with numbers. If you need a more detailed breakdown in one or two areas, I hope you can do a simple Google search which can bring you directly to the source, as opposed to me throwing the entire kitchen sink at you (which will make this article about 3x longer). I found a good site which aggregated the majority of its past three quarters performance here: http://m.kinibiz.com/tag/shahrilshamsuddin
In any case, it seems that the companys cost management has been ebbing up and down over time. Its not a cause for concern but it indicates that successfully battling the two fronts of stellar revenue growth coupled with excellent cost management is not an expectation you should hold dearly should you decide to become an investor. 

**Other**  
Besides that, none of the numbers represent anything out of the ordinary. You can scan them yourselves in the balance sheet, profit   loss and cash flow figures in the tables above; the material items from each statement are listed below their respective tables. 



**ANALYSIS**  
Ok, so heres the lowdown on the company. As you all should already know, the company has been going on a massive shopping spree over the past few years. Starting in 2012, it merged with Kencana Bhd to form SapuraKencana as we know it today....


*(continued... http://investingmy.com/sapurakencana-5218-kl/)*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's something which sounds so Japanese you just have to believe it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 15:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You have the power to make a difference </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 15:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does sprinkling a pinch of salt on an orange make me feel much fuller than eating it vanilla? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 15:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some creative ways to get a full ride to college? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 06:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Standing on the Edge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 06:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Target Acquired </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 13:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best GIF to go with the 20th Century Fox theme? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 13:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An average day for the Russian male </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 10:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a joke to make someone's day, don't upvote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 10:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] How many of you take drugs to stay productive (i.e. awake)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 02:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is what happens when investment bankers get burnt out spending 100 hours at the office </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 02:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.scribd.com/doc/142919907/BabyDick-Capital-Investor-Presentation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You are the new editor of Buzzfeed. What's the most arresting title you can steal from Reddit, and which links would your article point to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 15:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asked a colleague who bikes to work everyday for advice on safe road cycling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 17:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upon hearing the FCC reclassifying the internet as a public utility </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 17:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Would it be possible to introduce a new word into popular culture? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 10:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something like 'fetch'. Use it everywhere you go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When will self-driving cats become available at the earliest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 19:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You are Neil Armstrong just before taking your first step on the moon, with millions listening on the radio for your first words. How do you capitalize on it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 15:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Neil Armstrong had accidentally tripped when taking his first step on the moon and exclaimed, "S***!", would the first words on the moon have been recorded as that? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 15:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remember TwitchPlaysPokemon? Now there's TwitchPlaysStockMarket </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 07:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Office: 20 Years Later </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 07:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why hasn't e-reader monitors caught on in the workplace? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 06:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember an article a few years back saying that e-readers would become increasingly cheaper to produce once scale can be achieved. Well, the opportunity seems ripe for the legions of bankers, nurses and engineers who read MILLIONS of PDF files daily on what are basically mini-sun displays. Why are e-reader monitors still so exclusive and so expensive if the demand is so apparent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> u/Marcooo87 draws his girlfriend who is fighting cancer into an anime series she loves. Whole sub sends well wishes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 06:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I miss when memes used to be about imaginary situations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 18:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good Guy u/Warlizard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 18:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL online merchants actually do not require your credit card's CVV number or expiry date to process a transaction. The number is demanded purely to protect them from fraud chargebacks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 18:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most clich supervillain name? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 15:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am establishing global dominance, but just fired marketing department due to budget cuts. Need help to SEO my brand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opulence, I has it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 10:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit right now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 16:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/new right now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 16:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I found this funny story on Quora </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 11:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In one of his books in Techical and Fundamental Analysis, Jack Schwager tells to story of the technical analyst and the fundamental analyst having dinner together.  As the fundamental analyst reaches for his glass of wine, his sleeve brushes his steak knife off the table.  Both men watch as the steak knife tumbles through the air, as if in slow motion, and sticks in the fundamental analyst's foot.

"Why didn't you move your foot?" asked the technical analyst.

The fundamental analyst replied, "I was waiting for it to come back up."

Never try to catch a falling knife, or pick the bottom of a downtrend.  You will be wrong 85-90% of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bloomberg has an epic 404 page </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 10:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bloomberg has an epic 404 page </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 10:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Elon Musk was Iron Man, and Obama was Captain America, which superhero would your favorite celebrity be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 07:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> u/fscomeau bets a year's salary on Apple stock, becomes venerable hero in /r/wallstreetbets. Culminates in a hospital visit puking green bile. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 02:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does the strength of a radioactive wave decrease exponentially as the distance from the target increases linearly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 01:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> u/lulzlullington's abusive boyfriend violently restricts her constitutional rights and she can't do anything about it. Entire sub intervenes with grand outpouring of support and offers her urgent remedial advice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 15:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something went horribly wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 06:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> u/SA_NOCLDWAIT gives wonderful career advice about finding a job you love in finance, but which could apply to just about any industry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 17:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attack on Titan 3D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 15:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/AdWA9Ix.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attack on Titan 3D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 14:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> u/b1shopx lists down all the useful Alien Blue shortcuts, e.g. tapping a comment with two fingers to upvote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 15:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What's the best thing to put on sliced bread? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 10:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor guy here, send hummus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk's plan to build a Satellite Internet is debunked by ex-Iridium employee (satellite phone) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 11:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  *Source:*  
Scroll to the comment section of this BusinessWeek page, or Ctrl+F "mozumder": http://www.businessweek.com/articles/2015-01-17/elon-musk-and-spacex-plan-a-space-internet#r=rss

For convenience, here's the comment in full: 

mozumder  alonsoperez  3 days ago


This is not going to happen. Musk has no idea what he's getting into.

I worked on the original Iridium satellite phone project. I built a simulator for the entire network, and the handset uplink bandwidth was 2400 baud. Yep. Just 2400 bits per second.

Now we can do things like improve coding efficiency and maybe add a little bit more power to the satellites (although Iridium satellites are huge already) or perhaps bring them a little closer to earth, and at the very best case we might get 10x improvement. So now we're up to 100kbps.

That's not even 2G speeds. And who's going to want that, especially now that 3rd world countries have already solved the internet-access problem with 4G-LTE cell towers?

If you want faster speeds, you'll need expensive tracking dishes or phased-array antennas, and at this point your market size dramatically decreased. Pretty soon your market is going to only be 10,000 or so airplanes and ships. That's it. (lol @ the idea that there's going to be 200 million customers.. try 20,000 instead.)

After all that, you'll still never get close to fiber-optic speeds, which are hitting 10GBps now for the corporate world, literally a MILLION times faster, and doesn't have the power-cost problem that wireless does.

Sorry Elon Musk, but this is a dead-end project. Many smart people have already tried to solve this and failed, and you're not adding anything new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> u/MyLifeSuxNow (Jenny's husband), how do you feel about Reddit spinning your life tragedy on the web and making you an Internet sensation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 02:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My name is Zack. AMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 13:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi I'm Zack, the imaginary guy who captured your imagination together with Jenny (XOXO), Carly, mysterious guy X, and OP. You may have always wanted to get the story straight from the horses' mouth, (rather than sleazy Jenny) but I understand that's sometimes a little hard to do with imaginary people. But Reddit is amazing - it connects the physical realm with the imaginary realm! So ask away! I won't hold back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> His Name is PUTIN </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 09:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin talking to a secret KGB agent in disguise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 08:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who have been hit by two-wheeled vehicles before, how jealous are you of people who have been hit by four-wheeled vehicles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 04:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or any other number of wheels, I'm not racist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP explains why he would put chopped veges in a ziplock bag </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 03:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL there is an Onomatopoeia website which lists down all known sounds literally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 06:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calling it #bubbleYOLO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 17:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gentlemen, price in your expectations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why doesn't the Constitution only legally allow political parties to hold no more than e.g. 25%, 33%, 40% of the vote? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 09:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would represent the conflict of interest situation way fairer, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the Tesla Model 3's $35,000 sticker price scientifically realistic in the next 3 years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 02:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Orpheum Auditorium in New Bedford, Massachusetts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 15:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abandoned Coal Plant in France </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 15:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MSN Messenger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 15:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abandoned Mining Town at Eastern Siberia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 15:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most classy thing you can say in ALL CAPS and BOLD LETTERS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 15:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the coolest thing you can make with a 3D printer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 16:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most awkward </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 16:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] 'Double-tap the lockscreen clock' Activator to show/hide a predefined image </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 09:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For instance, a spouse or your dog. Or both, if they're one and the same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/investing gives a great argument for GOOG </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 08:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Tesla Killer: Chevrolet Bolt, a $30,000 electric car with 200 miles per charge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 06:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which is more important, hardware or software? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 16:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which is more important, hardware or software? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 12:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They weren't kidding when they said Star Trek had a lot of lens flares [x-post /r/gifs] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 15:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coolest Macbook Sticker Ever (x-post r/thelastairbender) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 15:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Age 40 on the left, age 53 on the right </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 17:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Constructing an asset allocation model for optimal geographical diversification </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 16:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A client recently tasked us with creating a relatively simple asset allocation model for optimal geographical diversification. We're a relatively small shop, so we usually don't create models - we just work out the details in our heads and make the decision. Since it's a low priority concern, the job was delegated and re-delegated until it's reached me. So... here I am, seeking advice on reddit.

I've been doing my own research for awhile before it crossed my mind that some of you here may have done it before. Basically, what I've done so far is just a basic risk parity model and constructed an efficient frontier, which might satisfy someone who hasn't seen one before (i.e. the client) but probably not my bosses. I don't think he's looking for a full blown statistical thesis on the relationship between Brazillian oil wells and Chinese political dynasties, but if anyone could share their experience it would be greatly appreciated. For context, we're looking at 4 regions - USA, Asia Pacific, China   ASEAN. 

Thanks!

P.S. I've seen some of the geographical diversification studies while Googling around -  it doesn't need to be that complicated. We're just looking for something respectable which can still be explained to the laymen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Constructing an asset allocation model for optimal geographical diversification </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 16:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A client recently tasked us with creating a relatively simple asset allocation model for optimal geographical diversification. We're a relatively small shop, so we usually don't create models - we just work out the details in our heads and make the decision. Since it's a low priority concern, the job was delegated and re-delegated until it's reached me. So... here I am, seeking advice on reddit.

I've been doing my own research for awhile before it crossed my mind that some of you here may have done it already here. Basically, what I've done so far is just a basic risk parity model and constructed an efficient frontier, which might satisfy someone who hasn't seen one before (i.e. the client) but probably not my bosses. I don't think he's looking for a full blown statistical thesis on the relationship between Brazillian oil wells and Chinese political dynasties, but if anyone could share their experience it would be greatly appreciated. For context, we're looking at 4 regions - USA, Asia Pacific, China   ASEAN. 

Thanks!

P.S. I've seen some of the geographical diversification studies while Googling around -  it doesn't need to be that complicated. We're just looking for something respectable which can still be explained to the laymen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Google Chrome was named as such partly because one of the lead developers liked fast cars and partly because all the other suggested names were terrible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 16:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AQR - Why We Lever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 03:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> America suddenly reverts to an agrarian Roman society. What have you recently done to deserve a sentence of 30 lashes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 01:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you're ever feeling down... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 16:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 16:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This office had an outdoor fountain which collected rain. Regardless of the weather, you could smell the dewy smell of rain, i.e. petrichor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 14:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They said I could be anything, so I became a sperm whale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 14:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's over $9.00!!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 14:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Killing an eagle with an exploding bear [Far Cry 4] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 08:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gamer commits atrocity during competitive speedrun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 08:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What SFW content do you use Incognito mode for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 07:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blind iPhone owner requests a tweak for sight-impaired jailbreakers (link in comments); OP delivers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 04:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the average net takeaway of a bank robbery in 2010 was $7,500. In 2006, it was only $4,330. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 07:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Project Homeless </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 06:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You have to cut off Australia's eleven cables to the Internet with the tools currently at your disposal or Comcast kills your family. How do you do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 03:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You hav3 36 hOurs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you're goofing off and your crush walks by </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 14:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 13:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trust Fall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 10:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where did the phrase "I can't even" originate from? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 04:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Silk Velvet background for NC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 16:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ material made of something like this for the background, akin to what iOS 6 used to have: 

https://www.google.com.my/search?q=velvet+silk espv=2 biw=1920 bih=979 source=lnms tbm=isch sa=X ei=MHehVJbIF82yuASokoHQBg ved=0CAYQ_AUoAQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just heard the ultimate first world problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 15:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL TIME Magazine once ran a legitimate ad for a Blackberry for $10.5 million, which came with a free private island </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 16:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THANK YOU Dev X for Tweak Y U da best!!! XOXO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 16:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now where's my karma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Courageous North Korean woman describes her harsh life to an international audience (prepare tissues) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 15:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] CCLoader for iOS 8 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 03:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would appreciate having Dynamic Media Controls in Control Center back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does Bank of America 2031 bond have 12% coupon when 10 year Treasury is barely above 2%? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 17:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **2031 BoA**:   
http://screener.finance.yahoo.com/z2?ce=5815054147501815417549 q=b%3D3%26cll%3D0%26cpl%3D-1.000000%26cpu%3D-1.000000%26mtl%3D-1%26mtu%3D-1%26pr%3D0%26rl%3D-1%26ru%3D-1%26sf%3Dy%26so%3Dd%26stt%3D-%26tc%3D1%26tm%3D1%26yl%3D12.000000%26ytl%3D-1.000000%26ytu%3D-1.000000%26yu%3D-1.000000

**2028 Morgan Stanley too**:   
http://screener.finance.yahoo.com/z2?ce=5215547145581715715850 q=b%3D3%26cll%3D0%26cpl%3D-1.000000%26cpu%3D-1.000000%26mtl%3D-1%26mtu%3D-1%26pr%3D0%26rl%3D-1%26ru%3D-1%26sf%3Dy%26so%3Dd%26stt%3D-%26tc%3D1%26tm%3D1%26yl%3D12.000000%26ytl%3D-1.000000%26ytu%3D-1.000000%26yu%3D-1.000000  

Relatively new to bonds, please be gentle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does Bank of America 2031 bond have 12% coupon when 10 year Treasury is barely above 2%? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 17:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **2031 BoA**:   
http://screener.finance.yahoo.com/z2?ce=5815054147501815417549 q=b%3D3%26cll%3D0%26cpl%3D-1.000000%26cpu%3D-1.000000%26mtl%3D-1%26mtu%3D-1%26pr%3D0%26rl%3D-1%26ru%3D-1%26sf%3Dy%26so%3Dd%26stt%3D-%26tc%3D1%26tm%3D1%26yl%3D12.000000%26ytl%3D-1.000000%26ytu%3D-1.000000%26yu%3D-1.000000

**2028 Morgan Stanley too**:   
http://screener.finance.yahoo.com/z2?ce=5215547145581715715850 q=b%3D3%26cll%3D0%26cpl%3D-1.000000%26cpu%3D-1.000000%26mtl%3D-1%26mtu%3D-1%26pr%3D0%26rl%3D-1%26ru%3D-1%26sf%3Dy%26so%3Dd%26stt%3D-%26tc%3D1%26tm%3D1%26yl%3D12.000000%26ytl%3D-1.000000%26ytu%3D-1.000000%26yu%3D-1.000000  

Relatively new to bonds, please be gentle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does Bank of America 2031 bond have 12% coupon when 10 year Treasury is barely above 2%? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 17:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **2031 BoA**:   
http://screener.finance.yahoo.com/z2?ce=5815054147501815417549 q=b%3D3%26cll%3D0%26cpl%3D-1.000000%26cpu%3D-1.000000%26mtl%3D-1%26mtu%3D-1%26pr%3D0%26rl%3D-1%26ru%3D-1%26sf%3Dy%26so%3Dd%26stt%3D-%26tc%3D1%26tm%3D1%26yl%3D12.000000%26ytl%3D-1.000000%26ytu%3D-1.000000%26yu%3D-1.000000

**2028 Morgan Stanley too**:   
http://screener.finance.yahoo.com/z2?ce=5215547145581715715850 q=b%3D3%26cll%3D0%26cpl%3D-1.000000%26cpu%3D-1.000000%26mtl%3D-1%26mtu%3D-1%26pr%3D0%26rl%3D-1%26ru%3D-1%26sf%3Dy%26so%3Dd%26stt%3D-%26tc%3D1%26tm%3D1%26yl%3D12.000000%26ytl%3D-1.000000%26ytu%3D-1.000000%26yu%3D-1.000000  

Relatively new to bonds, please be gentle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the Japanese maglev bullet train, Shinkansen, sports a sterling record of zero fatalities over its 50 years of operations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 16:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Had to do a double take when I heard my colleague complaining about this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 15:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ladies, we got a new star in town! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 15:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where did the concept of the four elements of Fire, Water, Wind and Earth as the fundamental building blocks of science come from? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 16:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems this philosophy is present in different ancient cultures throughout the world despite them not having or having limited contact with each other (e.g. Greek, Chinese, Egyptians) Why is this such a common and recurring theme among the scientists of those times?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You break up with your ex not knowing he/she is a mind-switching leprechaun, and they put you into the body of a North Korean peasant, tasking you to convince your fellow brethren that the whole state is a sham to return to your body. With the limited tools at your disposal, how do you do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 16:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do stray cats bolt away like lightning when they see a human approaching from 10 feet away, yet show no fear when a 2 ton car barrels toward them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 15:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't the noise and relative size scare them at all? Or are their sensory organs not equipped to recognize danger from a modern creation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
