<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9584</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 18:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Especially in a free state like the US, and much of the world, where military service is volunteer based. Perhaps you disagree with the government's use of military force, but you can still support and wish the best for those that volunteered to put their life on the line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 17:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1900's like entire century or 1900's like 1900-1909? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just started watching The Americans, and holy crap this show is great. Why isn't it getting more hype?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 15:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely love the show. The writing   acting is fantastic. Each episode keeps you on the edge of your seat and the plot moves along too, it doesn't get stagnant. But I talk to friends and most haven't even heard of it and those that have, haven't seen it or know much about it. And I didn't hear much of anything regarding it leading up the Emmy's. What gives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just started watching The Americans, and holy crap this show is great. Why isn't getting more hype?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 15:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone do the Campus Wheelworks Group rides? How are they? What distance(s) do they do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 22:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help making a chart with data on different sheets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 17:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to make a simple bar graph using data across several 8 different sheets. All it is a numerical value in cell H2 of each page. I just want each of the 8 values to be a column in the graph. How do I do this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Reddit, do you have a favorite poem or quote from a poem? What is it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 15:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WANT] Leaves of Grass, anniversary edition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 15:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will trade other books, money or pay shipping! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend forgot the word 'water' apparently. Brilliant substitute. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 15:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I did NOT mean it like this. It was just a good excuse to be away from my desk for a couple minutes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 23:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JP Bullfeathers trivia night - any good? How is it run? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 22:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jason Isbell -- Cover Me Up [Americana/Rock]. This whole album is oozing with soul and beautiful lyrics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 16:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone done Bacchus Movie Night? How is it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 18:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 44 Things to Do in Buffalo in August </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 14:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which past HBO show should I start watching? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 17:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got Amazon Prime so now I have access to all the past HBO shows. I haven't seen any HBO besides GoT, so I was wondering what I should start watching first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just got Amazon Prime and have access to the past HBO lineup. I've never watched any HBO besides GoT. What should I start with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 17:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Went to a Brazilian steakhouse last night. This is how I feel the next day. Worth every bite. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 18:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's an oldie, but this never fails to make me laugh. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 20:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL That Hemingway hunted for U-Boats in the Gulf Coast during WWII out of a sense of duty to his country and for pure adventure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 16:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Smelling farts could actually be good for your health, prevent cancer, strokes and heart attacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 14:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WSIG] Having Indecision Disorder...I know they're pretty different, but...Kemet, Euphoria or Bruges for my next purchase? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 17:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'd love to get a round up of all the "extras" on kickstarter for board games. Cool storage solutions, dice, accessories etc. What's out there?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 16:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trajan Commodities/Shipping Question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 20:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you ship commodity cards, are they then also able to be used in the end game scoring of the bonus tiles that give you 3 points per shown commodity? Or can you only score those if you take the seaport action to lay those in your player area? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Reddit, what's your favorite Pandora station? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 02:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Reddit, what's one YouTube video we should watch right now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 21:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] of great importance for my dear friend for the World Cup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 19:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I want to make a gif of that Charlie Murphy skit with Rick James when he's stomping on the couch saying "F YO COUCH" but replace the couch with waffles and update the text accordingly. However I don't have the technology available on my phone." This is a request from my dear friend and I want to make this for him. It's the US game today and his birthday. Is this possible?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:Why can some people sing well, but others can't hit a note to save their life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 14:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One soccer player sitting atop another soccer player </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 23:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conditional formatting for whole row based on two columns. Please help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 17:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My goal is to highlight the whole row based off Column B being greater/lesser than Column C, but excel always interpets Column A (which is words) as greater than the any numerical value. So it'll will never highlight Column A when B is less than C. 

[Here is my example](http://i.imgur.com/kOgkm76.jpg). I'd like each row to be uniform.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ultimate Frisbee in Dublin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 15:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I'll be in Dublin this Friday - Sunday and was wondering if there's any pick up ultimate around the city?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Besides clothing, what are the essentials to bring with you on a solo travel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 16:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The specificity made it so much weirder/stalkery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 14:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best public transpo package for Ireland? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 19:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be backpacking Ireland for 12 days this summer and I was wondering what the best options would be. I'd like to buy a package ticket if possible. It seems Bus eireann and Irish Rail are the two main systems. Are there tickets that includes a pass for both? 

I'll be going from Dublin to, Wicklow, Kilkenny, Waterford, Cork, Kinsale, Killarney, Kerry, Galway, back to Dublin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the biggest backpack size (in liters) that can typically be carried on a plane? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 05:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want to get into cycling - what to look for in a bike? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 15:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to spend a ton of money. It'll be my first bike, but I want something more than a rusty bucket off CL. When I'm looking used, what brands should I keep an eye out that offer a reliable "starter" bike? Can I get anything decent for $200-$300?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What I've learned about Reddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 00:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crashing at a friend's after a party. I'm really good at picking up on girls' signals... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 22:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite movie that no one else seems to like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 17:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 28yr old American guy, looking for a couch in Dublin May 23-25! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 15:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just looking for a place to crash in Dublin for a night or 2 while I start my backpacking through Ireland! I'm real easy going, looking to meet some awesome people and experience the Irish culture! I can cook too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beat you by a day, I Guarantee It meme! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 18:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Browsing Reddit when I woke up this morning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 18:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With all the dads excitedly posting about passing lawn mowing duties to their kids... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 14:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Backpacking through Ireland...best bus/train routes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 21:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be going off to Ireland for 12 days in a month. Basically making my way from Dublin, around the southern coast, up to Galway. I've heard the public transpo is pretty good in Ireland. What's the most bang for my buck and best routes to take along the way? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what's the worst comment you've seen get gilded? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 21:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The sarcastic, actually popular opinion UOP's are getting old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 19:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what movies would you want to see a sequel for that never got one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 15:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Agricola feeding question for new family members </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 04:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you add a new family member, will they only need 1 food for the next harvest, or will they only need 1 food if they were 'born' in a harvest round? Say, I added a family member in round 12, at the round 13 harvest would they cost 2 or 1 food? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone played Agricola on boiteajeux? Can you do solo campaign or just 1 solo game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 22:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I read 25 pages of Cloud Atlas and couldn't have been more bored. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 17:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I missing out if I stop now? I can't remember the last time I ever quit on a book, but I can't remember ever being less drawn into a book. What do people think of this book? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Painting the Tzolk'in gears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 14:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just got Tzolk'in yesterday and I am exciiited. I'd love to paint the gears, but I've never done any miniature painting or anything like that. What do people recommend to use in terms of paints, brushes etc? No clue where to start </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone played the Suburbia campaign in the iOS app? Question... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 05:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm running into problems with Atlanta, specifically the Connect All Tiles bonus. I'm reaching one gray to another and various points along the outside. Every tile is connected through the tiles somehow. I don't get why it keeps failing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wondering how peoples' experiences with Kickstarter have been! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 22:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never backed anything on Kickstarter. Prices can be so much higher than what a typical game costs, I have trouble justifying the investment on something I've never seen. So I was wondering how other gamers look at Kickstarter. Have you backed games on Kickstarter? Have you regretted any? Great experiences, bad experiences? What's the general flow like when you back something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WSIG] Tzolk'in, Robinson Crusoe, Bora Bora, 1775 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 19:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I typically like medium to heavy strategy games with minimized luck (terra mystica, eclipse, castles of burgundy, suburbia etc). If the game has a stronger thematic play to it, then all the better, but not crucial.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To the insanity wolf of the guy breaking up with his gf on a cruise with her family </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 16:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is Finley. He loves pretty much everything. Especially running. It took about a half hour to get him to sit still for this picture. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 15:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, meet my frisbee loving mini aussie! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 02:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kid tries a "shortcut" during a race </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 18:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon Deal of the Day 3/14 - Harman Kardon CL Precision On-Ear Headphones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 13:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:Why, after throwing up (ate some bad food) do I not want to eat/am not hungry for a day or two? Shouldn't I be extra hungry after purging? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 17:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wrensanity Continues with Simba! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 18:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Visiting Ireland for 2 weeks in late may - june. Any festivals or events during that time I should check out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 18:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going to Ireland for 10 days and need a backpack, any recommendations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 14:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely don't need something huge. I'll be staying in hostels/hotels every night, so no camping eqpt needed. I was looking at the Osprey Stratos 36. Seems light, accessible and organized. Any others I should check out? My main wants are light, organized storage areas and 35-40L. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend organized a youth outreach boardgame night. He asked 4 of us to bring   teach them games. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 16:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a group that regularly gets together for board game nights and we were more than happy to help out and teach them (anywhere from high school to college) games! It was a lot of fun. [**Here's what we were able to muster up**](http://i.imgur.com/vfEVqzK.jpg) 

Favorites of the night were King of Tokyo, Pandemic, Dominion and Burgundy. Pretty much all of the people were new to games, so they didn't get into the heavier stuff. We're going to try to do this every 1 or 2 months, so we hope it continues! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL There is an NFL Arrest Database and there are 685 entries since October 2010. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 19:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Backpacking Ireland this summer...which hostels are best? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 19:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any recommendations on hostels in Dublin, Galway and if there's any around cork, killarney, limerick or brunner would be much appreciated. I always just like to look at forums and not just review sites, since there's so many paid reviews nowadays. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Traveling to Ireland: Tour or Independent? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 16:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm planning a trip to Ireland and trying to decide whether to use a tour (likely Go Ahead Tours) or just backpack it. People that have done tours of Ireland, is it worth it? Would I be better off planning it myself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone used WriterAccess? How'd you get started? Were you successful? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 18:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I live in a building managed by E Square Capital. Heat is "included" in my rent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 00:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My pipes froze 3 weeks ago during the blizzard. The cold water pipe has not worked since and yesterday the hot water froze too, nothing comes out. They have still not come to fix anything. Came home from worl today to find ice formed in a bowl and all along the hose attachment. They refuse to fix anything, saying the city isn't giving enough pressure (no neighbor is reporting this, we checked) and won't raise the heat. Several of the apartments have dogs. They are threatening to file litigation against anyone who doesn't pay rent or tries to break lease and move out. I'm still holding on to my rent money. 


tl;dr - do NOT move into one of their buildings. 

Pictures:

http://i.imgur.com/EMRoRjfh.jpg   (Note the faucets are on and no water)
http://i.imgur.com/NNwx8u2h.jpg

http://i.imgur.com/aWjtXqzh.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help conditionally formatting for adjacent cells </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 22:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So basically, I'd like to conditionally format cells in a chart based on their adjacent cell. Some if it is simple: For instance if the cell in Column C says "Total" I'd like the text in the same row in Column D to be bold with a green fill. Is this possible? What formula would I use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the best free learning courses available online (at any site)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 18:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should clarify...actual specific classes within sites live Kahn Academy or edX </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL There's a sugarless gummy bear from Haribo...and it's horrible. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 18:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Visiting Toronto this weekend. Best bars to watch NFL playoffs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 22:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be staying on Yonge st for the weekend and was hoping to catch the NFL playoff games on Saturday. Any good places within walking or quick cab ride distance? I heard Sports Centre cafe is decent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Haven't gotten Fifa in a few years...need some serious help with defense! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 20:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I haven't gotten Fifa since 11, well before this new manual tackling was implemented. I overpursue every player with the ball, constantly whiff with the tackle button. And holding contain just keeps him a few yards off and generally lets the guy go right by him if he makes a sprint. I'd love some tips, cuz I am just not used to this and it is frustrating as hell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any games where you play with certain "house rules" instead of the game's included rules? If so, what? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 21:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just finished The Unbearable Lightness of Being...and I hated it. I'd love to discuss it tho! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 21:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simply put, I thought every character in the book was profoundly unlikeable, and while I generally enjoy Kundera's prose, I felt this book overly disjointed. I'd love to hear other peoples' thoughts on Tomas, Tereza, Sabina, Franz, the ending, the philosophy of the book, dreams or anything else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got a few books for Christmas, which should I open up first?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 15:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 7 Reasons Buffalonians Shouldn't Hate Snow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 18:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many 5 year olds could you take if they all swarmed you at once? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 19:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teachers of Reddit, what is the worst parent interaction you've ever had? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 01:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the weirdest conversation you've overheard in public? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 21:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WSIG] I have $20 to amazon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 18:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd prefer to keep it under the $20, or at least real close. I have lots of medium to heavy strategy games, so I'd like something lighter anywhere from 2-6 players.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keith Law's (ESPN baseball writer) 2013 list of his Top 50 boardgames </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 19:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keith Law is one of espn's lead baseball guys, has a pretty big national following and is a huge boardgame fan. He updates this list annually and included a couple 2013 releases including Bora Bora. He puts in some pretty nice summaries and full reviews if you follow the links.

http://meadowparty.com/blog/2013/12/06/top-50-boardgames/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most obvious or ridiculous scientific study you've ever seen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 22:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the best Trivia spots (and times) around Buffalo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 22:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best vacuum for pet hair? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 21:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a fortune to drop $300, $400 or more on a Dyson animal vacuum, so what would people recommend for the best bang for the buck on a good vacuum for pet hair (I have an Aussie) in maybe a $100-$150 range? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could wake up tomorrow with any ability (not a super power) what it would be? Why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 15:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Power Grid problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 21:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friends and I played our first 3 player game last night and I have some questions with problems we ran into. I started on the West Coast in Vegas and quickly fell behind as it was very expensive to span out, and my buddy found cheap expansion in the midwest and I could never really catch back up, because later I was completely blocked from expanding East as all the cities had 2 houses on them. This leads to my other question...the Step 3 card is at the bottom, and we had 2 houses on every single city in our 3 areas (the other 2 people had built 16 each), but we still had lots of power plant cards to go. So we spent several rounds simply holding auctions/passing on auctions, collecting resources   money. Until we got to the Step 3 card, built a bunch of houses and the game was over. Is this normal?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cash 'n Guns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 16:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know where I can find this? Or even better, does anyone have a copy they want to sell?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dog trainer recommendations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 23:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I have a 4 year old dog that doesn't do great with other dogs. Do people have recommendations for a training school or an individual dog behavioral therapist?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dog is a bit of a dick with other dogs, what can I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 21:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a 4 year old mini australian shepherd. He's fantastic with people. Loves em all. However, he doesn't do well with dogs. He gets uber-excited when he sees them and immediately tries to sprint right at em and jump on em (I'm 99.9% sure it's playing). This freaks other dogs out and they growl/bark/snap at him, which then scares him and makes him defensive. I know he needs to be socialized more, but I can't because of this and friends with dogs won't bring their dogs over or really want him at their house. 

I was thinking about bringing him to a doggy day care for some immersion therapy but I don't want him to end up being crated the entire time because he can't get along with any dog. What kind of tricks or training things can I do?

TL;DR my dog sucks with other dogs, need training advice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm looking to get into a series. What are your favorites? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 16:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Terra Mystica delivery came today! This game is beautiful, can't wait to play it tonight! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 00:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/j5A7h74.jpg

Tip of the cap to Z-Man games. This game is beautiful. The colors are vibrant, the board is thick (even the back of the gameboard has great artwork!) and everything feels of top notch quality. Any helpful tips so I can reign supreme in my group?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Delivery came today! This game is beautiful, can't wait to play it tonight! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 00:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a slow day in the neighborhood today. Anyone want to play some games at boiteajeux?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 14:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a broken XBOX360 (white) and broken PS3 (original model 40gb). Does anyone want them? For parts or something? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-26 00:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: for some questions: I'm not looking to sell em. I'm moving, they're broke, if some of my buffalo friends want me for parts or paper weights, just come pick em up! For what's wrong with them: Xbox boots up immediately to red light (also the pop-in hard drive from the side/top is gone). The PS3: when it turns on it beeps, blinks a green light a few times then shuts off as it blinks a red light then stays off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After dealing with Time Warner for 3 hours and getting nowhere </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 15:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After dealing with Time Warner for the past 3 hours and getting nowhere </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 04:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have these. Are they worth anything (more than face value)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 00:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poo-Pourri Commercial is real and hilarious. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 18:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone please photoshop my friend's kid to be hanging from a helicopter?! Thank you! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 18:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Helicopter: http://i.imgur.com/jXmpiQk.jpg

Kid: http://i.imgur.com/a0r3iAo.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone please shop my friend's kid to be hanging from this helicopter?! Thank you! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 18:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kid: http://i.imgur.com/a0r3iAo.jpg

Helicopter: http://i.imgur.com/jXmpiQk.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well, as long as we're following instructions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 22:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby Gorilla born at the Buffalo Zoo! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 21:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Went to ring my friend's doorbell. NOPE. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 17:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we stop it with the duck telling people to wrap it yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 05:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This happened at the office today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-26 17:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL That Winston Churchill was a Nobel Laureate in Literature </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 18:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All I can think: EEEEAGLE! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 15:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone ever created a board game? How'd you start? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 17:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first ever Paula's donut. Whoa. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 15:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thinking about becoming an engineer now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 17:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When my grandpa sees well-spoken black athletes interviewed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 20:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite backhanded compliment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 16:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every time I have lots of free time to work out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 14:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a longtime lurker that's started to be more active </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 16:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baseball has a "perfect game." What would be your boardgame victory equivalent? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 20:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Retail workers of Reddit - what are your best shoplifter stories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 00:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BrettspielWelt connection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 19:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have the client downloaded for brettspielwelt and a decent amount of the time I'll have serious lag. It'll be someone's turn and then just nothing happens...no turns are made, I can't click anything, I can't type a message and there is nothing wrong with my internet connection. Has anyone else experienced this? Any solutions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any other good looking board game Kickstarters with Euphoria ending? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-13 17:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twilight Struggle rules question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 18:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just got Twilight Struggle and have unbowed and am looking through the rules, and I just want to clarify something on placing influence tiles in a region. 

So if the enemy has influence or control in a country, can I gain control simply by placing more influence tiles? Lets say my enemy has control of Cuba (3) and I over a course of some turns place 6 influence, do I gain control? Can it be better to do that, if possible, over rolling for realignment or coups?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After I do all my laundry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-15 02:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite weird thing you've ever eaten? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-03 22:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Agricola - Baking bread  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-06 23:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friends and I are setting up our first game of Agricola and playing the family variant. Is it possible to bake bread in this or can you only do that through the improvement cards? 

Any other tips to playing our first time? Common things that confused you guys the first time around?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eclipse end of game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 20:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my friends and I have no played Eclipse twice and loved it. However, it seems to me both games progressed very peacefully then the end of the final round and it blew up into a massive onslaught on each other for  a few high valued hexes. It made the game seem very "last round dominant" if that's a thing. Has anyone felt the same while playing the game or are we just bad it? Is there a way to get to the game to progress so the first 8 rounds don't just feel like a set up for the final 9th round where everything was decided? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WSIG] Agricola, Stone Age, Small World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 01:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friends and I love the German style strategy games and have played a ton of settlers, Puerto Rico, Dominion, 7 Wonders and eclipse (played for the first time a few days ago and loved it). Now it's pretty much my overdue turn to contribute a game and by and large everything I've read for these three games are all positive reviews. I'd like to find a balance of complex, randomness to encourage replayability, and something that doesn't take crazy long like an Eclipse or Through The Ages. Just looking for basic pros and cons, personal experiences with the games, and what not. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
