<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6584</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 19:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this true?  If yes, one of the most horrifying images I've ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 19:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be interested in informed responses to this question, but I've read that Oscar Wilde could read two pages at a time, one with each eye.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 18:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your comment and sincere apologies if I am incorrect.  

Please read the artist's statement: 
"With "Tears of Nanjing" I want to show my deepest sympathy and love for all those totally innocent people who were perished so unjustifiably and with outmost cruelty, but also I want to remind the Japanese leaders that as long as they do not want to face the history, humanity cannot and will not possibly forgive and forget". (Gene Emerson) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The great Mark Reizen (beautifully) singing Gremin's aria from Eugene Onegin at age 90. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 18:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 18:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pavel Lisitsian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 18:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favorite operas, Ariadne auf Naxos by Strauss!
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VugbX5UgrLY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 18:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In fact, R-K's opera fueled the "Salieri poisoned Mozart" rumor, inspiring Shaffer's play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 17:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aloe gel, let it dry. Then try some coconut oil or olive oil and let it soak in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 17:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first performance of the 4 Last Songs occurred after Strauss' death.  He wrote these most beautiful songs with Kirsten Flagstad's voice in mind, and she premiered the songs with Furtwngler in 1952. Many critics consider their live collaboration to be the finest of all recorded performances of these songs.  Unfortunately, the sound quality is wretched, but one can hear the magnificent interpretation in spite of the poor sound.  
Thank you brocket66 for this post.  4 Last Songs are the ultimate, final flowering of the German Romantic tradition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 15:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abendempfindung by Mozart (try Schwarkopf).  Too many to count by Schubert, but try Gretchen am Spinnrade, Erlknig, An Sylvia, Die Taubenpost, Litanei aus dem Fest, Nacht und Trume, and so many more (he wrote over 600.) Many Russian romances by Tchaikovsky, including Amid the din of the ball, None but the lonely hearts, Why, The fires in the room were dying out.  Richard Strauss' Four last songs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Tears of Nanjing" trio by young Canadian composer Gene Emerson, age 13, in memory of Japanese atrocities resulting in deaths of 300,000 innocent Chinese, a crime denied by Japanese government. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 15:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brilliant Russian Easter Overture (Ormandy Philadelphia Orchestra 1946) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 02:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
