<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject71</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 16:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank You </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 14:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today in the NY Times: Was Mike Brown a patsy? Did he have ties to the Free Cuba Movement? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 14:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care who endorses who. To me it's all about track record and what they can do for the county as a whole. Saying you don't like someone because of who endorses him is like saying you don't like the Cardinals because Jon Hamm is a fan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 23:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last I heard was this as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 16:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $56.72 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blake Shelton - Good Country Song </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 02:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 01:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great bomb right there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 20:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. Thought it was my phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 18:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's My Job by Conway

She Thinks His Name Was John by Reba </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 16:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell we would have gotten bail together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 16:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't hear about Tusk until Clerks 3 was canned for the time being and that was 2-3 months ago. You'd think somebody would of thought to at least release a trailer or plug it someplace other than his podcast. Have a feeling that this is turning into Jersey Girls 2.0. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 16:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MY EARS!!! OH GOD MY EARS!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 05:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 27, born   raised in the Midwest, and 95% of the people I know have kids and are or were married. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 05:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just turned 27 Wednesday and this fits me perfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 01:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These latest ones give me a chance to "practice" before the big one. Can't wait for the big one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 23:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tough - Justin McBride

Big Boot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 19:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can your SS see what subs you are subscribed to or is it based all on your comments and post? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 17:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me want to put batteries in the GPS and get back out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Great-Grandpa (Maternal Grandpa's Dad) Late 40s-Early 50s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 17:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 16:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If soft scrub and a green pad isn't cutting it then it sounds like somebody shouldn't be touching the pans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 08:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to the network the PPVs have turned into Sunday Night Raw unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 17:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love this song but hard to believe it's 23 years old. I feel old now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 04:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I mentioned on FB for anyone who saw it, but signed up for Postcards and Trick R' Treat for my first EVER exchanges. So excited I can't wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 00:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must find this store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "MORE WALKING (AND TALKING) DEAD: PART 1" - A Bad Lip Reading of The Walking Dead Season 4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 21:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 19:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually cross the Lewis and Clark, take a left at 100, and take the river road through Grafton usually making Pierre Marquette the turn around point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 19:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can remember it like yesterday. Was listening to the scanner at the time they put a call out for a construction accident with person trapped. Next thing I know they disregarded the ambulance meaning he was already gone. Have to say Bob was one of a kind. Never got the chance to meet him but just by looking at what he has done you can see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 03:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where was this when I was in meat class in Culinary School? Would have saved me a ton of wrong test answers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 21:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope just saying he better look again because she's not only topless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 15:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Topless huh? Yeeeeah ok. Hey OP you see that area below the tan line? Yeah that's where you came out. Sweet dreams! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 22:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have had both and would take t-mobile over Sprint any day. Granted I did find some deadspots with T-Mobile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 15:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lived here all my life and have never heard this story so fill me in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 15:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only misdemeanors!?!? SMDH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 02:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the one I was thinking of but this works so much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 01:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need that Picard pic STAT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 23:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had two of "that guy" in my neighborhood. One moved away 2-3 months ago and he was the street drunk. Everyday his wife would leave for work and he'd go up get himself a bottle and get shitface wasted. Had to call the cops on him a couple times because he'd want to fight after getting drunk.

Other one still lives next door and is a good guy in all but he's out there. When he's outside his voice carries where I'm sure you can hear him blocks away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Find of 612 vintage video game boxes to go up for auction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 21:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 17:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR if this was already posted:

http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2014/09/20/quiet-neighborhood-shaken-by-small-plane-crash/15977361/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 16:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny part of this is you'd get the ticket and he'd drive away Scott free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 16:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's no different than what it is now. I mean someone can still raise a shitton of money, withdraw it, and go live it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 01:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 01:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would love to see these typed up and published. I'd buy on release day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 23:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically a box to hide something. Back in the day they used to have bootleg cars that had secret compartments to hold moonshine. That way if the cops were to stop ya they wouldn't find it. This box here though could have been in a house where if it was raided by the police nothing will be found. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 19:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a bootleggers box made to look like an old radio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 17:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember about 20 years ago when a local grocery chain added computer screens with gps to their carts. Now this was mid-90s so that was advanced for us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 05:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old Town Donuts?

Yeah the DD didn't last long at all. Went once and had such bad service I never went back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 04:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dave is that you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> T Graham Brown - Wine Into Water </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 03:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 00:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine happened earlier this year, and it doesn't sound like that big of a thing but it was to me. I connected with a girl I know on a personal level. Basically we sat up and talked all night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 19:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god this screams PsBattle material. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 15:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's scary about it? If you don't want the work done and know that it's BS just throw it away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 03:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I don't think it's low blood sugar because after I sleep I wake up feeling just fine, and plus I can still function when this happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 03:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it. You have anymore you could post? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is it when I get extremely tired my body starts to shake and I get nauseated? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 23:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 21:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need an AMA with your Aunt.

Edit: Just saw where one is being planned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 20:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pedobear Approves! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 19:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wood chipper and pig farm nuff said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kiwi Berry Packaging Logo-Generic to Fantastic (This man sure does love bumper stickers.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 15:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 22:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This great news calls for this: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ye8mB6VsUHw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 22:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got one in my wallet right now. Had to ax over the app along with a copy of my culinary school idea. If you're not in school they require a business card. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 22:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh let's present the evidence shall we: http://fox2now.com/2014/09/08/two-jefferson-county-construction-workers-describe-michael-brown-shooting/

"The two unidentified men, who were working for a Jefferson County construction company, watched Michael Brown die from half a football field away."

"The Fox 2 witness immediately wrote down what he saw.  He also drew a diagram showing him and his co-worker about 50 yards away."

Oh and here the unreliable witness kicker: "Both witnesses said they did not see the reported altercation at the police car, but looked up after hearing a shot or shots."

Also I've noticed that before the incident occurred your last post was 2 years ago but let this happen aka something that could build karma you're back and posting about it like crazy. All I can say to that is the bandwagon has left the station Bye Felicia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 20:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should cross post this in r/nottheonion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 20:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why post a link when you won't believe it. In a way you're just like me. What I mean is you believe what you believe is right and won't be turned any other way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 20:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do know that distance changed right? When it was first reported they said 50 yards away yet the next day it went down to 50 feet. Anyway I'm done talking about this because i got better shit to worry about than a black kid getting shot by a cop. It turns into the same old song and dance and the song keeps skipping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 15:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Explain to me how in the hell the construction workers saw what happened when they stated themselves they were a half a football field away and only looked up after hearing the first shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 15:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's Matt Foley's wife. She left the van down by the RIVER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 15:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a test tube holder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 15:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it took some of those 6 weeks or months to come forward. Enough time to make up something based on what the others are saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 01:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sauce? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 00:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This IS a jury looking at every piece of evidence laid out before them in order to consider an indictment or not. This is not a fly by not thing that is going to be done in one day just because they have 6 wow 6! eyewitnesses that are not all that reliable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 23:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is no where enough evidence to indict somebody because it is not reliable and not the only evidence they have. They have to look at the actual autopsy reports not only the one the family ordered which IMO is unreliable because the Dr. performing it didn't have the x-rays or the clothing. Also they have to look at the self defense claim thoroughly and make sure it was actually self defense which looks to be the case. Like has been said before unless Ofc. Wilson is hung by the balls none of the protesters are going to be happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 23:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loved your character in Waiting. Was that the role you tried out for to begin with or what they thought fit you best? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 23:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if that's enough evidence which it's not last time I checked toss everybody up and throw away the key cause I'm sure we've all done something where there were 6 and more eyewitnesses. It's why when I was going to school for Criminal Justice they taught me to separate the witnesses so they can't feed off of each other which seems to be what is happening here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 23:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah there might be 6 eyewitnesses BUT are they 6 reliable eyewitnesses? I could saw I was an eyewitness too by going by what others are saying. Doesn't necessarily mean that I was there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 19:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Special Agent Orach Red here with Special Agent Sun Daisy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 15:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comedy Forum in St. Charles still around or is that all Electric Cowboy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 03:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mainly depends on what area you're in. Since certain parts on St. Louis have unique delivery options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 03:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably going to come up with another sob story just that in this one the grandmother died and they want to spread the ashes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 00:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After reading the article and the comments here I just have to say this: The problem here in not McCullough it is the fact that the protestors want Ofc. Wilson hung by the balls to put it simply, and the protestors are feeling that with McCullough prosecuting the case he won't do that. I mean the Pope, Al Sharpton, Jesse Jackson, or Your own mother could be the prosecutor on this case and unless the balls are hung the people asking for McCullough's resignation still won't be happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 20:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chef here too and the only thing I'd use that for is decoration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 18:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see Wayne Brady skinned Blue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 16:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm saying with fall coming early we're going to get hit with winter early as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 01:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well no wonder it's hard  read and at the bottom where if people found what they wanted higher up they're not going down that far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World Series 87 Post Dispatch Press Plates (x-post from r/Cardinals) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 23:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World Series 87 Post Dispatch Press Plates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 23:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 22:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh the fat coconut eater. He has had some good matches in the past but the last year or two its been ehh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> T. Graham Brown - Which Way To Pray </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 15:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ricky Van Shelton - Keep it between the Lines (Official Video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 14:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 08:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LET HIM OUT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 03:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hooters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 03:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you find that at? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 01:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until you get rid of the people running that town i.e. the Mayor and Police Chief it's going turn into that saying You can polish a turd and it's still a turd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 19:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ditto. Birthday is a week from Wednesday and was thinking Fast Eddies for lunch but this place needs the business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 02:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give that server the middle finger from me for even taking that order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 00:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sauce? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 21:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not in the tread.
Not in the tread?
Not in the tread they said.
So brush your teeth and go to bed.
If your Mother find you, you'll end up dead.
Cause it's not in the tread they saaaaaid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 21:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh come on just roll with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Grandpa circa 1950s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 19:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Small Business Protest Planned For Ferguson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 01:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doomed TBM 900 Pilot Twice Asked for Lower Altitude </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 23:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Strait singing Boot Scootin' Boggie (HD) - Brooks and Dunn ACM Last Rodeo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 06:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TAK- I Am So Cool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 06:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Closing Up Shop After 95 Years: Yacovellis, RIP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 21:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The NWS has issued a HEAT ADVISORY for the City of St. Louis 9/4/14 from 1PM - 7PM. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 18:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ice Bucket Challenge video leads officers to wanted Omaha man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 06:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Burger King Worldwide Inc. in talks to acquire Tim Hortons Inc. | Mergers-Acquisitions content from Nation's Restaurant News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 21:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blake Shelton - Neon Light (Official Audio) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 03:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> St. Louis Area Sooner Fans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 19:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know of a bar here in St. Louis that'll be showing the PPV season opener? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
