<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5916</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 16:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you know it was a Brazil guy? Do you have his Steam profile?
If not, how can you prove it was not you who was hacking?
I'm not jumping to conclusions, just asking.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 15:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somehow... Players are still playing and don't complain.
Why did you come here? GO back and play FACEIT! Noone is forcing you to play matchmaking at Valve servers.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 15:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the way you talk, it seems like you don't mind cheating yourself.
Good luck on mining those bitcoins too... :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 12:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do bar pull ups and tricks mostly, when i go play CS:GO i can't get a single kill cause my arms get all twitchy/shaky.
I think taking a run before playing would be a better idea :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 12:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping for an eco ace... The title should be called "How to exploit a glitch to get an unfair advantage".
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 21:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait... There is no defuse animation..?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 17:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god, "Freeman was here" is a reference to Half-Life saga o.O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 21:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make the smoke mass rotate towards player, not it's camera.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 19:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could agree with you on that, however it still needs balance improvements as i keep finding the round outcomes unequal. I'm not talking player skill wise, I'm talking about rotation time it takes for CT's to come from A to B, CT's wouldn't be able to defuse in-time if they are on the other side of the map.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 11:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I firstly do the layout, then i make the spawns for a show. Every other part of the map is being made afterwards. (DEV textures, scaling, geometry, texturing, props, decals ETC).

Usually spawn is the first place you see when you start playing the map, so i wan't that place to be as impressive as possible.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 11:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But not THAT complex! :D
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 21:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I'm changing scale and layout :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 20:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, i didn't explain quite well. What i meant is, CS:GO is running on the newest Source engine version! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 19:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure thing, PM me. :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 19:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, that's why I'd love suggestions how to improve the layout. I will be removing some parts of the map, as well as bringing new ones.
Thank you for feedback! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 19:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CSGO is a brand new engine, don't worry, i won't make the map cluttered. Every mappers 1st priority is optimization, as it plays the biggest part in competitive! 
I will focus on bringing de_storm and de_vegas as soon as I'm done with de_torn. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 19:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If so, why? What do you think would make you wan't this map? Any suggestions are appreciated :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 15:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/3vBhZh7.png
Very early sneek peak... CT spawn is way shorter than on 1.6 due to ridiculous time it takes to get to the bombsites. Also, the spawn roof has been lowered unlike original Torn, as when jumping down it dealt 40 health of damage.

I would love suggestions coming, if anyone is willing to collaborate you can always PM me, as at the moment it's 1 man project. :)

Let me know if you'd like some more screenshots! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 14:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give it a try, here's a better layout -
http://www.counter-strike.pl/pliki/images/092001/CS2D_DE_TORN_SUB.jpeg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 11:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You managed to do it by playing with the most over-powered auto-sniper in the game. Against Silvers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you like to see de_torn in CS:GO, if so, what changes do you think would make the map more balanced? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 11:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 19:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need to do a fundraiser for a CS:GO tournament, maybe a petition? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 16:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's such a minor thing i didn't even knew this thing existed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 19:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you mate, i got 6 days left of my ban cause of this stuff.
WHERE'S THE FIX VALVE? It's been almost 2 days! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 17:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a bravo case model in Hammer, I'm so making this when i have free time :P Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 15:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did contact. I just want Valve to notice that this is happening not only to me, but a lot of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CSGO CRASHED, GOT COOLDOWN :/ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 14:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 19:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about we just have a classic 1.6 knife, with it's finger flip animations?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 15:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all about preference, some people like me would rather take careful but  deadly shots conserving ammo, instead of spamming bullets going for a kill.
I'm not saying p2k is bad, but USP-s iss just a bit more "accurate" choice for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 12:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, like wise man once said - Treat everyone like shit cause they'll still treat you like shit. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 21:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god, not another silo/storage/crate style map!
Also, where's the overview? I wan't to see the layout before downloading.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 21:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a DDOS, Valve servers are way more powerful than for a single person just to go and simply crash them.
It was a lag switch, and for those who don't know what it is - It's basically turning cable on and off, making server loose client packets.
To be simple, you can "simulate" lag to other people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 19:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how they keep fighting against VAC, and our job as community is to assist Valve fighting them back.
I think what's important for Valve is to be aware of such websites/forums, where they can keep track of new cheats coming.

The best way to reduce the amount of hackers is not to simply ban every cheater once they pop up, it's the core.
They should keep making VAC updates more regular when a new cheat comes out, so that it takes longer for them to flood.

It's an idea. I'm sure they are working very hard against cheaters already. OP, thanks for informing. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 18:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a way to fix it would be to place a clip brush where the bug occurs at Hammer.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 15:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm been learning Hammer a shit-ton recently. Does anybody wanna cooperate working on this? PM if you're interested. I'd love to work on something like this! :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 15:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the connector between two buildings, apparently they are too close as bombsites together. Maybe, make the parking building the bombsite? The round multi-stories one.
It would be hard to make it though.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 22:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Props are a bad way to hide maps flaws, i personally suggest focusing on geometrical brush-work and beauty of the map (lighting, look, theme) instead of trashing all over props.
Also, to start you gotta make these pics into a layout, hard part :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 17:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you downvote this, at least tell me why. Write your opinions in the comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 21:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fixed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smoke + Deagle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 21:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 18:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cpl_mill is de_mirage on CSGO if I'm correct.
EDIT: I'm mistaken, it's cpl_strike </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 14:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way too over-edited :/
Nice frags tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 14:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BOT Frank vs BOT Lester...
I can't image that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 12:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't wan't to make wallbang areas too powerful though, as in 1.6 you can pretty much wallbang anywhere you wan't and still pick a kill or two.

I will take your advices into consideration :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 17:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a VPN. Free ones aren't the best ones, but should be something to help against DDOS'ers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 16:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be replacing them. Don't worry :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 12:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't like the theme of Nuke and how it's CT side oriented, that is all. It is also because of Nostalgia, and some features which Valve removed; Such as ability to open doors by throwing a grenade at them, or crouching in vents.

Yes, I'm using 1.6 port as a bare-bone, although I'm slowly replacing the geometry to more detailed brush work. I wan't to keep 1.6 scale and features.

For more detailed answer, look at the post i made above.
EDIT: ImDose explained it the best, it's just for fun. Some people enjoy stuff like that. Like i do! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 12:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As you can see it's not an edit of Valve's Nuke, it's a complete 1.6 port.
All scale and layout is completely the same. Some players asked me to port the Nuke and make a detailed version of it. Instead of retexturing it, i also try to add geometry additions to it, prop models and everything else.
 
There are a few good reasons why i would wan't to remake Nuke, first of all - There's way too much "Competitive Edits" for Valves Nuke. You can't keep bashing it. It's been released, and every slight change makes a huge difference (Like the outside entrance by Volcano's edit, it added a whole new tactic to the game. You would have to change layout drastically. That's why, i wan't to make my version of Nuke. It would feel close, but it wouldn't be the same map.

Also, it's because of nostalgia. I think a lot of 1.6 veterans can relate.

That's why I'm asking what people wan't, because if i find this as a good opportunity to expand the map and i will gladly do it if people wan't so. (Add new routes, choke points, make it different.)

I also think that the original theme for the map was a lot more realistic. (Blowing up nuclear missiles in deserted base)
At the moment de_nuke is basically a de_plant/de_nuclear. I'm talking about design.

Lastly. Pro players even though they love Volcano's edit, they didn't appreciate that you were able to run in vents. I find it silly. In 1.6 version you would get slowed down when running around at upper A, in CSGO you get a lot more space which gives a way more tactical position to CT's on an already CT sided map. You could simply run over above the squeeky door and the whole "A strat" would be ruined.
At the moment i wan't to limit space at A for CT's, but still keep the option to shoot at squeeky/house/outside.
Even adding a ramp from house to heaven would make a RADICAL difference.
Also, on 1.6 you were able to fake open doors by throwing a grenade at them, in CSGO you can't do that in Nuke anymore. I'd love to bring that back too.

Anyways, i could remake the whole map, and i could keep it as a detailed port/remake of 1.6. Depends on how people wan't it.


I would really appreciate constructive criticism, and i really favor everyone's opinions/thoughts. I note them, and i will try to reply to questions.

Thanks for asking. 

P.S - Train has already gotten an 1.6 edit by Volcano, take a look -
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=epMBBbcxVL8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 11:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you can flashbang boost there? 
Valve said they removed flashbang boosting but it still seems to work partially :D 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> De_nuke remake. Let me know what people think/want. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 11:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 15:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lester OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 17:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine the way to fix it, would be to make smoke particles rotate at player rather than camera. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 22:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @codename_rondo Exactly my point. If i was the guy to get trapped I'd kindly ask them, or just stay in the room till they get killed by someone. They wouldn't stand there all round anyways.

Team-killing is not always a way out, especially considering 7 day ban :P

Also, in the video he even tried to shoot one of the guys through the wall, which looks very obvious to me. He was rude, and he got what he deserved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 21:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He deserved the knife :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 21:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you actually watch the video? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 17:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh... I think you've got very high FPS, lock it down to under 500 (100 is enough for me.)

fps_max 200


I'm not too sure about this, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 22:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you look very closely you can see that it's fake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 16:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're very right at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 16:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch the comment i made above, i didn't say anything about ranks being associated with unboxing knifes :P

About the Smurfing, i know you can't find out if someone is playing on friends account/computer, but you can find out if someone has alternate accounts on IP. It wouldn't solve the problem, but it would reduce it drastically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 16:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me explain it a bit, i didn't articulate what i meant properly :D

What i mean is; Some people get lucky with getting a knife from a case, maybe even a few (Which is what i doubt). If you sell a knife on Steam Market, you can pretty much buy as much CSGO gift codes for alternate accounts as you wan't.
Ignoring that, you can still buy CS:GO for VERY cheap when it's on sale.

@BrokenStool You don't know what i meant. I didn't even say anything about trading...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smurfs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 21:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Valve needs to do something about smurfing, it's getting out of control lately.
Recently i had a match. It ruined my whole day, i didn't even wan't to play competitive anymore. I had a high ping, it is my internet provider problem, even though that wasn't the cause. Pretty much the whole enemy team were a bunch of smurfs, one Global Elite and a few Master Guardians on Silver accounts. They weren't those nice smurfs who tell you what you do wrong.. Give advices, help out in situations and do it for a purpose of making stuff better. No... They we're making fun of us, purposefully ruining the match.

Here's a few ways Valve could reduce the problem -
- Make a limit of Steam accounts per-IP.
- Add option to Solo Queue on matchmaking, so you don't get pit against a pre-made team. (While your own is random picked)
- For friendly smurfs, add a new feature - Coaching. Something like TF2.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 18:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am i the only one here that thinks this is kind of creepy? o.o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 18:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, is SweetFX VAC safe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 21:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friberg, so majestic :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 11:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean, this?
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w0CoRJb82SQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 19:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It happens to me too. Hope Volvo fixes that.

But there are still people who wait untill the last second, those, are the annoying ones :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People not pressing "Accept" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 18:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know those moments when the "accept" button appears, and someone doesn't press the accept button or wait till the last second? I really hate those people.
Hope i'm not off-topic.

What do you guys think? (It's specifically if your not playing with a team but with random people) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 13:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please, no... Don't do mistakes that COD montage makers do. Especially that shockwave effect when shooting. It's nice tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 21:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting bug... Not useful though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 21:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, as a mapper i can say this is possible to have certain objects to have different prop locations at every round/match. I even saw a tutorial on how to do it on 1.6 Worldcraft.


It needs logic controllers (Only mappers will understand).

In short, yes, it's possible. But very limited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
