<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5681</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fall Out Boy - Dance, Dance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 20:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gettin ready for bed. Reddit, meet Adali! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 03:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 22:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, no business, no moneys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 22:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plot twist, it IS your dad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 20:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, he is really getting downvoted to hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 19:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I work in the restaurant industry, tonight is going to be terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 19:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Up next- tornado fries! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 19:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> by Jack Handy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 19:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely common on boardwalks as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 17:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only available runningbacks that weren't kept (1st rounders anyway) are Jamaal Charles and Shady McCoy. I'm leaning towards Shady at this point, and grabbing a bigger name reciever with my second pick...thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 21:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh still don't know yet. A Pete, Aaron Rodgers, (Aaron Hernandez lol) the more I think about it, the more I think Megatron might be taken. What else could I go for? I was thinking maybe CJ Spiller, but like I said, not sure who is being kept. Our commissioner is kind of lackluster this year with relaying information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a PPR draft coming up. I have the 5th pick, Matt Ryan was my keeper, where should I go? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 17:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The kicker is that the guy with the very first pick has a hard-on for Tom Brady and is almost GUARANTEED to pick him. I'm looking at Megatron or Shady McCoy. Any thoughts?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 02:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! It looks like when I play Kerbal Space Program drunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 16:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who are you talking to that regards this game as the best ever, Rockstar employees? I have never heard of anyone calling GTA IV as the best game ever, or anything remotely close. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-GF meme has a name!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 15:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-31 03:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8 years ago, I used to sell weed. One day, me and Momma Dukes got into a bit of a tif, (I was 17 at the time, so the argument was pointless) and all of the sudden she says, "Ya know what?" and proceeds to walk up into my room, a few seconds later, comes walking down the steps with a quarter pound of weed I had in my room. She throws it at me and tells me, "There's no way you are smoking all of that bud!" (My Mom, 48 at the time, referring to my weed as "bud," was shocking enough, on top of the fact she found it) She then tells me she already called the cops..I walk upstairs and put the weed right back where I had it. I come back downstairs and my Mom let me sit in absolute fearfor about 10 minutes until she told me to get rid of it, I was a moron for doing it, and she didn't call the cops. That ten minutes, I thought I was fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-28 18:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friends daughter found out this way... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 08:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 08:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes sense, maybe I should devote more of my time to wasting it on Reddit... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 08:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heard that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-23 08:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember AOL? Young redditors don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-23 08:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It took me FIVE YEARS to get this song out of my head, ten years later, IT HAPPENS AGAIN!! DAMN YOU TO HELL, here's the most nostalgic upvote I've given so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-22 04:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was expecting a math equation. Still, I'll take some boobs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-22 04:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome good sir. Good day to you. I SAID GOOD DAY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-22 04:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes I wonder...do some of these people READ comments before making a comment that is almost exactly like one made a few comments before...then I think...this is Reddit...so no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 05:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would I like my BLACK coffee? In a cup? Yea, don't just splash it on my face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 16:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After reading everything, watching the video..I've come to realize that this guy is a total dickbag, and what he did was absolute garbage. I have no endearing things to say towards him, and I certainly hope he gets all 4 years in jail. What you did was help our government further their fight towards "owning," the internet entirely. Thanks asshole. (Oh, the people with the Guy Fawkes mask at his press conference, 100% serious? Wow.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-15 02:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't the booze...it was a front wheel drive slowbalt ss that caused this :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 06:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're* 2 hours later, and we are just catching this? Somebody must pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 06:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you reading them all right before bed too? Terrible idea...but I can't stop.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 18:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MCA from the Beastie Boys...only time I've ever been upset over a celebrity death. Guy was awesome, Beastie Boys are no more. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 06:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you did there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 06:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Social networking... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 06:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have given up social networking for lent...I mainly use twitter and facebook, my girlfriend gave up pinterest and fb, as that is the only social networking she uses...we are still debating, should I have to give up Reddit too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 06:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the smile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 06:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worked right out of high school as a cabinetmaker for 5 years. Realizing how depressed everyone in my trade was due to money and general unhappiness, I looked at myself and realized...time to face facts, I'm gonna encounter some shitty times if I go to school and work a shitty job...I'm now enrolled in school, on par for President's list, and loving every minute of it. (I am in school for computer networking) Quite a change, best decision I've ever made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 19:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't upvote this enough. I believe this is a dream that all well-qualified, yet underpaid workers have. Good luck at your next job, hopefully better pay with less a-holes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 04:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such an awesome AMA! Never heard about  you before til now!! Cool to see you do a straight up, quick response AMA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 23:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you know that producing edm was or you? What was the thing that just made it all click for you? Also, Philly soon? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-16 20:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sexy...but the wrong place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-09 17:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys are just plain cold with all these jokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-09 16:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm down voting because, why are we still talking about Kazaam?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-09 16:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess he is skipping all of the valuable advice from this thread and coming right from your intelligent idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
