<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8998</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 02:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Life expectancy is determined by a variety of factors. If we look at data from info like the CIA Fact book or other popular sources we aim to correlate the expectancy with other variables like GDP, individual household income, growth rate, etc. and surely will come to find that life expectancy surely has increased when looking the basic models of the demographic transitions. Moreover, although we spend a lot of money on health care; health care is still incredibly expensive in the United States. Medicine and other procedures pick the personal pocket more commonly than the pocket of another person in Europe. It's expensive to the person. So we spend a lot of money on health care in order to make it accessible to everyone; however, it is very expensive to the individual and the majority of the wealth in the US goes to the top 1% leaving a reasonable chunk of the population struggling to afford unreasonable medical expenses. In addition, as seen in other comments, our daily habits have a great influence on life expectancy in addition to other factors you can correlate. Ultimately though, we still have a pretty high life expectancy and in terms of population; it's mind blowing to ponder how drastically the world will change if life expectancy increased by let's say... another ten years. All of this is simply crazy. By 2100, the worlds population is predicted to reach 11 billion people. Just some food for thought
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists identify new drug that slows the ageing process and could dramatically increase our life expectancy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 01:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your Brain on LSD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 18:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers Image Wave-Particle Duality Light For The First Time Ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 02:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 05:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of everything that's happening in the world this "problem" receives the largest response. Well god damn. Maybe this is the solution to world hunger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 23:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's "funny" how some will say that the constitution does not explicitly promise our right to privacy. It's even "funnier" that the constitution doesn't promise the rights it explicitly states.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 18:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how all of these comments will change over a period of 100 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
