<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1032</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-24 13:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was awesome! I'm really digging this subreddit!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-24 13:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the post. I really enjoyed the song. Especially the whole "rain stick" sound in the background. One of those few bands that get to me on the first listen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-04 00:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using reddit on my phone, sitting on my rolling chair. I clicked on the link and it was taking a while to load. I moved the phone closer to my face to see it better and it starts screaming at me! All this images start blaring at me! I pushed away from the image but forgot it was on my phone, which was still in my hand; I couldn't get away T_T
I panicked and struggled to press the Home button. 
It's been awhile since I've been scared shitless, I praise you for this terrifying find! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-01 14:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah hah! That blank stare with that smile gets me everytime!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 09:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took a girl to the shooting range for a first date. It was for Valentines and my date really enjoyed doing something she's never done before. We had time to talk on the way to the shooting range but once there talking is minimal. I think the adrenaline from shooting a gun the first time really helps out during dates in general.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 16:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very nice! I like the expressions on em! You should make more ^_^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 14:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, thank you. Currently using it as my phone wallpaper. Didju make this by any chance?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
