<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3651</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 20:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll never begin to understand the people in those comments. Even the direst homophobes shouldn't want a portion of the population not to get healthcare. It boggles the mind how people can hate so strongly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Demetre Daskalakis is a Harvard-educated physician who traded the laboratory for the nightclub, in an effort to bring public health services to NYC's underserved gay population. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 15:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First complete map of Mars since 1987, released by the USGS. The extensive, detailed map shows that ancient rock exists in many more locations on the Martian surface than previously thought. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 21:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 17:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We believe the HBP is not a well conceived or implemented project and that it is ill suited to be the centerpiece of European neuroscience.

Ouch. Wonder how that'll affect the US Brain Project...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alcohol is responsible for 10% of deaths among 20-65 year olds in the U.S., according to a recent CDC study. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 15:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 22:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...in 2012. Love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 16:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scumbag BICEP team. Getting us all excited over nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 15:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's amazing that these robots are realistic and detailed enough to "fool" real animals. In a way, this is also a victory for materials science...   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another victory for the Standard Model of Physics. A study published today in Nature Physics further confirms the existence of the Higgs Boson, by proving for the first time that it breaks down into fermions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 20:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 17:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL: Curiosity was in fact the first rover to ever die from cancer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 17:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, I thought all cosmic radiation was EM radiation. This is going to suck for Mars One.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 16:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the original scientific paper: http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24724938 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The First Family Tree of Beer: A Team of Geneticists is creating the Beer Yeast Genome Project, which will allow researchers to breed new brewing yeasts in spite consumer resistance to GMOs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 16:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate Change may bring rising tides and storm surges to New York City. This architect re-imagines the city with permeable streets and barrier islands. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 19:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Computer Program Could Help Solve Arson Cases. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 14:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that some Sunscreens are Flammable, so every now and then someone applies sunscreen, only to burst into flames when they get too close to the BBQ. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 14:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HIV is slowly adapting to its human hosts, according to a study published yesterday in PLOS Genetics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 14:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study of the physics behind fruit flies' sharp, banked turns could change how we build flying micro-robots, according to a paper published today in Science. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 16:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that mosquitoes prefer certain blood types, and people with the "O" blood type are more likely to get bitten. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 20:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
