<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6084</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The galaxy's core is about to explode. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 20:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in 2006, teenage fans of a popular Portuguese soap opera began experiencing the physical symptoms of a fictional disease that was introduced to the characters on the show. The "outbreak" spread to over 300 people. It is considered an example of mass hysteria. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 18:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-16 22:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, be careful. Remember when reddit successfully identified 10 of the 2 Boston bombers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that during the Cold War, the US Air Force developed a top secret plan to detonate a nuclear bomb on the Moon, as a show of force. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-16 20:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-15 20:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not lovin' it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in 2004, a 19m tall sculpture of Jesus, named "King of Kings", was erected in Ohio. It was the 7th tallest statue in the United States at the time. In 2010, it was struck by lightning and was destroyed by the subsequent fire. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-15 09:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 20:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a Dos Equis commercial here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 20:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will pop right in with this submission to show how hard that is. 50,000 words ~~would be~~ is so tough to do! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 19:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's right. OP should from now on proof his words prior to posting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 18:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a 50,000 *word* book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the common or button mushroom is simply the juvenile form of a Portobello mushroom. They are the same species. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 17:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 20:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's the red line for this kind of stuff? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 19:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, a good number of those Athenians were of the other persuasion, I hear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 18:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article, TIL also that "toad" was a common nickname given to prostitutes and courtesans at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The human finger can discriminate between surfaces patterned with ridges as small as 13 nanometres in height. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 16:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greece unemployment rate at a record 27.9 percent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 16:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a hurricane doesn't form in the next 10 days, 2013 will have the slowest start to a hurricane season in recorded history. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 15:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the concept of an atomic bomb was introduced in a novel by HG Wells in 1914. Eighteen years after its publication, the physicist Le Szilrd read the book, was inspired, and two years later filed a patent on the idea of a neutron chain reaction, leading eventually to atomic bomb technology. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 07:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do movers expect a tip? If so, how much? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 03:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is in North America, btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 23:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Relevant.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Higher_education_bubble) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2013 in running for the latest first Atlantic hurricane on record. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 19:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some 2-Year degrees pay off better than BAs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 19:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that during the 1983 US Open, an errant serve from Stefan Edberg struck a linesman directly on the groin. The linesman fell backward, striking his head, and fell unconscious. He died in hospital five days later. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 21:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that it is estimated that the number of rats in New York City may be as high as 32 million. That's four rats per person. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 19:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 06:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently the model for Chloe wasn't so happy in Paris."She, after throwing a party for friends, boiled a soup of poisonous matches, drank the concoction and died." The reason for her suicide is thought to be unrequited love. 

RIP Chloe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 06:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disgraceful yes, but I can report that the painting is doing just fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that one of the most famous pubs in Australia is the Young and Jackson Hotel. It is famous for its portrait "Chloe" of a very nude 19 years old girl, which hangs over one of the bars. It was considered scandalous at the time, but still hangs there. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 05:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the actor known as Moriarty in Star Trek TNG and the butler in The Nanny is actually from Arkansas, he doesn't have an english accent at all but is one of the best ever at doing one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 05:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in some places in the world, it is illegal to die. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 04:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Puccini's 1910 opera, "La fanciulla del West", is set in the American old west, featuring a bandit, a sherriff and a "bartender at the Polka saloon". Some consider it the first "Spaghetti Western". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 17:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ring functions like a smart card for public transit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 21:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that when the Space Shuttle Challenger exploded in 1986, this joke spread quickly around the world: "Q: What does NASA stand for? A: Need Another Seven Astronauts." This was before widespread use of the internet. The joke spread literally by word of mouth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 22:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 06:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not me for sure, I may have assumed that people knew that the internet existed prior the the world wide web, and had its own stuff like chat, usenet, and muds/mushs. Sorry, a bad assumption. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that before the world wibe web, internet users had multiplayer role-playing online games called MUSHs. This stands for Multi User Shared Hallucination. These games were played via the unix command line, i.e via text, no graphics, but were enourmosly popular amongst college students at the time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 05:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-21 07:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if serious... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in 2010, a couple from Italy thought they had booked air tickets to Sydney, Australia, but ended up in the small town of Sydney, NS, Canada. My first reaction was fear" said one of the Italian tourists, when learning that he was in Canada, not Australia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-21 06:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 05:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry! Time heals all wounds. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 05:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit... has anyone ever beaten the game, all of it? Just curious.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that one of the most difficult video games ever is Ghosts 'n Goblins, in arcades in the 80s. Even if you managed to beat it, it was revealed that the boss had laid you a trap and that you had to beat the whole game again at a higher level of diffuclty. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 04:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that crack pipes are sold as fake flowers in a glass tube at convenience stores. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 09:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 02:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish this wasn't buried. Well said, pacman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 01:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recommend [this article](http://www.theaustralian.com.au/news/features/fearless-matriarch-of-resistance/story-e6frg6z6-1226111207166). VERY late in life (age 88 by my reckoning) she said she wanted to die in London and moved to an expensive hotel in Piccadilly. She ran out of money, though, but the hotel didn't want to kick her out. Prince Charles started footing the bill. She had her own stool at the hotel bar, where during her nineties she would have at least 6 gin and tonics a day. Good for her, I say. She died in 2011 at age 98. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 22:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I don't wanna talk to a scientist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that during WWII, the Gestapo's most wanted person was New Zealand born Allied agent Nancy Wake. Among her numerous exploits, she killed an SS soldier with her bare hands, to prevent him from raising the alarm during an undercover raid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 21:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mass Effect clothing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 07:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 16:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know someone who tried to eat a blackberry once. It had to be surgically removed and its battery had gone dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that one of the most misspelled words in the English language is "misspell". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 16:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China zoo under fire for disguising dog as lion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 14:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 21:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ghosts 'n Goblins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syrian refugee camp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 18:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 12:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not this by any chance?

http://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/1j2cqb/til_that_in_ancient_rome_one_of_the_most_common/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 12:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that was quick! Glad to share your link. I'm very interested in what they cooked up in antiquity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 11:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's something very very strange in these woods, Cooper.

Oh, ewoks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that if you ever want to eat a flamingo, there is a recipe for it from the ancient Roman celebrity chef Apicius. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 11:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Accident map of Montreal! This map illustrates the relative danger of intersections in Montreal, based on data from police reports. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 02:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 00:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Higher_education_bubble </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man finds a pair of trousers inside a tree. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-27 13:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-27 06:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh Perth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the gravestone of ACDC's first frontman, Bon Scott, has been stolen. It's not the only time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-27 06:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-26 18:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should call it the Colosseam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in ancient Rome, one of the most common cooking ingredients was called "laser", from the silphium plant. It does not exist today: it was so delicious that it was harvested to extinction from its natural habitat in what is now Libya. We think that it probably tasted something like garlic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-26 02:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 02:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm very curious as to why cycling isn't included as a most common mode of transport category. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New interactive map of Montreal filled with census data. It's a major timewaster! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 22:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Bashar al-Assad, Queen Elizabeth II and Che Guevara have something in common: They all recieved the "Order of the Southern Cross". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 05:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Brazilians' enthusiasm for the internet led to the decline of fotolog.net and google's now sort of defunct orkut.net. There were so many Brazilians on these sites that they stifled anyone else's contributions. It's called the "Brazilian internet phenomenon". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 07:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 07:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a gut feeling that this field is just in its infancy, especially with the decreasing cost and increasing usefulness of metagenomic studies of the microbial flora within animals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 20:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently he wants to build the first one between San Francisco and LA. The trip would take 30 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 21:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the original press release from the Edmonton Police:

http://www.edmontonpolice.ca/News/MediaReleases/markmarekcharges.aspx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 20:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the most underrated games of the last couple of years, was Sleeping Dogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 07:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The original link contains this sentence:

"In a joint sale for US$40 million, Abbott sold their rights to Desoxyn and Tranxene to Ovation Pharma."

"Ovation Pharma" links to a page to their website and from there directly to the link I just posted, which shows undeniably that methamphetamine is sold by that company. Unless you think we need to be held hands around the internet, don't insult our intelligence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 06:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.lundbeck.com/us/products/cns-products/desoxyn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that methamphetamine is manufactured legally in the United States by Ovation pharmaceuticals and is sold under the brand name Desoxyn. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 06:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 05:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a real tragedy. I hope we can find some way of preserving magnetic tapes. There must be so much out there to preserve but the high throughput means of doing so escapes me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the first 1 million dollar budget movie in America (1916) also featured the first full female nudity in a mainstram film. It was a commercial success, but no copies of it exist. It is a lost movie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 05:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 17:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the working language or languages there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 05:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here's an amazing video of a very brief encounter with these people...

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OaPYwlXOTzQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the Sentinalese people have lived on an isolated island in the Indian Ocean for an estimated 60,000 years. They reject all contact with outsiders and are the last group of people who have had virtually no contact with the modern world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 04:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
