<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9821</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 03:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ask that because a verb is defined as an action or a state of being....... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 03:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use it in a sentence where it yeilds it in form to be an action.





Morals evolving renders them meaningless? Religion has changed does it render that meaningless? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 03:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a religous belief </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 03:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it is not a religous belief  religous attitude or  religous practice. Again where are you getting your conclusion from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 03:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe this post is not for you since you cease to make an assumption. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 03:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where does it say religion is the representation of moral development?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 03:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not looking for years of teaching as religion is interpretive. Im simply asking how you interpret it and how adam and eve fit in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 03:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats contradictory, if the bible is not a moral guide book as you say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worship is giving worth to something, in verb or noun form. Giving or practicing giving worth to something is not an action.



In verb form, the mayans built a temple to worship the gods. There is no action in worship of the gods, building the temple is an action.




Morals evolve as society and human intelligence does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohh, didnt know that, thats pretty cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does he direct that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> didnt adam and eve get banished from eden? How does this happen if evolution took place on earth not eden? Im just asking how this fits together and how its woven into your beliefs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. In an evolved society with evolved humans and an evolved moral system killing others for pleasure isnt the path to least resistance,ie the path to least suffering.




Isnt what you are referring to exactly what happens in religous text? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are arguing morals come from religion, the question is extremely relevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So then morals do not come from religion, if they come from God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the second one but you did edit the 1st one after i commented </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where? Link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh? I dont understand that last post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? If we evolved on earth though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you read my post? Morality evolves, ie the choices being right or wrong, as human intelligence and society evolve.



Again, worship is not an action so.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is about as well played, and epic a villian can get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didnt see anything in your link about them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might work for you but the question is based on your choice, if you cant make one, thats perfectly fine, but again the topic at hand is not for you.




The point is i have questions as to which you pick to help me understand, a non choice doesnt help me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite character from a Martin Scorcese film? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good, bad, main, supporting, etc. He has some of the most memeroable movies in film history, out of his films who was your favorite creation? and why?




I have to say Bill the butcher is my fav </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Np, fair enough. But where does adam and eve come into play? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It matters in the sense of are we talking about primitive or evolved morality? Are we talking about killing for pleasure or self defense? If you have followed my defining terms all this matters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Np </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is not an action that is a product of belief, no action involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me rephase, i think you should read the description before you comment, as the question has to do with either or, not neither. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did the fall happen if we evolved on earth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really, you make no sense. But i will look for answers elsewhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didnt answer it in regard to an evolution or creationist view



God creates in both which do you believe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Religous attidudes is an attitude of a belief in God and or worship. Thats a standard defintion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where does your definition come from? You just made it up? Then yes it is a problem to define things personally and expect the rest of the world to change their definition </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bible does say where sin came into play, hinting at its existence in the garden of eden. But i assume from your comments you dont take it literally.




Just curious, do you ever lend thought to where sin started, or is it a non issue for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not implyin you do or i know everything, but depending on your interpretation of evolution or creationism how does adam and eve fit your beliefs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You see how this, your pov, is a bit confusing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You believe in creationism as in the world is 6000 years old, or evolutionary creatism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats the definition </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you get a definition religion is moral development? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its like a deist who believes in god but doesnt worship, he has no religion.




If you are trying to imply natural religion, that is hardly a religion, and not the sense i mean it in as can be explained in my description and comments, and is really just a technicality that has nothing to do with this topic
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Religion hints at a god and or some form of worship. I dont worship natural laws or reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is not what religion is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course it matters an answer would prove that morals do come from religion. If you cant answer it proves morals do not come from religion. Its a simple question really, that i pose to you again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont see how what your saying other than religion is different from mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No you can be agnostic and teach your children reason and natural laws.



If thats the case my question should be revelant, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats exactly what im saying. You are breaking down morality to its primitive form before reason is truly developed. So primitive moralityy is based mainly off of the natural order of things. As reason evolves, the natural laws dont, so does our morality.



What you are saying im saying but it seemed like you are trying to place an evolved reasoning into primitive morality. When i ellude to morality evolving it can only be one of the two elements as natural laws dont change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does adam and eve fit in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Morality can be taught in other ways? Then we have no issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So animals ceased to sin before humans were created? Why wouldnt satan bring sin to the animals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no option in surviving, it can be neither good or bad. Its the only option, if you are not surving you are dead, no option.




Its the way you choose to survive which becomes right and wrong. Here you are presented with options. The right and wrong ways to survive are shaped over time through human intelligence and evolving society.




If morals dont come from religion where are you saying they come from? Just curious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats the topic at hand lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you name a moral act a believer can do a non believer cant?




If morals come from religion, there should be an act a person who doesnt learn religion(morals) cant do a religous can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats what im after. If sin predates adam and eve how does this story fit into your religous views?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, and your saying original sin didnt start with adam and eve as the bible says, sin existed since animals have? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then back to my first question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When was that distintcion made between how we sin and a dog does is basically what im after? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a nessacary part of living, as natures laws teach us the path of least resistance. It is neither good or bad, the options you take to complete these nessacary survival steps become good and evil.




I have answered this question if you kindly look through the thread before you pose existing questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to be more specific. Self defense, etc




Can you name an action a believer can do a non believer cant? If a non believer is not taught morals though religion there should be an action a person who is taught religion can do a non taught person cant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can animals sin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if adam and eve didnt exist neither did the serpent amoung them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does that work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My question is how does adam and eve fit in? If we evolved from animals and animals cant sin, where did original sin come from and how does adam and eve fit in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok but that they were without sin at first that gives way to an orignal sin at some point.




If we evolved from animals where did we get the ability to sin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its neither good or bad its a way of life, its a nessacary part of surviving. There is no option, you eat because you are hungry. Good and bad can only come from options. The way you choose to survive becomes good and bad.




Are you avoiding my question? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought adam and eve where without sin. There choosing becoming original sin. If you believe in evolution where did this start? Do animals sin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The meaning of morality is the action of meeting your nessacary needs. Thats morality. Good morals are those that cause least suffering. Bad morals are those that cause most suffering.




As we evolve and start living together, ie society, the good and bad evolve and consquently become more clearly defined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay that does make sense. Its quite an interesting concept, thanks for your replies and bringing this to my attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As i attempt to answer your questions only fair to attempt mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont understand the question in context to my answers. It has that meaning, the system you defined it as is created due to avoiding needless suffering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im trying to understand, and i will investigate further, its quite interesting.




Thinking as a religous person, if God has set a moral guideline how does that become individually subjective? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No morality has meaning as we evolve it becomes more clear, and certain actions become unnacceptable in a society.




The morals of a caveman would be differnt of a man living in an evolved society. Again as we grow and our society evolves so does morality.



Name an action a believer can do a non believer cant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No a non believer is not taught morals ftom religion, so there must be an act a person who is taught through religion can do that someone who isnt cant do. I ask it again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an interesting concept. Can you elaborate further? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where does the fall come into place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your first half of post is nonsensical.





To name an action is exactly the point of the post, if you cant name an action it becomes clear morals are not taught by religion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its part of being an animal. You are hungry you eat its a nessicity. As you take paths to how you eat, you are presented with options. The options that will lead to less suffering become good and vice versa. As humans grow and societies evolve these actions become evolved morally, with the actions to feed these nessacary needs it becomes clear what is right and wrong as society takes form.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and that moral system is derived from avoiding suffering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Np </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Killing life doesnt apply to living life. Survival is an instinct, trying to survive without suffering completely is also an instinct. When you are hungry you eat to avoid starving.



If god is moral explain the flood, the promotion of human sacrifice, slavery,and all the other immoral acts commited in the bible? 



Name a moral act a believer can do a non believer cant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea, im assuming this is aimed at someone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good and bad are derived from the instinct of avoiding suffering. As humans grow and socities evolve right and wrong are defined more clearly.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Name a moral action a believer can do a non believer cant.




IF morals are taught through religion, there should be an action a person never taught religion (morals), shouldnt be able to do a religious can </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Morals do not come from religion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's quite unreasonable to assume morals come from religion, even a Christian reading the bible can tell the immoral things that are happening throughout the bible. It can't be the grounds of morality, if itself isn't grounded. 



Simply have to name a moral action a believer can do that a non believer could not do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you are a Christian and believe in evolution where does original sin come from? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are not a creationist and believe evolution, how does Adam and Eve fit into your religion. If the Adam and Eve story is for interpretation not to be taken literally then where does original sin come from? 



If you believe in creationism and Adam and Eve story literally, how does this fit together in your religious understanding of the two? 



EDIT the point of this post is not to Offend but an attempt to understand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone read "A history of knowledge" by Charles Van Doren? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 22:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it worth reading? What did you think of it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: The invasion of Iraq was the right thing to do. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 00:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to start by I believe we made horrible mistakes once we entered Iraq. The biggest being the dissolution of the Iraq army and the laws that were passed to essentially keep them out, there were many many more but this is the biggest.



The invasion of Iraq was a good thing in these ways. Sadaam was a true representation of evil. All of his evils need not be explained one by one, but I think it's universally held he was evil and poison to the country he was ruling.



 As far as WMD, bush had conflicting reports as to whether they were there or not. Even if the reports leaned in the favor he did not presently own, there was evidence he had been trying to obtain WMD. Should we wait till he had obtained such to invade where he would surely use his obtained WMD in war? He also has the history of using WMD in war. He also stated in his trial, he did give the illusion to having WMD because he was worried if he didn't and it was known Iran would invade. He also I believe in 1998, not sure this exact year, refused to cooperate with having people come into the country to examine if he had WMD or not something he agreed to do in the early 90's.



He was also giving diplomatic immunity to terrorist and war criminals. He might not have had direct ties to bin laden but was aiding other terrorist and war criminals in other ways. The war on terror was not just about bin laden but to all terrorist organizations. 




To summarize, He wAs a terrible person to be in power, giving the illusion he had WMD by his own admission and history of being willing to use such, and aiding terrorist and war criminals. This was a good thing to strip him of his power. With that said we made many mistakes after the invasion. As far as setting up the governing body, dissolving the iraq army,etc. but as far as the decision to invade it was the right thing to do, and it lessened the places terror could operate in that part of the world. Also showing USA would not tolerate these many threats, not one or two, as other leaders have done,  but the many violations sadaam has committed will not be tolerated. Change my views

_____

 *Hello, users of CMV! This is a footnote from your moderators. We'd just like to remind you of a couple of things. Firstly, please remember to* ***[read through our rules](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/rules)***. *If you see a comment that has broken one, it is more effective to report it than downvote it. Speaking of which,* ***[downvotes don't change views](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/guidelines#wiki_upvoting.2Fdownvoting)****! If you are thinking about submitting a CMV yourself, please have a look through our* ***[popular topics wiki](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/populartopics)*** *first. Any questions or concerns? Feel free to* ***[message us](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=/r/changemyview)***. *Happy CMVing!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV:The things science cannot explain is not a reasonable place to put God. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 09:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a former catholic and no longer believe in God. The argument I hear for proof of god is mainly in the things science can't explain. Something couldn't have come from nothing, dark matter, intelligent design, etc. This is nonsensical.



You are essentially issuing in the same behavior ancient civilizations did. They could not understand at the time the weather, the sun, the cosmos, etc so it had to be God. All of the scriptures are written by people who had no such knowledge of the things They claimed to be God, and their lack of knowledge bleeds through as science unlocks more and more.




Now this is not to say God exists or does not exist. This is not my debate but my debate is where people are putting God. I think it quite possible to believe in God and also believe that science will shed light on the places it is the dark. Hence this post. To me is not reasonable in a world where people don't believe in God,or who believe in a different God, that putting on a label on the unexplainable is God. It is logical to put your faith, so to speak, in that science will explain these things in time, and that your belief in God belongs else where.



Now I also want to clarify to do the the things my debate touches on is not wrong, or immoral, it is simply unreasonable, not logical. I know there are many things that can give credence to your personal experiences and the deep thing inside most people there is more to this world than us. And that the proof of God is not a thing that can be measured in scientific terms. But I disagree that the universe, or multiverse, and all it's contents cannot be explained by science, and it's not logical to put god here. Change my views

_____

 *Hello, users of CMV! This is a footnote from your moderators. We'd just like to remind you of a couple of things. Firstly, please remember to* ***[read through our rules](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/rules)***. *If you see a comment that has broken one, it is more effective to report it than downvote it. Speaking of which,* ***[downvotes don't change views](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/guidelines#wiki_upvoting.2Fdownvoting)****! If you are thinking about submitting a CMV yourself, please have a look through our* ***[popular topics wiki](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/populartopics)*** *first. Any questions or concerns? Feel free to* ***[message us](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=/r/changemyview)***. *Happy CMVing!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:How can anyone trust truly trust their stockbroker? What proof is there and how can the Jordan belforts' of the world get around such? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 07:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: The Shining(movie) does a poor representation of the hotels true power, as opposed to the books intent. Spoiler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 01:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First I will say I love both and like alternate versions of the same story. On the other hand I donnot understand the argument that the hotel is represented just as evil as it is in the book(not to be confused with the hotel is not evil in the movie).



Kubrick makes intended changes to the books plot seemingly to down play the true evil of the hotel. Take for instance the different endings. In the book the hotel is destroyed, and the movie it's left standing. If the hotel is as evil in the book as it is in the movie, the hotel should have been destroyed.


Take the maze scene. Kubrick places this maze scene in where Danny is chased by the insane gone over the edge jack. Where as the book jack is possessed by the hotel and chases Danny through the halls, his voice and demeanor is extremely unfamiliar to Danny. Jack seemingly goes over the edge as opposed to being possessed by a the hotel. 



Last example is the hedges. The hotel can control the hedges and bring them to life. As Danny's shine gets stronger and fuels the hotels power the hedges go from just moving their positions, to being able to attack the occupants. This is left out seemingly to downplay the hotels capabilities. That's as good place to start as any so Change my views.
_____

 *Hello, users of CMV! This is a footnote from your moderators. We'd just like to remind you of a couple of things. Firstly, please remember to* ***[read through our rules](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/rules)***. *If you see a comment that has broken one, it is more effective to report it than downvote it. Speaking of which,* ***[downvotes don't change views](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/guidelines#wiki_upvoting.2Fdownvoting)****! If you are thinking about submitting a CMV yourself, please have a look through our* ***[popular topics wiki](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/populartopics)*** *first. Any questions or concerns? Feel free to* ***[message us](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=/r/changemyview)***. *Happy CMVing!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eyes wide shut. Was kidman.... Spoilers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the movie and i get it for the most part. Its an unfiltered view of relationships, sex, power, women's desires being equal to mens, etc. My question is relating to kidmans dream half way through and reaction/response at the end. Was she saying she was part of the secret society and had group sex there, or are the two unrelated? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Nye vs. Ken ham. What did you think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 08:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First if you havent seen it, you should watch its informative and entertaining.



Curious to see how many people here agree with Ham? How many agree with Nye? How, on either side you're on, does this fit with your religous beliefs and was anything said that surprised you? Or change what you previously believed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite Stephen King plot? and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 07:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is Pet semetary. The wendingo(i think thats right) lining the back story to the cemetary, just makes this plot brilliant imo.



Almost tempted to rule out The stand now but im interested in the why. So whats your favorite and why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who today could best direct The Count of Monte Cristo? Who is best suited to play the leads? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 07:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What director would you choose and what actors would you like to see?



Im unhappy with all movie adaptations ive seen so far and would be cool to see different scenarios of who could pull it off? Thanks ahead for your comments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: The Prestige, the machine does not work. Spoiler alert. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 06:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will start by I have struggled with this concept since it has been brought to my attention. I know this movie extremely well, better than I should, and have previously debated just about every scene. Not to say the this conclusion is right but to say I do know the film and the characters well. 



My basic theory stems from, The movie constantly allures to what and how magic is done, which has nothing to do with 'real magic' but with deceit. That's what the machine is deceit.  Will give  a summary of my theory now, leaving out the beginning and end, and details as my post will be too long for any interest. I will elaborate on the beginning and end , and details once the discussion begins.



So Borden does have a twin, tesla is real, angiers visits are fabricated from the diary and his ending speech being as such. Upon Angier capturing Fallon and receiving the key to Borden's diary(tesla) is where I will start. Angier visits Tesla finding out there is no answer to Borden's secret( Angiers original motive), and tesla has no "magic". So he begins to come up with away to frame Borden, not just kill him, but ruin his reputation and acquire custody of his daughter. He uses the fact Borden has sent him to tesla, to begin his frame up. He uses a useless tesla machine to add flair to an old trick, and spark interest in Borden. Angier also needs "real magic" to obtain a theater, no simple trick will do, as Borden hs already ruined his reputation. He uses a double to pull off his trick, with the illusion of being transported. He doesn't drown his double every night just the night of the murder. To ensure Borden will be confused he uses the element of mysterious tanks being transported from the theater every night, otherwise Borden will easily see he is using a double but with the mysterious tanks he sparks enough interest from Borden to want to see backstage, as this is vital for the frame up to work. 



Angier is the pledge and turn and root(or other double if you prefer) is the prestige, ie on the balcony. Angiers motive at this point is no longer magic or the applause it's simply to frame borden. Borden makes multiple appearances at the show wearing a disguise. Angier needs to spot and identify this disguise in order to carry on with the frame up, which is why he doesn't do the frame up the first night he enters the theater, and eventually Angier does discover Borden. Knowing his routine and the fact he will come again because he hasn't been picked to view the machine or backstage, he sets the frame up. Seeing Borden enter the theater he tells his assistant to pick Borden out of the crowd that night, also telling root he will be the pledge and turn for the transported man ( not the other tricks) on this night. As Borden is being picked from the crowd, Angier and root switch, the frame up plays out Angier flees the theater. This is the jist will elaborate further on the end scene and the like upon the discussion beginning.



I will add a few of the questions about the machine working theory that I have, which can be answered by my theory. These questions could be preluded with "if the machine works"



What is the tank Caine and Angier are pushing during the ending scene? If if the last clone is in the morgue, and the tank had been broken to extract the clone what tank are they pushing?



Why store the clones? What not rid of them every night?


What is the air bubble at the end in the only visible tank.



How did Angier gain full control of both his legs while drowning? The movie goes through some length to show how damaged it is, why do this if it's not meant to be.a clue



If Borden sends angiers to tesla, it's his plan, why wait till he has  captured Fallon to give him Teslas name, why not give it to him when he gives Angier the diary?



I have more of my theory to share, and more question to ask those who disagree it this is already too long. Looking for reasonable, logical, light hearted debate, so bring it on reddit change my views
_____

 *Hello, users of CMV! This is a footnote from your moderators. We'd just like to remind you of a couple of things. Firstly, please remember to* ***[read through our rules](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/rules)***. *If you see a comment that has broken one, it is more effective to report it than downvote it. Speaking of which,* ***[downvotes don't change views](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/guidelines#wiki_upvoting.2Fdownvoting)****! If you are thinking about submitting a CMV yourself, please have a look through our* ***[popular topics wiki](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/populartopics)*** *first. Any questions or concerns? Feel free to* ***[message us](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=/r/changemyview)***. *Happy CMVing!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the better actor to you and why? Tom cruise or Leonardo Dicaprio?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 01:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why these 2, well I had this debate with a friend recently, i wanted to know what Reddit thinks.




My case is for Leo. I feel Tom cruise is very similar in alot of his roles. Leo to me has taken more risk, is more convincing at different types of roles, and simply picks better movies. And the fact Scorsese works with Leo, amoung many other actors again and again and has worked with Cruise once is odd.




Again tell me who you like and Why?



EDIT: im more interested in your why then who </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you heard of bands making records in this way??? What do you think about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 04:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lead singer and guitar player for the Wild hearts, Ginger, decided to release a solo album. Instead of dealing with the record company, he decided to set up a fundraiser deal. Where people interested in buying his record would send him money. I think the first 10,000 was like 50$ and the rest was 25$. 




The first 10,000 recieved 20 songs then a vote was taken as to which 10 made it on to the record. The top ten made it. Once the songs were finalized the first 10,000 got both the official record and the record of the other 10, i believe in both cd and record format. The ensuing investors received the official record.




I just love this idea. Getting your chance to participate in the making of the record and taking all outside influence away, leaving the artist with complete freedom. Other bands have used this strategy, including Radiohead(not 100% this band).




 REDDIT what are your thoughts? Do you love or hate it? Would you participate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ozzy and his unforgiveable Greed. Did you know??... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 03:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ozzy and sharon have been fighting the surviving members of the randy rhodes era, over their rightful royalties. Bob daisley and lee kerslake have been trying to receive their fair share but are getting denied. They had ample share in writing the music and recording "Blizzard of Oz" and "Diary of a Madman", although they did not tour on these records.



Ozzy went so far as to remove their tracks and rerecord them when they were remastered. To stay consistent upon the release of the 2 albums box sets, Daisley offered up hours and hours of early takes, demos, and studio outtakes, Ozzy refused because Daisley wanted royalties instead of it being bought outright.




As a lifelong fan of Ozzy, i cannot forgive him for this greed, and i have just recently stumbled upon this. To think you cant even buy the orignal music from the randy rhode era is infuriating. Tell me what you think Reddit.




I dont have links but this can be found with a quick google search. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The prestige, the machine does not work, why do you think differently or agree?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 00:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have watched the film many times, close to twenty. It makes more sense that it doesnt work, really the only thing that makes sense imo. There are clues everywhere in the movie once you grasp the timeline and Angier and Bordens never ending deception (this includes angier's last attempt to fool borden at the very end). 




I wont go into specifics here, but will debunk the theories presented in the discussion. Whether you agree or disagree completely let me know what you think.



EDIT: SPOILER ALERTS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best movie in the last ten years and why??? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 00:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My choice would be avatar. The special effects combined with a powerful story just hit the right notes for me. What is your Personal best of the last 10 years?




I also thought django unchained was amazing, and There will be blood that imo has the best acting in the last 30 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [xb1]Selling 225k for 21$ PP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 00:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paypal preferred. Willing 2 go 1st with trusted buyers. Willing to do multiple transaction or use a MM. Quick n easy hmu.

Http://www.reddit.com/r/MCSRep/comments/33qaq8/umaddlabber928_mcs_rep_profile/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [xb1] Selling 500k for 55k or 12$/100k PP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 02:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paypal preferred. Willing to do multiple transaction, MM, or other ways to keep both parties safe. Fairly new here but have bought n sold here, hmu im reasonable.

Http://www.reddit.com/r/MCSRep/comments/33qaq8/umaddlabber928_mcs_rep_profile/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [xbox1]selling 200k 4 25$ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 02:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lookiing to sell 200k together. Will break up payments. Paypal preferred.

Http://www.reddit.com/r/MCSRep/comments/33qaq8/umaddlabber928_mcs_rep_profile/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/maddlabber928 MCS Rep Profile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 19:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *4\21\15
* xbox 1
* If you clicked a link to this page, please make sure that you're on the real /r/MCSRep. Double check the username that linked you and make sure it matches the username of this rep thread EXACTLY and  isn't just SIMILAR. Note that just because you're reading this doesn't mean a scammer didn't include this note in their fake profile to trick you into a false sense of security. Always double check, and don't get tricked or scammed! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
