<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9175</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 11:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly Escaflowne </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 10:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> V/H/S 2 is pretty good as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 10:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shouted at the screen for the last five minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 10:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God yes! And, when you think about it  [](#s "you realise that there is no real threat and that only real villain is the now helpless old woman who dies half way through the film! ") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 10:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sleepaway Camp  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know what's going down on High St, Northcote tonight? Bottles being thrown at cop cars according to facebook. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 12:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most problems can be solved by watching Suddenly Seymour from Little Shop of Horrors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 10:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Random Acts of Pizza - Melbourne Edition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 09:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been a while.

Had a shithouse day?

Send me a message and I'll send you a pizza. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a good, local web designer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 04:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone suggest a good Melbourne based web designer to help me put together a basic site for my business?

I'm looking for someone creative (read, artsy) who is also professional.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking to create the ultimate list of con artist films. What have I missed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 01:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whoopi Goldberg's career summed up by google </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 05:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The website for Wild, Wild West (1999) is still up! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 00:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best TV show adaptation of a movie? And the worst? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-20 17:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched Zombieland recently and it made me feel ill. However, M* A* S* H, Buffy and Heartbreak High (Australian soap for teens I grew up on) all eclipse their cinematic origins.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The greatest anti-drug video ever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 11:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do hate most in reviews? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 13:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've recently given up reading Empire and listening to film podcast because I got sick of spoilers and bad reviewes. Just because the film is called [](#s "Seeking Friend For The End Of The World") doesn't mean [](#s "the world is going to end in the movie") so don't mention that fact in the film! 

I'm also sick of the obsession with focusing on whether the reviewer liked or disliked the film. That was important when we had only papers to tell us if films were worth watching, now, with the internet, we can get a sense of quality in seconds. 

I want **real** analysis! Make me think!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Amputees feel heat more than other people because arms and legs take hot blood away from your internal organs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-16 08:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stationery store moves! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 05:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stationery shop is not stationary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 05:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Ray Bradbury helped create a text based computer game version of Fahrenheit 451 in 1985 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 03:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Heather Graham played Arnold Schwarzenegger and Danny Devito's mother in the movie Twins in an uncredited role. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 14:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Oscar The Grouch is Jewish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 03:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm looking for awesome performers... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 01:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run a weekly variety show called The Variety Collective which I shamelessly PLUG here ever once and a while.

We're currently looking for new acts who'd like to perform at the show. We book professional and semi-professional performers including magicians, circus performers, sideshow artists, clowns (the good ones, not the creepy American style ones), musicians with gimmick and pretty much any other skill based entertainment you can think of. 

If you know of anyone or are a performer yourself it would be great to hear from you. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hate ukulele players? Then you'll hate this show tomorrow night. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 01:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oliver Clark - Atomic Thrust (Official Music Video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 02:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wanted to watch a classic Australian movie...eh, close enough. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-15 11:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit Gold for anyone who can name a con artist film I have not seen! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 10:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love con artist movies.

I just wrote a book on them which is coming out next year.

So, if you can name a con artist movie that I haven't seen I'll give you some sweet, sweet gold. 

I'm pretty picky about what films I consider con artist movies. (Ocean's 11, The Usual Suspects, The Thomas Crown Affair don't count I'm afraid)

http://scams.wikispaces.com/Cinematic+Scams

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone remember the interactive movie Tender Loving Care? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 09:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why news.com keeps stealing from reddit... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 13:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What movie that terrified you as kid seems silly now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 14:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember having nightmares about this scene from Pee Wee's Big Adventure.

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uzolCu-QLw0

Now, I don't know what I was so scared of. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the single scariest frame of a film you've ever seen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-04 15:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's always been Invasion of The Body Snatchers (1978).

http://www.filminamerica.com/Movies/InvasionOfTheBodySnatchers1978/invasion23.jpg

Even the Mad Magazine parody gave me nightmares.
What's yours? Post screenshots if you've got them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favourite practical, non CGI, special effect in a film? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 10:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pick your favourite scene using special effect created with latex, models, perspective, stunts, explosions rather than CGI. 

Link to a video or pic if you can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Carly Simon's father was the founder of Simon   Schuster publishers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 03:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Thankyou Water' donates a portion of their profits to evangelical charity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 13:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Thankyou Water' linked to evangelist charity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 13:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Like 'pepperoni pizza'   'ice cream'? Check out 'grinding salt   vinegar chips into your open eyeballs.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 08:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I collect scams. What small scale swindles have you pulled? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 11:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Power goes out at Northcote Town Hall. Magicians moved show to outside and do their show by torchlight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 13:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL - Muhammad Ali performs magic tricks...and then reveals the secret to the audience in order to "show you how the devil deceives you." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-07 16:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How magicians find your card. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 23:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What changes have film adaptations made that have improved on the book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 13:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Often, a movie adaptation will improve on the original book. The following are films I feel are an improvement on the source material. I've used spoiler tags as most relate to the ending.

Breakfast at Tiffany's
[spoiler] (#s  "The introduction of the love interest and the rain-soaked finale makes for a cheesy conclusion but I love it all the same.")

Fight Club [spoiler](#s  " 'You met me at a very strange time in my life" and then Boom! In the books, the attacks fail and he ends up in hospital.' ")

Matchstick Men [spoiler](#s "The reunion in the carpet store and the reconciliation with the wife  after the finale twist doesn't appear in the novel and it's kind of a downer.")

Thank You For Smoking [spoiler](#s "In the film, he becomes a hero and returns to work. In the book, he becomes an anti-smoking advocate.")

First Blood [spoiler](#s "In the original novel, Rambo is the bad guy and is shot to death. In the film, he is a troubled veteran whose actions are understandable.")

The Mist [spoiler](#s "In the film, he shoots his young son in the head to save him from the monsters in the fog not realising that help the sounds he hears is the army on the way. In the book, they simply drive into the mist.")

What are your favourites?



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you try and stop people talking/texting during movies? If so, how? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 00:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fran and Wayne Houchin escaping from strait-jackets while suspended 50 foot above Northcote Town Hall this morning. As you do. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-28 04:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got given the letters RMUGRDAE in a live anagram game show. My answer was not accepted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 01:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For my cake day, I'm having a board game party and it's a bit of a mindf*ck. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 06:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blogger drives SIMS to the brink of insanity in order to see how mental illness is depicted in video games. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-17 11:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Russel Gilbert and Shane Warne practice magic tricks together. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-17 05:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is 'Dumb Ways To Die' really a PR stunt to make Metro more likeable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 03:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listening to the radio a few weeks back, they were talking about the 'Dumb Ways To Die' video and it's success. 

One of the guests, who works in advertising, suggested that the advertisement's goal is NOT to make people safe around trains but to make Metro more likeable. 

It's much harder to be cynical about a whimsical safety advertisement than a whimsical crappy-public-transport-authority advertisement. 

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IJNR2EpS0jw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm one of the organisers of the Melbourne Magic Festival. AMAA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-10 16:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few people have bought up the Melbourne Magic Festival in the past few days so, as one of the organisers, I thought I'd start a one-stop thread for people to ask questions, make requests and post Arrested Development quotes.

The festivals runs from 1-13 July at Northcote Town Hall.

http://melbournemagicfestival.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did you know there is magic theatre in Brunswick with weekly magic shows? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 08:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A little video I made. Magicians will like the milk and cookies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-06 14:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL That Wonder Woman was created by an inventor of the polygraph, a polygamist and BDSM proponent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-03 02:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A lot of people have been wondering why 'ape' is a racist term. This is a great answer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 03:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I saw a guy ram a car with a dirt bike today... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-27 11:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a guy ram a car with his motorcycle today and then swear at the driver. 

Sadly for him, the car was an unmarked police car and the driver and his passenger were cops.

The sirens went on and the jerk freaked out, sprinted across Bell Street and dove head first over the eight foot high fence before disappearing into the scrub around Merri Creek.

The cops took after him and the last thing I saw before the lights changed and I had to drive away was the podgy copper trying to scale the fence after him.

It was like something out of The Bill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for under 18 musicians...nothing sus. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-27 07:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In hindsight, saying 'nothing sus' makes it sound sus.

I need a talented under 18 year old musician to do three songs for a gig on 5 June. It's a variety show (comedy, magic, circus etc.) and we need a shit hot musical act. 

There is some money involved which is nice. In the past, we've had everything from piano accordions and choirs to MCs and standard covers. 

Hit me up at info@conman.com.au or below. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That view count is really messing with my OCD. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 10:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A friend got to the bottom of his Gloria Jeans coffee and found this waiting for him.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 03:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A friend got to the bottom of his Gloria Jeans coffee and found this waiting for him.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 03:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Ten Most Wonderful Things Committed To Hansard As A Result Of The Skywhale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-17 10:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Ten Most Wonderful Things Committed To Hansard As A Result Of The Skywhale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-17 10:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I tried to combine my love of board games and magic into one video. I'm quite pleased with the result </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 10:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wanted to make a video that combines board games, magic and mind-fuckery. This is the end result. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 10:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you haven't seen Canberra's Skywhale yet, you are in for a treat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 07:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got in a little trouble at Parliament House last night... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 04:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do a show about scams and con artists and had a gig last night at Parliament House. Security searched my bag and, after seeing what I was carrying, decided to call the police.

My evening ended with me being interrogated by the Australian Protective Services for 20 minutes while they did a background check on me. 

"But officer, I'm an HONEST con man..." didn't seem to cut it.

In hindsight, trying to bring a hammer, two nails, a sharp knife, a lock picking set, two loaded dice and a small bottle of lighter fluid into the building might have been a mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since we're in a nostalgic mood, here is a little My Secret Valley. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-05 13:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a child I feared ghosts, spirits cruel and malicious... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 06:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for board game groups in Melbourne </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 04:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm putting together a board game event in July and I am looking for groups that might be keen to have some input on the show.

http://melbournemagicfestival.com/speaker-lineup/beat-the-cheat/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This show has free entry if you bring a friend on Wednesday night (it's a facebook link...sorry) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 03:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Melbourne Magic Festival is on again! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-23 02:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A reddit themed palindrome I'm proud of. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 redditors showed up to my comedy festival show and this is the result.... (I love you guys) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 04:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free Tickets for Comedy Festival </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 11:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've three double passes to my comedy festival show.

It's looking like a quiet night and I've got the Herald Sun reviewing my show. All the other reviews have been glowing but getting a nice review in print would be great. 

The show is an expose of my time as a regular on Today Tonight and all the awful things you didn't know about that show (as well as the awful things you already do know) 

If you're keen, email me at info@conman.com.au

PS - I've tried not to make this a blantant plug for the show. I'm really just giving away some tix.

EDIT 2: - The reviewers have asked to SWAP night to WEDNESDAY! So if anyone would like to come WEDNESDAY night, please email info@conman.com.au. Obviously happy to see the comps who are coming tonight!

www.conman.com.au/todaytonight
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a flyerer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 06:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for someone who is enthusiastic and friendly who'd like to hand out flyers for me for my comedy festival show tonight (and several other nights) from 7:15-9:15 in town.

I can afford $15 per hour. 

Let me know if you're keen.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This orphan kitten has the best name ever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-23 06:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This cat looks like Batman. He needs a home. Adopt him... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-23 01:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have three double passes to this show for tonight...who is in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-13 00:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I help run a weekly show at The Brunswick Green. Every few weeks we invite a few redditors for free to get new audiences.

This week, I have three double passes. Hit me up on info@conman.com.au if you want one. 

https://www.facebook.com/events/346992812087221/?fref=ts

"If it wasn't for the last minute I wouldn't get anything done at all"

This week's Variety Collective is packed full of last minute acts direct from the Adelaide Fringe and warming up for the Melbourne Comedy Festival.

NEIL SINCLAIR - Comedian and lying bastard!

BAYDEN HAMMOND - Magician and swell guy!

CHRISTOPHER ZALUSKI - Foot juggler and NICA graduate!

BOSS OCTOPUS - Sketch comedians!

KIM CHRISTENSEN - Contact juggler and street performer!

WITH your host, the man the Adelaide Advertiser described as having 'a pumpkin shaped head' NICHOLAS J. JOHNSON!

8:00pm on 13 March

The Brunswick Green
313 Sydney Road
Brunswick

All Tickets - $10

https://www.facebook.com/events/346992812087221/?fref=ts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever seen a game like this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 15:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been developing a simple yet kind of addictive card game over the past year. The idea is for players to act as spiders and spin a web to help win a prize. Players can cut, tangle and steal each other's webs.

There are pictures that explain the game better here at the facebook page I set up the other day...

https://www.facebook.com/danglegame

Have you seen a similar game before?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need a handyman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 10:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need a QUALIFIED handy man to build some floor to ceiling, wall to wall shelves. The job with probably involved a bit of joinery.

Any recommendations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free Tix For Redditors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 22:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I opened my stand up show Today Tonight, Tomorrow the World last year in Melbourne and couldn't have done it with the support of all the redditors who plugged it and came along.

So i'm paying it forward and giving away some free tickets to my show at Gluttony for the next two weeks. 

We had a full house last night and comments from twitter said:

"Just saw Today Tonight. Magnificent! Highly recommend." - @screamcreative2

"go see this show! you will be surprised!" @traceymathers 

"This is a brilliant show, everyone should see this show, very smart comedy." lebby panaayiotu. 

If you'd a free double pass hit me up on email to info@conman.com.au with the date you want to come (I'm on until the 9 March).

www.conman.com.au/todaytonight

EDIT: Thanks for the love guys. Had a few redditors come in and see the show last night. It's a tough fringe for performers so it's nice to know I have friends out there. I can spare a few more tickets if anyone missed out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I love fiverr.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 04:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Complete History of Today Tonight (with action figures on six cans of red bull) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 05:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free Tix: The Variety Collective on Wednesday night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 01:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run The Variety Collective every week at The Brunswick Green on Sydney Road. 

We have a rusted on fan base of people who come every week to watch comedy, magic etc.

I'd like to bring in a new audience so I thought I'd give a few double passes to my reddit friends.

Send me an email to info@conman.com.au.

https://www.facebook.com/events/362457663861245/?fref=ts

EDIT ONE: A few tickets left...I'll let you know when they are all gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone in Melbourne is selling an amazing Back To The Future collection... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 13:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't cancel Today Tonight and make me the new host... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-03 09:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't cancel Today Tonight and make me the new host... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-03 09:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pretty sure my new show is responsible for Today Tonight getting cancelled. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 02:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An open letter to Goodlife </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 13:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TO: Goodlife Health Clubs, Australia
SUBJECT: Are you shitting me?

I quit your crappy gym FIVE YEARS ago. 

You wouldn't take no for an answer and spammed me for MONTHS afterwards. 

I had to threaten legal action to get you to stop sending your damn crappy emails.

And now, in 2013, you've started again.

I'd rather sit alone in my house, morbidly obese eating shake-a-pancake from the bottle than ever deal with you people again. 

Sod off.

Nicholas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm planning a 'Flim Flam Film Fest' - What are the best con artist movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 00:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm planning a 'Flim Flam Film Fest' - Help me choose the best con artist films </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 00:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just saw two Deloreans outside Hall of Fame in Northcote  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 04:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and my damn iphone just ran out of juice.

Was it pair of docs? Or a paradox? 

EDIT:

Doxxus has pics:  http://i.imgur.com/WlKIP8G.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to make a simple site on Yola. I'd love any feedback. (be gentle :) ) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 23:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You and me both iphone - Imgur </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-18 04:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The O'reilly Factor summed up in one quote. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 14:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What makes you support a kickstarter game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 04:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was looking at the Kickstarter/Pozible projects I've supported and there isn't really a pattern to what I like. Sometimes I'm just on the bandwagon, other times I just want to know the game EXISTS (even if I don't play it)

What makes you support a campaign?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL That Moby was the first person to license every song on an album to advertisers.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 01:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone remember this series from the 1980s? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 13:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can only clearly remember two scenes.

One, involved a politician, possibly the prime minister standing on balcony shouting insanely while an aide tries to convince to take cover. Moments later, a nuclear bomb goes off.

The other, set after the apocalypse, sees a group of people kept in a cage while lions and tigers circle them as the new ruling class laugh at this 'reverse zoo'

it was a really disturbing satire of the politics of the time. 

(it's NOT Threads :) ) 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I accidentally invented a card game where spiders spin webs to win cupcakes. I need to get out more. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 01:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone had experience with this game printer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 04:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking to print my first card game and I've been recommended contacting this Indian company. 

http://www.playingcardsindia.com

Has anyone ever played any of the games they have printed? Or can you offer me any advice or picking a printer?

Thanks in advance.

EDIT: The game I am creating is called Dangle (http://danglegame.tumblr.com)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for film podcasts NOT obsessed with reviews </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-28 00:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love film but I am entirely sick of our culture's obsession with ranking, rating and reviewing them. 

I don't really care if a critic thinks a film is good or bad, I'm more interested in analysis, interesting trivia and where a movie fits in the history of film.

I spend less time here: http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1478964/reviews
and more time here: http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1478964/trivia

Can anyone suggest any good podcasts I can listen too?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Political Satire and Variety Show on Wednesday night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-27 02:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where to get cards printed good quality? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 23:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking to print a 100 card game next year and I'm looking at various options for printing.

The game involves a lot of laying down and picking up card from the table so I really need something thick and high quality.

I've check out game crafter but I'm looking for other ideas.

Thanks for any help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazing user review of Alex Cross from Metacritic.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-18 05:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone published the internet as a book in 1967 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-17 12:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rape survivor heckled at comedy night. It's not the whole story but it's still a very depressing read. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 21:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know if the Eastment St Billy Cart derby is on tomorrow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-05 10:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Making a poster for an 80's night this wednesday. I think I got carried away. - Imgur </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-05 02:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A celebration of eighties blockbuster movies... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-31 23:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scary Halloween Story Telling on Thursday Night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-24 13:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stomach bug!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-05 11:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been sick as a dog this week. I thought it was food poisoning but it's hung around for days.

Is there a nasty stomach virus going around?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How hipsters grieve </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-30 07:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free Comedy Tickets for Tomorrow Night! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-28 15:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It turns out there is some sort of sporting event on tomorrow night, the second night of my Fringe Festival show which means tickets sales are down a little. 

Since redditors were nice enough to come out to my test show back in August, I thought I'd throw out five double passes for the Saturday night show. 

The show is called Today Tonight, Tomorrow The World and tells the tale about how I sold my soul to the most infamous show on Australian television, Today Tonight!

Send me an email at info@conman.com.au to score one of the double passes.

https://www.facebook.com/events/412320292137593/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Victim blaming? Jill Meagher article </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-26 01:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comedy show - Confessions of a guy who has been on Today Tonight WAY too many times. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-24 08:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comedy Show - Everything you didn't want to know about Today Tonight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-24 08:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please print out this poster of missing Brunswick woman Jill Meagher and stick it up where you can! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-23 14:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever been on television? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-15 08:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm putting on a show in a few weeks about being a little bit famous.

Have you ever been on TV or in a movie? 

What did you do?

https://www.facebook.com/events/412320292137593/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do Sydneysiders dislike Melbourne? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 09:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in town for a few days and I keep hearing people dissing Melbourne.

I didn't know this was a thing. 

Also, people keeping telling me a look like a pedophile and/or hipster. 

Is there a big problem with hipsters/pedophiles in Sydney?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this the best Melbourne movie ever? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-11 13:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Random Act of Pizza - Bad Day? Good Pizza! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-11 12:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's that time again.

Had a shit house day?

Send me a message and I'll send you a pizza.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Random Act Of Pizza - Shitty day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 14:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had a shitty day?

Time for a random act of pizza.

Send me a message and I'll send you a piping hot pizza.

EDIT: Pizzas are all gone for tonight. May the pizza gods smile on you. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free Comedy - Looking for a venue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 12:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping to put on a free night of comedy while I'm in Sydney in a couple of nights.

I'll be previewing my new one man show before it premieres at Melbourne Fringe Festival at the end of the month. I did a preview earlier this week in Melbourne and it went quite well.

All I need is a small space with a bar and possibly a data projector.

Any ideas of where I could I put on such a night?
Would you guys like to come?

https://www.facebook.com/events/412320292137593/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a general ledger software for a finance-phobe.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 01:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suffer from anxiety, particularly relating to money and bookkeeping. Often, if I make a mistake on an invoice, I don't get paid rather than go through the stress of resending the account. It's a serious problem that I'm slowly working through.

As such, I just can not handle complicated book keeping software. I've been using a 20 year old copy of MS Money for years which has a basic ledger (income/expense) which has finally stopped working. I'm a sole trader who provides a service.

I need to upgrade but I can't find a piece of software I can handle. All I need is to track income and expense taking into account a 10% sales tax. (GST, I'm in Australia).

I'm working on Mac if that helps.

Thank you in advance for any advice you can give. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know any good Melbourne based Event's Guides? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-26 10:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to plug an event and I'm looking for good, free Melbourne gig guides (like Eventfinder or OnlyMelbourne).

Are there any that use or like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sleepwalk With Me - Can we get this movie in Melbourne (even in Joss Wedon doesn't want us to?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 03:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fans of This American Life will already know who Mike Birbiglia. He's a comedian who, with the help of Ira Glass, has made a hilarious movie called "Sleepwalk with Me"

http://movies.mmgn.com/Videos/SLEEPWALK-WITH-ME-Official-Trailer

It's only being shown at a handful of cinemas in the US and it would be awesome to bring it to Melbourne. 

Joss Wedon thinks this is a bad idea: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pj6_020FFXU

If you want this awesome film in Melbourne, head over to Cinema Nova's facebook page and twitter and ask them nicely. 

https://www.facebook.com/pages/Cinema-Nova/118158071574996
https://twitter.com/cinemanova </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comedy, magic, circus and science? Come check out this show on Wednesday night.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 05:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free Comedy. Must hate Today Tonight.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-31 04:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FREE COMEDY and AMA.

In October, I'm premiring a brand spanking new show at Melbourne Fringe.

It's a stand up comedy show about the time I appeared on Today Tonight, meeting Naomi Robson and getting screwed over by the show. 

It's called 'Today Tonight, Tomorrow the World'

I'm having a test run of the show on 28 August at The Brunswick Green and I'd really like to get some complete strangers along to laugh at my jokes or throw puppies if you hate it. (please don't throw puppies. It's not their fault I'm not funny)

https://www.facebook.com/events/412320292137593/

If anyone has any other ideas on how to get some people along to check out some free comedy, let me know.

Thanks. 

PS - You don't HAVE to hate Today Tonight but it helps.

PPS - Ask me anything about myself, Today Tonight or comedy.

EDIT - I've had 50 people email me at info@conman.com.au to book a seat. However, you might still get a seat if you just show up on the night.

EDIT - If you miss out on the preview, here is the Melbourne Fringe link. http://www.melbournefringe.com.au/fringe-festival/show/today-tonight-tomorrow-the-world/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Melbourne Magic Festival starts next week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-25 02:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am super pumped.

The Melbourne Magic Festival is on next week. I just found out the first show (the gala) I'm in has sold out.

Is anyone planning on going?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thinking of moving to Footscray/Seddon area </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-24 10:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I currently live in Northcote and I'm thinking of moving cross town to Footscray.

Will I be stabbed in neck?
Will my friends visit me?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a bottle of coke with a name on it for a magic show! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-24 04:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a magician (hoorah) performing at the Melbourne Magic Festival (hoorah) but I need some help. (boo!)

I'm looking for a 1.25 or 2 litre bottle of coke with someone's name printed on it from that promotion from late last year.

Any name will do!

If you can help, I can even get you a few tickets to a show. We've got stuff for kid's, adults, hipsters, crazy old cat ladies... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for bottle of coke with Name on it for Magic Show. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-24 03:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a magician (hoorah) performing at the Melbourne Magic Festival (hoorah) but I need some help. (boo!)

I'm looking for a 1.25 or 2 litre bottle of coke with someone's name printed on it from that promotion from late last year.

Any name will do!

If you can help, I can even get you a few tickets to a show. We've got stuff for kid's, adults, hipsters, crazy old cat ladies.

 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
