<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject889</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Love that new project feeling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 13:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spent months trying to think of a good cake day post, but now that it's here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 11:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This tealight holder looked shocked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 07:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Spoilers ADWD) [S04E02] Was there a girl dwarf amongst the jousters? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 00:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was looking fairly closely but couldn't tell if one of the dwarves was a girl. If not, then I can only assume that Penny has been cut... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brisbanites, where is the best place to get seafood chowder in Brissy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 08:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am mad for seafood chowder after I had it at Brett's Wharf a while ago...but that place has shut down.

So now I am on the hunt for an aweome bowl of chowder. Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers ADWD] Noticed this when rereading ADWD...What do you suppose it means for Davos? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 00:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The bones help," said Melisandre. "The bones remember. The strongest glamors are built of such things. A dead man's boots, a hank of hair, a bag of fingerbones." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A conversation about Organ Donation [X-post] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 00:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After seeing a post on Facebook about organ donation, I was appalled by the sheer number of people who felt that older people do not deserve organs because they have already lived their lives. 

I got so mad when these people said things like "that's dumb, why didn't they give the organ to a younger person?"

And while I know not every can know the details of how organs are allocated, it just bothered me that so many people thought so little of the elderly and felt that the young deserved more in life.

Youth really is wasted on the young! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Culture clash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 02:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a leaf edging pattern </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 01:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys.

I was hoping someone could help me find a pattern for an edging that would produce a similar result to [this]( http://i.imgur.com/nVDqJVm.jpg). The pic is knitted and I was hoping for a crochet equivalent.

Please and thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FO] Jar tea-light cozy with recycled denim yarn. Little bit potato quality. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 11:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An apt response </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 01:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel like a junkie when I go see my chiropractor. Gotta get my fix! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 00:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is a big confession for me. I have never done anything so rebellious </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 09:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan ordered to end Antarctic whaling by top UN court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 12:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ....I don't believe it! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 12:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FO] Lacy collar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 12:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what memory of yours always makes you cringe when you think back on it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 08:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know the one I mean. Something reminds you of this memory and you have to actively avoid remembering it to save yourself from the embarassment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what weird coincidence has happened to you lately that you want to share? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 20:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people don't care how that song you were singing in the morning was on the radio in car, or stuff like that. But I do!

Share </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My buddy keeps my legs warm while I crochet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 12:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just saw this on my feed. Made me chuckle. (Sorry if repost) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 14:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I do this even if I have known the people my whole lives. I'm just paranoid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 07:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend just got a new tattoo. He is 30... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 11:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What smell holds the most emotional value to you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 23:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smell is the Sense that is closest link to your memory. There are plenty of smells that instantly make me feel great happiness or some, real sadness and I either really enjoy coming across them, or go to great lengths to avoid them.

What are yours? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This showed up on my newsfeed. People are just making shit up now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 12:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My sister's new pup. Dem eyes! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-08 06:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Copped an elbow to the arm the other day. Became Popeye </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 13:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update] My Widdle Unicorn now has a hair-do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 23:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Widdle unicorn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 14:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just got this little fella yesterday and he needs a name. Any ideas Reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 04:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need some advice. Am I stressed, sick or is it all in my head? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 23:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an X post, forgot to put that in title.

ver the last few years I have felt like my general well-being is in decline. My co-workers call it stress, my friends call it old-age (I'm 24!!!) and my doctor just says it is nothing. However, the more I tally up my issues, the more I think/worry most of them may have a singular cause:

Tinnitus/v. sensitive hearing 

Blurred in one eye, nearsightedness (only recently discovered- never noticed before and not brought up in childhood eye tests)

Headaches/Migraines

Neck pain/severe muscle tension (Go to Chiro, Physio AND Remedial masseuse)

Forgetfulness (short term, things slip away quickly)

Twitches/muscle spasms 

Twitching eye 

Heart palpatations w adrenaline rush

Slightly enlarged optic nerve in right eye

Boughts of vertigo/dizziness/ ground feels like it is moving

Occasional insomnia (who doesn't get this, but i thought I would include it)

Fatigue

Lately, lack of enthusiasm for even fun activities


Bronchial cough

Short of breath

(Diagnosed with Stress-Related asthma. but as I lie here in bed, relaxing, I am short of breath, sooo....?)

I know some of these are general and vague problems that millions of people also deal with. I don't want a wild, obscure internet diagnosis, I just want to know whether, as Doctors, you would find these symptoms cause for concern. If so, I will push my GP to paying closer attention.

Further background: 24yo F Healthy weight, eats well, exercises regularly, normal blood pressure, previously noted 'slightly high' heart rate like I was nervous whilst getting tested (didn't feel nervous), no abnormal blood tests save for a single one with low blood proteins (retest was normal, ?lab error). Medication: The Pill and regular paracetamol for headaches

If it is just stress, what can I do? I take regular Me Time, exercise regularly, don't take work home with me, don't sit and fret on issues. This year I will be moving interstate but that decision is only weeks old and some of these issues have been around for a few years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doctors of Reddit, I need advice on whether I should seek futher help...or if it is all in my head </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 14:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the last few years I have felt like my general well-being is in decline. My co-workers call it stress, my friends call it old-age (I'm 24!!!) and my doctor just says it is nothing. However, the more I tally up my issues, the more I think/worry most of them may have a singular cause:

Tinnitus/v. sensitive hearing 

Blurred in one eye, nearsightedness (only recently discovered- never noticed before and not brought up in childhood eye tests)

Headaches/Migraines

Neck pain/severe muscle tension

Forgetfulness (short term, things slip away quickly)

Twitches/muscle spasms 

Twitching eye 

Heart palpatations w adrenaline rush

Slightly enlarged optic nerve in right eye

Boughts of vertigo/dizziness/ ground feels like it is moving

Occasional insomnia (who doesn't get this, but i thought I would include it)

Fatigue

Lately, lack of enthusiasm for even fun activities


Bronchial cough

Short of breath

(Diagnosed with Stress-Related asthma. but as I lie here in bed, relaxing, I am short of breath, sooo....?)

I know some of these are general and vague problems that millions of people also deal with. I don't want a wild, obscure internet diagnosis, I just want to know whether, as Doctors, you would find these symptoms cause for concern. If so, I will push my GP to paying closer attention.

Further background: 24yo F Healthy weight, eats well, exercises regularly, normal blood pressure, previously noted 'slightly high' heart rate like I was nervous whilst getting tested (didn't feel nervous), no abnormal blood tests save for a single one with low blood proteins (retest was normal, ?lab error). Medication: The Pill and regular paracetamol for headaches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh you sweet Summer child. Kids in outback Australia are feeling rain...for the first time ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 03:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stay classy Brisbane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 05:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Better buy 5 more </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 10:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSW man arrested for marrying a 12 year old girl in Australia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 01:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did I only just figure this out now?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 22:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dad just got a new bike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 11:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a girl walking home from an overnight shift, getting frightened by shadows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 19:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He looks pretty excited about the prospect </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 07:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Miniature cows have maximum awww </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 04:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what is the most expensive mistake you have made at work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 05:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just left a $2000 tube of reagent on the counter in my lab over the weekend, ruining it.

Beat that.

Edit: This is great! When I eventually get yelled at by the boss, I can just show her this and tell her life isn't that bad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Promises </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 22:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A conversation between my husband and I last night.

Husband: Hey train_subject889, remember the promise you made that you wouldn't let your crochet take over the house?

Me: Yeah...

Husband: Well, you broke it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I didn't have a pattern, but I was able to make a Bride and Groom for my sister-in-law and her fiance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 12:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dog smiles when you scratch her chest (Sorry for blurriness) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 23:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Winter is still 5 months away but I am prepared! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 13:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australian travelling to Boston to see the Pats play in October. Are there any special tickets I can buy to surprise my husband with that give a greater experience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 22:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My hubby is Pats mad. He has been following them since he was little, despite none of his family having any interest in the game. He just watched them play one day and hasn't stop watching since.

We are travelling to America in October this year and although there are many things on our to-do list, the whole trip will be based around us getting to Boston amd seeing a Pats home game.

Now, hubby will have his bday while we are over there, so I am hoping to find some sort of 'special experience' tickets to surprise him with. I'm thinking VIP box, stadium tour, anything like that. Hell, if I can somehow get him in the same room as Tom Brady, he would probably pass out with joy.

So, can anyone help me? Point me in the direction of a place I can get this? Or even just tell me if it is possible/affordable?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bought some wonderfully soft 30% milk protein yarn and need ideas to use it! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 05:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/uEcQCFI.jpg

I bought 7 x 50g balls just because they were on sale for $1.20 but now I don't know what to do with it.

It is gorgeously soft and slippery and feels magic against my skin, so I was hoping to make something like a jumper or shawl. But I haven't found any pattern that would work with the glossy, slippery nature of the yarn.

Suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crochet people are the nicest people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 23:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once or twice a week I sit next to a lady on the train who is an avid crocheter, like me. We first spoke when she complimented me on my amugurumi kitty I was working on. Over the weeks we have had great chats, discussing our favourite yarn brands, the best stitches and new patterns we have found. I look forward to my train trips now and enjoy our chats immensely.

This morning, the nice lady delivered on a promise I hadn't really expected her to keep and gave me a bag full of cashmere yarns with the condition that I make another kitty out of it just so she could see how it turned out.

I was very thankful and happy that someone would be so friendly and giving to a complete stranger, without expecting anything in return. 

Crocheters really are the nicest people! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a wedding coming up and am wearing this dress. Can anyone suggest what style of shoes I should wear? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 15:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> List of 17 items banned from central Brisbane (Aust.) during the G20 Summit - includes kites, eggs and lizards. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 04:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They are never funny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 02:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For Christmas, my step-mother just enabled my addiction. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 23:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My husband likes rotary engines, so I made him this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 10:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what out-of-the-box gift are you giving this year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 21:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And that, children, is why you should never buy plastic hooks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 23:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The last picture did it for me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 02:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what is your most embarrassing story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 11:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today I suffered some major embarrassment. Please help me realise that other people have it worse than me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My kitty, all finished :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 03:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made a friend. He brought me a flower :D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 12:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel like Frankenstein, putting his monster together... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 12:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Harlequin Beetle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 14:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To my sister and her husband with their 6 children aged 1, 4, 6, 6, 7, 7... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 13:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just opened the package of craft supplies to find this. Thanks random packager </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 01:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First gay couples legally marry in Australia. But their marriages may be short with the Law already being challenged </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 23:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My freckle is heart-shaped </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 05:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made a monkey [x-post fron r/pics] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 21:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made a monkey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 13:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bought a fancy loaf from the bakery. Pulled it out to inspect a few days later... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 23:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit is having a party; based on your username, what kind of guest are you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 04:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My neighbour's newest little addition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 22:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made this :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 13:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lady at work. She asked me to help her eat right, but ignores me everytime I tell her she should rethink what she is eating and then later complains about her weight and asks for my help again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 05:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the spirit of Rememberence Day, I found a crocheted poppy pattern. (Crafty Lion) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 00:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fun sized isn't very fun anymore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 11:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My husband dropped this one on me last night. It was a rare deep insight from him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 09:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lady at work is a Good Girl Mum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 22:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well, yes I do know actually... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 08:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remember, remember the 5th of November. Reddit, how do you thumb your nose at da Man on a mundane, daily basis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 23:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, protesting out the front of corrupt government building is cool and all, but what about us unsung heroes?

What is your mundane protest? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This trick just saved me $45 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 04:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little penguin is getting ready for Christmas :D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 12:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made a crocheting pillow with pockets for my hooks, yarn and other accessories. Not bad for my first time on a sewing machine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 23:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little crochet owlie, now with hat! [X-post from r/pics] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 11:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recently took up a hobby. This is one of my creations :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 11:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Close enough </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 16:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally finished my 6month-long winter throw project! Too bad it is now Spring </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 11:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What common word/phrase did you always mispronounce? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 05:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's the little wins that make your day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 09:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walking home from work, get overtaken by this guy. Did not catch whether he had a handlebar moustache or not </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 09:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found this little nipper at the beach today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 07:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what mundane task causes you to lose your shit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 22:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everybody else is cool, calm and collected doing these tasks, meanwhile you are blowing your lid because... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone heard of a company called Vemma and their 'business plans' for young people? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 23:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My step brother is interested in signing up for a business opportunity provided by a company called Vemma. The model is based on sales of healthy products supplied by the company as well as membership sign up.

 You have to pay to recieve the product and then your sales numbers and how many people you get to join equate to an income. They aren't talking huge dollars for the most part but it seems a little too easy.

It has been labelled a pyramid scheme, and I am not certain but I can see why it would be called that. [This]( http://yprzone.com/) is their website and [this] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QtSmuX9ID5o feature=youtube_gdata_player) is their video.

Does anyone know anything about them? Have any horror or success stories? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, meet the Cuscus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 15:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aussie logic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 15:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After being reminded that Big Brother is in its 10th season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 14:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First World Skinny Girl Problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 12:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turns out our dog makes an excellent gaming cushion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 12:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was expecting a lot more when my coworker said she had the WORST lunchbreak ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 11:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend's kitten, Sir Winston, has such pretty green eyes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-14 10:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sometimes us women are our own worst enemies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 00:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Same can be said for Chinese food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 12:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I never realised how damn big a B-52 was! (Low res) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 10:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And I will usually assume you are a bad parent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 02:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let us all take a moment from our busy lives and enjoy this picture of a tiny goat suckling my thumb </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 07:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rule #34 of Microbiology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 08:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sort out your priorities, people! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 12:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You all better be bacon-haters who think adult pigs are adorable...or I don't think I could stand the hypocricy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 22:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This isn't Facebook, people! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 15:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 7 Dog-Year Itch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 09:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, which would you prefer to know: the year of your death or the cause of your death? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 00:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And once you know it is unchangable...no avoiding it.

No suicide, that's cheating! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got home from a 12hour shift with the promise of Noodle Box awaiting me. Nice presentation, husband! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 14:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I must be looking in the wrong dumpsters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-05 01:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A woman (I assume) left this on my husband's windscreen while he was at the gym. She is bold, I'll give her that. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 13:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She was such a goofy puppy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 10:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My inner Nerd had a good chuckle at this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 03:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi r/crochet. I am making a granny square patchwork quilt and need some advice! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-29 00:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys! I am making a 12x12 granny square quilt. I am 56 squares in and still undecided about how I will join them all together.

I have narrowed it down to two techniques:

The [slip stitch]( http://attic24.typepad.com/weblog/joining-granny-sqaures.html) method

Or the [invisible stitch]( http://doyoumindifiknit.typepad.com/do_you_mind_if_i_knit/2010/02/joining-up-with-an-invisible-stitch.html) method.

So I am wondering if there is anyone out there who has used either/both of these methods who can give me some pros and cons. I dont mind that the slip stich is visible from the back but I do mind if i get unsightly ridges or awkward edges at the front.

[Here]( http://imgur.com/Vx1xfsr) is a pic of my progress :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New way to earn Karma! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 05:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't even have a bath without an audience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 11:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Allie Brosh's book is out. Hyperbole and a Half: Unfortunate Situations, Flawed Coping Mechanisms, Mayhem, and Other Things That Happened </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 04:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It didn't help that I had a cold at the time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 10:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first real project </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 15:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, who is your shame-crush? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 06:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know who I mean. That one celebrity everyone hates that you think is smokin hot. You can't bring yourself to admit your nasty feelings to your friends, so tell Reddit instead. No judgement here, friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We have a pressurised DNA extraction room at work. Today it was on the fritz. I almost passed out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 08:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We had to talk a lady at work out of doing this. It would have been child abuse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-26 13:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help for finding uses for a large amount of 12ply yarn. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 23:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am very new to crocheting and after bravely setting out to make a nice throw using 12ply yarn, I quickly discovered I was out of my depth. My throw started as a scarf, but I found it was too stiff with the 12ply so I carried on widening it, making a throw. 

I went out and bought heaps of the yarn I was using so I didn't run out, thinking I was a genius for stockpiling it.

But halfway through I realised my throw was just as stiff as my scarf...so I unravelled it.

Now, I am stuck with about 5 HUGE balls of purple 12ply yarn and neither the skills nor the knowledge to turn it into something useful.

So can anyone help me out with suggestions for a basic pattern I can use to get rid of all this yarn? Everything I try seems too intricate for it's thickness, or requires various colours when all I have is the purple... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm sure someone is going to let me know if THIS is a repost </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-22 15:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After seeing the news from Russia, all I could think was how lucky I am to live in a country that not only openly accepts gays, we vote them in! [X-post from r/politics] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 14:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do we get songs stuck in our heads and why is it so hard to get them out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 14:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I like the message this comic sends but not the visuals. Does anyone know of a better version or are willing to make one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-27 14:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uhh...what? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 22:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dog also enjoys playing with inanimate objects. These are her best friends, Nut and Rock. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 03:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend's dog had puppies. So much cute! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 13:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not foolproof, but still effective </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 11:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the few perks of getting up early on a cold, Autumn morning. I need to start appreciating the simple things in life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-19 23:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Khal Drogo. (Sorry about poor image quality) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-18 13:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think that just because Angelina Jolie had a masectomy, that is no reason for the media to be hailing her as a hero. CMV. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 23:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, what she did was hard, no denying that and attention on women's health is usually a good thing. But the media needs to stop glorifying sick celebrities. It portrays them as the benchmarks and 'poster-children' for a disease when, as wealthy and famous individuals with access to almost endless medical resources, they are in the best possible position while sick. 

Common people, like struggling single mothers and embattled pensioners have more reason to be called inspirations than celebrities. 

Furthermore, the media lauding these famous people as inspirations creates unrealistic expectations for normal people coping with the same situations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As an Australian, this is the impression I get of American Springtime. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-14 06:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Day 3 without my nose. I am starting to doubt whether my nose ever truly existed..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 01:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
