<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2590</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 04:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Q: What do you call a cheap circumcision? 
A: A rip off. 
Only ever get groans of disgust lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 04:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took me 8 reads to realize there was nothing wrong with it. You rotten redditers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that as "and it was the highlight of my life" 
I really need to read more carefully when I'm on reddit...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 15:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently hit that age where I'm doing it twice a week, aflush with cash, and confident in life and my assertions of right and wrong (lol let's see how long that lasts). Still living with my Parents (both of whom are undergoing serious midlife-crises). Life is good :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 01:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *of
Well good! I'd far prefer for abused people to grow up and become happy and productive members of society. Unfortunately for me, I'm stuck with my asshole of a cousin who, for some unfathomable reason, has decided she doesn't want to fit in with the demographic that you so eloquently pointed out exists. Imagine that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 00:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you're not *just* a cum bucket. You're a cum bucket filled with nerves who just said that it feels great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 00:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *little boy walks in. Sees grown man laying on floor with pants around ankles urinating straight into the air. Little boy walks out* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 00:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nearly every major pc game that has come out after 2014 is unplayable unless you have an $800+ computer. I mean, I can turn down the graphics and visual settings pretty dang far, but when you're playing with the same resolution as an ipod touch things are just a little bit ridiculous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 00:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know one abused girl. She is a huge asshole. She also happens to be my cousin and lives with me. 
I dunno where you got your info but from personal experience abused people are jerks. Everyone always says "you don't know what she went through" but I mean c'mon, it was for like a year when she was 6. That's no excuse to be an ass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 00:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait but you just said sex feels great. If you believe that it feels great, why are you not doing it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 00:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes they are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 06:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I CAME IN LIKE A- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 00:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://cdn.meme.am/instances/250x250/55671949.jpg 
Laughed my ass off at this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 00:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you rather watch porn of your parents or with your parents?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 22:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh from chat roulette?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 02:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd have Miley Cyrus stop singing and start doing por- 
Wait a second...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 18:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you poor thing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 18:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true. You've got that going for you. Reddit loves you 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 18:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's dead Jim  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 18:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to read this 3 times before I accepted the fact that it was real  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 01:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He says where you WOULD put your finger. Not just where it's physically possible to put it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
