<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5937</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 00:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That I won the birth lottery by being born in the US.

The trick with winning the lottery is to use it wisely and not piss it away.

EDIT: [A world map of the measles outbreaks in 2013](http://www.measlesrubellainitiative.org/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/mmr_outbreaks_cropped-640x360.png)

Outbreaks are NOT in Central and South America.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 00:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes: "The World Health Organization reported this week that 113 countries, including China, Russia, Iran and Libya, have higher immunization rates than the United States for 1-year-olds."

"data from the World Health Organization shows that measles-vaccination rates in Mexico and Central America are higher than the U.S. rate of 92 percent"

[Chart](http://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/preview/mmwrhtml/figures/m743a4t1.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 23:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [With veins](http://media.nzherald.co.nz/webcontent/image/jpg/20156/ba250530e8502687e283aa5e238d1e48884ff389_460x230.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 23:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compton Rate of Drinking Municipal Water: 93.80% 

Beverly Hills Rate of Buying Bottled Water (that is Actually Municipal Water): 78.33% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 23:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to World Health Organization estimates, the U.S. has a measles vaccination rate of 92 percent, while **Mexico and Nicaragua have 99 percent vaccination rates** and Honduras, Guatemala, and El Salvador each have 93 percent vaccination rates. If anything, those countries should be concerned about Americans coming down to visit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 23:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was right to stop it then, it is right to stop it now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 22:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take shells 1 and 2 in your hand, and form them together like a clam shell. Make sure you can grasp with them.

Grab hold of the feces with the shells and pull them out. Continue until all large bits have been removed.

Use shell 3 to scrape (be gentle!) and remove anything you might have missed.

Wash (or flush) the shells, wash your bottom with warm water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 22:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  when professionals mix their personal advice in with their professional advice

This is their profession. XYZ Healing Arts practitioners offer a wide range of therapies for healing body and mind including: Acupuncture, Chiropractic, Homeopathy, Massage Therapy, Physical Therapy.

I went in for Chiropractic, Massage and Physical Therapy and they did a great job. Thus I just tolerated the homeopathic advice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 19:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I made the above post, I read other posts and analysis.

The "Memorandum" is not a treaty - it is an agreement.

In the case of aggression, the remedy "if Ukraine should become a victim of *an act of aggression* or *an object of a threat of aggression in which nuclear weapons are used*" is to seek immediate United Nations Security Council action to provide assistance to Ukraine.

Morally I believe the U.S. made a commitment that it needs to keep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 18:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you Google "nightshade foods" you will find many suggestion that they can cause indigestion (and other intestinal issues) and joint pain. Since I was pretty shaken up in the car accident he recommended avoiding nightshades  - at least until my back recovered (which it did - I'm fine now). He did great physical therapy work, so I politely tolerated his homeopathy suggestions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 18:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  translation into different languages

If you want a real answer, I would suggest calling a librarian. They are amazing with topics like this, and they generally love the chance to answer questions like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 18:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nightshade also includes eggplant and tobacco. I had a physical therapist (after an auto accident) tell me to avoid all nightshades. F*** that - I love them all way too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 18:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, but I'm guessing there are many translations.

You can get free e-book versions since it's in the public domain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 12:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "Budapest Memorandum on Security Assurances" is a diplomatic memorandum signed in December 1994 by Ukraine, Russia, the United States, and the United Kingdom under which signatories made promises to each other as part of the denuclearization of former Soviet republics after the dissolution of the Soviet Union. Ukraine promised to remove all nuclear weapons, and kept this promise.

In return, Russia and the Western signatory countries essentially consecrated the sovereignty and territorial integrity of Ukraine as an independent state. In the "Budapest Memorandum," Russia, the United Kingdom, and the United States promised that none of them would ever threaten or use force against the territorial integrity or political independence of Ukraine. They also pledged that none of them would ever use economic coercion to subordinate Ukraine to their own interest. They also pledged to protect Ukraine if its security was threatened.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 11:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meat with nightshade - a Shakespearean pizza  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 11:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When post-Cold War Ukraine gained independence, it held the worlds third-largest stockpile of nuclear weapons. Rather than use nukes for protection, Ukraine sought and received assurances from the international community that its borders would be respected if it gave up its nuclear weapons. In 1994, the U.S., United Kingdom and Russia signed the Budapest Memorandum, in which **all sides pledged to respect Ukraines territorial integrity, refrain from using military force or economic pressure to limit Ukrainian sovereignty and provide assistance to Ukraine if it became the victim of aggression from another nation**.

Obviously, Russia has broken its part of that agreement. Now the question is whether the US will break theirs.

**If the U.S. breaks their word, they should consider the devastating impact on American counter proliferation efforts around the world**. How could any nation ever trust U.S. security assurances if they see, in the carnage and destruction in Ukraine, **the deadly folly of trading nuclear weapons for American guarantees**? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jordanian king quotes Clint Eastwood to express rage after ISIS execution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 09:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 08:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That the "Berenstain Bears" were once spelled "Berenstein" and that it proves that they're from a parallel universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 08:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And gum chewing - smack Smack SMACK **SMACK** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 08:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get the "strong compulsion" of nail biting, and how difficult it can be to stop the habit.

However - mine is very controlled, never in public, and only when the corner skin is built up (slightly calloused) so I'm basically trimming it. It's clearly "an irrational love". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 07:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Faith . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 07:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love biting the skin at my [distal nail folds](http://www.healthhype.com/wp-content/uploads/nail_parts_top.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 07:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Left Shark? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 06:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That God does not exit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 06:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Left Shark action wear** (if you have to ask, you're not my demographic) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 06:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only know what I have [read recently, such as](http://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2015/02/03/national/politics-diplomacy/constitutional-change-necessary-protect-japanese-citizens-abe/#.VNL6jUfF8SM):

After being unable to save two hostages held by Middle Eastern extremists, Prime Minister Shinzo Abe said constitutional change will be needed to protect the lives and assets of Japanese citizens.

Abe has said at times that with the current interpretation of Article 9, which forbids both the use of force to settle international disputes and the maintenance of regular armed forces, it is difficult to protect Japanese citizens in a changing security environment.

The Liberal Democratic Party has already presented a draft amendment to Article 9, and amending it is to carry out our duty of protecting the lives and assets of Japanese citizens, Abe told the Upper House Budget Committee on Tuesday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 06:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should be awesome, it's by Sun Tzu - the Art of War </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 05:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try very hard to **keep my posts positive**. But it's hard, especially when the truth is they're the weak. And I'm the tyranny of evil men. But I'm tryin', Ringo. I'm tryin' real hard to be the shepherd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 05:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet - they are considering changing their constitution so they can use their military for offense, not just homeland defense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 05:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The king who advances without coveting fame and retreats without fearing disgrace, whose only thought is to protect his country and do good service for his sovereign, is the jewel of the kingdom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 05:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happens after an explosion at a cheese factory? 

All thats left is de brie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 05:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or better yet - make it "opt-in". If I have to work to exclude tweets, I have one word for Google . . . 

**BING!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 04:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When post-Cold War Ukraine gained independence, it held the worlds third-largest stockpile of nuclear weapons. Rather than use nukes for protection, Ukraine sought and received assurances from the international community that its borders would be respected if it gave up its nuclear weapons. In 1994, the U.S., United Kingdom and Russia signed the Budapest Memorandum, in which **all sides pledged to respect Ukraines territorial integrity, refrain from using military force or economic pressure to limit Ukrainian sovereignty and provide assistance to Ukraine if it became the victim of aggression from another nation.** 

Obviously, Russia has broken its part of that agreement. Now the question is whether the US will break theirs. 

**If the U.S. breaks their word, they should consider the devastating impact on American counter proliferation efforts around the world**. How could any nation ever trust U.S. security assurances if they see, in the carnage and destruction in Ukraine, **the deadly folly of trading nuclear weapons for American guarantees**? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 04:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LPT: Try not lying to your friends. 

PS - most photos have a time stamp embedded so you'd be a liar, and busted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 04:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guy Code - as a California resident, this is why I will never vote for [Gavin Newsom](http://www.sfgate.com/politics/article/AIDE-QUITS-AS-NEWSOM-S-AFFAIR-WITH-HIS-WIFE-IS-2652745.php) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 00:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Zenni - I just ordered two pairs from them - one for daily use (with magnetic "clip on" sunglasses made to fit the frame), and a spare pair to leave in the car in case I lose/break the main pair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 23:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pupillary Distance (PD) is often INTENTIONALLY left off the prescription by the doc to try to force you to buy the glasses from them. 

Zenni has instructions on their website that tells you how to measure your PD (it's best done with help from a friend).

PS - I love Zenni. They even have models with magnetic "clip on" sunglasses. If you order these I recommend getting an extra/backup "clip on" if you plan to use it frequently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 07:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many have asked - what does this accomplish? 

If nothing else, **two ISIS bargaining chips have been removed  from the table**. (I would propose that the other chips should also be cashed in as soon as "judicially" possible.)

These two terrorist murderers were already sentenced to death, and ISIS forced the issue - - so death to ISIS terrorists it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 05:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sajida al-Rishawi was already on death row. She was sentenced to death by hanging by a Jordanian military court on 21 September 2006.

Al-Karbouly was sent to death row in 2008 for plotting terror attacks on Jordanians in Iraq. 

Their just sentences have now been carried out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 05:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found one answer: Al-Karbouly was sent to death row in 2008 for plotting terror attacks on Jordanians in Iraq.His sentence has now been carried out - he was hanged Wednesday morning. . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Were the ISIS prisoners that Jordan will execute (other than Rishawi) already sentenced to death before the pilot was brutally murdered? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 01:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple avoids US taxes by issuing $6.5B in bonds rather than bringing home funds from $157B held by foreign subsidiaries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 01:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft may have found the perfect way to cap Google at the knees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 00:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: When you get great service in a store, ask their name, go to your car, call the store manager, and complement the employee. It makes all 3 of you feel great. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 23:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: When you get great service in a store, ask their name, go to your car, call the store manager, and complement the employee. It makes all 3 of you feel great. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 22:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 50 Percent of US Pregnancies are Unplanned  High Use of Painkillers Increases Risk of Birth Defects  per CDC Study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 02:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sony Seeks to Delay Full Earnings Report on Studio Hacking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 19:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sony Seeks to Delay Full Earnings Report on Studio Hacking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 18:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:Why does Reddit automatically decrease karma points and votes on high scoring posts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 03:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tracked the karma points and votes of a front-page post (not mine) for a couple hours and Reddit reduced the scores twice. Is this typical? And why is this done? [Heres a chart of the points.](http://i.imgur.com/EwvmKzs.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Pimps wear lots of gold jewelry bought at pawn shops to re-pawn for bail money since cash is confiscated upon arrest but jewelry is not </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 00:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Russia Banned the Four Most Important Mat Curse Words  Cannes award winner and Oscar nominated Russian film Leviathan will have to bleep obscenities in Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 23:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Putin Banned Russia's Four Most Important Mat Curse Words  Cannes award winner and Oscar nominated Russian film Leviathan will have to bleep obscenities in Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 19:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Putin Banned Russia's Four Most Important Mat Curse Words  Cannes award winner and Oscar nominated Russian film Leviathan will have to bleep obscenities in Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 19:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Business travelers with kids  When checking into a hotel ask for a postcard. Fill it out immediately and send it home. Make this a habit and your kids will be more OK with your travel schedule. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 04:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Most Americans Admit They Don't Tip Hotel Housekeepers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 03:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most Americans Admit They Don't Tip Hotel Housekeepers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 03:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian Paper Prints Draw-Your-Own Muhammad 'Connect-the-dots' Cartoon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 06:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian Paper Prints Draw-Your-Own Muhammad 'Connect-the-dots' Cartoon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 06:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Threatening words scrawled on jet, attendants fired after refusing to fly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 19:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Allison Williams on Girls Anilingus Scene I had a couple of days  to rig the thing that I wore for the ass motorboating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 03:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why Reddit cares so much more about ~20 dead in Paris than ~2000 dead in Nigeria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 20:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As many as 2,000 people have been killed in Islamist extremist group Boko Haram's deadliest massacre yet in Nigeria. Most victims were children, women and elderly people who could not run fast enough when insurgents drove into the town of Baga, firing rocket-propelled grenades and assault rifles on town residents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cartoonists grieve Paris slaughter with ink and pen: Here are 14 of the best </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 15:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. news media avoid Islam cartoons linked to deadly attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 05:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The inside story of how an Idaho toddler shot his mom at Wal-Mart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 11:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why capitalize Alpha Centauri, Mars, Venus, Earth, and Europa (a moon of Jupiter) but not moon and sun as in: The Earth and moon are warmed by the sun.? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 18:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the AP Stylebook: "Lowercase **sun** and **moon**, but capitalize them if their Greek or Latin names are used: **Helios**, **Luna**."

But why? That does not make any sense to me.

**Edit**: Unless I missed it, no one has any answer as to "**WHY**" moon and sun are generally not capitalized by:

AP Stylebook, Garners Modern American Usage, Merriam-Websters Dictionary of English Usage, the NY Times, and many other literary sources (however scientific sources do tend to capitalize). **The "*WHY*" of the preference not to capitalize is still a mystery**.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: Nearly half the illegals in the US didn't cross the desert or pay a smuggler. They came legally and overstayed their visa. As did the 9/11 terrorists. And the US rate of visa approval has increased dramatically in recent years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 03:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: The "1980 - 2013 Stock Market Returns for Various Indices" are way better than you might think (8% to 13%) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 00:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: The male copulatory organ of many spiders falls off during mating to escape sexual cannibalism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 02:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: In the song 99 Red Balloons, a 99-year war results from the otherwise harmless flight of balloons, causing devastation on all sides without a victor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 05:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: The male copulatory organ of many spiders falls off during mating to escape sexual cannibalism - SCIENTIFICALLY ACCURATE SPIDER-MAN </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 01:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: The Federal Gov. owns about 50% of the land in the west, and less than 5% of the rest of the US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 00:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maybe I shouldn't be hiking here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 10:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 6-pound gold nugget is rock star of S.F. antique show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 20:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: Sweden built a cavernous underground, island naval base capable of withstanding a nuclear attack with 12 miles of subterranean roads in the 1950s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 00:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walking on the beach and, wait, . . . what is going on here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin's Reaction To Sanctions Is Destroying The Economy And China Won't Help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 18:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkish Airstrike Hits Kurds, Complicating Fight Against Islamic State </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 07:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top 50 Serial Killer Moments with Real Footage and Information [14 min] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 06:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What simple thing should you have learned WAY before you finally did? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-06 05:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At 40 it finally dawned on me that between haircuts it's up to me to shave my neck to keep it looking neat. DUH! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine needs to call Putins bluff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 03:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Right to Be Forgotten What search results for your name would you want erased? [Serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 02:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A top EU court ruled Google must amend some search results at the request of ordinary people as a "**right to be forgotten**", saying links to "irrelevant" and outdated data should be **erased on request**.

- In 2012, the European Commission published plans for a "right to be forgotten" law, allowing people to request that data about themselves to be deleted

- Online service providers would have to comply unless they had "legitimate" reason to do otherwise

- The plans are part of a wide-ranging overhaul of the commission's 1995 Data Protection Directive

While this does not apply outside the EU  what would *any* of you want erased? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salad time . . . </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 07:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mosquitoes  See how rain bounces off allowing flight in rainfall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 08:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gene pool stud bragging rights? Future Darwin award? . . . Both . . . </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 04:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who gives a fuck? ... why and how ? I mean ... HOW are you demonstrating that you care? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 08:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After what I've just seen on Reddit, I have to ask. Do you care about others? How are you demonstrating that you care? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parents of Reddit  How would you weigh in on this post about bad parenting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 08:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the post that's getting credit as a good dad](http://imgur.com/4epJWSk)
[and here's the thread](http://www.reddit.com/r/WTF/comments/21p6s7/does_anyone_else_think_this_is_just_bad_parenting/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Koreas exchange fire during North's military exercises </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 07:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BREAKING NEWS: South Korea Opens Fire at North Korea in Retaliation during Live-Fire Drill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 07:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there topics for which Reddit actively removes posts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 06:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this common if you post on certain topics? ... "Looks like you're either a brand new user or your posts have not been doing well recently. You may have to wait a bit to post again." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you successfully posted about T.E.S.|.A on the technology sub-Reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 05:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever successfully posted about T.E.S.L.A on the technology sub-Reddit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 05:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla eyes San Antonio for Gigafactory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 05:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What makes you smile along your daily commute? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 02:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought it was vandalized. Public Works Dept said its correct. New Math? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 23:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On my commute home EVERY DAY - - but wheres the Sharknado? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 21:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My theory . . . </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 23:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lost Malaysian plane: 20 Freescale Semiconductor employees on board. They design and produce embedded hardware   software including "Unmanned Vehicles (Ground, Air, Water)" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 06:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lost Malaysian plane: 20 Freescale Semiconductor employees on board. They design and produce embedded hardware   software including "Unmanned Vehicles (Ground, Air, Water)" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 05:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: Lost Malaysian plane: 20 Freescale Employees on board design and produce embedded hardware   software including "Unmanned Vehicles (Ground, Air, Water)" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 05:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lost Malaysian plane: 20 Freescale Employees on board design and produce embedded hardware   software including "Unmanned Vehicles (Ground, Air, Water)" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 04:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Un-Insured Redditors  Why are you choosing to opt out of Obamacare with the March 31 deadline approaching? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-13 03:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full disclosure - As a consultant, I canceled my small business policy, struggled through the appalling Covered California process, and ended up reducing my rates significantly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Malaysia Airlines jet might have disappeared </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-09 07:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She said "I can't live without you!" . . . So why isn't she dead yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-08 04:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin: "The law is still the law, and we must follow it whether we like it or not. Under current international law, force is permitted only in self-defense or by the decision of the Security Council." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 20:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the banana we grew up with is going extinct (banana provided for scale) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 01:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL - Russian Crimean War debt was so large that Alexander II, realizing the difficulty of defending Alaska, decided to sell it to the United States, in 1867 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 01:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Russian people love Americans but hate our Gov't. We generally like Russians but distrust their Gov't. Is there really no way we, the peoples, can overcome politicians to "just get along"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 06:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Komodo Dragons bite with: teeth like sharks, 50-80 infecting oral bacteria, venom, and can track its kill from 5 miles off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 02:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Keyboards have a second DEL key - how did I never see this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 09:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL My keyboard has a second DEL key - how did I never see this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 08:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One rabbit stew coming right up! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 03:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One rabbit stew comin' right up! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 03:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
