<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6818</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heartwarming positive video [6 min] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 00:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How are zoos able to house exotic animals without being deemed "inhumane"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 00:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not soapboxing! Honestly curious how we are able to have zoos ethically </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL I need updanks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 22:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This video of a man feeding a puma is hilarious/frightening </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 01:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN confirms God is also an Atheist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 19:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Le phone just auto-corrected GOP to DANK 420 times. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 19:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Cisco - The Beach [indietronica] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 05:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ----------- MAKE KANYE SMILE EVERYTIME YOU PRESS THIS BUTTON. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 04:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video of why you shouldn't tip waiters.. Only hats m'lady </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 13:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kings fan here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 05:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I love the Bucks...  Idk why but they are my East coast team.  They play with amazing style.  I have made alot betting on them because the critics give the spread so high against the Bucks...  Have pride in your team because I give you 2 years to be a contender.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These online advertisements are getting extreme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 20:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Cousins article talks more about Lillard than Cousins... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 20:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: When and how does a baby chicken realize it's in an egg and needs to get out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 10:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL who Mike Jones is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 10:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What person do you wish you could make just shut the f*ck up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 10:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the best freebies I should know about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 03:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like things like free grand slams on your bday at Dennys... What are some other tricks we should know?  Redbox promo codes, free food,  etc?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your master plan to get gold!? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 01:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your opinions on Russell? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 19:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are some of his most important works to read?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Jackie Chan has starred in multiple porno films. His penis is 20cm long. He also goes by the name Zach. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 02:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am Bill Gates monies... We are dank as fuck. AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 00:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do you dislike the Kardashians? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 18:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What "famous" person were you excited to meet but were extremely disappointed with the interaction? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 08:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What exactly are numbers? Do they imply truth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 06:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are numbers? Do they imply truth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 04:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly are numbers?  My professor and I were in discussion about them and he implied that numbers are entities separate from physics,  math,  and science.  We *use* them and apply them but math in itself doesn't imply truth...  Have you heard this and can someone explain his logic?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Brady has been virtually fumble free since he proposed a rule in 2006. Take a guess. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 19:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is gravity an incomplete theory? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 17:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard that we need to reorganize our theory of gravity.  Is this true?  If so,  what does this mean and why?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You are writing a book about your life.. What is the title? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 00:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alien apocalypse happens right now. Where are you and what do you do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 00:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I get Alzheimers... When I get Alzheimers.. When I get Alzheimers.. When I get Alzheimers.. When I get Alzheimers.. When I get Alzheimers.. When I get Alzheimers.. When I get Alzheimers.. When I get Alzheimers.. When I get Alzheimers.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 12:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gang signs are slang in sign language. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 12:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some of your best study tips for school? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 07:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't seem to get back into the school groove.  What are some study tips and habits?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is it that the Ukrainian crisis is barely a concern now that ISIS has risen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 06:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems as if the US just said fuck that crisis over there as Russia continues to wage war when at the beginning,  the US was threatening action.  The timing of ISIS seems to perfect.  Could Russia have helped the start this secretly?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When a police officer dies and they have a memorial.. Who patrols the streets? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 05:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serious question. I want to know if someone passes away in law enforcement, it looks like everyone that's a  cop attends.  Who is patrolling or working? Wouldn't this be the time to do a crime?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interesting video of how Jellyfish sting. (6 min) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 03:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts on Westbrook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 00:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have thought for the last couple years that Westbrook deserves his own team like the Celtics and then build around him. I just don't like how Westbrook is a 2nd option. Do you think that he should have him own team?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kings fan: History </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 06:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope you enjoyed this as much as I enjoyed losing to this.  kt is incredible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is with Rudy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 06:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pointed this out a few weeks ago.  ruby just collected his 7th technical of the season.  For a guy with a usually quiet demeanor,  this has been a big sign of him changing.  What do you think has happened?  We can't afford both our stars collecting 20+ techs a season. Ruby never got techs like this before this season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something unique about yourself that you would like people to know? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 04:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]What is the best way to improve your singing voice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 23:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your craziest college memory? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 08:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CAN is to have a memorial marathon of Aladdin in order to celebrate the life of the Saudi King. Am snigle BTW. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 02:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wanna recognize JT. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 20:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO Jason Thompson gets a lot of crap as a starting PF.  He has been a staple on our defense and has improved throughout the years.  He has been the longest standing King on the team and is amazing in the community. Relatively humble and hasn't had attitude problems. 

There is not one person on the that we have tried to replace more then him.  He has outplayed numerous candidates like T-rob,  Landry,  Patterson, Evans and Acy. Always been a fan but I believe he deserves more credit.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that if you buy a subscription to porches, you get a free tour inside one of the grils in the videos. I am a gril in one of the videos. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 16:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW JENNY PLAYED WITH MY PENIS. ONLY A LITTLE. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 06:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who are some players who on paper deserve to be in HOF but probably won't make it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 06:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ----------- How many people on Reddit tryna run train on Jenny's dank puss puss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 05:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do businesses have the right to refuse service? And to what extent? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 23:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starbucks announced today that they are extending pumpkin spice drinks in light of Jenny being basic bitch. [Confirmed] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 19:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link right here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that man was arrested for giving his dying daughter cannabis oil to ease the pain even when it had positive results. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 19:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> pope says "Birth control ban doesn't mean funk Zach or X". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 07:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LOST FEDORA! PLEASE HELP ME FIND IT. ! M'LADY NEEDS A DANK HAT TIP! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 06:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jus for kix </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ryan Reynolds shot dead in a pool in him hometown in Vancouver. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 22:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL fruit stickers are dank. Fruit is dank. Stickers are dank. And Jenny snatch is Dankiest of dank. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 19:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ayyyyyyyy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snoop Dogg is at a loss for words when a street child asks him what dank is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 18:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the denkiest danks I can buy on Pornhub for $69-$420? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 12:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by fapping to dank tent porn. I'm snigle gril 34. Pictures in comments. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 11:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 12th man right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 10:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gravity machine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 10:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where is a good place to volunteer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 07:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to help out the community and environment .  I am interested in planting trees,  feeding the homeless, etc.  I have checked out habitat for humanity but got no response. If anyone knows of anything,  please let me know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SO is interested in my meditation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 05:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have started growing in my meditation and knowledge and continue to grow.  my SO is interested in meditating and Buddhism with me but I feel uncomfortable with it.  I feel like it is my thing for myself and a mental release.  I also feel I have only been learning for a few months.  I feel it would make us closer but still hesitant. How do you guys deal with this? Any advice?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] What was your interaction with the Loch Ness Monster like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 04:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit... What is your story of when you met the Loch Ness Monster? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 04:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These crackahs wanna here a story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bar chord tips </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 23:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am having issues adjusting to bar chord transitions and barring the strings.  Any good websites,  videos or tips!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that researchers in Africa has trimmed lions manes into dankish chin beards. This has increased mating with grill lions by $9.99. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 20:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the difference between Jimmy Fallon and myself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 09:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is rich and I am on Reddit circlejerk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is your favorite current player? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 06:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the Kings and why?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Cat Stevens (creator of "Peace Train") is an Islam convert and was denied access to America due to suspicion or terrorist ties in 2004. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 03:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama says erection should exist but he should be able to unerect it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 23:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "God" allows you to change 1 thing in the world... What do you do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 23:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am one of the few people who hate Comcast. AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 06:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is Jack Box's Wikipedia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 06:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here is a Jack Box's Wikipedia.. Just cause </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 05:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You end up trapped in an elevator with the last person who pissed you off... What happens? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 05:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let us put this in perspective..  Elevator is broken...  That is why you are trapped.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]What is the nicest thing you have ever witness someone do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 03:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How are casinos going out of business? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 23:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand how they go out of business..  Lack of revenue.  But I don't really understand how you have cities like Atlantic city going under and whole companies like Caesars Entertainment going under. Are people not gambling?  Why the sudden crash when the economy is on the come up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you had $10, what is the best way to spend it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 21:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 01:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love your guys posts here and everyone is so informing. There is a new sub /r/sharingreligion that is curious about people's testimonies and stories. It is an awesome way to spread the word. Just wanted to thank you guys! Good way to help those looking at Islam for a chance to get info.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 00:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love your guys posts here and everyone is so informing. There is a new sub/r/sharingreligion that is curious about people's testimonies and stories. It is an awesome way to spread the word. Just wanted to thank you guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi you guys! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 23:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love your guys posts here and everyone is so informing.  There is a new sub /r/sharing religion that is curious about people's testimonies and stories.  It is an awesome way to spread the word.  Just wanted to thank you guys!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lose Cannon turned Christian and realized no religion mattered. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 10:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Growing up I had a family of 5 including myself.  My mother and father were divorced and very bitter people.  My mother was a Irish Catholic who drank often and suffered from emotional issues.  My father was a military Protestant who was semi abusive.  I was very rebellious growing up but fairly intelligent.  I read frequently and often pondered about philosophy and science. I was not forced into church except Easter of course for the grandma.  I was involved with partying and fighting in high school while being involved with the wrong crowd.  I eventually met a girl who introduced me to a christian church. I loved the fellowship and was engulfed with positive emotion.  I eventually did mission trips and became proactive in the church. My relationship with this girl seized and I focused on Jesus.  I eventually met a girl who I just loved.  Only issue was she was very immersed deep into the ranks at the church.  We started dating and this caused a mini uproar.  I was reprimanded, chastised,  tormented and disrespected by church officials for this relationship. Hypocrisy oozed out faster than I could have imagined.  Eventually I left my position as a youth group leader,  Bible study leader and Sunday school teacher because of this. I turned my back on religion because I realized that religion is made by people for people.  Dogma is just that... dogma. I eventually went back to reading my philosophy.  Nietzsche, Kafka,  Kant,  Schopenhauer and Hume all played a huge impact on my life.  I studied life as I am now finishing my BA in Philosophy.  My focus is religious studies. I was still left with a void until about a year ago I discovered Buddhism. I study and practice meditation,  Buddhism and Taoism.  I study the lifestyle...  Not the religion.  I believe that each person's life is for them to explore.  I realized Christianity is a very corrupt religion when it comes to their church but has taught me numerous things.  I believe one should explore all facets of their lives. This journey isn't over for me but just beginning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite cereal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 05:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best session I have ever had </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 05:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to share with you guys that I had the best Meditation session to date.  Not that I am grading them or one better than the other, this one was just very different.  I was sitting there in breathe for a few minutes when I began doing some chants as usual.  Maybe it was just one of those busy weeks but everything seemed to slow down.  I was very aware of my surroundings and very focused.  I returned to breathe easily and felt very content.  Sorry just wanted to share with you guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why don't we have a motorcycle lane? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 01:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was driving on a very busy freeway when I saw the usual crazy motorcyclist weaving through traffic. I then thought how efficient it would be to have a motorcycle lane. A small lane like the bike lane to the right of the fast lane. Prevent deaths, injuries, and vehicle damage. More people would be inclined to take advantage of this safe benefit and now we have a green solution to car emission and less money on gas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yeah... sounds about right. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 20:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yeah.. sounds about right. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 20:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is one musician/band who has changed your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 10:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why not have a motorcycle lane? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 05:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was driving on a very busy freeway when I saw the usual crazy motorcyclist weaving through traffic. I then thought how efficient it would be to have a motorcycle lane. A small lane like the bike lane to the right of the fast lane. Prevent deaths, injuries, and vehicle damage. More people would be inclined to take advantage of this safe benefit and now we have a green solution to car emission and less money on gas.

Edited:spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You have received news you have a terminal illness, What do you use your Make-a-wish on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 01:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Kombucha a fad or are their benefits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 00:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good unwritten social rules everyone should know? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 06:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you guys feel about sharing deodorant sticks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 05:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> International Redditors, Were you taught about The World Wars and how was it taught? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 00:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it in depth? How does it differ than how it is taught in America? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wasn't Muhammad quoted saying "Don't mistake me for a God like the Christians have mistaken my brother Christ"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 20:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else like Glen Rice Jr. in college? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 21:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed his play and I think he can be developed. I think he would be a good pick up now that the Wizards released him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do Tibetan monks protest by Self-immolation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 21:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that they are above pain and suffering and that death is the easing of suffering but isn't killing yourself killing a living being? What is the point of this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you were a kid, what would you brag about you dad to other kids? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 00:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Westboro Church still around? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 22:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How has nobody done anything to them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is one celebrity that you were happy failed in their career? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 10:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could live in any time in history.. When would you live? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 20:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, do looks not matter as much if a person is talented? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 23:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you more willing to date a guy/girl who normally wouldn't seem attractive superficially but has an incredible talent?

Ed Sheeran effect.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 23:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please... I beg you guys to stop whining about the FO. It hasnt even been a month without Malone.. Shit happens and we move on. OUR OWNERSHIP GAVE YOU A TEAM!!! Why are we questioning them so soon? You all thought a 6-1 start was our championship debut and you are expecting Corbin to jump right in and take us to the championship?

Same people wanting Malone back were crying about his rotations earlier. Have faith please and enjoy. This is the calming before the storm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secret Santa is an artist and he sent me one of his pieces! Thanks! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 10:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nahhhhh... Vivek is to smart... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 08:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We were 6-1 leading the league in RPG. Our plays have (I am assuming) the same ones Ty Corbin has been running with Malone since he got here. We have lost our fire and the team is off rhythm... sobbing up and down the floor and losing within winning margins by losing teams. Our TO are HORRIBLE!!

Why get rid of Malone? When we were winning...? Makes no sense unless you wanted to lose perhaps?

Falling bottom ten secures our 1st round pick (which we dont have for a few years), allows newbies developmental time (as we have seen with Nik and Ray. We got Rudy to sign and now we blame Corbin for our failure.. We polish up next year with George Karl. Otherwise I can't make sense of this... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Physics demand a creator to our current knowledge? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 03:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simply up to this point... Whether it will later or not isn't relevant.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else want to see Klitschko vs Wilder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 16:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can it happen? Will it happen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Older Redditors, Which was your favorite time period to live in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 05:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which period in time was most memorable to you and why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boogie Cuz and Rudy on top All-star return ballots. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 21:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you guys view hunting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 19:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your view on hunting? For or against it? Why?

Edit: I ask because I am at my SO house and her family are all really huge hunters. I have nothing against guns but we were watching hunting shows and they were shooting bucks... they went into the Bucks home and baited them in the illusion of mating and in turn shot them with a bow. Just doesn't sit right.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who was a historical figured who influenced you the most? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 11:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favorite sayings/figures of speech to use.? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 21:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a salesman and I love one liners.. what do you guys got! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do men still have nipples? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 09:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't hold any biological benefit at all. So why do men have them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some of the main chants you guys use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 03:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What chants do you use and why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do N. KOREA and US hate one another so much? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 20:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What exactly are the three branches of Buddhism? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 12:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have researched them a good amount and realized what I was practicing was Mahyana I believe... as I look at the other two they all seemed to mesh into what I believed was a singular belief but I guess they are different.. what makes them different
. What is Tibetan Buddhism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When does Grouplove come to California? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 04:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this band and want to see them but I only have seen them at Coachella... when do they tour Cali? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You are welcome Reddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 04:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Redditors, Do you want a funeral when you die..? Why or why not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 21:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came to the realization that I have requested not to have a service when I die. It costs a lot of money and I do not want to be mourned. If people would like to remember me, then I request they do it individually. How do you guys feel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hare Krishna vs Gautama Buddha </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 12:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanna start by thanking the wonderful souls of /r/buddhism for being such amazing colleagues in my spiritual growth. I have made some self realizations and now I am eager to learn more!

I ran into a gentleman awhile back who dressed like a Tibetan Monk trying to sell me prayer beads... I realized he was a Hare Krishna follower... what exactly is that? What is the difference between them and Buddhists? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bucks history of three point shooters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 05:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was pretty amazed at the Bucks history of 3-Point shooters. Michael Redd, J.J. Reddick and Ray Allen. Am I missing any? Why do they develop such good shooters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kings out of Rondo deal.. Mavs agree in principle for Rondo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 00:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buddhists do not worship a deity do they? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 11:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering if Buddhists have a deity that they worship. I don't believe Siddartha is one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best unfiltered, unbiased news source to get your news from? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 10:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [SERIOUS] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got lost in Toys-r-us today.. Luckily I found a friend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 03:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your opinions on Grant Napier? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 00:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time he talks I wanna vomit but im curious about what you guys think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drinkers and lifters...? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 00:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you tend to "party" a lot... what do you drink to not put on the lbs.? I am a huge Corona drinker but that is counter productive... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boogie + Monroe? That is a 4+5 combo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 00:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should we go for it? Would you trade our 1st rnd pick? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the stretch marks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 22:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am getting really red, bad looking stretch marks by my armpit area. (Bicep and chest-ish area) Why is this occuring and has anyone experienced it? 

Is there a treatment for it? Its kinda ugly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kings fire Coach Malone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 07:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, What was your worst blind date? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 10:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's prepare for HOU by watching Harden's horrible defense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 00:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the dumbest lie you/someone has told and expected the other person to believe it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 22:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kings fan here: Can we have Giannis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 06:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is he not an amazing player? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even when you lose... Derrick still manages to put on a show. Here's a reminder why. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 06:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cavs using an 8 man rotation? Was this there solution to end all the turmoil? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 04:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys use to handle anger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 06:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I want to try my best to follow the path to enlightenment.

What do you guys use to help with this?

Wow guys! What awesome feed back! Everyone had some good imput! I wrote a lot of them down and will keep a link to this thread. Keep up the good response s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In light of Rudy's extension, let us marvel at our #2 guy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 00:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kings fan here: How do you guys like having Tyreke? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 04:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kings fan here: How do you guys feel about having Thomas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 23:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys do to control your eating habits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 08:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am trying to cut down but cant seem to shake bad eating habits... what are some tips to shaking the habit.

Wow guys... there's a lot of good info here thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone else just beginning to love Casspi? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 05:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believed that it was a huge mistake bring him back to our team.. but he reminds me of how Jackson and Thomas used to light up the floor when the bench comes out. Great hustle and energy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who here read Sophie's worlds? What did you think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 11:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The shit you find on Worldstar amazes me... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 22:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just some George W. Bush and Putin bromance moments. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 20:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which country has produced the most merited Philosophers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 22:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read a lot of German Philosophy and was curious on your opinions on which country you feel was the most impact.

Clarify: which area in the world do you feel has produced the highest quality of philosophers and why?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some housing scams that I should look out for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 04:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am transferring to UCSC and if it is cheaper I would live off campus... something look to good to be true and I hear alot of stories of scams... what are some tips and warnings reddit?

I have a girlfriend who would be with me... split rent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just got a conditional acceptance on my TAG! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 08:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am now making plans on transferring for fall 2015. How is the job market? What is the best option for living... renting apartment or on campus housing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was a top salesman at Sprint. AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 09:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
