<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5173</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone likes Fast and Furious here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 04:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 04:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> amazing! you are so lucky because you can enjoy such beautiful scene on your way to work. i just meet the crowd of people every day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 04:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what's the karma for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so you mean they use the same number in different movies? why? why 555 can not be used? and they can just create a number that doesn't exist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always do the same thing as you. even if i have watched them for more than once, i still enjoy them when i watch them again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you mean you will watch them again and again?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah! totally agree with you. Friends is still funny and i do think good sitcoms will never be outdated! besides, i enjoy Good Luck Charlie very much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will you watch the TV series years ago? Like Friends? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 06:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> recently, i have been watching the Friends. but i found some of the plots are unfit for our life now. so i wander if anyone will still choose to watch TV series years before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 06:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i like the photos with the natural scenes and this one is good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 05:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my friends recommended me to see this TV series and it is really out of my expectation! it is awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 04:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is interesting, i am thinking about making a similar one for my boyfriend to give him a surprise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 04:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks delicious and easy to make. i will try it this weekend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 04:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am not quite sure but it seems that i know this scene.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 04:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is said that the movie intended to make people pay attention to the protection of wild animals. but i think it might have some backfires.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> who is your favorite actor/actress? which of his/her movie impressed you most? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 03:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
