<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9503</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-02 02:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So then using *pi* as a number base would simplify that number and complicate a lot of others, huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-30 18:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corrections are more effective when they're correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-24 05:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But can they discern the history of scrotal orgasms in men? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-23 21:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be interesting if this research had application to the design of digital hearing aids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-20 00:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T-Mobile is included in [11 Brands That Will Disappear In 2011](http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2010/06/18/11-brands-that-will-disap_n_617198.html#s102284).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-12 18:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The third is that to the extent he stands for anything, it is for maintenance of a status quo that continues to wreck the country in order to service the greed of a few oligarchs.  The fourth is that he fundamentally does not understand the powers and the role of the modern presidency.  And the fifth is that he maintains the worst communications apparatus in the White House since Jimmy Carter prowled its corridors.  In fairness to his communications team, though, he has given them almost nothing to sell.  You try singing the praises of bailing out Goldman Sachs one hundred cents on the dollar, or of a health care plan that forces people to buy plans they don't want from hated insurance vultures.  It ain't easy, pal.  Yet, on the other hand, Bush and Cheney had far less than nothing to sell when it came to the Iraq war - indeed, they had nothing but lies - and their team handled that masterfully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-11 02:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This needs to be widely read.  Why it would get downvoted is beyond me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-27 22:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Swallowed a whole bottle of ink on a dare.

Shat blue for a couple of days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-23 19:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "And, second, because Maddow gave us a partial reminder of what good journalism would actually look like in America." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-21 06:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe she was just being thorough and they were perfunctory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-17 03:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any similarity to [The minds of robots](http://www.amazon.com/minds-robots-behavior-conscious-automata/dp/B0007F7JCU)?  I'd loved reading that several times, each time increasing my comprehension from 10% to 15% and eventually as much as 20%. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-17 01:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good grief, what is it going to take to make more progress in getting over this shit?  It boggles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-16 07:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no experience with it but if I were in your position I would check out the [Olympus Digital Pen](http://www.staples.com/Olympus-Pen-E-PL1-Digital-SLR-Camera-Black/product_864186?cm_mmc=GoogleProductAds-_-Search-_-blank-_-blank).  Compactness is a great feature for a backpacker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-13 01:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe Nerdit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-09 22:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> click on a file, F2, copy file extension, ALT+Tab to notepad, click at the end of line 1, paste, ALT+Tab to Explorer, click on next file...
I'ts way too much time wasted.


For that specific issue, try [Filegrab](http://www.pcmag.com/article2/0,2817,5752,00.asp). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-02 17:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The only serious political energy in the country belongs to the tea party morons, and their media cheerleaders on Fox and, well, seemingly everywhere.  And they are calling  wait for it now  for less government as a solution to the countrys problems.  It boggles the mind.  Could an ideology ever have been more obviously shown to be catastrophic in its effects?  And yet here we are arguing in public about doubling down on those policy ideas, while the two major political parties both pretend to be limiting the worst practices of the most predatory actors, as they simultaneously accept bags of money from the very same folks at the very same time."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-02 00:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your boss is flat out wrong to say telecommuting is a guaranteed productivity loss.  He's probably projecting, since he himself might want to be goofing off.  It depends a lot on the person and you sound like you're a good match for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-04-30 21:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better to call them languages, which they are, than dialects.  Of course there are also dialects but that makes it seem like the difference between London and Liverpool or Minneapolis vs Birmingham.  Some of those Indian languages aren't even very closely related. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-04-25 06:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The headline is a direct quote from the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-04-23 20:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So female cops are an especially good thing, not just a matter of equity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-04-16 19:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you make of behavioural psychology as it applies to economics? Or how anthropological studies reflect on Homo Economicus?


Even a cursory glance at human history and most other forms of society outside the Western world reveal how culturally specific and temporal Economic Man really is; as the economic historian Karl Polanyi stated, no other society outside of our own has ever raised the pursuit of economic gain to the guiding principle of society or understood it as definitive of the human condition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-04-14 08:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that I use a password manager to produce secure passwords, it's hard to understand how I did it the other way for so long.  Why not just require users to use a password manager? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-04-09 00:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those options do ameliorate the stupidity of unidirectional adjustments but don't cancel it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-04-04 01:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Paul** says in Titus 2:9: Exhort servants to be obedient unto their own masters, and to please them well in all things; not answering again; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-04-03 00:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it about the guys that makes them think it's okay to have sex with someone who is very drunk?  Even if she consents that barely counts as sex with a **person**.  

Guy culture supports this behavior by bragging and by not calling someone out.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-04-03 00:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it about the guys that makes them think it's okay to have sex with someone who is very drunk?  Even if she consents that barely counts as sex with a **person**.  

Guy culture supports this behavior by bragging and by not calling someone out.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-04-03 00:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it about the guys that makes them think it's okay to have sex with someone who is very drunk?  Even if she consents that barely counts as sex with a **person**.  Use your head and heart, guys.  Failing that, use your hands -- you've had enough practice.

Guy culture supports this behavior by bragging and by not calling someone out.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-04-02 20:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "...the Christian philosophy  the most sublime and benevolent, but most perverted system that ever shone on man..." 

Often [misleadingly abbreviated](http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Thomas_Jefferson). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-03-26 05:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Websites/companies such as what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-03-26 03:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How difficult would it be to institute secure transport protocols that verify origin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-03-19 18:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the author of the article said doesn't look much like an *argument* to me.  Just a riff... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-03-14 17:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The link to the quote is [here](http://www.amerika.org/about/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-03-14 00:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tangentially related -- my daughter diaper-trained herself at about 2 when we were staying at a beach in Africa where everyone peed and pooped in the sand dunes.  She went naked most of the time but the important thing was being with adults, both male and female, and watching their process, including burying the poop.

Took the mystery out of it for her anyway and gave her something to imitate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-03-13 03:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Transparency, accountability and oversight -- in government at all levels, in business, Wall Street, Main Street.  These are not even partisan -- independents, sane Republicans, libertarians could get behind them.  They are general overarching goals that need specifics developed.  This group would be a good start to flesh them out and see what we could support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-03-13 02:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It ain't what you don't know that gets you in trouble. It's what you know for sure that just ain't so."	-- Mark Twain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-03-11 03:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and should be mandatory reading.  For educators, administrators and /r/education. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-03-08 21:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You brought up guns.  That wasn't in the article.  Did you read it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-03-05 20:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kindergarten through 12th grade.

So the article says. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-03-05 19:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> from the article:
Ninety-five percent of criminologists study blue collar crime.

Five percent study white collar crime.

Of the tiny minority who study white collar crime, ninety five percent focus on the individuals who rip off the corporation.

We are left with a small handful of criminologists  think Edwin Sutherland, John Braithwaite, Gil Geis  who have studied or are studying  corporate crime.

That would be crime by the corporation.

Bill Black is one of the most prominent of those living corporate criminologists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-03-02 08:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about Paths of Glory?  Been ages since I saw it but I remember it as very powerful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-27 03:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, Hobart!  One really picturesque city.  Too bad you're so far away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-22 09:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of these horror stories involve poor management.  Managers whose only criterion is that the stuff 'works' are asking for it.  Peer reviews would prevent a lot of it.  Letting a lone ranger work for weeks with no supervision is no way to run a railroad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-21 19:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This article](http://www.commondreams.org/view/2010/02/21-0) explains why that is.  Sad indeed, but also sad that progressives don't frame their positions in a way that works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-18 23:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you think AnnArchist is an anti-feminist troll?  Your conclusion-jumping is breathtaking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-16 03:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since they're saved, they can be sacrificed without sending them to hell.  Then the Muslims still have a chance to be saved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-15 20:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could a program be devised for middle school students that would give them practice in developing the kind of focused attention that this guy demonstrated?  Even a taste of the rudiments might be remarkable.  Astronauts, ER people and others need this.  How about if almost everyone had some? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-06 01:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to go shopping with you.  (xy, not gay.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-01-23 23:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And with the name calling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-01-18 01:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This XY is completely smitten with Gilmore Girls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-01-17 08:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The author of that quote, Naomi Klein, says elsewhere in the article:  

"In the United States and many parts of Europe, it is far-right parties and even neofascism that are giving the loudest voice to anti- corporatist rage."  

So it doesn't look like *she* equates corporatist with fascist.  But you didn't RTFA, did you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-01-17 08:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks to me like they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-01-16 19:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's just a matter of us all being in this together.  Your health impacts me and my health impacts you.  Just as I'm happy if some of my tax money goes to educate your kids.  Repeating 'individual' the way you do makes it seem like you really believe there is such a thing as a disconnected individual.  "No man is an island." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-01-15 06:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Aboriginal community referred to in the article is in Northern Canada.  Yes, they have lost, but not so much in colonial wars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-01-14 21:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's like the way an individual's safety is part of the commons, protected by police.  Individuals aren't opposed to the commons -- they're part of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-01-14 05:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It never ceases to amaze me how hard it is for some people to accept the idea of the commons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-01-12 21:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that's a helpful rebuttal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-01-11 18:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll find plenty of elaboration if you RTFA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-01-11 02:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In order of my preference:  B, C, A, AA.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-01-09 20:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some senators may oppose this new-old idea on the completely believable ground that they lack enough information about the legislation they oppose to discuss it intelligently for 10 minutes, much less several hours.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-01-08 05:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might find out if you RTFA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-01-04 00:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but not voting at all can be seen as an abdication and it won't wrest power from anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-31 06:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Acknowledging that you 'react differently to people who excite different impulses within you' doesn't seem shallow.  Besides, first impressions are not only about appearance.  And the studies of [thin slices](http://www.psychologytoday.com/articles/200407/the-once-over) show that the're often pretty accurate.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-31 06:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks are not all you have to go on.  There's the way people move and carry themselves, Their facial expression, their laughter, their energy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-31 05:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People react differently even when the context *isn't* sexual or romantic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-30 05:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another single-Xer here, moved to respond by the flurry of thoughts and feelings triggered by your post and all the comments. 

There is something of value in all the comments and I'm heartened by all the good advice.  The basic issues seem to me to be related to how to be in the world, and they apply to all of us, of whatever age or gender.  I don't mean to denigrate the advice about makeup and clothes -- it's good advice and may be more accessible than 'deeper' issues.  

Even though you don't want to move in with your dad, I hope you can find a way to use your relationship with him as a source of strength.  And I suggest that it's helpful to remember that however misguided your mother is, she loves you and mostly intends what she says to be for what she thinks is good for you.  And you can love her back, this deeply flawed woman, without succumbing to her warped views.

Make no mistake, though, Qeraeth is right in characterizing this as emotional abuse.  Not many of us grew up without some abuse, but still I think it's better to call it what it is.  The thing to do is to use that knowledge to free yourself from the entanglements.  Detachment doesn't mean separation, just kind of getting unhooked (huge work at your age, but you're up to it).

Stay tight with friends who understand and support you without a lot of judgement.  You don't need to push the others away unless they're really toxic, just don't tune yourself to their opinions.

This sub-reddit looks like it could be a valuable resource for you.  Use what works and don't let the rest slow you down.  Bless you.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-30 00:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The headline is a quote from two paragraphs above yours.  Though it would have been better without the quotation marks that imply it's a direct quote from Kucinich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-30 00:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting that there we no comments from tailgaters.  Because they dare not reply or because redditors are mostly too smart for that?  I'm inclined to think the latter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-29 04:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I do that sometimes.  Once to a cop who I hadn't noticed, but who dropped back quickly.  I've also had someone edge closer though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-29 02:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize the headline is a quote from the article, don't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-29 01:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-28 06:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong presumption. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-27 05:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate the nuance and gentleness with with you approach this.  

And wish you would apply it to Richard Dawkins and Christopher Hitchens instead of characterizing them as "Brilliant men who...fish in the mud for those who might take the bait." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-27 05:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Shantaram](http://www.amazon.com/Shantaram-Novel-Gregory-David-Roberts/dp/0312330537/ref=ntt_at_ep_dpi_1) by Gregory David Roberts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-27 05:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Happiness Hypothesis: Finding Modern Truth in Ancient Wisdom](http://www.amazon.com/Happiness-Hypothesis-Finding-Modern-Ancient/dp/0465028020/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 s=books qid=1261717942 sr=1-1) by Jonathan Haidt.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-26 03:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too quick with the name calling.  You could have [checked](http://lmgtfy.com/?q=%22too+smart+to+engage+in+politics%22+Plato). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-24 05:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This one](http://www.reddit.com/r/worldpolitics/comments/aebey/it_was_a_mexican_diplomat_who_once_told_me_that/).  But your point is well taken -- I looked a several before finding that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-23 06:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, nobody said it was.  That's a straw man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-21 02:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not your bone buddy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-19 21:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She may have had a different take on it if it weren't for the obscene bankers' bonuses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-19 21:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The complain may not be so much about the lack of an increase, but about the contrasting obscenity of the bankers' bonuses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-18 23:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Fully functioning"?  What percentage of Americans do you think are fully functioning adults? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-18 03:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the moron for posting the link, or Booman, who posted the linked article, Why Obama Should Stop Forcing the Left to Eat Sh*t, in the Booman Tribune, or both of us? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-17 22:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems to me the best chance for effectiveness would come from supporting issues a broad spectrum could agree on, not something that would divide for leftists from libertarians, free marketeers from social democrats.  

There are a number of voting reform issues -- some kind of [preference voting](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Preference_voting);  insuring the [integrity of the vote](http://www.verifiedvoting.org/); providing for expanded but verified registration; insuring that waiting lines for voting are reduced and are not skewed by voting district.

To the extent that we can call for accountability, transparency and oversight without having the arguments devolve into anti-regulatory rhetoric, those are overarching concerns that deserve wide support.  They also importantly allow for a correctable result instead of fixing even a good policy into place that later has unintended consequences.

A couple of personal favorites of mine are the abolition of corporate personhood, and opening media advertising to include issue advocacy so that the networks couldn't deny Adbusters, for example, the right to buy air time.  Those causes may have narrower support though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-17 20:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Notice it said "unemployed or underemployed." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-14 08:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm an unreconstructed feminist. Though I'm not into theory and haven't read much.  Used to love [Bitch magazine](http://bitchmagazine.org/) but have been traveling and don't see it much anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-14 07:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you had RTFA you would have read:
 Remarkably, the Senate bill still keeps Big Insurance safe from competition by preserving its privileged exemption from the antitrust laws.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-14 00:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have a look at [Reinventing Collapse](http://www.newsociety.com/bookid/3991) by Dmitry Orlov.  He also has a [blog](http://cluborlov.blogspot.com/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-12 18:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-07 01:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took the quote from the linked article by Dr. Matthew G. Masiello in the Tribune-Democrat of Pennsylvania, without checking the source.  Thanks to simonsarris for finding a source. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-11-29 18:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly the point of the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-11-07 15:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nowhere does the article say he is just as bad as Bush.  That's what you read into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-11-05 16:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flagrantly unconstitutional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-10-31 01:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where us the 'baby language'?  Downvoted for misleading headline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-10-26 16:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Rises' is UK usage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-10-19 16:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got a pretty good flavor of the article from what was freely available from the link.  How about commenting on that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-10-14 01:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  I got it from Common Dreams and only sometimes verify their links.  Guess I should do that all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-10-12 19:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you RTFA?  What is it that would prevent them from working as they do in Germany? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-10-08 23:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry about that -- thanks for supplying the link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-22 04:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's below the ad, so maybe you didn't see it.  The headline is a direct quote from the article.

And the reference to *Jewish* detracts, rather than contributes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-20 19:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understood it better when I supplied what seemed to be a missing comma -- *Way to legitimize the fringe**,** NYT* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-15 17:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Common Dreams hasn't responded to my suggestion to learn the difference between hyphens, n-dashes and m-dashes.  It drives me nuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-06 05:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See [Matt Taibbi on this](http://trueslant.com/matttaibbi/2009/09/01/bailout-propaganda-begins/) for a complete picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-23 23:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *I was relegated to having to manage my passwords in a password utility called KeePass. Obviously not ideal.*

But a password manager **is** the ideal way.  Trying to remember even a handful of passwords is weak, as is keeping them in an unsecure document.  And a memorable password is never as good as something like *CUcgbvnD3oUDGk2a8fCA*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-17 01:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like its predecessors, the Obama administration treats additional government funding as a solution to unaffordable health care, rather than its cause. The current reform will likely expand our governments already massive role in health-care decision-makingall just to continue the illusion that someone else is paying for our care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-17 01:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of the health-care interest groupshospitals, insurance companies, professional groups, pharmaceuticals, device manufacturers, even advocates for the poorhave a major stake in the current system. Overturning it would favor only the 300 million of us who use the system andwhether we realize it or notpay for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-17 01:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most important single step we can take toward truly reforming our system is to move away from comprehensive health insurance as the single model for financing care. And a guiding principle of any reform should be to put the consumer, not the insurer or the government, at the center of the system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-17 01:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A wasteful insurance system; distorted incentives; a bias toward treatment; moral hazard; hidden costs and a lack of transparency; curbed competition; service to the wrong customer. These are the problems at the foundation of our health-care system, resulting in a slow rot and requiring more and more money just to keep the system from collapsing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-17 01:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only in the bizarre parallel universe of health care could limiting supply be seen as a sensible approach to keeping prices _down_. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-17 01:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keeping prices opaque is one way medical institutions seek to avoid competition and thereby keep prices up. Without transparency on prices-and the related data on measurable outcomes-efforts to give the consumer more control over health care have failed, and always will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-17 01:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine confiscating all the profits of all the famously greedy health-insurance companies. That would pay for 4 days of health care for all Americans. Lets add in the profits of the 10 biggest rapacious U.S. drug companies. Another 7 days. Indeed, confiscating all the profits of all American companies, in every industry, wouldnt cover even five months of our health-care expenses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-17 01:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For almost all our health-care needs, the current system allows us as consumers to ask providers, Whats my share? instead of How much does this cost?-a question we ask before buying any other good or service. And the subtle difference between those two questions is costing us all a fortune. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-17 01:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insurance is probably the most complex, costly, and distortional method of financing any activity; thats why it is otherwise used to fund only rare, unexpected, and large costs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-17 01:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was nothing natural or inevitable about the way our system developed: employer-based, comprehensive insurance crowded out alternative methods of paying for health-care expenses only because of a poorly considered tax benefit passed half a century ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-17 01:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The federal government spends eight times as much on health care as it does on education, 12 times what it spends on food aid to children and families, 30 times what it spends on law enforcement, 78 times what it spends on land management and conservation, 87 times the spending on water supply, and 830 times the spending on energy conservation. Education, public safety, environment, infrastructure-all other public priorities are being slowly devoured by the health-care beast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-17 01:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless we fix the problems at the foundation of our health system-largely problems of incentives-our reforms wont do much good, and may do harm. Health care will need to become subject to the same forces that have boosted efficiency and value throughout the economy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-17 01:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The comprehensive reform being contemplated merely cements in place the current system-insurance-based, employment-centered, administratively complex. It addresses the underlying causes of our health-care crisis only obliquely, if at all; indeed, by extending the current system to more people, it will likely increase the ultimate cost of true reform. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-17 01:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Accidentally, but relentlessly, America has built a health-care system with incentives that inexorably generate terrible and perverse results. Incentives that emphasize health care over any other aspect of health and well-being. That emphasize treatment over prevention. That disguise true costs. That favor complexity, and discourage transparent competition based on price or quality. That result in a generational pyramid scheme rather than sustainable financing. And thatmost importantremove consumers from our irreplaceable role as the ultimate ensurer of value. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-17 01:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There needs to be a _business reason_ why an industry, year in and year out, would be able to get away with poor customer service, unaffordable prices, and uneven results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-13 04:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The issue of "planting" came up in the comments but nothing in the article suggested that.  I didn't find anything in the article that would support the notion that it was a plant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-12 03:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forced Camel Case.  Even In Email Address. Not Right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-11 22:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does americanoddjobs make irresponsible generalizations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-05 02:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of health care should be available to people that employ consistent poor decision-making over many years?  If they are very low income, as many of them are, how should it be funded? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-07 20:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many supporters of life with parole for minors would include their own children and relatives?

Case dismissed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-07 19:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if the author were charged with a crime, he presumably wouldn't assert a right to a trial by his peers.

Rights may be characterized as intrinsic, but that doesn't mean they can't be granted.  Over time, societies come to grant expanded rights.  

Many countries now treat health care as a right.  Some of wish to join them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-29 00:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about including [range voting](http://rangevoting.org/) aka [score voting](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Range_voting)?

It seems to have seval advantages over IRV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-24 00:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd appreciate a comment to explain the down vote.

Do you have such a source, or does the lack not make the arguments specious, or what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-21 04:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only admitter, yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-03 22:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The link to the pdf is broken or the pdf is corrupted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-03 03:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Resources on aging seem to be mostly about slowing, resisting, preventing, delaying or diminishing.  Where are some resources that deal with *preparing* for dimished capacity?  Examples:

*  Dealing with no longer being able to live in your own home
*  Accepting help with tasks you used to do yourself
*  Allowing health care 'strangers' to assist you with intimate functions
*  Learning to accept that others'judgements may be more competant than your own
*  Surrendering control over financial, legal or other important decisions, rather than having control wrested from you

Those of you more familiar with these issues than I can add many others.

[The Myth of Alzheimer's](http://www.amazon.com/Myth-Alzheimers-Todays-Dreaded-Diagnosis/dp/031236816X) has a great deal of very useful information and insight.  

Are there training materials that can be given to aging people, while they're still alert and independent, that will help them prepare for changes in their alertness and independence?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-02 04:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you get 'stooping'?  Nor was there talk of 'partisan media control.'

Why not improve the effectiveness of the left's message? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-01 04:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would only be fair to give women all the power, but just for 2000 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-01 03:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any style that's clear and consistent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-01 03:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Resources on aging seem to be mostly about slowing, resisting, preventing, delaying or diminishing.  Where are some resources that deal with *preparing* for dimished capacity?  Examples:

* Dealing with no longer being able to live in your own home

* Accepting help with tasks you used to do yourself

* Allowing health care 'strangers' to assist you with intimate functions

* Learning to accept that others'judgements may be more competant than your own

* Surrendering control over financial, legal or other important decisions, rather than having control wrested from you

Those of you more familiar with these issues than I can add many others.

[The Myth of Alzheimer's](http://www.amazon.com/Myth-Alzheimers-Todays-Dreaded-Diagnosis/dp/031236816X) has a great deal of very useful information and insight.  

Are there training materials that can be given to aging people, while they're still alert and independent, that will help them prepare for changes in their alertness and independence?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-31 23:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean gayphones? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-31 03:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personal interactions are one thing but politics is another.  People vote based on these issues and most candidates pay at least lip service to religion.  

I can get along fine with religious people here in the US until I find they're spreading ignorant propaganda and urging people to vote based on their dogma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-30 22:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which posts would make you think this is a matter of not liking Obama?  He just needs to be pushed and reminded of his promises to keep him from being co-opted by the oligarchy.  

FDR told activists in his own party, "I agree with you, I want to do it, now make me do it."

Obama needs the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-25 22:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone explain how [range voting](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Range_voting) compares to IRV, Borda, Condorcet or others?  I remember reading that range voting has many advantages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-20 21:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seemed to me the abstract indicated that social stigma *inhibits* empathy rather than facilitates it.  

Wouldn't it be something if fMRI scanning could be used to diagnose the empathy impaired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-20 03:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you read the article or just the headline quote?  It's from "The New Republic" magazine, hardly GOP-sponsored.  Have a look at what [Google finds](http://www.google.com/search?hl=en rlz=1C1GGLS_enUS291US315 q="the+new+republic"+liberal+conservative btnG=Search aq=f oq= aqi=) on whether TNR is liberal or conservative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-14 07:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FDA means *Food* and Drug, right?  The agency ought to be able to tell the difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-13 18:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was "the government" that exposed the scam.  Oversight, accountability and transparency are important for both government and the "private" sector.  Greed and corruption honor no boundaries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-09 08:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From William Gibson's [Pattern Recognition (2003)] (http://www.scribd.com/doc/10073557/William-Gibson-Pattern-Recognition-2003):
If there's any one thing about England that Cayce finds fundamentally disturbing, it is how "class" works--a word with a very different mirror-world meaning, somehow. She's long since given up trying to explain this to English friends.

The closest she can come is that it's somewhat akin, for her, if only in its enormity, to how the British seem to feel about certain American attitudes to firearms ownership which they generally find unthinkable, and bafflingly self-evidently wrong, and so often leading to a terrible and profligate waste of human life. And she knows what they mean, but also knows how deeply it runs, the gun thing, and how unlikely it is to change.  Except, perhaps, gradually, and over a very long time. Class in England is like that, for her.

I find this provocative.  Does it resonate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-04-05 07:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't that be like someone from Latin America calling him 'amigo'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-04-01 07:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Officious, indeed.

Definitions of officious on the Web:

interfering: intrusive in a meddling or offensive manner; "an interfering old woman"; "bustling about self-importantly..."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-04-01 04:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently read a href="http://www.economicgangsters.com/" rel="nofollow"Economic Gangsters: Corruption, Violence, and the Poverty of Nations/a.  It fit well with my interests but I was especially impressed by the authors' emphasis on research and the analysis of data rather than ideology.  Their advocacy for randomized trials looks fruitful where they are even possible.  

How is a layman with no economic training supposed to judge among economic explanations and prescriptions?  Either FDR exacerbated the Depression with his policies or he ameliorated it, but where is the objective basis for which side to choose?  Keynes and von Mises may both be wrong, but both can't be right.  

Sometimes I'm able to criticize the premises of an economic argument or definition.  For example, excluding 'women's work' from GDP calculations seems flawed from the start.  But often I am too easily influenced by the most recent argument I encounter, without anything but my gut to help me.

Most economic reasoning looks to me like its coming from different sides of the elephant, with little hope of agreement.  Is this all there is?

Surely there must be a better way.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-03-22 22:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you accuse Peter of posting blogspam? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-03-16 01:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone freaked out by the idea of rationing needs to recognize that we have rationing right now.  But instead of being administered by ethicists or physicians or even just bureaucrats, it's the result of the vagaries of employment history, geography, economic class and other less pertinent factors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-03-09 04:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is my town of about 15,000 a community? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2008-06-18 01:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got 1920 hits in Google with '"Hillary concedes" site: reddit.com'.  Removing the quotes gives 26,100 hits.  Why even bother with complicated reddit searches? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
