<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3431</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 17:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lesson learned: Chemistry kills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what are the most terrifying chemicals known to man and what do they do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 17:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have there been any records of training child soldiers from when they were young/genetically modified soldiers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 15:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 10:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every account on reddit is a bot except you. please.Every account on reddit is a bot except you. Every account on reddit is a bot except you. help. Every account on reddit is a bot except you. Us. Every account on reddit is a bot except you.Every account on reddit is a bot except you.Every account on reddit is a bot except you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what's the most creative thing you can say? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 10:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the most popular websites/browser-based games out there? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 10:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What advice would you give a freshman chemistry major? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 10:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 06:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing! Was just curious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I'm a student studying in a foreign country with a student visa and committed a crime there that deserves death in my home country, will I be extradited back to my home country and sentenced? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 04:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the Invisible Hand to truly work, is it true that you must have a perfect market situtation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 02:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need to write an essay arguing whether the Invisible Hand was good or bad but I can't think of any points aside from definitions, help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 00:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most beautiful word you know? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 09:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 09:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 11? Wow! I must be really behind the times haha. Had no idea children were already aware of the references to economic theory, Reinmannian manifolds, Debussy's La mer and such!

Jokes aside, who cares about age?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You're listening to the greatest orchestral performance of your life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 08:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, how do I get over depression caused by a book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 08:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just read "Flowers For Algernon" and for the past two days i've never felt this depressed before... help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If my nationality is a country that gives the death penalty and I currently study overseas in a foreign country that does not, will I be sentenced to death if I commit a crime that would deserve death (in my country of nationality) in the foreign country, will I be deported and charged? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 00:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 13:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda sad my engineering field doesn't get to do all the cool stuff you guys are talking about.. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 10:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in a non-US high school atm! To be honest, at this point I don't really even know what it means to know a concept... I mean, I can answer the questions after practicing them for a while but I have no idea what you mean by understanding the concept. Like, i'm going through geometric distributions right now and I could say that if X was the number of failures before a success it would look like Pr(Xx) = (1-p)^x so maybe that counts as understanding?

Thanks for the pop book suggestions! I'll definitely look for them. I've actually read Frenkel's Love and Math too and would recommend it to you, it's great!. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 06:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently doing high school math and the topics we're doing are stuff like volumes of solids of revolutions, differential equations (at a hs level of course),  markov chains, hypergeometric distributions, density functions, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, I think i'm terrible in math so how in the world can I improve if I think the subject is boring? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 05:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to study for my math test but find it incredible dull and boring. Many people have told me that math is as beautiful as my other interests like poetry and composition and that the beauty is analogous to a stark sculpture where beauty really is in the eye of the beholder but I can't seem to find any remote sort of beauty. I mean in Physics and Chemistry, it's much easier to appreciate the science because it's applications and presence is soo much more observable to the average person but mathematics; I am aware it's the language of the universe and without understanding it we would be blind, etc .but I can't seem to find any sort of accessible beauty or appreciation for math.

Any suggestions as to what I could do or see or read to gain an insight into this mysterious world?

edit: By dull and boring, I don't mean math! I'm referring to the test. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:What exactly is Amnesty International and what do they really do besides making online petitions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 01:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want to major in Chem in Uni but haven't done high school chem? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 04:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, so I have a bit of a dilemma. I've recently just realized that what I really want to study in College is chemistry, now the problem is that I haven't taken any AP/IB/A-Level/ etc. Chem in HS (only did one year of IB SL chemistry). As of such, i'm required to take a bridging/foundation Chem course to make up for my lack of Chem. Seeing how I lack basic chem, would it really be a wise decision to major in Chem even if I really enjoy it?

Just for additional info, in terms of HS science, I only took AP Physics B, C, AP Calc AB, BC and AP CS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 04:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean by infinite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 16:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but I find it admirable that he would face his worst fears to try to save someone he loved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Enrique Granados, a revolutionary Spanish composer, died attempting to save his drowning wife after his ship was shot by a German U-Boat even though he had a deep fear of water and could not swim at all </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 15:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
