<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8834</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-25 18:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point, but technically he would still have Stark blood in him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-25 18:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but he was legitimized as a Stark, which makes him the heir to Winterfell. If anything I think that it would become voided if it were ever to come to light that he was actually Rheagar's son.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-24 22:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start using the tape deck hookup and then come talk to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about a certain theory involving Jon (Spoilers up to AFFC) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-24 22:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen a lot of talk on this subreddit about the R+L=J theory. Some people think that this would make him heir to the Iron Throne. Correct me if I'm wrong, but wouldn't he still be a bastard but only with a different father? He still would not have any better claim to the throne then he does now. I could be completely wrong here so if I am will somebody please explain what the significance of this theory is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-24 22:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I just watched it last night. Thought it was a pretty good movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those of you who need more Sean Bean, I give you Black Death </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-24 22:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-24 21:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because one person says Fringe is bad, doesn't make it a bad TV show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-17 22:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe I missed this. What pages? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-17 20:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am paraphrasing, but I think he says "and her honeys all mine"

EDIT: Dammit. Late to the party </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-11 01:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-10 01:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you have to be lying face down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-07 20:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, but I am just speculating here anyways. The new WiiU controller would be more useful than Kinect functionality for ME3   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-07 19:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is directly from Nintendo conference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-07 19:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second image to the left of EA sign. Wonder how they would use new controller.

EDIT: this image is from Nintendo conference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mass Effect 3 on Wii? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-07 19:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-06 22:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title: House Stark
Shield: Stark

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-06 21:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that is only because you never got a PoV chapter from her until AFFC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-02 21:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck you Jamie Lannister </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-02 18:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are so right in stating that the above gentleman is correct.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-02 18:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am laughing just thinking about this, and what my probable reaction to this would be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-02 18:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People to stand close to me at grocery stores while I am shopping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-01 05:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honesty is almost a negative trait right now in the current job market. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-31 16:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot even being to describe how hard that made me laugh.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-31 05:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least he can re-watch all of his favorite TV shows. The question is...how does he know which one's were his favorite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-27 16:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wish I didn't read as fast as I did. Now that I am finished with all four books I can't sop thinking about A Dance with Dragons!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-27 05:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was just about to post this until I saw yours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-26 18:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of these characters have much bigger roles in books 2 and 3, so I would imagine that they will also get more screen time as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-24 21:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should've bought from KMart. They had a really good deal on L.A. Noire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-18 21:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, has she drank from a garden hose and survived? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-18 21:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cleveland is actually not that bad. I live/work here and have no problem with this city.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-07 02:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> unless you have a Wii... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-25 09:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I cast Lvl. 3 Eroticism. You turn into a real beautiful woman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-22 01:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "In summary, laboratory tests and driving studies show that cannabis may acutely impair several driving-related skills in a dose-related fashion, but that the effects between individuals vary more than they do with alcohol because of tolerance, differences in smoking technique, and different absorptions of THC." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-18 01:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my text ringtone *LISTEN* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-15 00:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overall average for WI according to your link. In Ohio, starting wage is $33,671 and averages is $50,314. Regardless, I would have to agree that $38,284 is a very low average salary in WI.

source: http://teacherportal.com/salary/Ohio-teacher-salary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-14 23:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly though...it's a user review for a videogame. I could log on right now and give it a 0/10 just for spite. I would care more if we were talking about a Critic Review.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-12 06:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are talking about starting wages. A teacher with tenure will end up making much more than $35,000. I would be more concerned about losing benefits, because I would say that is one of the stronger benefits that teachers get once hired.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-11 23:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but that is the same boat every kid is in when getting out of college. Even $30,000 is a very livable wage. I am not saying I agree with what is going on, but I don't think teachers are underpaid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-11 22:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Ohio, starting wage for a teacher is about $35,000. Take from that what you will, but after becoming tenured teachers can start to earn a very nice wage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-10 22:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this is from Youngstown State University I wouldn't be suprised if people just don't show up and email the professor after the exam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-08 23:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enslaved: Odyssey to the West  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-04 01:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone has the right of police protection. What RP is saying is that one person will end up paying for their education while another doesn't have to pay a dime. Same goes for healthcare.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-04 01:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a lot of people here are taking that quote out of context. He is talking about college, not kindergarten. 
A better quote is this:
"Prices go up on the tuition and then we give them grants and then they get out of the college and they owe $200,000. It makes no sense whatsoever. I don't think how anybody can justify it."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-02 02:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-24 02:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree with this. I think you overestimate the value of our technological advantage. We are an occupying force in Iraq, where someone can bomb a humvee and then go run over to a mosque and hide. Precision air strikes are basically pointless. Both sides are still shooting bullets at each other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
