<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3482</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 05:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't it'll drive you crazy or into depression after a while.  Sometimes you need to take a reddit break too.  Info overload. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 05:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more likely he acted due to the influence of drugs, possibly prescription ones.  I've raised a bunch of gamers and none have turned into murderers or bad people in any way.  Interestingly, none were on prescription drugs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 05:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post a question, then expand on it in your text.  You need to guide the reader towards a goal or general topic, not just throw a bunch out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 05:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We" don't, individuals do.  I never look back and I never regret. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 05:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have stop looking at the big picture for a while and concentrate on the small one that is your life and the people you know.  Live in the moment, not the projected path. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 05:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anything happen after you die? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 05:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This post is extremely disjointed and I don't understand exactly what your question is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 05:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> newegg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 05:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You hate yourself more than anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 05:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be pretty screwed.  If I ever lost a big argument against my dog, I'd be toast since he weighs more than I do and could easily take me down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 04:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a terrible question to ask a parent of little kids.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 04:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends, can they be tracked and controlled by any arm of any government? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 04:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.humanmetrics.com/cgi-win/jtypes2.asp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 04:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't introduce any foreign object into my child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 04:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, it does become repetitive.  I suggest you offer ideas for improvement to the mods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 03:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would he when he didn't use them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 01:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stick a beak on her and she'd look like a duck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 01:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing, it goes away on its' own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 01:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's a trade-off I'd always pick sight.  I can live without music better and easier than without sight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 01:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't read anywhere yet that Sony actively helps the NSA like I have for Microsoft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 01:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could always learn sign language to communicate but I could never develop a replacement for seeing the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 01:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There it was, all black and shiny just hanging there like a kite caught in the power lines, swaying back and forth, back and forth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 00:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you should stop calling your child racist names before you live to regret it, or she does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 00:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're judging a country's food product by what you had at one hotel, that's the problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 00:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Raw oysters straight out of the shell after we dug them up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 00:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Psyche!  Far Out!  In Your Face!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 00:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Toyota. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 23:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soccer.  Worked like a charm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 23:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suburban </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 23:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do they really?  Not according to this; http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Human_rights_in_North_Korea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 23:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> employee reason?

Because these things are done intentionally without our knowledge.  If you don't know they're doing something then there's nothing to stop.  It's only later, much later, that we become aware of things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 23:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another North Korea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 23:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Front pocket, left hand side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 23:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/PoliticalDiscussion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 22:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's huge, it's beautiful, the food is great and plentiful, I can work where I want to, be with whoever I want, come and go when I please and I can live without fear today, unlike so many people in the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 22:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanked a cop for doing a nice thing for some guy in a parking lot.  He showed up and unlocked the car door for him.  With all the bad stuff I read about police officers, it was just a nice thing to see and it saved the guy some trouble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 22:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could still say exactly what I thought.  I'd get in trouble for that now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 22:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://dprogram.net/2012/11/10/worldwide-mass-animal-deaths-for-2012/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 22:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ignore the religious text and go down to the [List of Mass Animal Deaths  Event Summary for 2012  408 Mass Death Events in 66 Countries](http://dprogram.net/2012/11/10/worldwide-mass-animal-deaths-for-2012/) complete with links.  I don't agree with you due to the sheer number of dead animals worldwide in 2012 alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 22:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one can tell you whether or not you'll bond with your child.  You either want to, or you don't, it's that simple.  You're making it out to be some grand thing that no one has ever gone through before and is some great compromise you're making.  Stop it.  It's a new human being you're bringing to life and it's made from you. It's the greatest gift there is to give and is the only lasting contribution you'll probably ever make.  It's an investment in your own future.  If you don't want to end up a lonely old man you'll consider what things you'll want and will make you happy throughout your life.  For most people, it's the happiness that love and family bring.  If that isn't for you, let your wife find it elsewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 21:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regarding your title, I like going outside, it's pretty nice out there.  As far as your text goes, stop whining and do something about it if you care that much.  Complaining on the internet is not a solution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 21:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not everyone wants to be burned up, including me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 21:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not pontificating, I'm a grandparent who's cared for too many foster kids because of dads who didn't want to be dads.  I've far more real experience than you do, I'd bet. It's been my experience that it can go either of two ways; either he bonds with the newborn within a few days, or he does not.  If he does not, the child suffers and so does the mother since she's constantly having to make up for his lack of participation or, sometimes, abusive behaviour.  I'm sure there are some marriages that survive, but at what cost to the innocent child?  If you don't want to be called  daddy or won't step up for your own offspring, don't make someone else pay for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 21:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add another one to the list of growing unexplained mass animal deaths. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 21:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure there are some, but far more are not and do not welcome children into their lives.  If you don't want a kid, don't have one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 21:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because this question is asked every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 21:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cave?  You'd make a horrible dad.  Do both of you a favor and get a divorce so she can pursue what she wants in life and you won't have to deal with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 21:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's scum, always wanting to get into other people's lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 21:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> f.lux is free software that warms up your computer display at night, to match your indoor lighting. http://justgetflux.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 20:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This wouldn't be a real contest, the Navy Seal would win every time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 20:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, there are no children here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 20:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be taller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 20:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to take my daughter to Busch Gardens as a surprise.  No particular reason, I just felt like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 20:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, not yet.  There have been times when it was worse than we're in now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 20:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, you have to register and no, it is not the draft.  At least, not yet anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 19:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any job that involves hard manual labor and working outside in all weather.  They do jobs none of us want to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 19:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Instantwatcher.com](http://instantwatcher.com/) is a great site for finding and rating Netflix movies.  You can find plenty of ideas here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 17:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New employees who come in thinking they're smarter and know more about everything than anyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 19:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither, he's an American concerned about things he's seeing and is informing us, as anyone with half a conscience should.  He's put his own safety in danger for the good of the country.  How many politicians do you know who would do that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 19:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laying on the sand at the beach at night staring at the sky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 19:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because many have no sense of modesty or decency.  I've seen far worse things hanging out or falling down than bra straps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 19:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because people don't use the search function or look back at older posts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 19:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People get sidetracked, that's part of the fun in many threads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 19:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be anything.  It could be cover-ups of governmental involvement in many "suicides", "car accidents", "terror plats", etc.  It could be the plan of initiating martial law for some supposed good of us all.  It could have something to do with the intentional grounding of the economy, or, it could just be a recap of everything already disclosed.  There are far too many things to wonder about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 19:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd mind my own business and go to bed.  It's his yard and he can dig whenever he wants to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 19:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care what people post on facebook or where they get it from.  I've probably already seen it anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 18:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would they fight for something they already have? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 07:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Smiling Man turned out to be a redditor who posted about it just the other day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 07:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phillip Seymour Hoffman.  He kills every role he gets.  The man deserves an Oscar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 07:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Young teens" -

males = guys

females = bitches

There's something wrong in your thinking.  Get your shit straight before posting this crap.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 18:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a weird, funny and sometimes disturbing place, much like Wonderland, only I'm not Alice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 18:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been around for years and isn't exactly a secret.  There are articles mentioning the site everywhere these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 18:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judge Ito.  The cats' facial hair looked just like his. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 18:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We used to be able to do this without worry just a few years ago, and did because it was fun.  These days it just isn't smart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 18:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure we are, and it's purposeful.  Look around at the people you know and see how many you'd call intelligent or use good critical thinking skills.  Media manipulation keeping people uninformed and ignorant is an overwhelming success.  They buy into it willingly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 18:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are good reasons why people don't want their pictures attached to their user names or crave the attention of pervs online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 17:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, makes no sense to me either.  Hmm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 17:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> View vs few, check your wording.

I would think you could too, but no, they say you will not be able to see any of them with earth bound telescopes due to resolution and brightness issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 17:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a time limit for new users.  Observe the limit, post when you can and it will stop after a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 17:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'd have to build facilities to mass produce this stuff with no real benefit.  It's better to give people the means to take care of themselves rather than making more new stuff we really don't need. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 17:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's ridiculously expensive and unnecessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 16:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It works.  That's good enough for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 16:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They sound like rules for 10 year olds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 16:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't noticed anything different.  It seems to be working fine for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 08:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, not familiar with that one.  You might want to try /r/tipofmytongue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 08:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, the only one I know about involved all three.  Good luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 08:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It certainly catches you off-guard.  For a minute you wonder if they're possessed or something, then it dawns on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 08:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it regarding Duchenne Muscular Dystrophy, the Rose Bowl in Hawaii or the Make A Wish Foundation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 08:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moon(s) pic from my porch. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-17 23:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Billboard provides water from air for thousands in Peru. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 17:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How old would you be if you didn't know how old you are? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-01 23:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like 38 would be good for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marijuana joint falls out of assistant city attorney's pocket -- in court, in front of police officers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 00:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marijuana joint falls out of assistant city attorney's pocket -- in court, in front of police officers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 00:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what are you listening to right now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-11 03:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ok reddit , the PowerBall lottery is up to $320 million, lump sum payoff of $213.3 million.  What would you do with it if you won? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 07:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First thing I'd do is hire a good attorney and disappear for a while.  I don't think I'd tell anyone I'd won or where I was.  How about you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would your reaction be if one of the images coming from the Mars rover showed some kind of face peering into the lens? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-06 14:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do little kids always cut the hair off of dolls? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-24 17:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not-So-Rare Southern California Snail tree. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-23 21:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since scientists have found an almost completely intact mammoth, can they clone it and bring them back? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-04 17:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Found here](http://news.discovery.com/).  SInce there was muscle tissue, I assume they could extract DNA and recreate this animal. Is this possible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vatican calls for a Central World Bank </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-25 05:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for that video about a man who was able to talk for one hour a day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-31 04:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a video about a brain damaged man who could only talk one hour a day.  Does anyone have a link to that, please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your top local news story today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-04 18:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The top headline in my local paper is about a 22 year old who rear-ended a truck on a high-rise bridge.  The impact pushed the truck off into the river killing the driver.  The police found a crack pipe in the 22 year olds' car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does iodine do (physically) for people subjected to excess doses of radioactivity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-15 23:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been reading a lot lately about iodine pills for those exposed in Japan and of shortages now occuring in California.  How does it help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blackwater moving operations from NC to Florida. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-09 18:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's the end of the world as we know it.  Where would you start over and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-30 03:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just finished watching the movie "2012" and started wondering where I'd set-up shop after a global upheaval.  If you could pick any location on earth to start life over with your family, where would you pick and why?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your opinion of the meaning of Luke 17:21? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-10 06:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think Jesus meant when he said "The kingdom of God is within you". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
