<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1598</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 11:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be nice to have another post on how to get a project licence and an institutional licence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heart repair breakthroughs replace surgeon's knife </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 11:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 18:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should say, the post was written by a PhD student from Imperial University London </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How hard is it to get a licence to carry out animal research in the UK? Read on! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 18:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-22 15:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many of these animals that PETA picks up don't get to the shelter. Around 1% of the animals are adopted ... most shelters have much better rates than this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-22 15:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were doing this at the same time as protesting the death of one cat

http://speakingofresearch.com/2013/02/08/a-lesson-in-hypocrisy-as-peta-cries-foul-over-one-cats-death-while-secretly-killing-hundreds-more/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-22 15:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were doing this at the same time as protesting the death of a cat

http://speakingofresearch.com/2013/02/08/a-lesson-in-hypocrisy-as-peta-cries-foul-over-one-cats-death-while-secretly-killing-hundreds-more/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 14:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair play - how come you don't agree with IVF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Macaques to Humans: UK regulator gives cautious thumbs up to advanced IVF techniques to prevent mitochondrial disease </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 14:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 17:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good news - the US seems to be folowing the UK in phasing out chimp research </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liver transplant breakthrough set to save thousands of lives: Thank the pigs! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 16:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 13:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone (same person?) did one on vaccines a while back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Public Conversation on Animal Ethics: The good, the bad, and the ugly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 12:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 12:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolute gold. I'll get out the bollinger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 18:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SR has a couple of goals. Standing up against illegal extremism (which represents only a very tiny minority of the AR movement - but one with a disproportional voice) and standing up against misinformation. The second action IS needed, as there is much distortion of the science. 

The slow down in medicine is happening. Only a few airlines will continue to transport primates - used for vital medical research (and only where other animals would not be suitable). This prevents some research going on, and raises the cost of research - reducing the amount of it.
Activists broke into Marshall breeding facility and took the animals. Raising the cost of research, reducing it.
Activists are protesting the movement of the AZ dogs - if they managed, AZ would simply end up breeding more, and having to put them through the same processes - this does not make "better" research, or "better" animal welfare.

Now, we need to be sure not to underestimate the importance of animal welfare. There are many working towards this. Some push is from the AR movement, some from the animal welfare movements (e.g. RSPCA), most is from the animal welfare officers within the labs. I had the job of looking round a lab the other day, and you should see the pride from the NACWO (Named animal care and welfare officer) of the primate lab discuss all the systems he has in place. The importance of diet, group housing, horizontal bars and viewing platforms in the enclosures, and mostly good training of the animals to reduce their environmental and handling stresses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-15 17:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brandon, thank you for your reply.

We are indeed all on the same side in both wishing for further medical advances and wishing for the continued development of alternative methods. The 3Rs, developed by two scientists in the 50s, have been the cornerstone of animal welfare - aiming for the refinement, replacement and reduction of animal research (something we should all agree on).
There are some promising technologies in the pipeline that should replace some bits of animal research (lung-on-a-chip is a more recent one), however there is no sign of technologies that can replace all of animal use for medical research, nor is there a sign that new areas won't continue to be developed with a need for animal use.

This link was aimed at informing people on both sides (it was also posted elsewhere) as to how projects are taken from being an idea to a study.

You are right when you say scientifically minded people should go with the best results, and then add a healthy dose of leaning against animal use. However, you cannot get a project approved if there are alternative methods available. In the UK that is checked by the Home Office, in the US it is checked by the Institutional Animal Care and Use Committee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-15 11:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a lot of work in labs aimed at ensuring animal welfare remains high. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-14 23:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would have thought deep brain stimulation would have said it all:
http://pro-test.org.uk/facts.php?lt=aa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Closer Look at How Animal Research Progresses from Idea to Study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-14 18:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 13:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's essentially a trailer for an episode of BBC dispatches. There will be more footage on that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How easy is it to buy a gun in Texas? (BBC) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 03:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 11:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need to convince me off UKIP - I would never vote for them. Nonetheless, I agree with the workfare program - we have a terrible prison system with ridiculously high reoffending rates - something has to change. Japan probably moves too far away from human rights in its prison system (e.g. no conjugal visits destroys families), but there must be lessons we can learn from them.

Scrapping CPS, human rights etc - that's terrifying and one of the many reasons I would not vote UKIP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-06 10:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hasten to add that I am not a fan of UKIP, but I feel what was written above on prisons wasn't telling the whole story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-06 10:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With regards to inmates doing physical work, I don't think they have prison labour for military efforts in mind.
I'm not sure whether I agree with it, but Japan has very strict prisons, all inmates must work long days, and more importantly they have very, very low reoffending rates.
http://www.economist.com/news/asia/21572257-even-japanese-criminals-are-orderly-and-well-behaved-eastern-porridge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 20:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Closer Look at How Animal Research Progresses from Idea to Study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 17:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vince Cable announces he doesn't want to take leadership from Clegg (BBC) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 13:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 18:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I confess under normal circumstances I loathe to link to the Mail. It's not high quality science writing, but the article was interesting and reasonably well explained and I've provided the original paper below for people's perusal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 18:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who are asking for it - here is the original paper:
http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/22654062 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 18:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the hell?!

1. Lib Dems are not a minority party (smallest of the 3 major parties)
2. The major vote wasn't split between Tories and Labour, Labour got almost no vote
3. If there was a straight run off between Tories and Lib Dems, the Lib Dems would have won it- they have much more support in the area </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 15:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good question - I guess the next stage of trials will work that out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 15:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The veterinarian has rehomed the breeding dogs. The rest would not be suitable for rehoming on the decision of the vet.

It would also mean the same beagles would just have to be bred again in the UK - which is against the idea of reduction of animal research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Allowing a paralysed rat to walk again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 13:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paralysed rats can walk again after a cocktail of drugs and retraining </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 13:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 18:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you rather own bank or charing cross branch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK Guide to Twitter Laws  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 12:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Case Study: Animal Rights vs Animal Research SEO (thoughts welcome, I am not an SEO expert at all) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 17:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A huge bank of resources for students to use when writing essays relating to animal testing (see links at bottom of page for each topic) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 11:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How biomedical researchers can face up to animal rights campaigns effectively </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 16:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 15:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hopefully </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Artificial retina developed through animal research lets blind people see again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 15:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 12:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Government's still borrow when in surplus if cheap credit is available. Also, money comes at certain points in the year (when taxes are due) so they often borrow at one point in the year and repay later on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 11:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are two potential risks (I won't say they will or won't happen because economics is unpredictably complex much of the time).

- Firstly, a fast rise in government spending involves the government borrowing from abroad and from markets. Essentially this can absorb all the available cheap credit which really need to go to firms - so firms have little money to invest. This is called "crowding out" of investment.

- Secondly, deficit's must have a credible repayment plan. If you don't then the markets lose  faith and your borrowing rates skyrocket - this results in huge chunks of money going into repayment each year. This is what happened to Greece and Italy last year (and almost France). Compared with the UK, which in its tight-fisted austerity, maintained market trust for repayment, so credit remained cheap. This credibility not only affects governments, but can have a knock on effect to bank and company borrowing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-21 12:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should absolutely take account of the authors interest, but unless you can criticise what he says, that's not enough to dismiss it. 

The author accepts the findings of the original paper, but suggests that the NYT article overstates what is contained in the sources. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-21 12:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BUAV argue the government promised to reduce animal research - what was meant was within the principle of the 3Rs.

There has been huge increases in expenditure on alternatives - most obviously seen by the fact that money into biomedicine has gone much much faster than the use of animals (thus most money is going into non-animal methods). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-20 16:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-20 13:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also worth noting that arbitrary reduction of animal research across the board (rather than individual experiments) is that it just pushes it overseas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reduction: A Measure You Cant Measure - Explaining why animal rights groups should not be calling for a reduction in experiments in the UK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-20 13:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 03:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little bit sweeping. Some vegans (at best - most seem to just prefer to say companion animal and then treat them like a pet). 

Anyhow, you're dodging the question. Let me go another way - Do you get rid of a threadworm infection? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 19:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's important not to exagerrate what the original paper actually says (which the NYT headline does) - see a rebuttal here: http://speakingofresearch.com/2013/02/15/why-mice-may-succeed-in-research-when-a-single-mouse-falls-short/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 19:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's important not to exaggerate what the original paper actually says (which the NYT headline does) - see a rebuttal here: http://speakingofresearch.com/2013/02/15/why-mice-may-succeed-in-research-when-a-single-mouse-falls-short/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 18:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nature had an article today about the use of GM mice:
http://www.nature.com/news/proteins-behind-mad-cow-disease-also-help-brain-to-develop-1.12428 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 17:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a link to the original NYT article:
http://www.nytimes.com/2013/02/12/science/testing-of-some-deadly-diseases-on-mice-mislead-report-says.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why mice may succeed in research when a single mouse falls short: A rebuttal to the recent NYT article on mouse models </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 17:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 17:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can catch it from your dog - so the hypothetical remains </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 11:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHat do you do if you get a tapeworm?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 20:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fortunately cosmetic testing is banned in the UK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The British Government takes a strong stance in support of animal research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 16:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 13:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full original paper:
http://diabetes.diabetesjournals.org/content/55/6/1546.long
(sourced in text as well) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Type I Diabetes cured in dogs using gene therapy - one step closer to human treatment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 12:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 16:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zeus wants him dead - we all saw the thunderbolt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 20:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The USDA inspected the facility and found no wrong doing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 16:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never thought that an English breakfast might not translate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 16:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That film is 30 years old... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hypocrisy as PETA protest death of a research cat on one hand, and hundreds of shelter cats with the other </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 11:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that was people using apple headphones... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 13:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that, but sometimes it seems a little "tacked on". The "it's unethical, and even if it was ethical it doesn't work".

However, the scientific arguments against animal research just don't seem to add up - as many of the debunked articles in the link above </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 00:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm, seems like the counter to the "33 facts of vivisection" ... still a few more to debunk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 17:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then this discussion should hold no interest for you. Prof. Lovell-Badge's article was meant to dispute those activists who were misusing that statistic for their own argument. You were not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 15:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a scary world when activists can hold medicine to ransom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 14:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Full: bacon, sausages, bakes beans (with mini sausages in), mushrooms, cheese and scrambled eggs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Hidden Fried Breakfast - The Greatest Development in Morning Tastiness [1000x670][OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 13:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 12:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all drugs must be tested on animals - so difficult to find </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 12:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They use the first argument a lot - the statistic is often quoted as "92%". The latter stat could never be tested, it would be unethical to give a treatment which killed animals to humans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 12:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The UK has had a ban for years, Europe has just fallen suit. Hopefully the US will settle on a set of alternative tests that will satisfy regulators (they are getting there). It does make it difficult to use novel chemicals in new cosmetics, but honestly, we don't need new lipsticks at the cost of animals. 

I support animal research for medicine, but I'm all for dumping both cosmetic testing and the LD50 tests (who cares about the dosage that kills 50% of mice - The LD10 would show a dosage that's too high). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 11:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no data - it would unethical to move forward a drug shown to be dangerous in animals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 11:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> read the post - the 9/10 refers to a specific "fact" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 03:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To my mind negative rights always entail a duty. My right to life entails a duty not to kill, and so does yours - the result is that neither of us kills one another. When it comes to those who can't think for themselves, such as babies, society deems it right to extend that right as they have the potential to fulfill their duty later on. Similarly, those in a vegatative state have a potential to get better. 

An animal will never be able to understand the duties entailed by their rights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 00:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cosmetic testing is banned in the UK - which is a good thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 17:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of which 17% turn out to be precisely true upon review </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 17:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The TGN1412 disaster has been the only situation where anyone has even nearly died in Stage I clinical trials that I can name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 16:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dfgb - go and google "Drug Monkey" and "anti-vaccination" and you will have all the science debunking your claims written clearly and scientifically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nine out of ten Statistics are taken out of Context: Debunking the most commonly misused statistic by animal rights activists. Written by Prof. Lovell-Badge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 16:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 15:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, in the situation of rights-duties, the word "duty" has a rather grander meaning than in casual conversations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 15:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A human cannot appeal to its rights when dealing with another animals - the other animal doesn't understand. Rights exist to mediate human-to-human interaction - it is meaningless across species.

Rights are an expansion of the golden rule - if you don't do this to me, I won't do it to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 15:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's amazing seeing the improvements in mouse models in the field of neuroscience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 15:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Children DO have a right to education, thus the state has a DUTY to provide it.

Responsibility is an alternative to rights. So a painting of the Mona Lisa has, itself, no rights - nonetheless society deems we have responsibility to look after it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Animal research: a want or a need? (The McGill Daily) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 13:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 13:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree, it is there to mock this idea that animal research is some terrible cruelty when the reality is that it is tightly regulated and far more humane than anything that goes on in nature.

If it is about how we expect humans to act towards animals then it is a responsibility not a right - rights entail duties which an animal cannot carry out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 13:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a shorthand for saying that? Do I use [OC]? Still new to Reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forget the Ritz, everyone knows the grandparents do the best afternoon tea [816x612] [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 13:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 10:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose that's a small advantage to this mass bird-kill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's a Cat-astrophe: Why the number of animals killed by cats is a problem for animal rights activists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 10:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 13:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the support - it's great to see scientists, veterinarians and technicians start to speak up on this complex issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 12:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll note that deaths in Stage I clinical trials are almost unheard of. Certainly no deaths in the UK for the past 30 years and only one major incident (TGN1412). So animal research remains a crucial step to protecting people.

Secondly, most animal research is not for testing drugs, it is for developing drugs and in that stage it is crucial. You can't cut up a human to see how a disease is spreading or how it works. How would you get a breakthrough medicine like the HPV vaccine (against cervical cancer) which is originally a mouse protein - without the use of animals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why would a vet work in an animal research laboratory? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 18:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beware of Wheelchair Mobsters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 13:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Statistics from UK Census show no religion up 11% over the past decade. Christianity down 12% </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-11 11:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-20 12:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? It's a fun way of looking at the scientific debunking of many animal rights claims </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-16 16:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i see it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
