<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3286</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your most anticipated games of this year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 03:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Everclear make me bigger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 01:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wait a second guys... is Rich Piana... not natty??? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 00:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which natural bodybuilder do you look up to for inspiration? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 20:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's Rich Piana (or as I call him, Richy Poo). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you ever fire up the ol' 360 (if you have one)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 17:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing this to play The Witcher 2 in anticipation of The Witcher 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is 6.5 inches a good penis length? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 19:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is The Witcher 2 worth playing through? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 20:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a lot of hype for The Witcher 3, so I was wondering if it's worth playing The Witcher 2 on the Xbox 360. (I don't have a powerful PC, so I can't play the original Witcher.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fasting as a form of penance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 20:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel very guilty about accidentally killing my dog (I was playing with him near the top of the stairs, and he fell down to the basement, breaking his back, so I had to put him down), so I am going to start fasting to punish myself. I am not sure how long I should fast. I am thinking 90 days. Is this appropriate, or should it be shorter or longer? (I'm not overweight or anything, so there isn't any weight that needs to be lost.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many times have you been in a mental hospital? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 18:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And why were you admitted?

three times for me

1. mania

2. anorexia

3. catatonia
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you need to have played the previous Witcher games to understand the story of The Witcher 3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 18:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Witcher 3 looks like an interesting game, so I was wondering if I have to play the previous games. I have an Xbox 360 and an Xbox One, so I have the ability to play the second and third game. I see that the first game is only available on PC, so as my PC isn't powerful enough to game on, I am unable to play the original game. Am I OK with only playing the third game, or should I also play the second? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What are the most depressing songs you know? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 05:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best Turtle Beach headset for the Xbox One? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 22:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to know when to start bulking? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 23:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ended my last ketogenic cut at 106 lbs (from 205 lbs), which led me to a psych ward. I then gained 44 lbs eating whatever I wanted and not exercising. I have since lost 10 lbs after re-starting keto. My question is: when do I stop cutting so I don't end up in the same place again? The bodyfat calculator put me at around 19% bodyfat. Due to my last extreme cut, I have really no muscle whatsoever. I'm pretty sure I would be considered skinnyfat right now as I have a slight belly and man boobs. Indeed I don't want to bulk quite yet. Should I cut to 120 lbs?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best keto foods to buy at Trader Joe's? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 21:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to be near a Trader Joe's tomorrow, so I was wondering what to keep my eye out for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone have experience with ECT? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 21:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm undergoing a series of ECT treatments (on #9) for catatonia. Does anyone here have experience with ECT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to convince my parents that keto doesn't equal an eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 20:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started keto last February at 206 lbs and ended at in October at 106 lbs, which led me to a psych ward, in which I had to go back to carbs and gained 44 lbs. Now when I say I want to go back to a ketogenic diet, they dismiss it as "the eating disorder talking." How do I convince them that keto is a legitimate diet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is SuperPump 3.0 keto-friendly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 19:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the bodybuilding.com page if you don't know what it is.](http://www.bodybuilding.com/store/gaspari-nutrition/superpump-30.html)

I took two scoops of it and now I feel really bloated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transition to maintenance after a long cut? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 23:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started cutting in early February of this year at 205 (obese) and am now 138. I have been on a ketogenic diet throughout the cut. I'm 17, male, and 5'7". I heard that after a long cut you're supposed to slowly add back calories (reverse diet). How do I go about this? How many calories do I add per week? I have been cutting on 1,400 calories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a need to reverse diet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 00:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have cut down from 205 (obese) from February of this year to 138. The body fat calculator at my gym says that I am around 12% bodyfat. I am male, 17, and 5'7". I didn't start tracking calories until 71 days ago, so I can't say what my calories were before I started tracking, but as of 71 days ago I have kept my calories at or below 1,400. Is it necessary to reverse diet to maintenance calories (adding a set amount of calories each week until maintenance is achieved)? If so, how would I go about this? How many calories would I add per week?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most accurate food scale that I can buy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 01:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been using a cheap food scale that lately has become very unreliable. I want to be able to track my macros accurately, so I would like to buy one I can rely on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ankle pain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-06 20:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started running in intervals a few days ago on a track, walking on the curves and running on the straight part, this lasting about an hour. I have since experienced outer ankle pain in both feet. I am male, 17, 140 lbs, 5'7", and am running in Kinvara 5's. I have just started running, so I am wondering if this is typical beginner's running pain or if I'm doing something wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does it matter how much protein you eat in one sitting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 02:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that eating too much protein in a day will kick you out of ketosis, but what if you eat like 80 grams of protein in one sitting (but staying below the protein limit for the day)? Will eating a lot of protein in a short period of time kick you out of ketosis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jerry's take on enhanced actors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 00:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this a good amount of calories to cut on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 20:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am cutting on 1,400 calories (around 105 protein, 101 fat and less than 20 carbs). I am 17 years old, male, 5'7", 152 lbs, 18.4% bodyfat. I'm running ICF 5x5.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much fish oil to take per day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 19:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now I'm taking a cheap fish oil which has 300 mg of EPA and DHA combined per capsule. I take 6 capsules a day. Is this a good amount to take? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's all relative </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 03:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is 5'7" manlet territory? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 18:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 17 years old and I'm only 5'7". Am I doomed to a life of a manlet, or am I tall enough to not worry about this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would it be a bad idea for a new runner to wear a barefoot shoe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 22:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking about buying the Merrell Trail Glove 2. Is this a bad idea for someone beginning to run? This shoe appeals to me because it could double as a shoe for lifting and running. Should I instead get a dedicated lifting shoe and a more traditional running shoe like [this](http://www.adidas.com/us/product/mens-running-cc-rocket-boost-shoes/IEU81?cid=D66285 breadcrumb=1z13071Z1z11zrfZsvZu2Z1z13y9l)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S4E7] My favorite scene of last night's episode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 16:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the first RHCP album you listened to in full? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 19:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it was Californication. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Damn Ikea (x-post from r/gameofthrones) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 17:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why must you awaken me from my Slumber? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 02:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the better singer: Frusciante or Kiedis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 02:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't stop laughing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 01:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't the Women shave their arms? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 03:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arm hair on one of the Women is disgusting, and to be perfectly honest it offends me. Why do the Women refuse the shaving? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How To Get Your Girlfriend To Train! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 03:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Frusciante -- God [alt rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 00:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jon Lajoie -- Please Use This Song [Comedy] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 20:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Frusciante - Your Pussy's Glued To A Building On Fire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 00:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is Mr. Slave doing with my gerbils? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 05:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They keep disappearing! Whenever I ask him about it, he always responds by moaning, "Oh, Jesus Christ." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's wrong with my TV? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 19:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Toshiba 46SL417U LED TV. When I press the power button, a green light (which usually flashes once when it is turned on) flashes 3 times, stops for a few seconds, then flashes 3 times again and repeats the process indefinitely. No picture or audio. I unplugged it for about an hour and plugged it back it with no change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's wrong with my TV? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 03:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Toshiba 46SL417U LED TV. When I press the power button, a green light (which usually flashes once when it is turned on) flashes 3 times, stops for a few seconds, then flashes 3 times again and repeats the process indefinitely. No picture or audio. I unplugged it for about an hour and plugged it back it with no change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What nicknames did your mom give you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 03:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something on your hard drive that you never want anyone to find? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 02:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your least favorite songs from each album? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 20:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favorite non-album track? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 22:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Favorite album? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 04:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is Stadium Arcadium. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What food scale do you use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 18:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you provide an Amazon link? I'm going to get a food scale, but I don't know which one to get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Season 4] Game of Thrones Season 4: Inside the Episode #1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 04:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great dip I found at Costco </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 02:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.laterrafina.com/chunky-spinach-artichoke-parmesan-dip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What shoe should I try on to know the size of adiPower I should order? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 03:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There aren't any stores that I know of that stock adiPowers, so what shoe has the same fit as the adiPower?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are Detour bars keto-friendly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 19:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.drugstore.com/detour-15g-whey-protein-bar-lower-sugar-chocolate-chip-caramel/qxp353992?catid=326472 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best Vibram Five Fingers model? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 03:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be using them primarily for lifting. I also use the elliptical and bike. I'm not a very big runner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would it be weird to bring 3 pairs of shoes to the gym? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 03:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm running a full body program, which means I do squats and deadlifts on the same day. I like to squat in adipowers and deadlift in chucks. I also do cardio post-workout, for which I use running shoes. Would it be considered weird to bring all 3 of these shoes to the gym? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TP] A sports mascot is an "unobtainable standard of beauty" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 03:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you do at the gym that makes you feel superior to others? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 02:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's squatting ass to grass while most everyone else is doing parallel/above parallel. I always feel like going up in their face and shouting, "ASS TO GRASS, BUDDY!!!!!!!!!!!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I saw The Wolf of Wall Street today... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 04:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Cooking with Cersei Lannister </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 15:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Season 4] Weapons   Training Featurette </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 17:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How should I track things that have "less than 1 gram" of carbs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 15:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coconut Oil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 14:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Season 4] Game of Thrones Season 4 Premiere </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 22:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were to forever leave reddit, what would your reddit tombstone say? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 23:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BCAAs and keto </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 02:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite South Park episode? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 02:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should adiPowers be used as an everyday training shoe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 01:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or are they more for competition/maxing out? Also, are they for an advanced lifter, or are they ok for all experience levels? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [All Spoilers] How is the show going to handle... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 16:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the Walk of Shame? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have any good guacamole recipes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 04:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are you addicted to Reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 21:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long is it safe to fast? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 20:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With keto I find it very easy to fast for long periods of time without getting hungry. What is the maximum amount of time one should fast? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BCAAs and keto </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 03:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> help with buying beta alanine in bulk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 18:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does [this](http://www.amazon.com/Beta-Alanine-1000-Grams-2-2lbs/dp/B008Z84IQQ/ref=sr_1_11?ie=UTF8 qid=1394903564 sr=8-11 keywords=beta+alanine) look good? 1,000g for $35. Is this quality beta alanine? Do you recommend something else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] See Westeros in Style in this Minimalist 'Game of Thrones' Opening (x-post from r/asoiaf) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 17:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (No Spoilers) Are the Tales of Dunk and Egg worth reading? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-13 23:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Season 4] Brienne's maniacal laugh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-09 00:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Season 4] Game of Thrones Mixtape Preview </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 22:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My right pec is bouncing without my permission???? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 03:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My right pec is out of control. It is bouncing randomly without my consent. Why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I squat ass to grass or parallel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 04:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xtend or Purple Wraath? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 00:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is erythritol keto-friendly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 19:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to drink Monster Zero Ultra. It has 2 grams of erythritol per can (no other carbs). Is this ok? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the difference between the old Hyde formula and the new one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 14:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Season 4] Dany Dragon Tease </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 22:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Season 4] Tyrion Tease </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 22:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are olives keto-friendly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 00:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite Quest bar? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 14:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is Chocolate Chip Cookie Dough. Also, how often do you eat Quest bars? Do they make you stall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is intermittent fasting a good idea on keto? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 06:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [All Show Spoilers] Do you watch the special features? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 06:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some books with great character development? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 05:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to really care about the characters like I did in A Song of Ice and Fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's a boy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 00:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] What are some books like ASOIAF? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 06:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Creatine Monster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 19:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a cold Friday afternoon, I had come home from school. I had been thinking of the gym all day. I was hungry, didn't have any lunch. In fact, I didn't eat because I spent the money. For the past month I was saving up for something. Something special which I bought at GNC. I was surprised they didn't ask for ID; I was pretty sure the cashier noticed how nervous I was. Anyways, my mom asked my how my day was when I got home, but I ignored her. I have more important things to do. I run to the bathroom and unpack my bag. In my school bag is a white plastic bag from GNC. I open the bag, first removing the receipt and flushing it down the toilet to get rid of the evidence. My heart was racing now. I unpack the creatine monster from the bag.

I wonder what people will be asking me when they see that I will be 50lbs heavier. Should I say I was just eating a lot? I remove the label from the tub and tear it into a thousand small pieces. I flush that down the toilet, too. It is time now. I run up to my room when my mom ask me what I am holding. I panic, sweat drips down my forehead and my teeth chatter. "Mom, it's just for a school project". "What project?" "I don't know mom I just started it!". A tear runs down my cheek. I run upstairs and open the creatine, scooping upservings into a clear water bottle. What have I gotten myself into? I fill it with water and drink it. There is no turning back now. The creatine monster is inside me now, it will control me. What should I do if I die? I cant let my family know about this.

I open the creatine tub and throw it all out the window; a white cloud of mysterious dust sparkles into the wind so graciously. I feel the substance taking control of me; I am now the monster. I walk downstairs, its time to work out; time to get big. Now I worry, I don't want to get too big; people will think I use steroids. I do use steroids. No I don't. Creatine. All I see is the weights now, I am almost downstairs when I hear "Do you want a cookie I just baked?" I know I do not have time for this shit now. "No mom I do not want a fucking cookie." I walk in the basement and drop to my knees before the weights, tears running down my cheeks. I turn to the right and look at myself in the mirror. Oh god, what have I done? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [All Spoilers] Do you give characters nick names? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 16:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I call Quentyn my Quenty Bear.
Victarion is my Vikkey Bunny.
Strong Belwas is Belly Boo Boo.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this Buffalo Wild Wings meal keto-friendly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 02:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 12 Thai Curry traditional wings with 2 containers of blue cheese </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [All spoilers] What devastated me more than the Red Wedding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 18:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When my Quenty Bear died. :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [All Spoilers] Who should play Quentyn Martell? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 04:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who are you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 04:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, not your name, not your job, not your hobbies, not your personality. Really, who are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you didn't eat that one muffin that one time, where would you be now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 03:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Which version of the season 3 blu-ray are you getting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 02:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you getting the regular version, Lannister version, Targaryen version, Stark version, or Amazon limited edition dragon statue version? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best pair of compression shorts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 03:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I avoid compression shorts tearing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 02:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Don't say "Get a bigger size." That's not the problem. They fit perfectly.)
I bought a pair of Under Armour ["Core"](http://www.dickssportinggoods.com/product/index.jsp?productId=13050949) compression shorts, and after less than 3 months of wear, a hole appeared at the leg seam. Both leg seams were falling apart. 
I'm thinking of buying a new pair of compression shorts. How do I prevent them from breaking down? Is there a certain way of washing them? Should I get a different brand/model? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adidas Adipower or Adidas Powerlift 2.0? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 00:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is 5'7" short for a guy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 20:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He has something very special planned for Valentine's Day... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 05:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Should I get the Stark or Targaryen Season 3 Blu-ray? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 03:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best Buy is offering Lannister, Stark and Targaryen slipcovers for the season 3 blu-rays. I already have the Lannister slipcover from season 2. Should I get the Stark, Targaryen, or both? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [All Spoilers] Have you ever fallen for a fake spoiler? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 19:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard somewhere that Cersei killed Tommen. I read the last part of ADWD anticipating this scene.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [All Spoilers] Which character death hit you the hardest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 06:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it was Quentyn Martell. I threw my Kindle across my bedroom when I read his death scene. I just sat in my bed crying, wishing that it wasn't true, that my Quenty Bear wasn't dead. It threw me into a deep depression for months, mourning the loss of the best character in ASOIAF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something you've done that you would never let your children do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 06:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will there be a Borderlands 2 complete edition? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 06:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed DLC is still being released even after the Game of the Year Edition came out. I was going to get the GOTY edition, but not if an edition will all the DLC will come out in a few months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you use subtitles when you watch Sherlock? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 00:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ADWD] This made me lol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 03:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which Buffalo Wild Wings sauces are keto-friendly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 16:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Who is your favorite Dornishman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 15:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you like to read multiple books at once? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 19:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jason Blaha 5x5 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 00:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I refuse to fap until I get to 8% bodyfat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 17:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has been written.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is is possible to gain strength while cutting on keto? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 17:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this the perfect whey protein for keto? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 16:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever played Everclear pong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 03:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same as beer pong but you fill the cups (same size as beer pong) completely full with Everclear. Has to be pure Everclear, 190 proof, no mixing it with juice, you have to chug it all down with no breaks, and no chaser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What keeps you up at night? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 03:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite brand of athletic clothing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 03:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever been depressed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 02:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is so, why were you depressed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All-Knowing Pug </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 02:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think the drinking age should be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 01:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jason Blaha's 5x5 program </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 21:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do guys claim that keto makes their dick bigger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 20:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this some sort of inside joke? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this subreddit like for people who are addicted to porn/fapping? Like Don Jon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 19:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> are you guys fucking serious </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 19:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there's nothing wrong with fapping. it's completely natural. grow up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you define a small, average and large penis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 02:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long is a small penis?
How long is an average penis?
How long is a large penis?
Also, do you care about penis size? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cardio during keto? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 01:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started keto a week ago, and I have no stamina to do cardio. I am usually able to use the elliptical for 1-2 hours, but in the past week I can only do it for a few minutes. I still have enough energy to lift as much as I've been doing pre-keto, though. Is this just a symptom of the induction phase? If so, how long will it last?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is everyone so big on Quest bars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 17:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have like 25 grams of carbs...how is that keto-friendly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keto breakfast ideas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 17:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tired of bacon and eggs everyday. What do you eat for breakfast? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have something very important to ask you guys... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 17:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
