<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1519</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 01:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In indian church we MUST clap. And honestly I love that part! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 15:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally using Head and Shoulder should suffice.

However, if it is severe then you can apply nizoral prescription shampoo that should take away the problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 14:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eat insoluble fiber.

FiberOne cereal, an apple, etc. 

Fiber will make you feel full longer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 04:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what career choices did you make as a result of this?

Did your parents past work position offer any gains to you. Maybe getting into a good school or job, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 03:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 22:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I just learned something here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 04:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use ur floormat and put it under your wheel. This will give it something else to ride on instead of ice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 04:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My suggestions :

1. Buy an egyptian cotton towel
2. Do not put towel in dryer, just hang them.
3. Wash by hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 02:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the reason I ask is because I've given gross, net, and just out of the wallet. This is how I have felt.

((Gross - net)*10% - Given to various charities of my choosing) + (net *10% to local church) -- Current approach -- Feel somewhat joyful giving this way since I can choose to give to charities I want to give to , but still feel legalistic. 
Gross straight to church - Didn't really feel joyful doing this so went with the plan above. Mainly didnt feel joyful because money was going to local church and the money was primarily being stored in the bank.
Net Pay - Loved this approach only because I felt how can I give more than I actually bring home. But was told that the proper approach is to give a tithe on gross. And well felt guilty, ya di yada.
Wallet - Felt great but always felt like I should given even more than just a couple of bills. Usually I don't carry to much cash.

That said, I think I can give at all levels, and I can surely say that God has blessed me over the years abundantly. 20K+ increase in salary over the last 3 years. So needless to say I am blessed for that. However, I miss the joyful giving that I used to be able to do. And I wanted to test out to see which approach is best. I believe NT approach is by your own will but 10% is def a good standard, and God approved :). 
So the reason for my question was mainly to see if people have tested out both theories and to see which one they like/enjoy, which ones they were most blessed with, etc. 

And to the fact of legalism, well maybe it is, but following Gods guidelines can ultimately change your heart. I mean heck i never thought I'd be able to give beyond my net, but I can, though maybe a little bitterly. And I'm only bitter because I know most of the money just goes straight to the churches savings account when it should be used to fix / maintain the church and to use it to help the current congregation increase their faith.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 01:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh, I'd be curious for someone who teaches EDM music too. Fruity loops specifically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AMA Request] Billy Graham </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 01:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 03:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When did you feel the most joy in giving?
During net, gross, etc. Also, why the variation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Poll] Tithing : Gross or Net? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 23:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you tithe? Gross or Net? 
Do you use 10% or another percentage?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remove non-hdr pics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 17:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there an app or any kind of utility that removes all non-hdr pics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 00:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yupp, just used mailstrom for something else and well its pheneomenal!

They can have my money! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 00:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must admit that Mailstrom is pretty awesome at analyzing my email. Though for some odd reason it was unable to delete my emails. Though that maybe due to the fact that I deleted the emails in my system after seeing the analyzed report. I'm going to give it another try on my other email address. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 00:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of API do you guys use? Reason I ask is because i was thinking about creating a similar app using MailSystem.Net. But since you guys already have a good software, well there goes my plans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 03:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would u teach christianity before jesus?

You would probably treated like the false messiahs of that time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 02:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For reefs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 02:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, my suggestion would be that if you want to understand your girlfriends religion then your best bet is to learn from her.

Ask her that you want to be part of her spiritual life and for that you want to learn whatever you can from her.

That verse couldnt have been a better choice. Those two commandments of Loving God and Loving one another truly embody the entire rules of Christianity. 

However, if you want to understand Christianity better on your own then read the bible. Start from one of the gospels, either Luke or John. The gospel will tell you about Jesus and pretty much what following Christ is all about (Christian = follower of Christ). Then you can go from cover to cover if you wish. But start from the gospel.

And of course, attend her church. The pastors job is to explain whats in the Bible (like that verse) and to take care of the people attending that church.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where does the remaining materials of a demolished building go? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 23:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So when they demolish a building. Do they just throw everything to landfill. Or do they reuse it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 05:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yupp!

Even though I grew up as a Christian I still manage to have a fall out. A time where i searched to see if I really was a Christian or just raised up that way.

Though I did alot of stupid things during the fall out. I eventually realized that nothing in this world will give me the joy that following Christ does! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redbox </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 14:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does one start a redbox business?

How much does it cost initially?

How much can you make/month? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 19:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you stop being Bourne?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 22:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tl;dr Lenovo Yoga 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 20:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow. kudos to your dad!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 01:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used it to cook my eggs today. They're Pun-omenal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 20:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SA would rather spend the time/money on providing aid to people than to aid colleges. Especially considering the cost of colleges these days. 
(my personal opinion) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 20:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I used to joyfully give 10% of my net tithe. But over the years I started giving 10% of my gross tithe. But wasn't happy so I gave 10% of my net tithe to my local church and (gross-net) * 10% tithe to charities that I wanted to give to. Giving this way allow me to give both to my local church and charities of my choice. And its a great tax deduction ;).
Personally, I would rather just donate the net tithe because I don't see how giving on something you don't have makes sense. Not to mention most of the money I give to my local church goes right to the Bank for future storage rather than to take care of the place.

Though I haven't read Crazy Love maybe you should check that out. I understand you want to be faithful but the New Testament (from what I understand) does not require 10% but requires a cheerful giver (2 Corinthians 9:7) which essentially can mean less than 10% or even more than 10%.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 19:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 19:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for using your talents. These are amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 22:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Do not be overcome by evil. But overcome evil with good" Romans 12:21

Was a verse centered on during a youth retreat and has helped me to keep doing good in the face of evil (or just general bad things). I probably need to face this verse again rather than getting lukewarm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 22:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I can't listen to Christian radio. Its the same song and the same artists for years.

KLove is a haven for TobyMac and Chris Tomlin. Not bad artists but every other song shouldn't be from them and it shouldn't be the same song they have been singing for the last few years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 20:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wanted to say that this comment has made me re-view of what books I will buy down the road! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 18:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Signed up for the course! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 06:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with you! Stay strong! Seek a counselor. Thats what I'm doing. Preferably a christian counselor.

Also check out the app InstaPrayer if you have access to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 02:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For most programming jobs you will not need anything more than Algebra 1 or even basic Arithmetic. You will however need to pass at least Calc 1 to get a BS degree in CS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CS Data Structures - help me understand them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 02:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I graduated few years ago but can't get over the fact that I never fully understood how proofs worked or for that matter any of the material that is taught in the data structures class.

I know major companies desire that their employees understand these concepts but I had a very difficult time understanding the material. We used an outdated textbook that was printed in maybe 1960-1970s and professor used examples of pascal to illustrate the various sorting algorithms.

Anyway, what I'm trying to get to is that is there a modern or maybe a simpler explanation / course / book that can explain all the terminology, concepts, etc. that one should have learned from a regular CS Data Structure course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 02:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish I had seen this sooner. Sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 02:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this worth it? Safe?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 15:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tako in Bensalem, PA. http://philadelphia.menupages.com/restaurants/tako/menu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 15:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have freedompop in Cheltenham, PA area and the service isn't bad. Im using the $10 plan. I don't think it will be good for doing much the interent speeds arent that fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 00:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mom of bomber says that the FBI had the bomber on their radar.

http://www.businessinsider.com/tsarnaev-brothers-mother-fbi-boston-bombing-2013-4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 05:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.accessmylibrary.com/coms2/summary_0286-14735923_ITM

I'm not sure if that's the complete article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 06:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sprite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
