<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1805</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-19 21:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To keep calm I breathe in through my nose and slowly exhale through my mouth for about 15 seconds, makes me feel at ease and makes me laugh about whatever it was I was getting stressed about. I know it seems small and stupid but it really works.

When my nana died I just tried going for runs with music playing and tried be around people as much as possible to help move on. It worked quite well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-19 21:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was one I did when I was bored and was nothing more than childish but I gave out 2 notes on asking people to call back "Mr C Lyon" and "Mr G Raff" The number I gave them was for a zoo. Childish but made me chuckle watching them on the phone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-19 17:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hot wheels cars, they were just badass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 00:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know if already posted but I'll go with James Bond shooting the camera and the blood trickling down  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 16:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Martian Manhunter, should have had one from the off with the new 52 launch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-04 03:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being interested in physics and SPAAAACCCEEEE!!! Not even at school this either this is where I work at now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-04 03:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to songs are duality by slipknot and how you like me now by the heavy. Go to band is either AC/DC, Audioslave or Alice in Chains </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 04:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Batman vs t'challa (black panther) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 04:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kryptonite

But in all seriousness a picture of a scary clown/IT would make me break down. Went to a circus once and had to leave when the clowns started coming into the audience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 04:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prison break. First season was brilliant then it just went horrible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 04:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wear a green lantern ring and make sure you have a blue lantern close by just in case </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 04:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No matter how dark the night gets, the sun still rises in the morning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 19:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The smiley gang. They were around an area where apparently they got kids and slashed their faces (like the jokers) Obviously everyone believed it even when there was not one person walking around with any scars like that (myself included)

This was in Manchester  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 15:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It. Penny wise the fucking clown. Scared of clowns because of this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 15:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toy Story 3. It's when the little girl picks up Woody and makes him wave to Andy that got me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 09:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All it takes is one bad day to reduce the sanest man alive to lunacy. Thats how far the world is from where I am. Just one bad day. You had a bad day once, am I right?

The Joker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 12:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R2D2  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 12:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man utd vs bayern Munich 1999 champions league final. The last 3 minutes I nearly collapsed. Just look at the bayern players to see the devastation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
