<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2082</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 10:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that a very closed-minded, unfair and naive way of rating movies? For example, a movie without any actors or a silent movie without music would for example score 0 on acting and/or sound design automatically? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 02:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> La femme qui se poudre (1972). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 23:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use a scale from 1 to 5 to rate movies, so a perfect score is 5/5 for me. Here are the 26 movies that I've given the highest score possible:     


* Banshun (1949)     
* Un condamn  mort s'est chapp ou Le vent souffle o il veut (1956)       
* Smultronstllet (1957)     
* Jalsaghar (1958)     
* Hiroshima mon amour (1959)    
* Pickpocket (1959)   
* Le trou (1960)    
* La notte (1961)     
* L'eclisse (1962)    
* Nattvardsgsterna (1962)       
* Sanma no aji (1962)         
* Tystnaden (1963)      
* Suna no onna (1964)     
* Andrey Rublyov (1966)     
* Tanin no kao (1966)      
* C'era una volta il West (1968)    
* Erosu purasu Gyakusatsu (1969)      
* Spalovac mrtvol (1969)      
* Die bitteren Trnen der Petra von Kant (1972)      
* Solyaris (1972)     
* Jeanne Dielman, 23 Quai du Commerce, 1080 Bruxelles (1975)  
* Zerkalo (1975)      
* Stalker (1979)       
* Krhozat (1988)        
* Der siebente Kontinent (1989)    
* Stntang (1994)      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 21:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's far from one of my favourites, but it's indeed a good movie. One of Philip Seymour Hoffman's best performances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 20:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is! Quite good and gritty with a nice soundtrack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 20:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 17:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But then again, Iranian films overall have really bad distribution from the start. All of the movies I mentioned have at least been released on DVD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 15:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the best one of them all. Solyaris (1972) by Tarkovsky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 14:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2001: A Space Odyssey (1968) and Solyaris (1972). They're also way better in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 14:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Five of my favourite Iranian movies:   

* Jodaeiye Nader az Simin (2011)   
* Khaneh siah ast (1963)   
* Nema-ye Nazdik (1990)  
* Nun va Goldoon (1996)   
* Ta'm e guilass (1997)   


Five other Iranian movies really worth seeing:    

* Avaze gonjeshk-ha (2008)   
* Ayneh (1977)     
* Gaav (1969)    
* Sib (1998)   
* Ten (2002)   

Kiarostami's Koker trilogy is of course a must see too, but I tried not to only name movies by him. But be sure to watch Nema-ye Nazdik (1990) and Nun va Goldoon (1996), those two are great gems from Iran. Nun va Goldoon (1996) is also directed by Mohsen Makhmalbaf, Samira Makhmalbaf's father. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 14:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen it. Not that horrible, but too thin, simple and a bit superficial for me to like it more. I got the feeling that the movie wanted to be too much at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 10:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not really one of the top choices for me at all when it comes to what I want Criterion to release. I would rather see a release of Gummo (1997) then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British Film Institute Q3 Releases </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 02:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 00:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your choices are not bad. My list would probably look like this:     

1. Spalovac mrtvol (1969)       
2. Les yeux sans visage (1960)       
3. Possession (1981)     
4. Onibaba (1964)       
5. Yabu no naka no kuroneko (1968)      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 20:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two-Lane Blacktop (1971). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 19:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mulholland Dr. (2001). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 18:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hiroshima mon amour (1959), 90 minutes of perfection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 14:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tanin no kao (1966), Stalker (1979) and Solyaris (1972). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 19:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hiroshima mon amour (1959). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 23:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dead Man (1995), his best one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pather Panchali [1955] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 00:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 16:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solyaris (1972) of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 05:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stalker (1979). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 04:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Andrey Rublyov (1966) and Marketa Lazarov (1967) are both amazing in their realism. Both of them are dealing with a main character each, but they also portray rivalry. The first one dealing with the fighting between rival princes and the Tatar invasions, while the last one deals a lot with two different clans. Both movies also deal with religion and how it affected the Middle Ages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 03:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say that these ten are the best ones:    

* Antichrist (2009)    
* Eraserhead (1977)       
* Hxan (1922)              
* Krkarlen (1921)   
* Les diaboliques (1955)           
* Les yeux sans visage (1960)      
* Onibaba (1964)      
* Repulsion (1965)    
* Rosemary's Baby (1968)    
* Yabu no naka no kuroneko (1968)     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 02:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edipo re (1967) by Pier Paolo Pasolini. The screenplay is adapted from the famous Greek tragedy by Sophocles. The movie starts for example in pre-war Italy, but the setting is later changed to the ancient world. Probably worth to know. But basically almost the entire movie is set in the ancient world. Good stuff. If you want a good biblical story, check out Il vangelo secondo Matteo (1964). That one is also directed by Pasolini and is a great and interesting retelling of the story of Jesus Christ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mula sa kung ano ang noon [2014] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 01:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 00:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen Stalker (1979)? One of the best science fiction movies ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 00:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The controversy surrounding Greed (1924) by Erich von Stroheim is very interesting. There's some stuff written down about it on [Wikipedia](http://tinyurl.com/yfy9vl6). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 23:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice stuff. That movie is truly a masterpiece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Norte, hangganan ng kasaysayan [2013] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 23:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 23:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My top three:    
1. Jeanne Dielman, 23 Quai du Commerce, 1080 Bruxelles (1975)     
2. Die bitteren Trnen der Petra von Kant (1972)    
3. Belle de jour (1967)      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Loneliness of the Long Distance Runner [1962] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 22:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 22:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll probably show up soon. I just think we have to wait some more. Nothing else to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 22:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ending of L'eclisse (1962) is fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 21:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ten of my favourite horror movies that shouldn't be missed out:    

* Eraserhead (1977)   
* Hxan (1922)   
* La chute de la maison Usher (1928)    
* Les yeux sans visage (1960)    
* Nosferatu, eine Symphonie des Grauens (1922)    
* Onibaba (1964)     
* Possession (1981)   
* Repulsion (1965)     
* Spalovac mrtvol (1969)   
* Yabu no naka no kuroneko (1968)     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 20:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you referring to Meatballs (1979) by Ivan Reitman? If so, it already has been released on Blu-ray. [Here](http://www.blu-ray.com/movies/Meatballs-Blu-ray/427/) is the US version and [here](http://www.blu-ray.com/movies/Meatballs-Blu-ray/41364/) is the Canadian one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 20:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if I would call that an essay really, but then again, that term could be quite vague. Most of it consisted of objective facts. I was expecting something more and critical. It didn't give me any new insights either. Anyways, it's always nice to see Tarkovsky getting some space here. It's a great film nonetheless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He truly was! Yeah, I love that picture too. They were so cute. And I like what Kurosawa said about his movies:     

*"To not have seen the films of Ray is to have lived in the world without ever having seen the moon and the sun."* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen several threads about it here. And it gets mentioned now and then in all kinds of places. It's even the most successful Irish film of all time if you look at the box office. The reception for it was mainly positive, there's somewhere over one hundred reviews for it at Rotten Tomatoes for example. So I wouldn't say that it's an unknown movie really. It also won some awards and got some nominations.     

But to contribute with a film to the thread, I'll say Tobenai chinmoku (1966) by Kazuo Kuroki. I posted about it in similar threads before, but I can't recommend it enough. To take an example, only 148 users have rated it on IMDb. It's rarely mentioned overall. It doesn't even have an official DVD release. I hope it gets a Blu-ray release one day, it really deserves it, or a double format release. One of the most underseen masterpieces of Japanese cinema of all time. Such a great film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 18:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scandinavia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 18:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the Blu-ray releases by Criterion are not the same region as the standard region in Scandinavia for example. So you have to get a region free player or one that plays that certain region to be able to watch them. Or do something else. It's a lot easier with DVD releases though, that's usually no problem to fix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 17:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I use it as a standard on the Internet. English isn't my first language. And I don't like some English titles, so I always stick with the original ones, as those are the original titles and nothing else. Also, every movie has an original title, some movies don't have English titles at all, so I don't want to mix it either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 17:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like region codes at all either, it sucks. Especially for us in Europe when it comes to Criterion for example. And a good region free Blu-ray player seems to cost quite a lot too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 17:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if you missed it, but there's already several Blu-ray releases of it. One [German](http://www.blu-ray.com/movies/The-Adventures-of-Buckaroo-Banzai-Across-the-8th-Dimension-Blu-ray/86439/), one [Spanish](http://www.blu-ray.com/movies/The-Adventures-of-Buckaroo-Banzai-Across-the-8th-Dimension-Blu-ray/124960/) and one [Australian](http://www.blu-ray.com/movies/The-Adventures-of-Buckaroo-Banzai-Across-the-8th-Dimension-Blu-ray/98243/). Arrow Films is also releasing it in July this year, [here's](http://www.blu-ray.com/movies/The-Adventures-of-Buckaroo-Banzai-Across-the-8th-Dimension-Blu-ray/128699/) a link to that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 17:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you mean Gallipoli (1981) by Peter Weir, it actually got released on Blu-ray today. There is [this](http://www.blu-ray.com/movies/Gallipoli-Blu-ray/125128/)	edition and also [this](http://www.blu-ray.com/movies/Gallipoli-Blu-ray/125494/) one.      

Anyways, ten movies I have seen that should be released on Blu-ray:         

* Erosu purasu Gyakusatsu (1969)   
* La maman et la putain (1973)   
* Mujo (1970)   
* Pisma myortvogo cheloveka (1986)   
* Quatre nuits d'un rveur (1971)    
* Shinj: Ten no Amijima (1969)    
* Spalovac mrtvol (1969)   
* Suna no onna (1964)    
* Tsuit no zawameki (1988)    
* Un homme qui dort (1974)   

And ten I haven't seen that really need to be released on Blu-ray:       

* Al-mummia (1969)    
* Ashani Sanket (1973)   
* Der brennende Acker (1922)   
* Gu ling jie shao nian sha ren shi jian (1991)   
* Khesht va Ayeneh (1965)     
* L'amour fou (1969)     
* La nouba des femmes du mont Chenoua (1979)     
* Ragbar (1972)    
* Tobenai chinmoku (1966)    
* Qing mei zhu ma (1985)     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Trailer For Philippe Garrels Cannes Premiere In the Shadow of Women </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 17:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 16:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the big studio flicks are the ones that gets the general public excited and hyped, there's no doubt about that. I'm not a big fan of Marvel from the beginning, so I don't really get let down by their movies, because I know quite much what to expect from the beginning. I would say that the best movies usually (or more like always) are those that aren't a part of Hollywood, Disney and Marvel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 15:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't say I'm excited for any of those really. At least there's other interesting stuff coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 15:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> La peau douce (1964), Viskningar och rop (1972), Sanma no aji (1962) and Die bitteren Trnen der Petra von Kant (1972) are some of my favourites when it comes to the latest releases. Sanma no aji (1962) was an upgrade though, I don't know you count that too. It's going to be interesting to see what's coming in the future, they'll probably announce new releases quite soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 15:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Film Comment and Sight   Sound (also published by BFI) are great and interesting sources, as someone already mentioned. IMDb is great for information mostly, like production details, cast, filmographies etc. There's really no other site that is as universal and complete as IMDb when it comes to that. Be sure to check out the external reviews by critics on IMDb though, you will found links to many different sites (including Sight   Sound) that together will give you a massive amount of all kinds of reviews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 14:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it sad that people are different when it comes to taste? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 13:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Popil i diament (1958) by Andrzej Wajda. And yes, it's great! One of the best polish films ever made. It's a powerful depiction of war and how it can affect a person's choices. The cinematography is also beautiful and especially Zbigniew Cybulski is fantastic in his role. Probably the best movie dealing with Poland's war and post-war history. If you have the slightest interest in cinema, this movie shouldn't be missed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 13:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, Murph also wanted him to go find Amelia, so he also had a reason to leave. I think Murph mostly was satisfied with Cooper keeping his promise, that he would return to her. I don't think one should put that end scene you mentioned as the main focus, how long he stayed there or how long he didn't. I didn't like the movie, but for me, it was entirely because of other reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 13:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no set release date yet. I think they will announce new releases in a couple of hours or maybe in a day or two, they usually do it in the middle of the month, so we'll see if it's going to be announced. If not, I'm sure it will come in the near future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 12:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks probably amazing. It seems that it will be released by Criterion on DVD/Blu-ray too, which sounds even more amazing. And I hope they will restore more of Ray's work soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 12:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not my favourite by Bresson either, but it sure is a great movie. I love how powerful it as and still so minimalistic and spare. I'm a big fan of Bresson's special film theory and his rules, so this is entirely a movie in my taste. Everything is stripped down to the barest essentials. Every composition is well-thought out, everything we see is supposed to be there and Bresson really knew what was important and what was not. The editing is totally uncompromising and unbending, everything is beautifully shot at the same time too. The movie overall is claustrophobic and gloomy. I also like how it's quite deprived of humor, drama and feelings, but still manages to be powerful and nuanced without villains and heroes. Bresson's movies were special, there's really nothing like them. I think this movie is a magnificent reconstruction. I have to rewatch it soon! Bresson surely was a master. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 11:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting stuff. Polish cinema really has some gems to offer. He's picked out some great ones. It's just too bad that I live thousands of miles away from the cities that are having the event. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Dramatic Story Behind Satyajit Ray's 50s Masterpiece 'The Apu Trilogy' (Exclusive) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 11:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philosophy Film(s) on Notebook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 11:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 11:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Game (1997)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 11:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would also say that it's one of the best silent movies ever made! It's very special and well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 11:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great! I hope you'll like it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 11:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you haven't seen Repulsion (1965) by Roman Polanski, it's of course essential. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 11:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's 15 documentaries I think would be very interesting to see in the collection:     

* Araya (1959)    
* As I Was Moving Ahead Occasionally I Saw Brief Glimpses of Beauty (2000)    
* Dead Birds (1963)    
* Dialogue with a Woman Departed (1981)    
* Diaries Notes and Sketches (1969)      
* Feng ai (2013)    
* Forest of Bliss (1986)   
* Fragments of Kubelka (2012)    
* Ladoni (1994)   
* Pour la suite du monde (1963)    
* Pripyat (1999)   
* Resan (1987)    
* Sayonara CP (1972)    
* Taiga (1992)     
* Tiexi qu (2002)    

Since I haven's seen them, I can't say why and so, but they just look very interesting and I surely want to watch them. It's also intriguing when Criterion releases stuff you haven't seen. Also, some of them don't have Blu-ray releases either, which would make it even more fitting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 11:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, I've seen 26 of his movies and from what I have seen, he surely is one of the great ones. These are my three absolute favourites:   

* Nattvardsgsterna (1962)     
* Smultronstllet (1957)    
* Tystnaden (1963)       

Some other essential ones in my opinion:    

* Ansiktet (1958)   
* En passion (1969)    
* Fanny och Alexander (1982)    
* Hstsonaten (1978)   
* Jungfrukllan (1960)    
* Persona (1966)       
* Skammen (1968)   
* Ssom i en spegel (1961)   
* Viskningar och rop (1972)  

I can also recommend his TV mini-series Scener ur ett ktenskap (1973). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 10:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have only seen the first one, but I thought it was very silly, ridicilous, boring, ugly and mostly full of bad comedy. I guess I'm not a fan of the childishly Disney tone it has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 10:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know at least that I would have Werckmeister harmnik (2000) and No Quarto da Vanda (2000) on my list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Merry Christmas Mr. Lawrence [1983] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 10:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> La jete [1962] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 00:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 23:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stanley Kubrick. No doubt about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 21:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yjinb (1961) is a good starter that's quite accessible. I don't know if you have seen Per un pugno di dollari (1964) by Sergio Leone already, but that movie is basically a remake of Yjinb (1961), so if you watched it, you will probably recognize the story. If you don't mind the length and have no problems with it, Shichinin no samurai (1954) isn't really a bad choice either. It also has pretty much every key element Kurosawa is known for, so you will get quite a good overview if you start with it. If you don't want to start with a samurai flick, I would go with Ikiru (1952), it's easy to like and has a quite sympathetic story that's easy to relate to. I know many that started with Rashmon (1950) and loved it, it isn't one of his longer films, so that is one option too. It's a bit more complex than Yjinb (1961) though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 20:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do! Two good movies! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 20:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Room (2003). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First-hand evidence: William Gillettes restored 1916 Sherlock Holmes | Sight   Sound </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 19:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Das Testament des Dr. Mabuse [1933] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 19:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hxan [1922] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 19:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 17:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it quite obvious that the majority of people hanging out in this subreddit really likes superhero movies? Look at the news, the discussions and what gets upvoted, it's quite easy to tell if you've been here a while. By the way, I don't know if your second question was meant to be the same as the one in the topic or if you meant anything specific about the industry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 17:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't this a great opportunity for you to rewatch the movie then? And isn't it supposed to be you choosing what you yourself think are the best negotiation scenes? It seems like you aren't trying at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> dol vcel [1968] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 17:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 16:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if I would say that he's that underrated, but maybe not recognized enough and that his movies are quite underseen would be a better description. As for the downvoting thing, it seems that users on this site tend to downvote quite much that they've never heard of or anything similar overall. I don't really like the voting system at all, but that's another discussion. Anyways, Terayama did some good stuff! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 16:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, as I already said, the site isn't anything for me and I won't use it in the future. I don't use any similar sites either. I was just curious about what the suggestions are based on and adding a bit of contructive critique.

There's already similar sites with different filters too:     
[http://agoodmovietowatch.com/](http://agoodmovietowatch.com/)      
[http://www.suggestmemovie.com/](http://www.suggestmemovie.com/)    
[http://www.random-movie-picker.com/](http://www.random-movie-picker.com/)    
[http://5000best.com/movies/](http://5000best.com/movies/)       

That's just some examples. So your friend should try to come up with something special that makes his site differ from the lot. If he wants to make his site unique. Maybe he doesn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upcoming Pathe Classic Releases </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 11:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saraba hakobune [1984] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 20:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fellini - Satyricon [1969] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 23:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stntang [1994] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 21:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Le deuxime souffle [1966] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 15:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Angst [1983] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 13:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> O Sangue [1989] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 13:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upcoming Gaumont Titles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 03:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Das weie Band - Eine deutsche Kindergeschichte [2009] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 02:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Macbeth [1948] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 02:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Orson Welles' Falstaff: Chimes at Midnight and Too Much Johnson Prepped for Blu-ray </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 01:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trudno byt bogom (2013) [800x1117] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 23:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Krhozat [1988] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 21:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> L'eclisse [1962] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 20:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stalker (1979) [600x826] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 17:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Film of the week: Jauja | Sight   Sound </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 17:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trudno byt bogom [2013] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 12:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hor, m panenko (1967) [500x723] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 12:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Roy Andersson Collection Blu-ray </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 11:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red Shift [1984] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 17:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Name is Oona [1969] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 16:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Les enfants du paradis (1945) [544x791] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 15:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shnen [1969] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 12:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tri dcry (1968) [640x929] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 12:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Titash Ekti Nadir Naam [1973] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 12:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Il deserto rosso [1964] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 23:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dodesukaden [1970] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 11:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sakura no mori no mankai no shita [1975] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 03:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uwasa no onna [1954] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 23:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jalsaghar [1958] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 19:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gion bayashi [1953] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 18:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lektionen in Finsternis [1992] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 15:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frau im Mond [1929] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 12:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Die Nibelungen: Siegfried [1924] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 12:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Haha [1963] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 19:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Juhy no yoromeki [1968] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 13:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Akai satsui [1964] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 13:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> La peau douce [1964] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 11:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Die bitteren Trnen der Petra von Kant [1972] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 11:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
