<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8318</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 23:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has embodied the soul of mario. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 23:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly dumb question but I've never figured it out: How does one download a fan edit? It doesn't seem like links are openly available. Do you have to purchase a bootleg DVD or something?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 09:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who was born in 1994, this was actually pretty mindblowing to me how that presented these "new technologies." I guess this was cutting edge! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 09:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> weak skulls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 09:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on here documenting that something has landed on my roof. I'm horrified. I think somebody's trying to break in through my chimney. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 09:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...What the hell did I just watch???? Requiem for a dream 2? Christ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 22:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turn Up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 16:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yes! This. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 16:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever wonder if religion could be totally wrong, but there is in fact a divine power behind the workings of the universe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 16:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, I'll definitely check out those shows! I love that kind of stuff. And I've heard so much about A Brief History of Time, I'll try to grab a copy. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 16:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys, I posted this. I've been having some very grown-up thoughts lately. I'm 20 years old, and I've been an atheist as long as I can remember. I, like what seems like most people on the internet, always thought that religion is stupid.


This year, I've been revisiting some of my ideals. I became obsessed with space after watching 2001, the Cosmos, Contact, and Interstellar. The way I viewed the universe started to change. Are the scriptures all just gypsies and fairies, or is there any truth to be found? What is beyond the universe, and why did we come into existence? It's almost like I went full circle with my beliefs. Concepts that always seemed impossible to me now make more sense than ever. Marijuana and the art of film has given me a newfound spirituality. Pi and The Last Temptation of Christ gave me remarkable insight into what religion actually could mean. I thought that believing in God was close-minded. Now I wonder: is being an atheist the real close-mindedness? Shutting out all religious ideas doesn't seem 100% logical to me.


So tell me: ***Does God Exist?*** Has anyone else struggled with their sense of religious identity before? If anyone has any good science to bring to the discussion, that'd be great. Think philosophically, atheists. What lies beyond? Nothing? What could lie beyond? Could our consciousness transcend this dimension into another? Could extraterrestrial life be our biblical "God"?


Thank you! (I love having my mind blown!) :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think God exists? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 16:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does God Exist? *Could* a God Exist? I'd love mature opinions on the subject. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 16:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys, I asked the question. I've been having some very grown-up thoughts lately. I'm 20 years old, and I've been an atheist as long as I can remember. I, like what seems like most people on the internet, always thought that religion is stupid.


This year, I've been revisiting some of my ideals. I became obsessed with space after watching 2001, the Cosmos, Contact, and Interstellar. The way I viewed the universe started to change. Are the scriptures all just gypsies and fairies, or is there any truth to be found? What is beyond the universe, and why did we come into existence? It's almost like I went full circle with my beliefs. Concepts that always seemed impossible to me now make more sense than ever. Marijuana and the art of film has given me a newfound spirituality. Pi and The Last Temptation of Christ gave me remarkable insight into what religion actually could mean. I thought that believing in God was close-minded. Now I wonder: is being an atheist the real close-mindedness? Shutting out all religious ideas doesn't seem 100% logical to me.


So tell me: ***Does God Exist?*** Has anyone else struggled with their sense of religious identity before? If anyone has any good *science* to bring to the discussion, that'd be great. Think philosophically, atheists. What lies beyond? Nothing? What could lie beyond? Could our consciousness transcend this dimension into another? Could extraterrestrial life be our biblical "God"?


Thank you! It's all just so confusing!(I love having my mind blown!) :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 14:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a leasing agent for an apartment complex in Tempe, and the sales techniques they taught us to sucker rich college kids into signing contracts were very unethical. But maybe all sales are like that. Pure *evil.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 14:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the CoCo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 14:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She might also be doing it for you, as well. If a parent is telling their children that Santa does actually exist, there might be a degree of pressure in playing along. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 14:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could someone explain the deep web? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 14:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best thing I can tell you is:
*Don't over-think it*

Seriously, just go with the flow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 14:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on the mood. If you're trying to make out with this girl, I guess it's kind of complicated. Try gently rubbing your lips the back of your hand until you get a rhythm that feels right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 14:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that, kids, is how I met your mother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 14:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GTAV on XB1 and a couple pairs of vans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 14:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best picture @ a film festival. Won a Best Buy gift card...(wtf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 14:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 14:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just go with the flow. Let it come naturally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 14:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She probably already knows, honestly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 08:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you jizzed on your burger, what's the big deal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 01:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DSmeet   ABXY.... :'( R.I.P. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
