<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9972</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] League of Legends Level 30 GOLD Account [W] Steam Games / Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 17:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> S3 finished as GOLD IV, have around 90 champions and around 30 skins. If you are merely interested, contact me, I'll give you more informations.
Account wasn't banned a single time and I'm willing to use middle-man for our trade.
Already made around 20 trades on reddit.com/r/sgswap, so yea...
Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Titanfall - New competitive game on PC? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 20:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Titanfall - New competitive game on PC? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 19:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to find duck game: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 12:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know much about it, it's a 2D game, something like mario, you can collect points, kill small minions and stuff. 

It's older game, so I can't remember the details.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GOG] Big thanks to /u/PopRockRoll for gifting me Guacamelee Gold! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 00:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once again, thank you man so much, you made my day! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As the beta for Titanfall slowly comes to an end, what are your final thoughts about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 21:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think it's overhyped or it actually lived up to it's expectation. 

If you wanna check, I also made a video about it, and what I actually think about the game so far. 

Cheers!

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Lh5XF0BMk1c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] Guacamelee gold from Humble Bundle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 21:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Max Payne 3 [W] Outlast, Offers, tf2keys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 19:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Offer me here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With only having HDD 500 in PC, is Samsung SSD going to improve my performance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 15:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And, which one is better; 

Samsung 840 EVO 128GB SSD 
Samsung 840 PRO 128GB SSD

What benefits are if I get SSD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Max Payne 3, Dead Island Epidemic [W] Offers ( Outlast, Alice Madness Returns, Psychonauts from bundle ). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 11:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Max Payne 3 - looking for Outlast or Alice or offer me good singleplayer game 

Psychonauts - I'll give Dead Island Epidemic + Tomb Raider Background since it's in the bundle

Offer trade me here if you don't wanna lose time; 

http://steamcommunity.com/tradeoffer/new/?partner=92221888 token=4wqIZQVE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Max Payne 3 GIFT ROW [W] Outlast / Mini Ninjas / Single player oriented games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 20:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just trade offer me if you don't wanna wait till I answer your question about a trade; 

http://steamcommunity.com/tradeoffer/new/?partner=92221888 token=4wqIZQVE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Max Payne 3 + Dead Island Epidemic [W] Bureau XCOM - Currently $5 on AMAZON </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 15:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Titanfall particles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 11:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it just me, or particles are blury and not sharpened up? I have everything on high excluding triple buffering with 1920x1080 resolution and it's still 'blurry'. 

Is this due to game being made on source engine or me not being able to max it all out ( by maxing I mean triple buffering etc. ) ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Max Payne 3 GIFT [W] Offers / Games ( Mini Ninjas ) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 19:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Max Payne 3 GIFT [W] Games that I don't have / Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 17:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://steamcommunity.com/id/train_subject9972/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Max Payne 3 GIFT [W] Games that I don't have </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 17:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Normal rewards for going 11-3 in the arena? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 23:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't know how to draft arenas / play with Shaman. Any help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 15:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The worse you do in arena, the better cards you get in your pack? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 19:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's luck based, but I saw so many people get such a good cards ( even myself ) when finishing arena with bad scores. 

What do you think about it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That Van Cleef </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 21:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] League of Legends account, details inside [W] Good offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 14:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> S3 finished as GOLD IV, have around 90 champions and around 30 skins. If you are merely interested, contact me, I'll give you more informations. 

Account wasn't banned a single time and I'm willing to use middle-man for our trade. 

Already made around 20 trades on reddit.com/r/sgswap, so yea... 

Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it worth getting the last book in trilogy Hunger games to complete the trilogy or should I just read it online? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 18:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book vs E-book </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 14:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I just wanted to see other people opinions on E-books and do you use it often as way for reading, or do you avoid it unless you are unable to find it in physical copy. 

I find it hard reading books online, via computer/tablet or whatever device you are using. I  don't get the same feeling and it seems that I can't get into book enough for me to stay long. As for staying long, I also find it really difficult for me to read 20-50 or more pages on device rather than taking a book and chilling outside/sitting comfortable on your bed etc. 

So, how do you approach it, I know that physical copy of book can't really compare with e-book for many reasons, but what do you think about this overall? Are you comfortable to read a book on certain device as much as regular book? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harry Hole - Jo Nesbo = Good way to 'start' ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 13:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I'm not a frequent 'book-reader' or however you want to call it, or should I say, I "wasn't", but nowdays, I'm more into books than anything else, and even tho I didn't read books what really interests me are mystery books. 

I just wanted to ask, since there are many suggestions for ones that love mystery ( like myself ) to go and read Harry Hole series, so I'm simply asking what do you guys think about it overall, what's the best book from that serial, is it smart to start from beginning ( even tho I will 100% skip first 2 books ( Bat and another one, can't remember now).

Sorry if this breaks somekind of rules, if it does, please notify me, I'll delete the thread, just wanted to see other people experience of this novel since there are some mixed feelings about it overall that I encountered. 

Thanks, and cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for good book on vaication, text inside! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 01:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, I'm soon off on my vaication and I'm looking for good books. I recently started reading Da Vinci Code and I'm really into it ( I know I'm little too late for it, but better now than never :p ), so I'm looking for books that are similiar to this one, not in religious style, but books that are action packed, and that aren't full of description and stuff like that.
I didn't read a lot of books, and I'm starting to do it from this year ( 'new year resolution'), but I read few good ones, like Alchemist, Return and stuff like that, so I'm really newbie in this and looking for recommendation on good books.
Currently, I'm looking into Parfume book and Here to Stay: A Harrigan Family Novel from Catherine Anderson, so what do you guys think about these books, do you recommend them or whatso ever?
Thanks :)
TL;DR - to sum up, I LOVE MYSTERY, murders and investigations and stuff like that :p
EDIT: What do you guys think about book from Jo Nesbo, "Police: A Harry Hole Novel" ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stuck at rank 11, any suggestions and tips considering my Paladin deck? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 01:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my deck, 2 images since it continues to bottom; 

http://pokit.org/get/img/a3bee5a75eb389b08c5bf7c05c64b764.jpg

http://pokit.org/get/img/3ea6bb59c66ee78728833eb1a4465e1a.jpg

I have 0 legendaries, and I'm unable to craft any of them for now. Any suggestions on what I did wrong and how to improve? Thanks :)

PS: ( not that I'm implying that you need legendary to climb up, but lack of few of them is why I maybe inserted other 'not so needed' cards ) 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] 3 ref ( refined metal ) - TF2 + 3 snow globe cards [W] Hearthstone beta key </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-29 18:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> add for quick trade yo; 

http://steamcommunity.com/id/train_subject9972/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] 3 ref - TF2 [W] Snow globe cards, other cards to finish my set etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 19:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Hearthstone [W] Offers, it's relatively cheap so yea .. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 08:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Hearthstone key [W] Offers, it's relatively cheap so yea ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 08:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] 1.5 TF keys [W] Steam Sale Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 14:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As stated, don't offer me game that I already have please. :r </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Snow Globe FOIL #3 [W] Keys, offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 13:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have FOIL CARD, SNOW GLOBE #3, want tf2 keys, you offer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blizzard, what are you waiting for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 22:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need to wait whole day to update hearthstone considering my DL speed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 09:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] TF2 Keys [W] Star Craft 2 CD Key for Battlenet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 15:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As stated, what's your price, looking for SC2 keys, won't go first unless you're trusted trader. Have a good one. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Hearthstone [W] Game Offers, Keys ( relatively 'Cheap' ) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 21:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for few games or keys. 

Throw offers at me, we'll see what can we do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Assassin's Creed IV: Black Flag - Multiplayer, Hit or Miss? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 21:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So guys, don't know if there was thread for multiplayer, if not, this is great opportunity to talk about what you guys think overall, did it improve in any ways, or did it stay in the shadows of great singleplayer that AC series offer? What do you think? 

Also, if you are up to, check my thoughts of multiplayer overall; 


https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0KHXy2b00DY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to make AEROPLAN - letters/cards and then print them in certain program </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-29 18:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Assassin's Creed Black Flag - Optimization failure? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 20:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So guys, it's been 'a while' since the game originally came out on PC, and as most of you know, it wasn't perfect in terms of optimization. Although some got it to work perfectly, others experienced stutters, frame drops, screen tearing and many problems with their gaming rig. So I figure most of you are already digged into the game a lot ( unless you're one of the unluckies to have problems with optimization ), but my question is, what do you think about it overall? Was it better than AC3? Was it worse? What are yours experiences? 

Also, I made a video and talked little about it, so if you feel like it, check it out. Also there's a potentional fix ( but I figure most of you know for it by now ( using d3overrider ), so yea. 

http://youtu.be/Pr-_03Btnk0

TL;DR: Worse than AC3? Better than AC3? In terms of optimization and what do you think about it overall? 

Cheers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aveline DLC - Black Flag, PC?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 20:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, it says;  that it's exclusive to playstation, with additional 60 minutes of footage.

Assassins Creed IV: Aveline Exclusive to PlayStation, DLC Details

and I got it with my Deluxe edition of the game on PC 

I mean, wait, whaat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Portal 2 [W] Keys, Spec Ops The Line, Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 20:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for roughly 3 keys or Spec Ops.

Willing to hear offers from you guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] The Walking Dead - Gift [W] Pappers Please - key, humble store </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 21:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As stated, want this or tf2 keys, or offers. 

Whatever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] The Walking Dead [W] TF2 keys, Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 22:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for maybe Alien Rage Unlimited, or potentionally games I do not have. 

Not particuallry interested in indie games unless there's really good one you're offering. 

Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Walking Dead [W] Offers, Keys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-10 22:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also looking for BTA humble bundle, but I'm interested in it when they announce new games, so if anyone has it and still when they add new games thinks that he can do that, feel free to add me and leave me on his friendlist until they add new games. 

WB Bundle BTA. 

Offer me also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Walking Dead [W] Offers, TF2/D2 KEYS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-10 20:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't OFFER ME cards unless you play on selling a lot. Like a lot of them for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Walking Dead [W] Offers, TF2/D2 Keys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-10 19:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AS stated, have gift. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Walking Dead [W] Offers, BTA WB Humble Bundle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 23:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As stated, have Walking dead, looking for keys, or preferably BTA WB Humble Bundle. 

Thanks! :)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Walking Dead GIFT [W] TF2 KEYS, GOOD OFFERS! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 21:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Walking Dead [W] TF2 Keys ONLY </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 18:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Send me a trade offer here](http://steamcommunity.com/tradeoffer/new/?partner=92221888 token=4wqIZQVE)

Please don't send 1/1.5 keys. 

Need to sell it fast and quick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] CARDS, 3CSGO Sets [W] TF2 Keys! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 16:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check it out; 

http://steamcommunity.com/id/train_subject9972

add me. 

3 cs go sets = 1 key 

ALL my cards = 2 keys + free copy of BAD RATS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] 3x CSGO sets, 30+ cards [W] Other games sets, list inside </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 00:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have 3X CS GO sets, and 30 cards. 

Want sets(cards) for following games; 

TRINE 2


SPELUNKY

BATMAN CITY, ASYLUM AND BATMAN ORIGINS

SWAPPER

GRID 2




http://steamcommunity.com/tradeoffer/new/?partner=92221888 token=4wqIZQVE 

Use my link, and send me an offers for cards(sets)! 

You can also check what cards I have in the link I sent you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Batman Arkham Asylum, Lord of the Rings War in the North [W] Offers, Scribblenaut, Shank 2, Alan Wake, Pappers Please etc </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 20:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have these 2 keys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] CSGO, D2, TF2 KEYS [W] Good Game Offers, Walking Dead DLC, Pappers Please </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 21:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Want those for good price, and also looking for solid offers on steam games. 

Also wanna switch my 8 CSGO keys and 2 D2 keys for TF2 keys. 
Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] CSGO,TF2,D2 keys [W] Good game offers! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 20:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Check INSIDE [W] Bastion KEY </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 14:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3x Guest Pass: Red Orchestra 2: Heroes of Stalingrad - GOTY, Card, background and emoticon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Keys [W] Quickfire bundle - more inside </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 23:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing really more in here, just want that bundle with all keys in it, thanks. :p 

offer away or ninja add me like always on steam no matter what I say  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Cards, refined metal tf2 [W] Dark Sector </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 22:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need only this game, please post offers below. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Keys [W] See inside, someone who can buy from market. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 23:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have tf2/d2 keys and have also TOMB RAIDER Foil card. 

I'm looking for certain cards for Batman Arkham City and Arkham Asylum aswell as ARKHAM ORIGINS ( this one is the one I'm seeking most). 

I need someone who can buy cards from market in exchange for tf2/d2 keys. 

Please reasonable offers, and don't tell me I have steamtradingcard subreddit, because I hardly believe anyone out there is willing to do that especially not with 10 people active on that subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Tomb Raider FOIL, TF2/Dota2 KEYS [W] Batman Origins/Arkham City/Arkham Asylum cards/sets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 23:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As stated above. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] TF2 Key, Tomb Raider FOIL Night HUB [W] Cards! Listed inside! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 20:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need cards for following games; 

CIV 5
Tomb Raider
Batman Arkham Asylum
Batman Arkham GOTY
Mark of the Ninja


That's the one I'm interested in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] TF2 keys [W] Batman Arkham Origins Key / Gift, AC Black Flag </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 22:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As stated, looking for only, and only these unless it's a really good offer for certain game. 

Not interested in indie now, so don't offer me something like that please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BMGame has stopped working - Arkham Asylum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 20:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just get this, is there anyway to fix it on steam? :s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Keys [W] Batman Origins, Bureau XCOM, Splinter Cell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 21:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post your offers bellow. 

MOSTLY INTERESTED in BATMAN, I don't mind if it's key or gift. Whatever is cheaper and suits me more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Check list INSIDE [W] Keys, Game Offers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 11:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have following items; 

Ruling Sword

Mega-Kills: Juggernaut

Announcer: Juggernaut

Radiant Claive

Direstone Liferipper

The Horned Mother

Offers in keys and/or game offers.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Vintage Timebreaker [W] Keys! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-20 22:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There ya go, post your offers, best one wins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] TF2 Keys [W] Third Person Games - Tomb Raider, Blacklist, etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-19 22:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Searching for lowest price possibly, I don't care if it's a key or a gift, I'm gonna activate it anyway probably on my account. 

So feel free to offer me, I'm mostly looking for Third person games that are compatible with controller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PCGamesN Giveaway is over! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-16 19:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Civilization V Gold Edition UPGRADE [W] TF2 keys, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 23:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello guys, I have gift; 

CIV V Gold Upgrade </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] 5 TF2 Keys [W] Third person games - compatible with controller </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 12:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As stated, looking for some sweet third person games, willing to hear any offer regarding it. 

I don't need tho Batman Arkham City/Asylum as I already have both of those. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] 4.5 TF2 KEYS [W] Game offers, LOL SKINS for EUW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 22:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As stated, have 4.5 tf2 keys willing to hear you offers so shoot at me! 

Also, looking for Championship Thresh skincodes, so if you have one of those, PM me. 

WILL go first anytime if you have bigger rep than me, but consider that my flair hasn't been updated YET so i'm on 10+ trades now :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] TF2 keys, GAMES LISTED INSIDE [W] Championship thresh or RIOT BLITZ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 20:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Flair Profile] /u/train_subject9972 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 23:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SR INFO; 

| steamname: train_subject9972

| steamID32: STEAM_0:0:46110944

| steamID64: http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198052487616

| customURL: http://steamcommunity.com/id/train_subject9972

|  steamrep: http://steamrep.com/profiles/76561198052487616

Forum search results; http://forums.steamrep.com/search/search </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Assassins Creed 3, Batman Arkham CITY GOTY, Sonic All Star RACING [W] Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 21:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * [Alan Wake's American Nightmare](http://store.steampowered.com/app/202750/)

* [Assassins Creed III](http://store.steampowered.com/app/208480/)

* [Bastion](http://store.steampowered.com/app/107100/)

* [Batman: Arkham City - Game of the Year Edition](http://store.steampowered.com/sub/16547/)

* [Sonic   All-Stars Racing Transformed](http://store.steampowered.com/app/212480/)

* [The Binding of Isaac](http://store.steampowered.com/app/113200/)

* [Upgrade Civ V Standard to Gold Edition](http://store.steampowered.com/app/8930/)


[Inventory listing by TradeStarter](http://runtyrobot.com/tradestarter)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Batman Arkham City, Sonic All Star Racing, GAMES [W] Assassins CREED 3 ON SALE! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 21:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * [Alan Wake's American Nightmare](http://store.steampowered.com/app/202750/)

* [Bastion](http://store.steampowered.com/app/107100/)

* [Batman: Arkham City - Game of the Year Edition](http://store.steampowered.com/sub/16547/)

* [BioShock 2](http://store.steampowered.com/app/8850/)

* [Sonic   All-Stars Racing Transformed](http://store.steampowered.com/app/212480/)

* [The Binding of Isaac](http://store.steampowered.com/app/113200/)

* [Upgrade Civ V Standard to Gold Edition](http://store.steampowered.com/app/8930/)


Offer away! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Batman Arkham City, Sonic All Star Racing, GAMES [W] TF2 Keys / Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 21:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * [Alan Wake's American Nightmare](http://store.steampowered.com/app/202750/)

* [Bastion](http://store.steampowered.com/app/107100/)

* [Batman: Arkham City - Game of the Year Edition](http://store.steampowered.com/sub/16547/)

* [BioShock 2](http://store.steampowered.com/app/8850/)

* [Sonic   All-Stars Racing Transformed](http://store.steampowered.com/app/212480/)

* [The Binding of Isaac](http://store.steampowered.com/app/113200/)

* [Upgrade Civ V Standard to Gold Edition](http://store.steampowered.com/app/8930/)


Offer away! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] List Inside [W] CIV V Gold Edition - UPGRADE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 21:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have following to offer; 

Bastion 

Sonic All Star Racing 

Binding of the Isaac 

TF2 Keys  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] List Inside [W] CIV V Gold Edition - UPGRADE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 21:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] List inside [W] Bioshock Infinite! ROW GIFT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 22:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have following; 

Alan Wake's American Nightmare

Batman: Arkham City - Game of the Year Edition

Bastion

Nightsky

Sniper Ghost Warrior Gold Edition

Binding of the Isaac 

TF2 KEYS 

ALL games are ROW GIFTS, interested in trading them for Bioshock Infinite ROW gift, or mix of games with tf2 keys or I don't know, you decide.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [BF4] Performance issues - AMD Graphic card </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 12:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any way to fix it beside installing beta drivers and setting bf4 to low priority? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Cards [W] Game offers! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 15:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shoot me with offers, yo 

I have also 1 foil. 

Mostly looking for steam gifts ( Just cause works also fine, Isaac, or basically 'cheap' games for low prices) 

Will accept keys if it's the game I'm looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] 1 key [W] 2x Binding of Isaac </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 12:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add me for fast trade please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Sniper Ghost Warrior Golden Edition, Fearie Solitarie [W] Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 11:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both games are steamgifts! 

Looking for offers. 

I do not want any of the origin humble bundle keys, nor the previous bundle with Mark of the Ninja, Limbo, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Crysis 2 Maximum Edition Steam KEY [W] 3 RANDOM cards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 15:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As stated above, have key, want 3 RANDOM cards!

add for quick trade! 

http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198052487616 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] tf2 Keys [W] Dawngate Beta key </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-29 17:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As stated, I merely wanna see the prices that are about this game, and its closed beta invite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Game keys! Check INSIDE [W] Few RANDOM cards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-29 11:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, I have; 

~~Dead Space Steam Key~~

Crysis 2 Maximum Edition Steam Key

~~Medal of Honor Steam Key~~

~~Mirror's Edge Steam Key~~

Accepting 3-4 cards ( maybe less ) for each key, or if you take in a bundle, I can lower the price. 

Anyway, I'm highly willing to negotiate with this, so shoot me offers. IN CARDS. only in cards!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Troubleshooting] Printer problems! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 13:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello guys. My printer recently got out of ink, so I handed it over so they can refill my catridge. When I came back home to try it out, and put on the catridge, it's still red light on it, and it just blinks green for a merely second, then stands red solid. 

I have Xerox 3010/3040 printer, and I got the catridge refilled. 

I also have one question, is it normal for catridge to let down the ink, I mean, It's like there's a little hole or something and the ink is ( or powder) is slowly going out of the catridge. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Keys [W] Assassins Creed Black Flag or Watch Dogs Preorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 14:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As stated, I have tf2 keys to offer for AC Black Flag on uplay, or Watch Dogs. 

If there's anyone that can/want to do this, write in comments the amount of keys you want for it and I'll see what I can do about it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Steam keys - Humble Bundle - more INSIDE [W] Mark of the Ninja, Limbo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-21 16:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will trade multiple keys for either of the games!!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Keys [W] Humble Origin Bundle BTA / Battlefield 3 KEY with proof! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-21 14:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As stated, have tf2 keys, want Humble Origin Bundle BTA / Battlefield 3  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] TF2 Keys [W] Batman Arkham Origins, Splinter Cell KEYS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 20:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would prefer 'cheap' steam keys for above mentioned games. Name me your price and I'll see what we can do about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Bioshock Infinite KEY [W] Arkham Origins BATMAN Key </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-16 20:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Team Fortress 2 KEYS [W] Offers - Assassin's Creed 3/Dishonored/Far Cry3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-16 14:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm NOT looking for games like Spelunky, or such, rather than the games like Batman, Assassin's Creed, Bioshock that has pure singleplayer campaign.

If someone has the above mentioned games ( AC3, FC3, Dishonored with DLCS and TOMB RAIDER!!), please put the price so I can know what I'm dealing with. 

Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] 37 TF keys [W] Good game offers! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-15 14:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring it on! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frequent disconnects? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 18:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there anyone with similiar problem as mine, where I get disconnected from client or from the game( if I'm in the one)frequently ( every 5-10-15 minutes) and have to log back in everytime? 

What can be the problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm still ingame with the same guy, I won't backdown! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 21:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Quest(s) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 15:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, is it usually like this that you get 1 quest per day? Or is there supposed to get bigger as you progress through the game regarding levels and such?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No actual keys for EUROPE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 20:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Custom Controlls - Program </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 14:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello. I have unusual Controller for PC, but untill I get my hands on XBOX 360 controller for PC i have to for now stick with this one. Is there any program that allows you to custom change your controlls to be able to play any game with that custom design. 


When i go into game for example Bureau XCOM, or Dead Space 3, and when I go to configure controlls it just won't accept it, but I can play and hoover over menu with joystick. 

Any solutions lads?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OFFER] Origin Leftovers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 23:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put a number from 1-100, these are the games; 

Burnout Paradise - STEAM 

Command and Conquer - Red Rising - STEAM 

12 hours from this post, winners will be chosen. 

GOOD LUCK! :)

Thread is closed, we have the winners; 

/u/call_me_q won Burnout Paradise

/u/TAC0_cat won Generals Red Rising! 

Thanks everyone for participating ! :)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] 2 ref. metal [W] Offers in cards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 11:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As stated, comment bellow your offers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Ready] Mine Build </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 21:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's my computer overall; 

CPU; AMD ATHLON II X4 640 @ 3.00GHz QuadCore

Memory; 8GB RAM DDR3 1333MHz "Kingston"PC10666 CL9 

Harddrive; 500GB Sata

Graphic card; ATi RADEON Sapphire HD7850 1GB GDDR5

Monitor; Philips 21.5 inch

Case; AEROCOOL Vs-4 

What do you think? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interested what is this use for </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 15:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello guys. Just quick question about cables that are coming from PSU. I'm pretty newbie for these stuff, so I'm interested how to know which cable is supposed to go to harddrive, which one to DVD-ROM and such. I have 2 cables, and one is 6D, other is 8D, and the 6D was in my harddrive. What's the difference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMD Never Settle Bundle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 17:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello guys. I recently purchased mine Sapphire HD 7850 card, and I wanted to see if anyone is experiencing same problem as me when trying to reedem the code. It says; 

"There was an error processing your submission, please check all values and try again. If the error persist please contact AMD Support at support@amd4u.com." 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for websites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 16:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello guys. I'm not asking for any big help in particular, I just wanted if someone knows good site that you can learn about hardware stuff on it. What's the common one that's used widely, and that it has good reviews and tips. 

I already started reading on PCWORLD but I would love as many sites as possible. Thanks! :))

edit; to be more specific, would like to know about sockets, graphic cards, motherboards, and things like that, to know what each port does and stuff. ^^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Cards - Check Inside [W] Offers! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 14:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have following cards; 

Garry's Mod Trading Card - INVASION

Binding of the Isaac Card (s) - VI The Lovers AND IV The Emperor

Civilization 5 Card (s) - Bismark , Catherine, Foreign 

If interested, post your offers down below!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Binding of the Isaac cards [W] Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 21:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free to check in my inventory; 

http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198052487616/

Shoot me with offers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] CS;GO Cards ( Anarchist, Balkan ) Surgeon Simulator card [W] Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 01:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have 2 CSGO cards; Anarchist and Balkan and one Surgeon Simulator card ; Socking it to Ya. 

I'm looking to build badge either for Trine 2/Binding of Isaac, but i'm open for offers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Where has this SK been" - Joe Miller </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 14:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Do you want to talk about that a bit" - Jatt 2013 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 00:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Trine 2 Cards, Killing Floor Card, Emoticon [W] CS;GO FBI, Balkan and SWAT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 23:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the title says, pretty much I have these cards; 

TRINE 2 ; Zoya and Amadeus 

Killing Floor ; Husk 

1 Emoticon 

Giving all these for these 3 cards! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question regarding Deus Ee - Human Revolution - don't upvote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 18:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, apparently, while working on that mother quest, I end up having cops on my tail, and I can't get rid of them, wherever I go they start shooting at me because  I hacked that thing because I needed information about something. 

So, is there any possible way to interact with them so they stop shooting, or I just have to play all over again? :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Thanks] to bud369 for Surgeon Simulator 2013 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 17:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man once again, awesome funny game. 

All credits goes to this guy /u/bud369 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Laptop screen goes black but you can hear fans working </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 00:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As stated in title, while I do something, for a period of time, like watching movie, the laptop ocassionally and randomly turns black, but you can hear fans working, and there's still green light that's on too. it's like on sleep mode, but you can't wake it up or something. All I can do is turn it off, and turn it on again, but when I do that, it tends to happen again after short/long period ( long in terms of 1-2 hours, short in terms of 10 minutes ). 

It's about Toshiba laptop. Any help is appreciated, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Laptop screen goes black but you can hear fans working </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 00:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As stated in title, while I do something, for a period of time, like watching movie, the laptop ocassionally and randomly turns black, but you can hear fans working, and there's still green light that's on too. it's like on sleep mode, but you can't wake it up or something. All I can do is turn it off, and turn it on again, but when I do that, it tends to happen again after short/long period ( long in terms of 1-2 hours, short in terms of 10 minutes ). 

It's about Toshiba laptop. Any help is appreciated, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Laptop screen goes black but you can hear fans working </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 23:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Killing Floor - Husk / Background Skulls and Stripes - Sniper Elite Zombie Army [W] Trine 2 - Rosabel, Isabel, Pontius; CS GO cards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 15:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I'll give; 

Killing Floor - HUSK + 

mine rare Background for Sniper Elite Nazi Zombie Army + 

:PineappleGrenade: emoticon +

discount coupon for; 

66% OFF Awesomenauts

50% OFF Triple Town 

For that three card. I'm only interested in those cards, or CS GO cards eventually </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found Overly manly "man" in Bioshock. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 09:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Killing Floor Cards [W] Sniper Elite Nazi Zombies Cards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 11:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello guys. 

Here's what I have to offer;

Crawler

Stalker (x2)

Gorefast

Husk

I'm looking for;

Skeleton

Zombie Gunner

Zombie Soldier

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Herman Wolf - Sniper Elite Nazi Zombie Card [W] Any other Sniper Elite Nazi Zombie Card </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 03:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EXCEPT Herman, Boris and Screamer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Full Set Summer Sale Getaway Cards + CS;GO Swat [W] Giftable copy of Games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-29 13:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As it stands in title, have full SSG set of cards + 1 CSGO Swat cards, looking to trade for game in form of gift. 

Won't trade card for cards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Full set of Summer Getaway Cards [W] Keys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-26 17:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As said, I have full completed set of Summer Sale Getaway cards, looking for keys, or offers. I won't trade cards for cards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Full set Summer Getaway cards, more [W] Borderlands 2, Offers ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-26 11:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have Sniper Elite 2 Nazi Zombie Army and Trine 2 Complete Story too giftable. 

Post offers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Full set - Summer Getaway Cards [W] Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 09:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would more likely trade full set for card. 

The price on market, if you do the math, for full set is around 3$, so keep this in mind when offering. :) 

EDIT; i still have cards so if someone is interested, pm me with offer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] SS Kerbal [W] SS Dead Island </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 13:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only this above! 

http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198052487616 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Demoman (Profile Background) CSGO IDF [W] SS Bioshock/DeadIsland/Reus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 13:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If interested, add me: 

http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198052487616/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] SS Chivalry and more additions [W] SS Bioshock/DeadIsland/Reus/Prison Architect </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 10:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have any of following SS CARDS, add me, and we'll discuss: 

http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198052487616/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] CS:GO IDF CARD [W] Binding of the Isaac to fullfill my badge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 15:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I manage to find 4 cards for Binding of the Isaac, and craft a badge, I will also get few Summer Getaway Cards as I will be lvl 5. 

Also, who helps me out, will get from me duplicates or possibly cards that they need - Summer Getaway ones. 

Thanks!

and yea, i need this 4 cards: 

II The High Priestess

III The Empress

IV The Emperor

VI The Lovers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Counter Strike : Global Offensive [W] Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 16:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As said in the title, have CS;GO, offer me what you think would be proper for this. DO NOT add me, unless we make a deal. Offer in comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [W] Someone to spare copy of Binding of the Isaac card </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 09:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nevermind, my mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Binding of the Isaac Cards [W] Games - offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 14:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have next set of cards: 

0 The Fool

I The Magician

V The Hierophant

VII The Chariot

VIII Justice


Trading it for cheap games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Binding of the Isaac Card - The Chariot [W] O the FOOL Binding of the Isaac </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 18:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need one card for badge, if you have it, feel free to add me: 

http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198052487616/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] Surgeon Simulator 2013 - 66% off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 15:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello guys. 

Well, after being unable to afford Surgeon Simulator due to low amount of funds, I decided to ask any of you grateful people to make my day and buy me a copy of this game. It's certainly strange, and what is most important different game that I've been looking for to try out. 

I would be more than grateful if someone could take their time and money to make my day, and make me happy. 

Thank you in advance! 

My steam ID; 

http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198052487616/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] Left for Dead 2 on steam, currently 3.49E </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 11:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After having long boring half of july, with no funds to spend on games, I would really appreciate if someone could share free copy of his Left for Dead 2 with me. The game looks fun, and I would love to spend some quality gaming time with my friends, or even some of you guys who already own the game. I tried Killing Floor, but I wanna experience something 'new', different, and if any of you could provide me that, it would be awesome :) 

Thanks anyway for even reading this one :)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Troubleshooting] Can I input this graphic card into my PC ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-02 10:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello guys. 


Right now, i have this specifications on my PC: 


Inter Pentium D CPU 3.20 GHz


HP xw4300 workstation  - i think this is motherboard :/


PSU - I don't know how to check it beside opening the case, and on case of my PSU it says POWER OUTPUT 460w, so I guess that would be it??

and I want to upgrade my graphic card which is currently;


 ATI Radeon HD 2600 XT

with HD 5750 1GB ATI RADEON version. So, will I be able to do t his with mine HD 5750, how will it all work, with this PSU if it is this one, and motherboard, and CPU. 


Thanks guys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Help] Need help with Graphic card </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 23:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a pc that i have now;

CPU; AMD ATHLON II X4 640 @ 3.00GHz QuadCore

Memory; 8GB RAM DDR3 1333MHz "Kingston"PC10666 CL9 

Graphic Card; HIS ATi RADEON HD5750 1GB GDDR5 IceQ

I want to buy proper graphic card around 200$, and I want to change this graphic card because i recently got new monitor; 21.5 inch; 1920x1080, so i was thinking about buying HD7850, but i'm not so sure, so I wanted to check with you guys. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ocelote goes to Turkey! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-19 00:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lag on EU </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-12 17:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Message to Froggen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 23:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Karateka, Zero Gear [W] Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 14:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make your offer, i give this 2 games  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Check out this youtube gaming channel, and see if it suits you!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 15:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Juggernaut Sets [W] Games via Steam / Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-08 14:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 FULL SET - Of Ebony and Ivory - RARE SET 4.33

1 FULL SET - The Boar's Gods Set - Uncommon SET 1.99

ALMOST FULL SET ( MISSING 1 ITEM ) - Traveler on the High Plains - RARE 4

ALMOST FULL SET ( MISSING 1 ITEM ) - Aspect of Beast and Man - Uncommon 2.39 

add if you have something in mind : 

http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198052487616
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Sets for Juggernaut ( More Inside ) [W] Steam gift games / Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 13:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 FULL SET - Of Ebony and Ivory - RARE SET 4.33

1 FULL SET - The Boar's Gods Set - Uncommon SET 1.99

ALMOST FULL SET ( MISSING 1 ITEM ) - Traveler on the High Plains - RARE 4

ALMOST FULL SET ( MISSING 1 ITEM ) - Aspect of Beast and Man - Uncommon 2.39 

+ I can add sweets if you are up to trade (:

ADD ME if you have anything in mind : 

http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198052487616 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Inventory [W] Items for Juggernaut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-06 09:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine inventory :

add me to discuss if you have something reasonable to offer.

http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198052487616/inventory/

PS. Obviously won't trade mine juggernaut items!

i'm seeking for Four-Fangs the Swordbreaker, that's the core item that i'm loooking for, as also : 

Long-Fang the grey Blade 

Prey Tracker's Aspect Mask

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Inventory [W] Offers / preferably items for Juggernaut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-05 19:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine inventory : 

add me to discuss if you have something reasonable to offer.

http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198052487616/inventory/

PS. Obviously won't trade mine juggernaut items! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Check out my channel, and give me advice on how to improve myself! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-23 10:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming channel - Advices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-23 09:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good morning lads ( at least it is in Europe ).
I just stopped by, to show you few of my videos that I recently recorded. I know it's not that good, but I want from your advice because i think that this subredit cointans many gamers, to give me advice on what should I do to improve, what should I put in, or toss out.
Sorry for my low english, as it is not my primary language.

here's my channel :

http://www.youtube.com/user/train_subject9972

It would ment hella lot if you could like or subscribe, but the main thing why I posted this thread is to see what should I do to improve.
Thanks a lot guys. Have a nice day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Channel - Advices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-23 09:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good morning lads ( at least it is in Europe ).
I just stopped by, to show you few of my videos that I recently recorded. I know it's not that good, but I want from your advice because i think that this subredit cointans many gamers, to give me advice on what should I do to improve, what should I put in, or toss out.
Sorry for my low english, as it is not my primary language.

here's my channel :

http://www.youtube.com/user/train_subject9972

It would ment hella lot if you could like or subscribe, but the main thing why I posted this thread is to see what should I do to improve.
Thanks a lot guys. Have a nice day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gameplays - few games to show!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-07 10:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good morning lads ( at least it is in Europe ). 

I just stopped by, to show you few of my videos that I recently recorded. I know it's not that good, but I want from your advice because i think that this subredit cointans many gamers, to give me advice on what should I do to improve, what should I put in, or toss out. 

Sorry for my low english, as it is not my primary language. 

Here are the videos : 

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JE8XPK4YgmY list=UUVMesjfXPjiLdXrbW7Yo5Fg index=1

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C9XAV2Bxb28 list=UUVMesjfXPjiLdXrbW7Yo5Fg index=2

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d-R-VVsA6yc list=UUVMesjfXPjiLdXrbW7Yo5Fg index=3 

And here's my channel : 

http://www.youtube.com/user/train_subject9972?feature=mhee 

It would ment hella lot if you could like or subscribe, but the main thing why I posted this thread is to see what should I do to improve. 

Thanks a lot guys. Have a nice day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] Metro 2033 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-02 10:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would really appreciate someones generosity, if that someone could waste their time and a little money to give me Metro 2033. I'm asking only Metro, because i want to get it for my friend, as he is one of the biggest fans of games like Metro 2033, Bioshock or that. 

Anyway, thanks. 

Cheers!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Assassins' Creed 3 Optimization?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-24 19:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, did anyone manage to handle this fps drop that appers at Boston. I played a game like 5-6 hours in a row, to sequence 6. When i came into Boston, there was a huge fps drop. Previous sequences, or places were apsolutely fine. 

I have HD5750 1GB, 8GB RAM, and X4 640 3.0 AMD Processor. 

I don't see a problem in my configuration, but the reason why i posted this, is to see, if anyone manage to solve this problem. It bothers me, because after passing 22% of game, i had to switch to Need For Speed Most Wanted, because i want to play AC3 at full experience. 

TL;DR - FPS Drop mainly in Boston, if anyone knows how to fix it, let me know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Rochard + Renegade Ops + Binding of the Isaac DLC + Warhammer 40k Marine DLC + 2xDota2 [W] Batman Arkham Asylum / Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-18 14:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer batman AA, and would go all in for it. 

Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Rochard +Renegade Ops + 2xDota2 + Wrath of the Limb DLC + Warhammer 40k Marine DLC [W] Batman Arkham Asylum / offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 23:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ 

I'll give all of these things for Batman AA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Rochard, Renegade Ops, Wrath of the Limb DLC, Warhammer 40k Marine DLC, 2x Dota2 [W] Batman Arkham Asylum, Don't Starve / Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 14:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^
I'm willing to give all of these for Batman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Rochard, Renegade Ops, Wrath of the Limb DLC, Warhammer 40k Marine DLC, 2x Dota2 [W] Batman Arkham Asylum, Don't Starve / Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-14 19:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ 

I'm willing to give all of these for Batman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Assassins' Creed 2 Deluxe Edition [W] Batman Arkham Asylum + maybe ( bind of Isaac ) / Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-11 11:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also have few dota 2 keys to spare, so if you are interested, post here, or simply PM me for further trade. =)

I also have good League of Legends account with 5 full runes, about 80 champions and 20 skins. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H]Assassin's Creed 2 Deluxe Edition [W] Batman Arkham Asylum + ( maybe Bind of Isaac) / Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-11 09:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H]Terraria, Bind of the Isaac, Day of Defeat Source [W] Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 21:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTT Dota 2 invites + many others </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 09:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having 2 DOTA 2, Hawken Beta, Planetside beta, Smite beta. 

Any offers are welcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SK CandyPanda ?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-21 18:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yo guys, i just watched ocelote stream, and someone send ocelote a message, about candy panda, something me gusta and spanish shit' ( no offense ), and it was something SK ad carry, me gusta ad carry, something like that. 

Ocelote replied "ya veremos". If google translator doesn't lie, it says " we will see". 

I really hope CandyPanda come back, cuz i think he's awesome guy, despite what happened in the past, and his disinteresting to playing with SK. 

http://pokit.org/get/img/82896559a1592df86ce5d4c89c42d1bf.jpg  - top right corner

does this mean yellowstar is still "in" or what ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H][DOTA 2 via STEAM [W] Any skincode AT EUW Exept Samurai Yi or Riot Graves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-20 13:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Read Description [W] Any key that properly works on EUW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-06 22:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello guys.

I'm willing to trade few good beta keys for any of skins that properly works on EUW 

I have:

1) RAVEGED Beta Key



2)Second Raveged Beta key






4)Planetside 2 Beta Key 



I won't go first, but i have every single proof of skins that i got via gamersbook or so. 

Thanks.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doublelift: Azubu is overrated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 23:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H]Planetside Beta Key - Others cool stuff [W] EUW SKINS. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-08 12:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TeamFortress 2 items : 

http://pokit.org/get/img/69d834715f8231d4e34604d56223896b.jpg 
http://pokit.org/get/img/08fb2497ed1f567532abb9fec865c940.jpg 

Dota 2 Items : http://pokit.org/get/img/4922b868dc0daada5b74950e9585464f.jpg 

3.Orcs Must Die! 

2 Exclusive Character Skin 

4.Nexuiz Exclusive Medal 

5.Heroes of Newerth Alien Andromeda Alt Avatar 

6.Heroes of Newerth Account Icon Keys 

7.War Inc. Arsenal Bundle 

8.Free Realms Coin   Item 

9.Fallen Earth Xenofire Gun   Free Product Key 

10.Mass Effect 3 M-90 Indra Sniper Rifle 

11.Battlefield 3 Dog Tag Item 

12.Tribal Trouble 2 

13.Remnant Knights Giveaway 

14.Champions Online FFA Game Bundle Key

15.PlanetSide2 Beta key

Greetings, train_subject9972 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] MASTER YI + SAMURAI YI Bundle [W] Arcade sona or RAMMUS skin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 22:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to trade with me, send me a PM on reddit with a name on server. I'm on EUW. 

This skin works for EUW and EUNE. 

http://pokit.org/get/img/787b66aa0e0d01d5c7ad6285e49f4c24.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Changeing 2 SMITE KEYS For any skin on EUW.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-12 23:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title says it all. Changeing 2 smite keys for any skin on eu west. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
