<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8202</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 01:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm what was that?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 01:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GRONK SMASH!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 01:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its before the Pepsi halftime show  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 22:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who cares it's a year away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 20:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe r/CFB should have its own super bowl game thread so that it not overcrowded and full of irrational discussions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 07:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course they do this after cutting multiple former AirTran routes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 06:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well good luck man. You can message me if you get lonely   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 05:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it helps for me that I go to a small school (like 2100) so its kinda hard to not make friends over time becauase you know everyone. We don't hang out that much, maybe once or twice a month, and most of my "social" activity is with my roommate (who I actually like which is good). The most activity that I do with my friends is have lunch. So I'm still kinda a "shut in" but I am more active now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 05:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Republican a hypocrite? NEVER </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 05:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm shocked, SHOCKED. That Jeb Bush was ever a bully considering how nice he was to the Schiavo's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 05:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We may be amongst the last now, but when the supreme court rules we hopefully won't have a gay marriage ban. Think of it like the sodomy laws. Georgia's was overturned by the state supreme court about 6 years before the supreme court overturned it nationally (though the Georgia case didn't involve a gay couple). Even though we were amongst the last we weren't THE last.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 05:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in my last semester. I didn't really start making until my 5th semester and now I have a small circle of friends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 01:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good for him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 00:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I buy you a drink or do you just want the money? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 00:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I am, Yes I am, Yes I am! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 00:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a native Georgian I totally understand - I was pissed about Alabama, South Carolina, and Mississippi's laws being declared unconstitutional before us. I just want it to be legal here before the Supreme Court has the final word so that we can say that we weren't among the last  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 00:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Freshman year of college every Friday and Saturday evening I would order a pizza (or some other type of takeout food) and take my laptop into the study room in my dorm and just sit there and watch Netflix until about 2am while everyone else in the dorm was either hanging out or throwing parties. It was quite common for me to have to wear headphones just so I could hear because of all of the noise from people having fun. I would always make sure that my roommate was asleep before I went back into the room (he was a stoner and a party animal so this is why I didn't want to be in that room). The way that I would make sure that he was asleep is that I would go outside the building and look to see if the light was on in our room. Once it was out I would finally be able to go get some sleep. This went on my entire freshman year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 00:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about she loves me unconditionally. No matter what happens she is always there to cheer me up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 00:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The organization I work for advocates fewer environmental regulations and is against a minimum wage increase  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 00:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That shirts very becoming on you. Of course, if I were on you Id be coming too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 00:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because she is awesome!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 23:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I though it said Prague at first  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 23:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DOZENS !! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 22:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any other American breath a sign of relief once they realized that this was in Canada and not the US. (not to take away the awfulness of the case)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 22:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was better than what I though the link was going to be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 19:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Big 12 can't stay at 10 forever when 3 of the p5 have 14, and the other has 12. It will have to expand at some point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 16:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should be [ interesting](http://m.imgur.com/DKJhx9l) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 05:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, go ahead and tell everybody  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 04:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Behold](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uUcBvS0HdsE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 23:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure you go ahead and tell everybody about the apology  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 06:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how at the end the guy says "that's the boner killer right there"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 05:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well it is an Atlanta crowd  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 05:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's Atlanta fans for you.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 01:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly he is still smoking the stuff that caused him to pick her in the first place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 00:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a [video](https://www.facebook.com/video.php?v=888799191176498 set=vb.100817319974693 type=2 theater) 

He is up for adoption  

Yes he is real </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 21:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hate is a strong word don't you think?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 19:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at UVA's OOC. It's brutal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 18:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad convinced me and my brother that the hazard lights button was a "hyper button" that would make the car go faster. When ever he pushed it he would slam on the gas to make us believe that it was the case. I quickly figured it out but my brother would go on believing this for years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 17:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The families of the Chinese victims did. 
But some families were upset that the government decided on the fate of their loved ones without any concrete evidence.

In China, some family members refused to accept the official position that the plane was lost.
"They have found nothing," said Li Jingxin whose brother is missing.
"With nothing found, how can they make any announcement?''

Clearly they are so full of grief that they can't accept reality 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 17:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it does seem a little excessive. The idea makes some practical sense but as always the implementation doesn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 05:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a result of this coming out in the Israeli press the American Family Associations spokesman Bryan Fischer has been fired http://www.mediaite.com/tv/evangelist-bryan-fischer-has-been-fired-maddow-reports/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 04:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why he was fired. The Israeli press found out about this group and asked why is a group whose spokesman, Bryan Fischer,says America a christian nation, founded for christians, and only christians are guaranteed first amendment rights is funding a trip to Israel (the JEWISH homeland) for a major political party. Needless to say once all of the past things that Bryan said were reported on it did not look good in Israel so they fired him. They didn't have a problem with him until now. So don't believe anything the American Family Association says about them not standing for what Bryan says. MSNBC's Rachel Maddow does a great breakdown of the whole affair http://www.msnbc.com/rachel-maddow/watch/bryan-fischer-fired-ahead-of-rnc-israel-trip-390575171843 (the video in the link wouldn't work for me)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 04:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The video in the link wasn't working for me so I'll post the video from the MSNBC website [here](http://www.msnbc.com/rachel-maddow/watch/bryan-fischer-fired-ahead-of-rnc-israel-trip-390575171843), it is worth watching. 

TL;DR 

He wasn't fired because he was an anti-gay, racist, sexist, bigot. He was fired because the American Family Association is founding a trip to Israel for over 50 GOP members, including the party chair Reince Priebus. The Israeli press found out about this group and asked why is a group whose spokesman, Bryan Fischer, says America a christian nation, founded for christians, and only christians are guaranteed first amendment rights founding a trip to Israel (the JEWISH homeland) for a major political party. Needless to say once all of the past things that Bryan said were reported on it did not look good in Israel so they fired him. They didn't have a problem with him until now. So don't believe anything the American Family Association says about them not standing for what Bryan says.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 03:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The theory is that sense electric cars don't use gas they don't pay the gas tax, which funds roads. Therefore in a sense they are using the roads for "free" while everyone else is contributing to their upkeep through the gas tax. So you just charge them a straight up tax for having an electric car to make up for them not paying the gas tax.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 03:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't Putin want a bunch of far-right parties to be in power sense he is bankrolling most of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 03:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little back story

Roy Moore is a big time Christian. Before he was on the Alabama Supreme Court he opened all his cases with a prayer. He called on Alabama to use it's powers to punish "homosexual behavior". He famously put a ten commandments statue in the Alabama Supreme Court building in 2002. He was taken to court by secular groups and they got a federal court to order it's removal. He refused and was subsequently removed from the court by a judicial oversight board. Alabamans reelected him to his former position in 2012 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 02:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Georgia definitely needs to increase transportation funding and this seems like a good proposal, but I'm skeptical of anything that comes from the state GOP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 02:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> take $350 million from the highway fund over 2 1/2 years

So now their roads and schools will be shit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 18:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've always been in the ACC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 17:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reason I want it to bite them in the ass is so that the people who voted for this *cough* tea party republicans *cough* get voted out of office (hopefully with better people replacing them).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 08:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/romega just discussions about whats going on in town (I go to school here)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 07:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know you're on the wrong side of an issue when you think people who hold your beliefs would kill or injure a newlywed couple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 05:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's an article talking about BYU keeping punishments in house now http://collegefootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2015/01/22/dont-expect-byu-to-announce-miami-beach-brawl-penalties/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 05:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The definition of white.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 04:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You missed the part where they called for protections for people's "religious liberty" to be part of the bills. Just like the Catholic church I will not trust anything that they say.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 04:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 03:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so glad I don't live in Cobb county. Is it mean of me to hope that this ends up biting them in the ass as badly as the Marlins new ballpark did to Miami-Dade county?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 03:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well with the mayor of Roswell being Comcast's [bitch](http://www.theverge.com/2015/1/26/7878239/comcast-twc-fcc-merger-letters-politicians-ghostwritten) I guess we can't expect it there anytime soon. Hopefully it comes to my area (Milton).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 03:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well with the mayor of Roswell being Comcast's [bitch](http://www.theverge.com/2015/1/26/7878239/comcast-twc-fcc-merger-letters-politicians-ghostwritten) I guess we can't expect it there anytime soon. Hopefully it comes to my area (Milton) but with Roswell being next door and Alpharetta probably having the same position I won't hold my breath.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 03:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apologize for the video starting half-way through, that was a mistake on my part. Watch the whole video, it is really cute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 21:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly don't know why it did that, maybe when I went to the YouTube link from another website it did that   I didn't notice. That is not what I intended when I posted this but by the time I realized it had already been upvoted over 150 times and I didn't want to delete it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 05:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Ramblin Wreck](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O6JXKMxRgQ8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 05:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Setting multiple alarms on my phone and placing the phone on the other side of the room. But to be honest what gets me out of bed most morning is having to pee.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 05:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I told the other guy my position is that the money in politics - whether it's from the Kochs, Unions, Soros, Sheldon Adelson, McCutcheon, whoever - is DISGUSTING and TOXIC on our democracy and should be abolished.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 04:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes because conservatives don't have a hateful bone in their [body](http://www.lgbtqnation.com/2015/01/okla-career-anti-gay-lawmaker-introduces-3-bills-targeting-lgbt-community/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 04:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, Malaysia Airlines can't catch a break.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 04:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He deleted his account. You think we scared him off?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 03:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you are comparing now to 100 years ago? Hmm where have I heard that [before](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aV1VUS3Q2W0). So you want to cut programs that help people like Medicaid, Medicare, Social Security, and SNAP and prolong their struggle and let them decend into poverty? How nice of you. The only thing that needs to be cut is the DoD, and we need to raise taxes on the rich on close corporate and capital gains tax loopholes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 03:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes no fucking sense. How has the "government expanding out of control" (ps it hasn't) led to a system favoring the wealthy. Large government means more protections for individuals - usually low income or middle class. Less government means less regulations which means more money to be made for corporations and their CEOs. AKA the Kochs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 03:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you poor thing you're taxed to death! 
Seeing as you make only $30,000 a year (as you state in a post here:np.reddit.com/r/Liberal/comments/2mybbb/an_open_letter_to_reddit_liberals_from_a_reddit/) you already don't pay that much in taxes as you fall into a low tax bracket. I am advocating the abolition of super PACs and a limit on the amount of money you can give campaigns. What I would do first is say that money is not free speech, abolish super PACs, and say that corporations could not donate to candidates campaigns. People could still donate to political parties and candidates but it would only be $500 max. Then what I would do is close corporate tax loopholes and capital gains loopholes and use some (like maybe 6%) available for campaigns to dip into if they want, split evenly of course (by the way those taxes wouldn't affect you). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 03:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still $300 million less than the Kochs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 03:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My narrative is that the money in politics - whether it's from the Kochs, Unions, Soros, Sheldon Adelson, McCutcheon, whoever - is DISGUSTING and TOXIC on our democracy and should be abolished. I still fail to see how you can't agree with this.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 02:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your link proves my point. Outside groups - Koch - spent more on elections than Obama did. The fact that billionaires are trying to buy our elections is disgusting and I don't know why anyone would support them. And I call it the Fox News strategy because they pioneered it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 02:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing how the average voter in this country is incredibly misinformed, if you see an ad repeating the same lie it becomes true over time. It's called the Fox News strategy   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 02:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course he is a Republican  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 02:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course a Republican  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 02:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What world do you live in. This is NOT democracy. This is a few billionaires buying our elections. Left or Right it doesn't matter it should be illegal. This amount of money in elections is DISGUSTING. And by the way I missed the announcement, since when did greenpeace and unions have $900 million to spend on elections?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 02:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ~~Satan~~ Saban

Better yet why don't they ask the people that paid his mortgage 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 02:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money is NOT free speech. All is does is buy elections for the wealthy. This is a democracy not an oligarchy. And by the way unions don't spend as much as the Kochs and I don't think they should have the right to spend money on elections either.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 00:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can thank the Supreme Court 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 00:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What part of money in politics is toxic don't you understand  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 23:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think money in politics is toxic no matter the party. However I can't stand republicans acting like George Soros is on equal footing with the Kochs. The Kochs put Soros to shame with the amount of money they spend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 23:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you honestly believe that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 17:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah close to that. They probably want to be like the NBA and NHL where  half the league goes to the playoffs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 17:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I agree with ESPN here that Jan 2 would make more sense for the semifinal games than NYE but they knew this would happen when they signed the contract. You can't sign a contract and then back out. And who knows maybe having the semifinal games on NYE will be a ratings bonanza. You don't know until you try.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 17:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck the NFL. They don't need more playoff games.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 16:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my face when I'm on an airplane with a screaming kid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 07:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only been on reddit for 5 months and this is one of my favorite threads. I've done more commenting here than anywhere else. I really love the gameday threads. They make the games more fun to watch (and more interesting when their is a blowout or dud of a game)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 07:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This from the [Rose Bowl](https://vine.co/v/Ow32eva2bhw)

These from the Sugar Bowl when hopes were [high](http://media.giphy.com/media/TlK63EFmM5HlhO1cNxe/giphy.gif) and hopes [low](https://cdn1.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/2896068/bamafear.0.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 04:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is another Youtube link https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5bP3wGhdjmI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 01:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But did he talk about Beyonce? That's his main issue now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 01:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2000 McCain would be ashamed of 2015 McCain  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 01:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good luck with that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 01:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who the fuck cares what that asshole says  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 00:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would anyone below the age of 60 be a Republican in 2014  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 00:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He will not be stopped. Harbaugh, Harbaugh, Harbaugh, Harbaugh!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 21:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Virginia?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 06:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks pretty nice, just don't overdo the metallic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 05:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, we have our reasons. Leave us alone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 04:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you'll like this video about [Cleveland](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oZzgAjjuqZM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 00:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw my schools name on that list, very scary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 00:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know it's funny, UVA would be my third team (my dad is a huge UVA fan - the poor soul).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 17:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Christian persecution complex knows no bounds  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 17:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 17:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a gay man I don't get how gay people still want to be Christian, follow the Christian faith, and want their children to grow up in that environment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 17:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something tells me that this won't work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 17:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Freshman year of college every Friday and Saturday evening I would order a pizza (or some other type of takeout food) and take my laptop into the study room in my dorm and just sit there and watch Netflix until about 2am while everyone else in the dorm was either hanging out or throwing parties. It was quite common for me to have to wear headphones just so I could hear because of all of the noise from people having fun. I would always make sure that my roommate was asleep before I went back into the room (he was a stoner and a party animal so this is why I didn't want to be in that room). The way that I would make sure that he was asleep is that I would go outside the building and look to see if the light was on in our room. Once it was out I would finally be able to go get some sleep. This went on my entire freshman year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 17:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well this ain't looking good. I guess Vlad either lost his patience or someone insulted his toughness. I wonder if the EU regrets signing that agreement yesterday that allows Russia to selectively ban food from certain EU countries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 17:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a crazy idea, why not just raise the gas tax </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 17:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My thoughts go out to the Bush family.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 02:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your english is fine, it's just something that you don't hear everyday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 02:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real potato quality video. Still beautiful  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 18:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UAB hasn't been honest about a lot of things. [Like lying about the fact that a donor was willing to pay for new turf at the practice facility.](http://www.al.com/sports/index.ssf/2015/01/uab_faculty_athletics_rep_says.html#incart_river)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 17:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans being hypocrites usual  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 06:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Criticize the Military, say we need gun control, bring up religion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 06:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ted hasn't owned the team for about 19 years. When he sold Turner Broadcasting to TimeWarner in 1996 they got the Braves as part of the deal. TimeWarner sold the Braves to Liberty Media, a holding company controlled by John C. Malone, in 2006/2007. The Braves signed a TV deal about 5/7 years back with FOX Sports South/SportSouth, two regional sports networks owned by Rupert Murdoch's 21st Century Fox (formally News Corp). The deal was for 20 years and pays only $15 million a year. For comparison the San Diego Padres signed a contract 3 years later for $40 million a years and the Texas Rangers signed a contract 2 years later for $80 million a year. Logically if the Braves TV contract were on the open market today it could fetch somewhere between those numbers if not more. So yeah the Braves have a shitty TV contract that they are stuck with until the late 2020s.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 05:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the public transportation will still be shit though and traffic will be a NIGHTMARE as its right where 285 and 75 meet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 03:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats fucking wrong, it hurts business because they don't know if the government is going to shut down one day or if the debt ceiling will be raised because the GOP likes using our economy as a bargaining chip.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 03:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, totally believable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 05:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A special shoutout to the Louisville all black [uniform](http://uniformcritics.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/new-louisville-black-football-uniform-620x662.jpg), close up of the [helmet](http://uniformcritics.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/lou1.jpg) 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 05:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I thought, the headline is confusing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 04:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wake Forest's mascot is pretty [bad] (http://www.obsessedwithsports.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/10/wake-forest-mascot.jpg)

Shoutout to Indiana's [mascot](http://cdn0.sbnation.com/imported_assets/721767/mascot.gif) from the 70s

And I know it's a FCS school but the Southern Illinois mascot is [terrifying](http://fitsnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/08/saluki.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 04:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like something that might eat children^^^I'm^^so^^sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 04:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet parents showed kids this picture to get them to eat vegetables, otherwise they might come get you in your sleep.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 04:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't make the Orange [angry](http://media.syracuse.com/borkowski/photo/beastoftheeastjpg-71a281d426e952bf.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 04:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, did they let that thing around kids? I bet there are some great pictures out there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 03:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks you so much for this, great study music  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 22:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We wouldn't be talking about it if Penn St and Pennsylvania officials insisted on draging this out and getting the wins back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 22:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just go to mediamatters.org you'll learn quickly why </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 18:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll give it a chance but keep in mind people said that Colbert was also one dimensional when his show started out. Give it time, hopefully he finds his grove.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 07:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah Texas, the "gift" that keeps on giving.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 06:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is the new standard for painful/awkward interview  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 06:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an added bonus listen to the PSU hockey coach jump through hopes to try and defend the 409 stickers in a radio [interview](http://www.tsn.ca/radio/toronto-1050/gadowski-students-chose-to-wore-decals-1.186437) 

And read this article on a PSU fan site criticizing her for the remarks 
http://onwardstate.com/2015/01/18/ad-sandy-barbour-apologies-for-409-helmet-stickers/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 06:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A FUCKING MEN, seriously read intire post that he is talking [about](http://onwardstate.com/2015/01/18/ad-sandy-barbour-apologies-for-409-helmet-stickers/). PSU fans are fucking insane. They ones on here keep claiming that it's only a minority that are JoePa apologists. If that's the fact SPEAK UP and let your voices be heard because if you don't your school is going to forever be associated with child rape and cult apologists. As an added bonus listen to the PSU hockey coach jump through hopes to try and defend the 409 stickers in a radio [interview](http://www.tsn.ca/radio/toronto-1050/gadowski-students-chose-to-wore-decals-1.186437)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 08:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Update: Fox News issues TWO formal [apologies] (http://www.mediaite.com/tv/fox-formally-apologizes-for-claiming-muslims-have-taken-over-european-cities/)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 08:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is late, I'm tired, I have dyslexia, and I was on mobile: sue me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 08:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Color me shocked that they actually apologized TWICE. The first apology seemed well thought out and articulate but the second one was clearly scripted and came off as fake - especially that smile at the end. Changes nothing about Fox though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 07:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> will they be in Baylor green?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 07:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You put way too much effort into this, you need to start lowering your expectations now.

Edited for grammar and spelling  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 07:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of course it is /s  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 05:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the thing is that with cable networks (which is probably what you watched 28 days later on) don't have any rules when it comes to nudity or swearing they do all of the censoring on their own voluntarily. Broadcast networks like ABC, NBC, CBS, and Fox do however have rules regarding said stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 01:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe anything that comes out of his mouth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 01:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fox News rule no. 1 is to NEVER admit that you were wrong. There was the infamous incident when one of their anchors made the statement that "santa just is white". After a ton of backlash the next day she said that it was a joke (even though it clearly wasn't) and that people criticizing her were clearly liberals who were scared about how powerful Fox News is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 01:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By the way welcome to reddit seeing as you are very new.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 01:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the Fox News [non-apology] (http://video.foxnews.com/v/3994985513001/anna-apologizes-for-error-on-map-of-frances-no-go-zones/?#sp=show-clips) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 23:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Includes a non apology from Fox  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 23:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I give a shit that the wins were restored because Penn St. is acting like they were the victims in this whole debacle, not the KIDS THAT WERE RAPED on their own campus. Is the NCAA a shit show? No doubt about it. But why should Penn St get special treatment after the fact when schools like USC and Miami were not. Especially sense the scandals at USC and Miami weren't nearly as bad as the Penn St scandal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 23:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
What is most damning, for me, is that Paterno convinced Schultz, Spanier, and Curley to NOT go to police. After the other 3 resolved to go to Department of Welfare, Paterno convinced them NOT to do that. That is horrible.

"According to CNN in an email dated Feb. 26, 2001, Schultz wrote to Curley about a three-part plan that included talking "with the subject asap regarding the future appropriate use of the University facility,"  "contacting the chair of the charitable organization" and "contacting the Department of Welfare."
Former Penn State athletic director Tim Curley's alleged email could be damaging for Joe Paterno. (AP) It would have been better to skip directly to the third action and let the welfare authorities do the meeting and informing, but this should've been enough to end Sandusky's reign of terror. Except that Curley sent an email to Schultz and school president Graham Spanier on Feb. 27, 2001, that changed everything.
"After giving it more thought and talking it over with Joe yesterday, I am uncomfortable with what we agreed were the next steps. I am having trouble with going to everyone but the person involved. I would be more comfortable meeting with the person and tell them about the information we received and tell them we are aware of the first situation," Curley's email said

[source](http://sports.yahoo.com/news/ncaaf--joe-paterno-role-jerry-sandusky-coverup-grows.html;_ylt=Aur28zfJcBol6xK3nRW3Of4LcykA;_ylu=X3oDMTFoZnA0Y2I3BG1pdANCbG9nIEluZGV4IGJ5IEF1dGhvcgRwb3MDMQRzZWMDTWVkaWFCbG9nSW5kZXg-;_ylg=X3oDMTFrODdzYXZuBGludGwDdXMEbGFuZwNlbi11cwRwc3RhaWQDBHBzdGNhdANhdXRob3IEcHQDc2VjdGlvbnM-;_ylv=3)

by the way real unbiased opinion [there] (http://www.reddit.com/r/CFB/comments/2sjhpl/ncaa_chair_admits_to_not_reading_freeh_report/cnqlp59)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 23:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is most damning, for me, is that Paterno convinced Schultz, Spanier, and Curley to NOT go to police. After the other 3 resolved to go to Department of Welfare, Paterno convinced them NOT to do that. That is horrible.

"According to CNN in an email dated Feb. 26, 2001, Schultz wrote to Curley about a three-part plan that included talking "with the subject asap regarding the future appropriate use of the University facility,"  "contacting the chair of the charitable organization" and "contacting the Department of Welfare."
Former Penn State athletic director Tim Curley's alleged email could be damaging for Joe Paterno. (AP) It would have been better to skip directly to the third action and let the welfare authorities do the meeting and informing, but this should've been enough to end Sandusky's reign of terror. Except that Curley sent an email to Schultz and school president Graham Spanier on Feb. 27, 2001, that changed everything.
"After giving it more thought and talking it over with Joe yesterday, I am uncomfortable with what we agreed were the next steps. I am having trouble with going to everyone but the person involved. I would be more comfortable meeting with the person and tell them about the information we received and tell them we are aware of the first situation," Curley's email said

[source](http://sports.yahoo.com/news/ncaaf--joe-paterno-role-jerry-sandusky-coverup-grows.html;_ylt=Aur28zfJcBol6xK3nRW3Of4LcykA;_ylu=X3oDMTFoZnA0Y2I3BG1pdANCbG9nIEluZGV4IGJ5IEF1dGhvcgRwb3MDMQRzZWMDTWVkaWFCbG9nSW5kZXg-;_ylg=X3oDMTFrODdzYXZuBGludGwDdXMEbGFuZwNlbi11cwRwc3RhaWQDBHBzdGNhdANhdXRob3IEcHQDc2VjdGlvbnM-;_ylv=3)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 23:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> too me it seems like people are jumping thru hopes to try and come up with a way to say that JoePa was innocent. If I were Joe I would have gone to the police once the administration did nothing or at the very least told Sandusky that I never wanted to see him around the campus facilities again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 22:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no he wasn't almost 60, he was 55. yeah JoePa wasn't close to retiring but he still could have kept coaching. JoePa told the administration what he had heard and once it became clear that the Penn St administration was covering CHILD MOLESTATION ON THEIR OWN FUCKING CAMPUS  up he should have gone to the police like and normal human being with a conscious .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 22:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what are you talking about, he's 70 now. he retired in 1999 at the age of 55. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 22:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It still doesn't change the fact that if Joe went to police that they would have taken him seriously. This man was a god in central PA, if he had evidence, even circumstantial or hearsay, the police would have done everything they could to investigate. The facts that that you site doesn't change the fact that Joe did nothing to stop what was happening and the Penn St. actively covered it up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 22:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah another Paterno apologist. No he knew. Sandusky went from being coach in waiting to randomly retiring. The fact of the matter is that Penn St and Joe Paterno cared more about football than stopping a CHILD MOLESTER. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 20:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was agreeing with you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 20:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Southerner here who's actually been to France. I would say that what most people here say is true. The NE is more densely populated and has better flight connections to Europe that the Southern, Midwestern, or Western part of the country. It also helps that NYC is a huge financial center and Washington is the political center of the country. Also like someone else said people out west may have a stronger connection to Asia and people in the southwest have a stronger connection to Latin America.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 20:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cleveland might be NE politically or culturally but from a technical definition Ohio is part of the [midwest](http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Midwestern_United_States) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 20:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I would consider Ohio part of the Midwest  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 20:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gas taxes are used to fund infrastructure projects like roads   bridges. The federal gas tax hasn't been raised in 20 years and because of that funds are getting harder to come by. With the chances of a federal gas tax increase being almost 0, states are looking at the possibility of raising gas taxes on their own. The low price of gas at the moment makes it more palatable to raise the tax now than it was when oil was $100 a barrel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 19:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd feel like I was selling my sole if I worked there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 19:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I checked the front page and second page and didn't see it there. I can't help it if 2 different websites have the same article and title.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 08:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the great conservative freakout about transgendered and bathrooms continues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 08:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it has been reported in the past that Shep is gay, if he is that must be a terrible place to work  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 08:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the great conservative freakout about transgendered and bathrooms continues  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 07:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fox never ~~learns~~ cares  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 07:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fellow American here and I totally agree with you. Before going to France  all I heard about were how rude the French were. I personally never experienced that. Granted the school group I was with stayed in more of the touristy areas so there were more english speakers (and one could argue that they were putting on happy faces for tourists). However there were a few times that we were not in tourist areas.  The locals may not have spoken much english but we made the effort to speak French when ordering something or asking questions which they seemed to appreciate.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 07:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't fell bad. It was bought by Rupert Murdoch the guy who owns Fox News.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 06:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have changed the headline to make it more clear but r/nottheonion is SUPER strict about changing titles
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 06:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll take him on TV over Lou Holtz any day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 05:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the Le Pen metaphor  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 05:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/7drHiqr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 04:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess the rumors a month ago about a souring relationship between Whittingham and the AD were either false or resolved  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 02:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one here who think that this is wrong and that Penn St should not have the wins restored. I'm sick and tired of Penn St and Paterno fans acting like they were the victims here. The victims were the KIDS that Sandusky RAPED while Penn St turned a blind eye. Did the NCAA overstep? Possibly but guess what the NCAA makes up the rules as they go along. The NCAA is a dick to everyone (just look at USC) why should Penn St get special treatment when everyone else is punished to the fullest extent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 00:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they learn nothing from Jurassic Park </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 21:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess is something by either Fall Out Boy (again), Maroon 5, Katy Perry, Taylor Swift, or Drake. Wild card would be Lady Gaga or Lorde (doubtful though)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 21:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> never trust ANYTHING that the GOP puts forward as a plan/alternative  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 21:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUCK THESE ASSHOLES  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 21:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, introduce bills that have no chance of becoming law so that the GOP can focus all energy on that instead of things like tax and immigration reform  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 21:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> personally I wish for this [one](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FiEzKjycxTw list=PLnkEWtFM5LzdVdeMBFjW7p9y9hc-DbFXJ#t=13) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 17:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NOT A VIOLENT KILLING MACHINE  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 17:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the sheer stupidity of this country never ceases to amaze me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 14:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow I'm blind  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 06:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are calling us judgmental, but thats judgmental, to say were being judgmental when they dont know us, Booth argued.

-_____- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 05:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's weird seeing the US without sunglasses  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 05:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> excuse my ignorance but can you explain the poster in the background  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 05:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume you mean insects not incest :) 

I think insects is self explanatory. I DON'T LIKE BUGS. Orcas..... I don't know why I don't like them. Maybe I'm just more of a fur guy and I have a hard time imagining them as anthros - same with birds probably. (though I did warm up to reptiles so who knows maybe I'll warm up to them as well)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 04:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canines all the way. I'm just a dog person so I guess thats why I chose them (I have 2 fursonas a husky and a beagle). Others that I like are foxes, felines, otters, bears, and horses. Ones I don't really care for are birds, dolphins, pigs, insects, and orcas. I used to have a thing against dragons and reptiles but I'm slowly warming up to them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 04:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know fish could be such dicks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 04:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first year here as well. I really got into the game threads towards the end of the season and now it's like I can't watch a game without it. It makes watch football (especially bad football) more fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 03:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear a lot of talk coming from FCA, but i doubt that they will be able to achieve what they are claiming. To me this seems like VW a few years ago  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 02:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A French comedian responds http://www.mediaite.com/online/french-tv-host-mocks-fox-friends-for-fearmongering-on-muslim-no-go-zones/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 18:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> guess who's Aloe Blacc's record label: Universal Music Group. Conspiracy confirmed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 18:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about the fact that they put it in the headline. It's fine if they mentioned his party affiliation in the article but no they had to mention he was a Democrat in the headline because they are Fox News. If the head line just said "Politician Wins Special Election From Jail" it would have accomplished the same effect of getting someone to click the article.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 18:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you mean geckos  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 18:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a bunch of cowards. Even USA Today, a newspaper that avoids controversy like the plague (seriously their editorial board leans loosely left but they let right wingers publish rebuttals all the time to give the appearance of impartiality) and the most vanilla newspaper I can think of, published the cartoons http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2015/01/12/hayat-boumeddiene-amedy-couilbaly-paris-terror-attacks/21621219/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 18:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.themoscowtimes.com/opinion/article/russia-is-not-charlie/514369.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 17:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course Fox News needs to mention that it's a former Democrat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 14:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say it was a bad thing. I'm using that as an example as to how USA Today avoids controversy.  I'm just saying that it's sad that the McPaper that is USA Today has more balls than Sky News  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
