<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9446</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Moazzam Begg Arrest: Part of the Effort to Criminalize Muslim Political Dissent By Glenn Greenwald and Murtaza Hussain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 15:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Crazy Wisdom': documentary on Chogyam Trungpa, Rinpoche (88:51) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 11:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crazy Wisdom: The Life   Times of Chogyam Trungpa [2011] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 02:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> God in Buddhism - Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 02:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What embodies a healthy response to sex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 02:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bahamas: Billionaire claims he is getting younger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 19:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pictures from the Yarmouk refugee camp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 16:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yarmouk refugee camp residents gathered to await a food distribution on January 31st 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 16:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pew Survey: Palestinian Arabs Dislike America More Than Any Other Group </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 15:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cannabis Terpenoid Activity Table (x-post eldertrees) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 12:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama to host Dalai Lama at White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 21:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama to host Dalai Lama at White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 09:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tony Blair advised Rebekah Brooks on phone-hacking scandal, court hears Former prime minister suggested setting up 'Hutton style' inquiry, according to email from former News International chief </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 14:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rebekah Brooks email to James Murdoch.PDF </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 14:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens to your brain if you take caffeine and a soporific at the same time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 23:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens to your brain if you take caffeine and a soporific at the same time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 23:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alex Salmond's speech in full [28:26] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 19:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1928 Flood of London [624 x 460] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 01:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look Closely, Doctor: See the Camera? - PSYCHOSIS in the 21st century looks something like this... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 04:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK Drugs Petition Passes 100,000, Russell Brand Offers To Snog Signatory Live On Air </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 19:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The woman who murdered men 'for fun' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 18:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'The White Gallery' by Nectaroff - A poem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 05:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why MP George Galloway is Killing Tony Blair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 21:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look not in my eyes, for fear. - A. E. Housman, 1896. A Shropshire Lad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 12:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dolphins 'deliberately get high' (x-post /r/likeus) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 22:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC News | Upperlands school adopts Aston Villa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 06:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Years Most Beautiful Photos From Space </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 05:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to find out if someone has logged into your Reddit account? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 05:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If someone other than me has logged into my Reddit account, is there a way of finding out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why We Love War - David L. Roy (the views of an American Buddhist) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 00:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why We Love War - David L. Roy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 00:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THIS is what state repression of the free press looks like: The Guardian just released the video of British intelligence forcing them destroy computers   hard drives with info from Edward Snowden (x-post /r/privacy) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 15:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MOTD - Aston Villa vs. West Bromwich Albion Video Highlights   Interviews (29th Jan 14) - (12:36) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 16:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the Goals of the Season! - Delph (expert control) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 04:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Excerpt from 'Money, Sex, War, Karma' by David R. Loy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 22:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still, I can't help wondering if the puritanism found in some places in the Pali Canon is an historical artifact, resulting from a general disparagement of the physical body that seems to have become common in India and elsewhere[...] such attitudes were apparently part of the cultural milleu the Buddha was raised in. Or did they arise afterward, and were inserted into the Canon later?

Whether or not such metaphysical considerations were a factor, other, more basic issues must have been important. Some of them are obvious and have already been mentioned. Monastic sexual activity would be a distraction to say the least, and expend a lot of energy that would be better used in other ways. Think of how much time and effort sexual affairs and liaisons can involve, even when they are not secretive. Add to that all the tensions and jealousies that would be created within the Sangha.

Already it becomes apparent that having a more relaxed attitude toward sex would be fatal to the spiritual focus of the community. However, at least two other concerns must also have weighed heavily.

We tend to forget that until the 1960s there was really no reliable contraception. Since Buddhism prohibited abortion and infanticide, sex meant babies, and all the work of caring for them and raising themespecially the unremitting daily task of providing enough food, which is incompatible with a mendicant life. The consequences of this can be seen in the cautionary tale of Japanese Buddhism. Japanese culture has always viewed our natural urges as...well, natural. That very much includes the sexual urge, and many if not most temple monks had common-law wives and children before they were legally permitted to marry after the Meji Restoration. The task of providing for them eventually transformed the temple into a family business, with the oldest son expected to become a priest to keep that temple business in the family, regardless of whether he had any religious inclinations. As a result, Japanese Buddhism today is a thriving (and lucrative) industry focusing on funerals and memorial services, and not much else.

One more factor may have been the most important of all. Buddhist monastics are traditionally dependent on lay support. This means that the Sangha must be very sensitive to the expectations of their supporters. For example, Chinese monks and nuns became vegetarian not because their vows required it but because the laity began to expect it. Also, needless to say, it wouldn't do to have monks seducing their supporters' daughters (or sons). Moreover, laymen and women would not look kindly upon sharing their hard-earned food and other resources with renunciants who, instead of devoting themselves to their spiritual practice, spend time dallying with lovers.  Even today, when monks in southeast Asian countries like Thailand are discovered with girlfriends, it's sometimes the local lay community that takes the initiative in forcibly disrobing them.

To sum up, there are many strong reasons for the Buddhist Sangha to be strictly celibate. Which of these were the important factors? Early Buddhist texts do not help us decide among them, but my guess is that all of them were.

How does this shed light upon our situation today? If it is more or less inclusive, there are major implications for Western Buddhism, because few if any of those reasons for celibacy are valid for lay practitioners today.

Yes, there are still times (periods of intensive practice) and places (within practice communities) when sexual abstention is obviously wise to observe. Few Western Buddhists, however, still look upon nature, women, and sex as impure entanglements to be avoided. Most of us don't have to worry about what our lay supporters think, because we don't have any, at least not in the traditional sense. Today we have access to effective means of birth-control, so babies usually aren't an issue unless and until we want them to be. A new category of Buddhist has become common in the West: less than monastic in lifestyle (hence not subject to Sangha vows or regulations) but also more devoted to practice than laity have usually been.[...]

So...does that mean we can breathe more easily now, as we accept and enjoy the new sexual freedoms? Not quite yet. There is another aspect of sexual relationships that we need to be aware of, and it's one that is not usually acknowledged.[...]

Our own cultural perspective should not be taken for granted, as if it provided some universal standard. Present Western attitudes are historically conditioned too, in this case by a myth about romantic love that evolved in late medieval Europe[...]

Although some of the emphasis has shifted from finding the right spouse to finding the right sexual partner, there is still the same expectation of personal fulfillment whether through romance or sexual intimacy. Buddhism questions that conscious or unconscious expectation, just as it challenges other myths that predispose us to seek happinessthe end of *dukkha*in an unskillful way.

Sexual intimacy is a source of pleasure and gratification, and a very nice one it can be; it can also help create and sustain deeper, more meaningful relationships. Nevertheless, the sex drive is basically biological. Sex is an appetite. We do not use our sexual organs; they use us. That is why there is ultimately something delusive about the myths of romantic love and sexual fulfillment. Sex is nature's way, and marriage is society's way, to reproduce the species. Genuine happinessthat is, the end of *dukkha* for any of the parties involved has little if anything to do with it.

________________________________________________________

David R. Loy, *Money, Sex, War, Karma - Notes for a Buddhist Revolution*, (Boston: Wisdom, 2008) pp.72-75.

________________________________________________________

'A work of deep and urgent relevance.'Ethan Nichtern, author of *One City: A Declaration of Interdependence*.

'If you're interested in personal or societal change, this is a book you need to read.'Noah Levine, author of *Against the Stream*.

'I know of no other book that holds more promise for the survival and relevance of Buddhism in the modern world.'Lin Jensen, author of *Pavement: Reflections on Mercy, Activism, and Doing "Nothing" for Peace*.

'A flashy title... but a serious and substantial book.'*Buddhadharma* magazine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Excerpt from 'A History of Buddhist Philosophy' by David J. Kalupahana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 07:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **The Method of Discourse**


We often find references to four stages in which the Buddha would initiate and conclude a discourse. The first stage is represented as "pointing out" (*sandasseti*), that is, indicating the problem. If it was in reference to an individual, the Buddha would explain that person's situation. If it concerned an event, thing, or phenomenon, the Buddha would attempt to create some "agitation" (*samuttejeti*) by emphasizing the non-substantiality of the individual, event, thing, or phenomenon. This is the process of deconstruction, intended to avoid any ontological commitment. If the discourse is concluded at this point, the person to whom it is addressed will be left in a state of anxiety. During the third stage, the agitation is immediately appeased (*sampahaseti*) by pointing to a way out of the problem. This is the process of reconstruction or redefinition, which is achieved through the positive doctrine of dependent arising explaining the subject, the object, and morality and freedom. In doing so, the Buddha recognized the capacity of language to communicate the content of human experience, whether that relates to facts or values. In the final stage, the Buddha makes no effort to convert the hearer to his way of thinking, for the hearer tends to accept his explanation without much ado (*samadpesi*).

The discourse (*dhamma*) formulated in terms of language thus becomes the means of communication. Communication, not only among those who speak different languages but also among those who speak the same language, becomes impossible if one adopts either of the approaches toward language criticized by the Buddha, namely, strict adherence or transgression. The first would imply that each conception utilized in language has its incorruptible object (ontological commitment) unavailable to human experience, while the second would imply that human experience is incommunicable through language (that is, linguistic transcendence). The Buddha seems to have realized that the former is more perverse that the latter. His method of communication therefore deals first with the problem of ontological commitment and then with linguistic transcendence. 


This is an extremely significant method of communication and conversion, based on the Buddha's understanding of human psychology. His contemporaries, who failed to understand the psychological significance of this method of discourse, saw him as a person possessed of the magical power of conversion (*vaan my*). Yet there was no magic or mystery involved. All that the Buddha did was carefully observe the intellectual maturity and psychological state of each person and provide a discourse that would produce beneficial consequences for him. The Chinese version of the Agama passage that refers to the four stages rightly characterizes them as the Buddha's "skill in means".

"Skill in means" does not imply converting someone by discoursing on something that is obviously false. In fact, the two stages of causing agitation (*samuttejana*) and appeasement (*sampahasana*) correspond, respectively, to deconstruction of solidified conceptions through analysis (*vibhga*), which is the function of the doctrine of non-substantiality (*anatta*), and reconstruction of the same conception by the method of explanation (*vykaraa*), which is achieved through the principle of dependence (*paticcasmuppda*). Both these processes allow for a great degree of flexibility and are intended to eliminate both absolutism and nihilism.

'A History of Buddhist Philosophy - Continuities and Discontinuities' by David J. Kalupahana, (University of Hawaii Press; 1992) pp.65-67. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ibuprofen Can Kill Pot Buzz, Research Reveals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 20:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Excerpt from 'The Myth of Freedom' by Chgyam Trungpa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 02:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The preparation for the bodhisattva path is the unification of body and mind: the body works for the mind and the mind works for the body. The hinayana shamaha and vipashyna practices make the mind precise, tanquil and smooth in the positive sense - precisely being there, rather than dreaming or sleeping or hazily perceiving. We can make a cup of tea properly, because the body and mind are synchronized.

Then we are ready to leap on to the bodhisattva path, to open to the joy of working with sentient beings, including oneself. The bodhisattva makes friends with himself as well as with others. There are no mysterious, dark corners left of which to be suspicious; no surprises can occur to destroy the bodhisattva's spiritual intelligence, his dignity and heroism. This is the first step, the first *bhumi* or spiritual level.

The word 'bhumi' in Sanskrit, or the word *sa* in Tibetan, means 'earth' or 'level' or 'ground', the ground where you can relate with yourself and others. There is no mystification, no confusion; it is obviously solid earth. In other words, it is the equivalent of the basic sanity, fundamentally being *there*. Since the bodhisattva knows his body and his mind and how to relate with the two, the whole process becomes 'skillful means' because of such transcendental security. Which is more like being *in* security rather than being secured, rather than watching yourself to make sure everything is okay. That fundamental security comes from realizing that you have broken through something. You reflect back and realize that you used to be extraordinarily paranoid and neurotic, watching each step you made, thinking you might lose your sanity, that situations were always threatening in some way. Now you are free of all those fears and preconceptions. You discover that you have something to give rather than having to demand from others, having to grasp all the time. For the first time, you are a rich person, you contain basic sanity. You have something to offer, you are able to work with your fellow sentient beings, you do not have to reassure yourself anymore. Reassurance implies a mentality of povertyyou are checking yourself, 'Do I have it? How could I do it?' But the bodhisattva's delight in his richness is based upon experience rather than theory or wishful thinking. It is *so*, directly, fundamentally. He is fundamentally right and so can delight in generosity.

___________________________________________________________

From *The Myth of Freedom and the Way of Meditation* by Chgyam Trungpa (Shambhala Publications, Inc.: 1988). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British soldier criticises fighting 'for Queen and country'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 04:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this safe to eat if I remove the mould? http://imgur.com/a/ZG5H6 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 20:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this redcurrant jelly with mould safe to eat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 20:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NORML's Marijuana Health Mythology by Dale Gieringer, Ph.D. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 06:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much does a human ear weigh? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 05:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NATURAL LAW IN THE SPIRITUAL WORLD by HENRY DRUMMOND </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 21:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could someone tell me what is going on in this video? - BLACKBURN MATAMDARI 3rd MOHARRAM 2013 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-19 18:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should the UK follow Uruguay's lead and legalise cannabis? | Poll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 09:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "If we cling to our being Christians, Jews, atheists or Buddhists... we are responsible for wars and for confrontations between groups". Discuss. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 20:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Furthermore, if we cling to our being Christians, Jews, atheists or Buddhists, we 
will always be worried about what people may think of Jesus and the Christians, of Jews, 
of atheists, or of Buddha and the Buddhistsand when those with whom we identify are 
insulted, we will get offended and suffer, and we might even be willing to fight and thus 
run the risk of suffering blows, pain, bruises, wounds and even death (or to cause any of 
these damages to our opponent). However, if we defeat our adversary we will remain 
dissatisfied as well, since we will never be able to convince him that we are right, and he 
will keep on having a negative opinion of Christians, Jews, atheists or Buddhists. This 
dynamic is at the root of conflicts between groups, and in particular of warswhich, 
given the characteristics and number of present weapons, in the best of cases produce a 
drastic acceleration of the process of self destruction of humanity and, in the worst of 
cases, might cause the immediate destruction of life on our planet. Thus Krishnamurti 
was right when he asserted that, so long as we are this or that (which, as will be shown in 
the next chapter, in the context of this book means so long as we delusorily value our 
being this or that), we are responsible for wars and for confrontations between groups, 
with all their negative consequenceswhich nowadays may even involve global 
destruction.

~ Elas Capriles in [*Buddhism and Dzogchen*](http://webdelprofesor.ula.ve/humanidades/elicap/en/uploads/Biblioteca/bdz-e.version.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guantnamo's books blacklist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 21:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If someone asks you how you are doing, and you're so-so, how do you respond in an upbeat way? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 16:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to put a dampener on things, but nor do I want to come across with insincere positivity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Ngram Viewer - ennui, boredom, melancholia, tedium, acedia, melancholy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 20:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sexualities as found in books </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 15:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Ngram Viewer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 15:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Declining interest in Myalgic Encephalomyelitis/Chronic Fatigue Syndrome according to Google Ngram Viewer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 15:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silabbata Sutta: Precept   Practice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 09:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kalama Sutta: To the Kalamas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 08:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Cannabis' in various Indo-European languages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 04:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Albanian  -  kanp

Armenian  - cannabis

Latvian - kaepes

Lithuanian - kanaps

Irish - cannabas

Welsh  - canabis

Danish - cannabis

Swedish - cannabis

Norwegian - cannabis

Icelandic - kannabis

Yiddish  - Qanabas

German - Cannabis

Dutch - ~~hennep~~ cannabis

English - cannabis

Greek - knnavis

Persian -  

Russian - konoplya

Ukranian - konoplya

Belarusian - kanopli

Bosnian - konoplja

Bulgarian - indiiski konop

Czech - konop

Macedonian - kanabis

Slovenian - konoplje

Slovak - ~~konope~~ cannabis sativa = konopa siata;
cannabis indica = konopa indick
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free Buddhist Audio : Bodhisattva ideal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 10:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC - Adam Curtis - WHAT THE FLUCK! - The point at which journalism fails and modern power begins. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 09:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC News - Labour MP John Woodcock opens up about depression </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 07:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cold Heaven - Yeats, W. B. 1916. Responsibilities and Other Poems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 07:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paudeen - Yeats, W. B. 1916. Responsibilities and Other Poems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 07:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The bodhisattva complex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 05:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Dharma of Lou Reed - Many Voices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 05:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Combined Preclinical Therapy of Cannabinoids and Temozolomide against Glioma </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 17:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THC w/chemo produces best results for beating brain cancer - A Combined Preclinical Therapy of Cannabinoids and Temozolomide against Glioma </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 16:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THC w/ chemo produces best results for beating brain cancer - A Combined Preclinical Therapy of Cannabinoids and Temozolomide against Glioma </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 03:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Countries screening The Day of the Doctor simultaneously.jpg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-24 05:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Tom Baker was a monk for six years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 01:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RadicalChristianity: Getting to the Root of the Christian Life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 12:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was Jesus brown? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 19:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 10 most shocking performance artworks ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 09:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dances of the Planets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 18:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prism.name </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-26 23:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>      Memory is a prism through which 

     yesterdays's light is passed;

     Split into a rainbow of moments 

     each colored more dimly than the last. 

     How will today's light look tomorrow 

     and - how would tomorrow's look today? 

     Would the filter of time be as brutal

     if that prism were two-way?

  
    - Asbur Honnurth (Steve Meretzky)

      "Secret Recreations of the Soul"

      (c) Copyright 2007

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for portrayals of healthy sexual relationships. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 18:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I asked this question a while back in /r/AskLiteraryStudies - [link](http://www.reddit.com/r/AskLiteraryStudies/comments/1l83m6/portrayals_of_healthy_sexual_relationships/) . Can anyone think of examples in literature in which a long-term sexual-relationship is depicted as happy, healthy and non-neurotic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Benjamin Zephaniah calls for a new, internationalist political party. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 15:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Portrayals of healthy sexual relationships? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 15:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A place for posts showing the intelligence/percipience of animals: /r/likeus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 09:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This guy is good at gaming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 08:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lion Art - Moving Out Of Babylon (acoustic version) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 03:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Great celebratory music!) Mr. Vegas - I Am Blessed [Official Video] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 21:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Scholars - W.B. Yeats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 00:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zimbabwe - Live by Miles Davis on Spotify (41:50) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 06:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manu Tuilagi 'bunny ears' prank on David Cameron at No.10. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 03:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Penniless Optimist - Sam Redmore remix by The Electric Swing Circus on Spotify </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 03:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Birmingham cannabis protest - Sat 31st - 1-7pm - Cannon Hill Park </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 16:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Birmingham cannabis protest - Sat 31st - Cannon Hill Park </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 16:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC NEWS | Middle East | US used white phosphorus in Iraq </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 18:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to distinguish the metta-bhavana from the karuna-bhavana? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 03:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've realised that I've been practising the karuna-bhavana instead of the metta-bhavana. At the Triratna centre that I go to they teach the metta-bhavana to beginners. Whenever I do it I find myself trying to 'put myself in the shoes of' whoever it is I'm visualising. For, how can one love someone when one does not make an attempt to comprehend their situation? This entails compassion - i.e. karuna. 

Today, while going through the stages of the metta-bhavana I felt truly powerful paroxysms of pity. It was difficult to breathe and stay seated upright. It took a great deal of effort to regain composure.

I understand now why the karuna-bhavana is reserved for more advanced practitioners. What I would like to know is if anyone has any tips on how I can practise the metta-bhavana without having this problem again? How can one try to demarcate the metta-bhavana from the karuna-bhavana? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Portrayals of healthy sexual relationships? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 02:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was racking my mind to think if I'd read any novels (and plays/poems) that portray a positive, lasting sexual relationship.

Just as I was writing this, I remembered the relationship between the protagonist of McEwan's 'Saturday' and his wife. Apart from that, I found examples a bit thin on the ground.

Can anyone provide me with examples in literature in which a long-term sexual-relationship is depicted as happy and healthy and non-neurotic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sly   The Family Stone - "Can't Strain My Brain" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 17:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hope you guys enjoy this subreddit. I feel it can become a really interesting place to visit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 12:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A poem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 02:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     I've been high and I've been low. 
    And I know which I'd rather be. 

    At the top of the atmosphere it starts to get lighter - 
    All the colours, whiter and whiter.

    Around us all, beyond the air, 
    The whirling, crushing cosmos bear,
    Lonely. Unfair.

    The cosmos absorbs us all so small.
    Still love. Still pity.
    
      
***


Moral of the story: Cherish wise attention. Value a-voidance.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A visualisation poem that I've written </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 02:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been high and I've been low. And I know which I'd rather be. As you get to the top of the livable atmosphere it starts becoming lighter - more enlightened. Beyond - the vasty dark cosmos. Wise attention. Value a-voidance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have a memory that precedes learning to speak? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-21 05:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone have a memory from before you learnt how to speak?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any bands around today that are this good? [Up For The Down Stroke by Parliament on Spotify] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 08:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK reggae music - 'Rise Up' - ft. Brian Travers of UB40. Recommended. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 08:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Friendly Fire Band featuring Lion Art - Welcome to Holland OFFICIAL VIDEO | HD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 08:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ~~Give~~ Get up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 05:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'What Makes the Mindset of a Radical?' - Stephen Batchelor, (author of 'Confession of a Buddhist Atheist'), in conversation with neurophilosopher Owen Flanagan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 08:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Oh Who Is That Young Sinner" by A.E. Housman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 04:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some powerful and inspirational words about human nature - its past, current and potential state. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-05 02:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meditation is about stilling the mind so we can see clearly. Meditation is about getting into the actual life and experience of our consciousness. Meditation reveals how wonderful life could be. How free we could be. Meditation, and a simple ethical life, reveals the deep habits that have been a vital condition for evolutionary success: the single-minded urge for supremacy over other members of our own species; the survival of the fittest; of the quickest; of the strongest; of the randiest; the survival of the most cunning and selfish; of the best at supporting and promoting of oneself and one's kin; and, of course, the selfish exploitation of other species.

Probably all currently surviving species have been a condition in the extinction of all other competing or edible species. We are the first species to attempt to enforce fishing quotas and to limit our urges to hunt. Meditation and an ethical life increasingly reveals another possibility - a life beyond self-clinging beyond self-promotion - a life of empathy. Shantideva says, 'When fear and suffering are disliked by me and others equally, what is so special about me that I protect me and not the other.'

All of us need to respond to the suffering in the world. Are we going to respond more like an animal or more like a Buddha?

***


(Taken from this talk - ['Empty Cave: Reflections on Life, Practice and Enlightenment'](http://www.freebuddhistaudio.com/community/2013/04/20/empty-cave-reflections-on-life-practice-and-enlightenment/), by Saraha.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone read this book?- 'Confession of a Buddhist Atheist'. What do you think about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-04 00:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Stuart Mill - On Liberty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 18:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All of human history has led up to this moment. AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 02:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What to do with flat lager? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 04:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a house party the other day and have several opened but unfinished cans of lager that have gone flat. It seems wasteful to pour them down the drain. Does anyone have any suggestions as to what I should do with the lager? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jesus was a blood-thirsty terrorist. CMV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 15:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that the following passages prove that the figure of Jesus should be considered, using the language of today, **a blood-thirsty terrorist**:

* "But those enemies of mine who did not want me to be king over them  bring them here and kill them in front of me. (Luke 19:27 NIV)

* "He that is not with me is against me..." (Matthew 12:30 KJV)

* "Do not suppose that I have come to bring peace to the earth. I did not come to bring peace, but a sword." (Matthew 10:34 NIV)

I believe that were he simply an advocate of peace and 'turning the other cheek' it would be unlikely that the Romans would have scourged and crucified him. It is my view that he was most likely a perpetrator and advocate of violence, and that his subsequent portrayal as a pacifist is the result of historical revisionism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should 'WTF' be removed as a default Subreddit and be replaced with something more salutary? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 19:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Original Child Bomb by Thomas Merton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-28 20:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 30Giorni | The pact with the Serpent (by Massimo Borghesi) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 22:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You Suck!: Nancy Pelosi Booed, Heckled by Liberal Activists Over Snowden Comments | Video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-23 18:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Oxford Book of English Mystical Verse - Nicholson   Lee, eds. 1917. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-22 11:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McLibel leaflet was co-written by undercover police officer Bob Lambert | UK news </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 16:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC Radio 4 - Beyond Belief programmes - A good resource </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 19:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC Radio 4 - Beyond Belief programmes - A good resource </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 19:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to buy a book that translates the teachings of Jesus from Aramaic directly to English. Does anyone have any recommendations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 18:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are dairy cows happy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 07:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am getting into Buddhism, AMAA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 04:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ask Edward Snowden anything </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-17 17:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skyclad Christianity - What do people think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-17 06:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I believe that any proper Muslim must needs be a terrorist. CMV. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-17 02:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that belief in the divinity of Mohammed, and therefore the inviolability of the Qu'ran, is a central part of being a Muslim. In accordance with the fact that the Qu'ran instructs Muslims to ''wage war against the unbelievers'', ''cast terror into the unbelievers' hearts'', and ''forsake this world for the next'', becoming a terrorist is the logical outcome of being a Muslim. CMV.

EDIT: I have changed my view somewhat (see below). Thank you to everyone who contributed to the discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I no longer trust Google or Microsoft. Does anyone have recommendations for an email provider that offers a good degree of privacy/security? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 10:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have access to the Oxford English Dictionary. AMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-10 18:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On whistleblowers and government threats of investigation | Glenn Greenwald | Comment is free </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 20:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 24 years ago today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-05 19:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 24 years ago today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-05 19:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tory minister admitted on Question Time that the Snooper's Charter would be used to go after drug users. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-31 01:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Security services would have the power to know everyone who accesses UKTrees, for instance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any vegan book recommendations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 19:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Recipe books
* Nutrition books
* Books to persuade people about the merits of veganism
* Etc. etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (x-post from /r/eldertrees) The Latest Cannabis Discoveries That the Federal Government Doesnt Want You to Know About: Cancer, Diabetes, Crohn's, HIV, PTSD. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 16:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WEFUNK - Show Archive - What an excellent resource this is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-25 03:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Changing Face of Terrorism in Britain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 21:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What with all the 'hate crime' legislation, can anyone tell me what I can and can't legally say about Islam and Muslims in the UK? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 17:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Map of human rights of LGBT people in Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-17 13:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the poet Artaud said about opium in the 1920s is applicable to medical cannabis today, IMO. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-14 21:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mushnooms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-14 05:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Cornell West talks to Julian Assange about Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. and other subjects. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-14 05:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rousseau - On the Origin of Inequality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-14 04:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC Beyond Belief - Rastafari - Mon, 18 Feb 13 - Feauturing Tony Tafari, who is a member of the Rastafari Council of Britain; Dr Ellis Cashmore, Professor of Culture, Media and Sport at Staffordshire University; and Marzia Coltri, visiting Lecturer at the University of Wolverhampton. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 19:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is one of the most ridiculous things I've ever read. Genuine UK newspaper. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-12 11:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iFunk All Stars - Good To Your Earhole </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 17:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A list of ailments with symptoms and/or side effects that have been treated with medical marijuana. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 02:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iFunk All Stars - Good To Your Earhole (Funkadelic) live </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 17:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ANTI-BARDOLATRYTHROUGH THE AGES OR, WHY VOLTAIRE, TOLSTOY, SHAW, AND WITTGENSTEIN DIDNT LIKE SHAKESPEARE.  By Erin Sullivan Phd </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 02:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I. Shakespeare and the Value of Personality II. Shakespeare and the Value of Love HAROLD BLOOM THE TANNER LECTURES ON HUMAN VALUES </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 02:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] [image] Internet comic depicting everyone underestimating the loneliness of others and overestimating their own. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-02 22:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did people find Obama's joke about getting the munchies liberating or tasteless? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-28 13:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who haven't seen it: http://youtu.be/ON2XWvyePH8?t=8m6s

I'd be interested to know what everyone thinks. (It certainly isn't 'liberating' to those incarcerated). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama jokes about smoking weed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-28 12:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama tells cannabis joke. Tasteless or game-changing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-28 12:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think insects can experience happiness? If so, explain why. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-27 23:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was watching a moth pottering around. Do they live lives of constant fear? Or can they experience joy and happiness? Was wondering if it would be humane to squash it or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The EU is debating clamping down on seed selling. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 14:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This http://open-seeds.org/bad-seed-law/


I fear this will be bad news for the seedbanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just spreading the word about the medical benefits of the goodly herb </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 14:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Cannabis is a medically recognised treatment for the following ailments](https://www.marijuanadoctors.com/content/ailments/index): 

* Acquired Hypothyroidism
* Acute Gastritis 
* Agoraphobia
* AIDS Related Illness 
* Alcohol Abuse
* Alcoholism 
* Alopecia Areata 
* Alzheimer's Disease 
* Amphetamine Dependency 
* Amyloidosis
* Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis (ALS)
* Angina Pectoris 
* Ankylosis 
* Anorexia Nervosa
* Anxiety Disorders 
* Any chronic medical symptom that limits major life activities
* Arteriosclerotic Heart Disease 
* Arthritis (Rheumatoid) 
* Arthropathy, gout 
* Asthma 
* Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADD/ADHD) 
* Autism/Aspergers 
* Autoimmune Disease 
* Back Pain
* Back Sprain 
* Bell's Palsy 
* Bipolar Disorder
* Brain Tumour, Malignant 
* Bruxism 
* Bulimia 
* Cachexia
* Cancer 
* Cancer, Adrenal Cortical
* Cancer, Endometrial 
* Cancer, Prostate 
* Cancer, Testicular 
* Cancer, Uterine 
* Carpal Tunnel Syndrome 
* Cerebral Palsy 
* Cervical Disk Disease
* Cervicobrachial Syndrome
* Chemotherapy 
* Chronic Fatigue Syndrome
* Chronic Pain 
* Chronic renal failure 
* Cocaine Dependence 
* Colitis 
* Conjunctivitis 
* Constipation 
* Crohn's Disease 
* Cystic Fibrosis 
* Damage to Spinal Cord Nervous Tissue
* Darier's Disease 
* Degenerative Arthritis
* Degenerative Arthropathy 
* Delirium Tremens 
* Dermatomyositis 
* Diabetes, Adult Onset 
* Diabetes, Insulin Dependent 
* Diabetic Neuropathy 
* Diabetic Peripheral Vascular Disease 
* Diarrhea 
* Diverticulitis
* Dysthymic Disorder 
* Eczema 
* Emphysema 
* Endometriosis 
* Epidermolysis Bullosa 
* Epididymitis
* Epilepsy 
* Felty's Syndrome 
* Fibromyalgia 
* Friedreich's Ataxia 
* Gastritis 
* Genital Herpes
* Glaucoma 
* Glioblastoma Multiforme
* Graves Disease 
* Headaches, Cluster
* Headaches, Migraine 
* Headaches, Tension 
* Hemophilia A
* Henoch-Schonlein Purpura
* Hepatitis C 
* Hereditary Spinal Ataxia
* HIV/AIDS
* Hospice Patients
* Huntington's Disease
* Hypertension
* Hyperventilation 
* Hypoglycemia 
* Impotence 
* Inflammatory autoimmune-mediated arthritis
* Inflammatory Bowel Disease (IBD)
* Intermittent Explosive Disorder (IED)
* Intractable Pain
* Intractable Vomiting 
* Lipomatosis 
* Lou Gehrig's Disease 
* Lyme Disease
* Lymphoma 
* Major Depression
* Malignant Melanoma
* Mania
* Melorheostosis 
* Meniere's Disease
* Motion Sickness 
* Mucopolysaccharidosis (MPS)
* Multiple Sclerosis (MS) 
* Muscle Spasms
* Muscular Dystrophy
* Myeloid Leukemia
* Nail-Patella Syndrome
* Nightmares 
* Obesity
* Obsessive Compulsive Disorder 
* Opiate Dependence 
* Osteoarthritis
* Panic Disorder 
* Parkinson's Disease 
* Peripheral Neuropathy
* Peritoneal Pain
* Persistent Insomnia 
* Porphyria 
* Post Polio Syndrome (PPS) 
* Post-traumatic arthritis 
* Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD) 
* Premenstrual Syndrome (PMS) 
* Prostatitis
* Psoriasis
* Pulmonary Fibrosis 
* Quadriplegia
* Radiation Therapy 
* Raynaud's Disease
* Reiter's Syndrome
* Restless Legs Syndrome (RLS)
* Rheumatoid Arthritis
* Rosacea
* Schizoaffective Disorder
* Schizophrenia 
* Scoliosis
* Sedative Dependence
* Seizures 
* Senile Dementia
* Severe Nausea 
* Shingles (Herpes Zoster)
* Sinusitis 
* Skeletal Muscular Spasticity
* Sleep Apnea 
* Sleep Disorders 
* Spasticity 
* Spinal Stenosis 
* Sturge-Weber Syndrome (SWS)
* Stuttering 
* Tardive Dyskinesia (TD) 
* Temporomandibular joint disorder (TMJ) 
* Tenosynovitis
* Terminal Illness 
* Thyroiditis 
* Tic Douloureux
* Tietze's Syndrome
* Tinnitus 
* Tobacco Dependence 
* Tourette's Syndrome 
* Trichotillomania
* Viral Hepatitis 
* Wasting Syndrome 
* Whiplash 
* Wittmaack-Ekbom's Syndrome 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Posted this elsewhere today, but it bears repeating. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 11:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Cannabis is a medically recognised treatment for the following ailments](https://www.marijuanadoctors.com/content/ailments/index): 

* Acquired Hypothyroidism
* Acute Gastritis 
* Agoraphobia
* AIDS Related Illness 
* Alcohol Abuse
* Alcoholism 
* Alopecia Areata 
* Alzheimer's Disease 
* Amphetamine Dependency 
* Amyloidosis
* Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis (ALS)
* Angina Pectoris 
* Ankylosis 
* Anorexia Nervosa
* Anxiety Disorders 
* Any chronic medical symptom that limits major life activities
* Arteriosclerotic Heart Disease 
* Arthritis (Rheumatoid) 
* Arthropathy, gout 
* Asthma 
* Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADD/ADHD) 
* Autism/Aspergers 
* Autoimmune Disease 
* Back Pain
* Back Sprain 
* Bell's Palsy 
* Bipolar Disorder
* Brain Tumour, Malignant 
* Bruxism 
* Bulimia 
* Cachexia
* Cancer 
* Cancer, Adrenal Cortical
* Cancer, Endometrial 
* Cancer, Prostate 
* Cancer, Testicular 
* Cancer, Uterine 
* Carpal Tunnel Syndrome 
* Cerebral Palsy 
* Cervical Disk Disease
* Cervicobrachial Syndrome
* Chemotherapy 
* Chronic Fatigue Syndrome
* Chronic Pain 
* Chronic renal failure 
* Cocaine Dependence 
* Colitis 
* Conjunctivitis 
* Constipation 
* Crohn's Disease 
* Cystic Fibrosis 
* Damage to Spinal Cord Nervous Tissue
* Darier's Disease 
* Degenerative Arthritis
* Degenerative Arthropathy 
* Delirium Tremens 
* Dermatomyositis 
* Diabetes, Adult Onset 
* Diabetes, Insulin Dependent 
* Diabetic Neuropathy 
* Diabetic Peripheral Vascular Disease 
* Diarrhea 
* Diverticulitis
* Dysthymic Disorder 
* Eczema 
* Emphysema 
* Endometriosis 
* Epidermolysis Bullosa 
* Epididymitis
* Epilepsy 
* Felty's Syndrome 
* Fibromyalgia 
* Friedreich's Ataxia 
* Gastritis 
* Genital Herpes
* Glaucoma 
* Glioblastoma Multiforme
* Graves Disease 
* Headaches, Cluster
* Headaches, Migraine 
* Headaches, Tension 
* Hemophilia A
* Henoch-Schonlein Purpura
* Hepatitis C 
* Hereditary Spinal Ataxia
* HIV/AIDS
* Hospice Patients
* Huntington's Disease
* Hypertension
* Hyperventilation 
* Hypoglycemia 
* Impotence 
* Inflammatory autoimmune-mediated arthritis
* Inflammatory Bowel Disease (IBD)
* Intermittent Explosive Disorder (IED)
* Intractable Pain
* Intractable Vomiting 
* Lipomatosis 
* Lou Gehrig's Disease 
* Lyme Disease
* Lymphoma 
* Major Depression
* Malignant Melanoma
* Mania
* Melorheostosis 
* Meniere's Disease
* Motion Sickness 
* Mucopolysaccharidosis (MPS)
* Multiple Sclerosis (MS) 
* Muscle Spasms
* Muscular Dystrophy
* Myeloid Leukemia
* Nail-Patella Syndrome
* Nightmares 
* Obesity
* Obsessive Compulsive Disorder 
* Opiate Dependence 
* Osteoarthritis
* Panic Disorder 
* Parkinson's Disease 
* Peripheral Neuropathy
* Peritoneal Pain
* Persistent Insomnia 
* Porphyria 
* Post Polio Syndrome (PPS) 
* Post-traumatic arthritis 
* Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD) 
* Premenstrual Syndrome (PMS) 
* Prostatitis
* Psoriasis
* Pulmonary Fibrosis 
* Quadriplegia
* Radiation Therapy 
* Raynaud's Disease
* Reiter's Syndrome
* Restless Legs Syndrome (RLS)
* Rheumatoid Arthritis
* Rosacea
* Schizoaffective Disorder
* Schizophrenia 
* Scoliosis
* Sedative Dependence
* Seizures 
* Senile Dementia
* Severe Nausea 
* Shingles (Herpes Zoster)
* Sinusitis 
* Skeletal Muscular Spasticity
* Sleep Apnea 
* Sleep Disorders 
* Spasticity 
* Spinal Stenosis 
* Sturge-Weber Syndrome (SWS)
* Stuttering 
* Tardive Dyskinesia (TD) 
* Temporomandibular joint disorder (TMJ) 
* Tenosynovitis
* Terminal Illness 
* Thyroiditis 
* Tic Douloureux
* Tietze's Syndrome
* Tinnitus 
* Tobacco Dependence 
* Tourette's Syndrome 
* Trichotillomania
* Viral Hepatitis 
* Wasting Syndrome 
* Whiplash 
* Wittmaack-Ekbom's Syndrome 
* Writers' Cramp 


That represents a lot of people worldwide whose suffering could be reduced if cannabis was legalised.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] [song] What is this song that Nile Rodgers is playing? It sounds so familiar. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-23 01:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one starting at [02:35](http://youtu.be/VVmAXWZu_PQ?t=2m35s ). It sounds so nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I read this just now: 'In every single hot war in the world, at least one of the belligerents is identified as Muslim'. Is it true? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 09:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (UK only) BBC iPlayer - Isaac Newton: The Last Magician [VIDEO] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 00:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (UK only) So beautiful to watch when stoned: Isaac Newton - The Last Magician </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 00:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't let them fool you into thinking that Thatcher was a 'friend of freedom and equality'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 21:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Los Angeles Review of Books - Doctor Who And The New British Empire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 08:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Los Angeles Review of Books - Doctor Who And The New British Empire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 08:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did anybody hear this Andrew Neil anecdote? Real insight into the way Thatcher thought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 07:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sinad O'Connor - Black Boys On Mopeds (my favourite Thatcher protest-song) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 22:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remember the spirit of festival! Don't let Thatcher win! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 20:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Margaret Thatcher, a controversial figure on gay issues, dies aged 87 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 18:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Human rights campaigner Peter Tatchell commented on the passing of Baroness Thatcher, saying she was extraordinary for mostly the wrong reasons, but going on to say: I dont rejoice in her death. I commiserate, as I do with the death of any person.

He continued: In 1988, the Thatcher government legislated Britains first new anti-gay law in 100 years: Section 28. At the 1987 Conservative party conference she mocked people who defended the right to be gay, insinuating that there was no such right.

During her rule, arrests and convictions for consenting same-sex behaviour rocketed, as did queer bashing violence and murder. Gay men were widely demonised and scapegoated for the AIDS pandemic and Thatcher did nothing to challenge this vilification.

http://www.pinknews.co.uk/2013/04/08/margaret-thatcher-a-controversial-figure-in-gay-rights-dies-aged-87/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now that Thatcher's dead, can we try and return to the free festival culture of old? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 17:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey, do you mind if I tell you a story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 19:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey, do you mind if I tell you a story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 19:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you mind if I tell you a story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 18:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biblical Entheogens: a Speculative Hypothesis. (by Benny Shanon, Professor of psychology at the Hebrew University of Jerusalem) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 12:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biblical Entheogens: a Speculative Hypothesis. (by Benny Shanon, Professor of psychology at the Hebrew University of Jerusalem) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 12:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biblical Entheogens: a Speculative Hypothesis. (by Benny Shanon, Professor of psychology at the Hebrew University of Jerusalem) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 22:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Robbie Williams worked as a double glazing salesman before joining Take That. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 00:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Chrome - Now with added Bob Marley </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 00:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cannabis is a medicine and a nutrient </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 11:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can watch all of this documentary on modern history when stoned. So good. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-03 11:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Winning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 06:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is beautiful - Visualization of the endocannabinoid signalling system. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 16:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legalising drugs would be the perfect Tory policy | Ian Birrell | Comment is free </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 09:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not long left to watch 'The House I Live In' on the iPlayer. 'Best war on drugs' documentary I have seen. Must see. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 07:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Local band released this song about Mary Jane. Really quite good. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 04:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stuff like this is heartening </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 01:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just noticed that a friend of mine's mother who's a policewoman tweeted about 'The House I Live In'. Spreading those enlightened ideas is so important. http://www.bbc.co.uk/iplayer/episode/b01pzz69/Storyville_20122013_The_House_I_Live_In/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carl Sagan on trees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-24 06:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today, the love of cannabis is 'the love that dare not speak its name'. Short clip of Oscar Wilde's trial with Stephen Fry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 22:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'The love that dare not speak its name' - today this applies to our love of cannabis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 21:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Bhutan, young men are sent away for three years to meditate and smoke weed. That should be instated here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-17 00:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Caroline Lucas launches petition on drug policy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 11:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please sign Caroline Lucas' e-petition for an impact assessment of the Misuse of Drugs Act. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 11:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
