<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject765</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 02:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vine: Me eating a do- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-29 16:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is for soreness after you run. Fermentation is not an immediate process, it takes time. Lactic acid is a side product of fermentation. If you really want to rid yourself of being sore, stretch. It won't get rid of the pain but it will spread the lactic acid out throughout your body and you will feel it less.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 18:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GLaDOS: "There was even going to be a party for you. A big party that all your friends were invited to. I invited your best friend, the Companion Cube. Of course, he couldn't come because you murdered him. All your other friends couldn't come, either, because you don't have any other friends because of how unlikable you are. It says so right here in your personnel file: "Unlikable. Liked by no one. A bitter, unlikable loner, whose passing shall not be mourned. Shall NOT be mourned." That's exactly what it says. Very formal. Very official. It also says you were adopted, so that's funny, too."

Portal- One of the greatest video games of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 23:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Male Nipples  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 03:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rob Schneider  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 03:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are two white doors, one the door the heaven, one is the door to hell. Once you open you may never go back. Connected to each door is a machine. One tells nothing but truths, the other nothing but lies. You do not know which is which. You have one question to find out the answer. What do you ask?




ANSWER:
"What would the other machine say is the door to heaven?"
and do the opposite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 08:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was that a pun you sly bastard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 08:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a teacher but another kid in elementary school went on for about 5 minutes about his brother's wet dreams. Didn't really know what they were at the time, all I remember was the vivid hysterical laughter of the teacher as she ran out of the classroom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 07:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 06:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dad pulled this one one me yesterday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 08:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dad: "What does IDK stand for?"

Me: "I don't know."

Dad: "It's fine, I'll ask someone else."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 06:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Boys don't have feelings, they have muscles!"
Homer Simpson

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 23:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL Christopher Columbus never stepped foot in North America.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 16:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No fat chicks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 03:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR: Leonardo Dicaprio confuses you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 06:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get on a ROUTINE. Not just a weekend workout. Plan them out, Monday arms, Tuesday legs, Wednesday cardio ect. Tell yourself NO EXCUSES! NONE! DON'T CARE! Stick it out and you will learn to love it. There are thousands of at home workout routines you can do that will work. No "Six Minute Six Pack Tricks". Run, squat, sit-ups, pull-ups push-ups the list is endless. And That sip of water after a workout will be sweeter than any soda or Gatorade you will ever drink. If you do this you will experience a boost in strength, confidence, and overall happiness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 06:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screw you! Segways are sick. :[ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 06:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YouTube
NO I DON'T WANT TO USE MY GOOGLE+ ACOUNT!!!!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 06:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saying the phrase "May I have a cookie?" I asked a woman for a cookie at my son's birthday party. Got the most puzzled look ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 17:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whack it while you still can </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Northern California Ski Resort </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 06:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are men attracted to breasts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 06:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All straight men can agree we have a natural desire for the female breast, why? They are not a reproductive organ and only real purpose is to breast feed. Is it just something to play with or is it just something we have all agreed to be attractive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think my mom is an undercover dad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 08:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me: Mom, can I have a tissue?

Mom: Kiss you?! I hardly know you!

*Proceeds to chuckle to herself over a well executed joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [50/50] Smash Mouth or smashed mouth (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 19:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [50/50] Smash Mouth or smashed mouth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 18:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smash Mouth or smashed mouth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 09:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 08:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was around 3 I would hold out my penis and pretend to play it like a guitar. 

Just never found the right time to mention that.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 08:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Malaria has killed over half of the humans that have ever lived. (Approximately 50 billion)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 06:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You cracked the case Shercock! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 00:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pants -.- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 22:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> youuuuu....you are just...........ooooooh you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did the hat say to the other hat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 04:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I am a hat" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody else think we should kill cancer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 21:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do gay horses eat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-16 06:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The diet of a gay horse does not differ from that of a straight horse. That being said it is uncommon for two male or two female horse to be sexually attracted to each other, as it goes against their genetic drive to reproduce. The usual farm diet of a horse can be split into two parts: structural (fiber) and non structural (sugars and starches). Naturally the horse needs complete access to a fresh water source and an open plain. 

The following article should have sufficient information for those looking into the proper diet and nutrition for their horse:
http://www.caes.uga.edu/publications/pubDetail.cfm?pk_ID=7824 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-16 06:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly the best anti joke I've heard. I tip my hat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 03:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who knew Skyler and Jessie had a thing together?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-29 23:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing missing is Brian Cranston and Stephen Colbert roller skating to Daft Punk.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-21 00:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the number one tip you can give a high school freshman about wrestling from your experience? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 17:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So detached from your mother have you ever felt a real connection to one of your 7 step dads?
You are an extremely strong person for being able to talk about this.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
