<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7762</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 04:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take it you don't eat junk food then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 03:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black holes are the buttholes of the universe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 00:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't rape the messenger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 23:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lies! OP said 2 cute girls. I only see 1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 20:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Left over chicken soup + pizza. Reddit,you failed me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 02:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Destiny. One of the most boring games I've played.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 01:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This deserves more up votes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 01:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When they were your age the economy was stronger and the cost of living was lower.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 20:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Areola grande </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will eating 2 dozen eggs in 1 sitting hurt you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 00:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 18:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I agree that you get what you pay for (your example of the $50 dollar dj), I don't see the reason for the vinyl supremacy.  

It doesn't matter what medium you store your music on, there are talented djs in all facets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 18:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biscuit in the US is basically a baked roll of bread.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 07:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dildo blades </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 06:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So did you fry it or bake it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 01:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $98.50 daily for me. Living in Orange County CA. Lol! It's damn expensive here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 01:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See the link for more info :)

http://www.ssa.gov/survivorplan/survivors.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 22:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on your diet but if you're on a ketogenic diet,  I find that hunger is not a huge issue. 

The ketogenic diet trades out your dependency on carbs and forces your body to use fats for energy.  I eat foods high in fat and stay away from carbs. I find that hunger strikes less often and I can go longer between meals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 20:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Social worker here. You and your siblings may be entitled to survivor's benefits from the government. It should be a few hundred dollars a month for each person. Get in contact with your local social services agency.  I'm sorry for your loss.

EDIT: posting link for survivors benefits site. 

 http://www.ssa.gov/survivorplan/survivors.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 20:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I AM that guy so I always end up censoring my interesting fact and go with something more mundane,  like hiking ( which I don't actually do). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 17:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wash my ass after shits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 17:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did OP just watch human centipede recently? Or more shocking, OP is researching to see if s/he can make a human centipede. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 16:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume you're talking about your computer not WIRELESSLY connecting to your router. I'm going to state the obvious, but have you checked to see that you didn't accidentally turn off the WiFi on your laptop? 

If that's not the case then I suggest connecting the computer directly to your router using the LAN cable (in order to access the internet) and downloading the wireless driver from the hp website and try reinstalling it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 08:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You never go full retard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 08:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Headphones, my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 08:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just yours, but everyone's. Have you read the book Sperm Wars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 08:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every pack is a family pack if you put it on wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 21:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My small penis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 21:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It had to be said lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 01:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liege waffle is king! Other than that, I prefer a triple stack of pancakes, of which I will eat 1/12 of it and discard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 01:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who love Apple </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 01:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who poop on me while I'm eating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 01:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Green glowing antifreeze </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 00:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I should have elaborated. I work at a fed agency. I clicked a link on reddit and it logged it into my system as porn. Which it was not btw :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 23:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just guessing but I think it has to do with your saliva breaking down the structural bonds of the gum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 22:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree, I just got done reading about black holes and quantum physics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 22:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well at least you're spending that quality time with your father that you've always been missing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 22:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Communication is key. I just come to an agreement that works for both parties. It's nice to talk to each other sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 22:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was old enough to realize that the teachings I was receiving in bible class were hard to believe. Upon questioning them I was only given circular arguments which basically boiled down to, "we are adults and we know more than you, so listen to us."

In my middle school years I learned more about history. I learned about how past civilizations had gods for things in nature that they didn't understand and couldn't explain (Roman god of the sun, etc.) We look back on it now and think they were silly for having a god if the sun or god of the sea, yet we (organized religion) have a god that created the universe, since we can't explain that (yet).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 22:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, anything that breaks the ice, leading to conversation is always a good start.

I wouldn't say it was the most effective way to pick up girls; that's entirely up to how well the resulting conversation goes combined with her actual interest in you.

They were a good ice breaker is what you meant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 20:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotcha :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 20:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article states that he was not in the same town at the time she claimed the rape occurred. She blatantly told a lie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 18:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's already been proven that he is not guilty then why isn't the accuser instantly punished? You get punished for falsely screaming "fire" in a crowded building. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 18:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Masturbate furiously. Or alternatively, I listen to music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 18:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I clicked on a reddit link and got flagged for porn. Now it's logged into the browsing history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 18:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bed full of lesbians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 17:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say the latter, since it is widely accepted that the light that we see from stars occurred eons ago. Therefore, the present is not observable while it is happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 17:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather not be famous and dead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 02:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but he got killed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 02:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you wish for a lawyer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 02:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do we ever really live in the present? Everything we see, feel, hear or sense has to go to our brains and then be processed. Even though it takes milliseconds to process, we are never truly experiencing "the present."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 02:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "When I was 4 years old, I started walking. When I was younger, I could not walk." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 02:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why were you thinking about penises in the shower? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 02:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /end thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 01:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed, signing a check does increase the paper that it's on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 21:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neelix doesn't look like he enjoys performing as a DJ and his style of music is very progressive. It's great for listening to at a desk but at a festival it's boring, for lack of a better word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 21:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really depends on the crowd and what he "thinks" the crowd is receptive to. I was at a private show he did in Hollywood last weekend and he stated that he was playing a Perfecto Dark set but the crowd was a bunch of hipsters who barely even knew who he was. 

Only about 3 tracks in, he started to progressively get more mainstream with a more "pop" sound. The last song, all the hipsters jumped up and sang along to. I had no idea what song it was. So as a DJ he completed his job to get the party going, but I can't say I enjoyed his set much.

TL;DR He will play what the crowd is receptive to, whether it be pop or more underground. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 21:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might try looking into minimal techno or minimal trance. Although when you mention "slow, darker" trance in your title, I'm inclined to think progressive psytrance, but that's just me haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 20:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously drinking more. Also I like to DJ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 20:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make myself owner of Earth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 20:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At speeling correctly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 20:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try not to associate with people who cannot keep commitments. Either that or very harshly ridicule them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 20:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hitler's ghost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 20:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 - The first computer to pass the Turing test.

Already happened [here](http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/computer-becomes-first-to-pass-turing-test-in-artificial-intelligence-milestone-but-academics-warn-of-dangerous-future-9508370.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 21:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're at a psytrance party, then the people who came want to listen to psytrance. I hate it when they put artists who play radically different styles back to back at a festival. It really breaks up the musical flow of the night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 19:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What record pool and what genre is most prominent in it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 07:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, hold on. "Forced to fuck?" That's the definition of rape. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
