<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject898</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some of you might now appreciate this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 10:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overly Manly Man makes pizzas better than Poppa John </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 10:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When a girl asked if I brought a rubber </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 09:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Like a fat kid love cake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 08:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This would've helped Romney win... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-12 10:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What my friend said as we watched Ellen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-12 10:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first image that would pop up if Reddit held a "2 minutes of hate" rally  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-11 14:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every time I wake up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-08 18:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When my dog licks my plate and leaves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-08 00:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ever since my first election day, my dad has taken me out back to the shed to discuss the issues. then, once forced to agree, we always vote together. what are some of your meaningful election day traditions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 09:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fartney 2012 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any documented cases where companies payoff game review sites?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 01:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched the IGN review of Halo 4, and never have I ever seen such incredible amounts of ass kissing in my life. The reviewer was literally embarrassing to listen to because he acted like he was blown away and was about as bad at acting as the new Master Chief voice actor. I own Halo 4 and aside from graphics, the gameplay is identical to previous iterations. Nothing about it should appeal Halo fans who actually want the series to progress, because sadly, it has not. So, I ask you, do you think these reviewers get paid to say nice things?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do we start a revolution? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 01:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We obviously know that our country is fucked and ran by a bunch of rich faggots. Our two party system is the biggest joke in the world and half our population stands by idly and bickers about Obama and Romney. I'm sick of just reading about how screwed up everything is, I'm ready to do something about it. What do we do? How do we give this country back to its people? It's obviously not gonna start at the ballot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad Luck Brian celebrates his birthday on Facebook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 03:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can people make it to Heaven through Love alone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-04 23:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sudden Realization Romney </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-03 21:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one who thinks this scale is off? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-02 18:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> http://turntable.fm/ambient_chillout_trip_hop2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-02 17:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would hope everyone is aware of this website </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lemme learn ya sumtin' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-02 17:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every time I watch those Jack Link's beef jerky commercials  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-02 08:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI 5 - Why does the media always act like there are only ever 2 presidential candidates every election?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-02 00:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't they talk about the 3rd party candidates? They seem more preferable to me than Romney or Obama anyway. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do hurricanes usually form near the Eastern side of the United States? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-02 00:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It always seems like they form near Florida, respectively. But Y NO South Cali??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it bad for a Christian to date a non-Christian? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-31 07:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tonight I met someone who was beautiful, nice, had a good sense of humor and was just generally everything I was looking for. We then somehow got onto the topic of Religion and I expressed my faith in Jesus and she expressed that she is "Spiritual". It didn't end in argument, and it allowed me to share my testimony, etc. Fortunately, it didn't make things weird or anything. I would just like some advice from Christians if this would be wise to pursue if the possibility presented itself. I know what the answers are going to be, so please, help me to understand, because this person seems to be something special that doesn't come along very often. Thank you. 

EDIT: apparently she has a boyfriend. sweet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As I read the replies to the top comment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-30 09:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do people think of the multipayer kills in Halo 4? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 23:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find if the kills in a multiplayer game get repetitive, the entire game gets old very fast. What do you guys think of the kills and rag doll thus far? Also, what kinds of things are deal breakers for you and a new game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wondering Dory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 04:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He knows the best ways to get ahead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 04:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ...Moving on </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 04:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else think Yoshimi Battles the Pink Robots (album, by) - The Flaming Lips , reminds them of Earth Bound? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-25 21:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone else sick of Death Animations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-25 10:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the advent of rag doll, and Euphoria physics used in games like GTA, and Backbreaker, why don't more games shy away from rehashed and reused death animations that make kills in games like Halo and CoD less satisfying and more repetitive? 

I play a shooter to have fun killing things, not see the same thing over and over again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dane. Cook.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-25 01:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think about this during every debate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-24 21:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> REQUEST - H.P. Lovecraft inspired artwork </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-23 09:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always loved the atmosphere Lovecraft creates with his description of entering tombs, down spiral stair cases with no light except a torch. Or the insanity that is instilled through the rising of Cthulu. Anything from his stories would be fantastic. Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What things pissed you off when they probably shouldn't have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-22 08:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll start. 

I remember when the "Passion of the Christ" came out and hearing somebody say, "The Pope came forward today and has declared after viewing 'the Passion' that, 'It is, as it was' ". 

That pissed me off because, since when is the Pope the king of God?

Then I realized that a lot of the Catholics viewing this movie would have trusted the Pope's opinion. But that still doesn't make sense to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What she said every time I wanted to buy the new Halo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-22 07:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> list the most common sites you visit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-22 06:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I visit, gmail; facebook; turntable.fm; ign; youtube; youjizz; and a few other lame sites. What are your most common? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does he look like a bish? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-21 06:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does he look like a bish? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-21 06:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Hipster Anthem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-19 21:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brian gets a text </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-19 01:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brian's feeling naughty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-19 01:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evil Josh Romney </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-18 10:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're on your way to big time, Ron </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-18 09:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're on your way to big time, Ron </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-18 09:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What I just realized about comment threads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-18 08:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newest Shock Video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-17 11:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it easier to communicate if you're deaf? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-17 09:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there truth to the Bible saying humans can live to be 120? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 22:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does it feel like to get eaten by a shark? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 01:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just curious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The Derby Girls" - roller derby documentary! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-07 19:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just want to be the first to say...FUCK VALVE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 22:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After two months since the release of Counter Strike: Global Offensive on Xbox, there is still not a single patch or update that allows you to actually play with your friends. What the fuck is the point of buying the game!? Go fuck yourself Gabe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kitty Jesus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-02 09:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 98 Nissan Maxima Crankshaft Pully (cost to fix?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-29 01:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any ideas on how much the part and cost of labor would turn out to be? 
I live in PA if that matters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every time I go out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-24 20:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone seen real life MIRACLES done in the name of Jesus? please share </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-23 05:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please be honest. I think some real life stories of healing, and other amazing experiences through God would bring great joy and increased faith to everyone here :)

EDIT: Thanks for all the stories and experiences, and I pray everyone has been strengthened in their faith through reading them. Keep em' coming! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [sci-fi] The Traveling Planet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-10 05:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A colossal planetary orb overlooks our home. Nearly at the climax of its Kiss with the rock we call Earth. Some of the most amazing shades of blue you'll ever see. Colors you don't find here. Colors artists attempt, and fail to replicate. It only peaks every 68 years, but you can always see it coming months in advance. A new star in the sky at first, then within half a year's time, the harvest moon dawns forth its peak. Some call it our planet's passing lover, some call it the thief, because it always drags our moon with it for a time before gravity can set itself right - which it always does. But when it does come, its always an exciting time here. The world seems to come together for nearly a year in the common endeavor to appreciate what some hold as God's passing eye. It pushes the rain away from certain areas, and you always know it's closest when the clouds gather and the water just won't stop falling. And then comes the twilit days and shadowless nights. By the time the sun hits noon, the sky is eclipsed, and the blue hues don't miss anything after sun down. It truly is an experience that all should share in at least one lifetime.

Sheel and I laid under the aquatic nightlight, atop our favorite get away spot overlooking our village - Of which was celebrating Peak Banquet. The festival lights gave illusion that the night's excitement was nearly at its apex, paralleling the sapphire that penetrated our night. I felt almost invigorated by the energy the blue bulb in the sky was giving off. And when we got away from all the noise, its song can be heard through energetic vibrations that hum only soft enough for those who listen closely - those who seek to hear. And as we laid there, holding hands, I could feel the vastness of the cosmic sphere reverberating through us both, nearly enhancing through our physical connection.

"They say it's getting closer, you know", Sheel gently let out. In my near hypnosis, I nearly missed what she'd said.

"Ah... You don't buy into that Collision Course fear do you?" I rattled off in nearly the same words I've heard from my parents time and time again. She paused for a long while, her eyes reflecting equally beautiful seas of blue back at the monster in the sky.

"I don't know...my father's been doing a lot of work at the observatory lately, and he says...something's changed." Her gaze never broke from the atmosphere, and I had no words to say. "He says at this rate, this might be the last cycle before...The Event. Silence filled the air as what she said began to pass over me. Fireworks could be seen popping and fading in sparkling reds and yellows near village square. The irony of it all nearly brought a smile to my face. We laid there quietly, looking directly at what some held in highest form of natural phenomenon and beauty, and by the same means, could very well bring about our end. But the fear, the fear had not over taken me. I knew I was exactly where I was suppose to be. Sheel grasped my hand even tighter, we looked into each others' eyes, and all I could hear was that gentle hum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> nigga from green mile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 06:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Redditors, are you a SHOWER or a GROWER? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 05:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey married Redditors, is getting married worth it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 06:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Traveling Planet - A Years Kiss (Short Story) [leave thoughts/comment :) ] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-02 21:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to identify a tool on campus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 22:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All I see on campus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 22:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Romney called Obama, "A monkey". Obama proceeded to throw shit at Romney at which point a 16 yr old, neck bearded, atheist Redditor jumped up and ate it.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 20:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> here's a .gif  

EDIT: annnnd....it's gone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Natalie Portman dislocated her rib during production of Black Swan and discovered that the film's budget was so low they couldn't afford a medic. The actress gave up her own personal lunch-time helicopter trips to McDonalds so one could be hired.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 18:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She even munched Mila Kunis' rug pro bono

EDIT: pro boner  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Failed my NCLEX again... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 16:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Failed it for the second time. Did 100 Questions a day for a month and a half - KAPLAN online resources.  Not sure how to approach it this time around. For those who passed, please explain to me the specific manner in which you went about studying so I can emulate that and also pass. Thanks :) also pray for me if you could.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just took NCLEX for 2nd time. Had some questions.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 21:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> took it today 8/30/12  0800-1245

-Got 245 Questions
-Finished the test on a Multiple Answer Question (not sure if I got it right, also not sure if that's a positive sign)
-got quite a few multiple answer questions, probably around 10-15 (still not sure if thats a good thing, but i hear those are higher end questions)
-only got 3 dosage calc out of 245 (which I hear the less dosage calc, the better)

Overall the test was really hard, but i feel i knew more than I did the first time (still not much lol). Was just looking for thoughts, ideas and support. :)

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds, "about four-thirds of all Redditors love Mitt Romney" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 15:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> blah blah blah America blah blah blah Fall of the Roman Empire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-26 02:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweden </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deltron 3030 album cover - Dan the Automator  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-25 16:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Odd Space V1 - DISENT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 18:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We should add our own mini stories to go along with these awesome landscapes! :D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 13:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What time does Counter Strike: Global Offensive release for Xbox Arcade/PSN?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 23:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kettel   Secede - When Can (flavors august 12 mix) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 05:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today I fucked up... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-19 00:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lopped off my dick with less-than-average sharp scissors.

And then I buried my sleeping 3 day old infant underground. I doubt she's woken up yet. 

EDIT: don't tell mom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone on Reddit ever talk BAD about Obama? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 07:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I see on Reddit is negative statements about Romney, which I understand. But, why nothing about Obama? Why does this site lean so far left that it seems almost to refuse to give any sort of basic criticism to our current president? You would think, even by chance, that at least a few articles would make it to the front page once and a while. Am I the only one who notices this bias?... 

EDIT: Since I have you all here, I will now proceed to revealing that Satan runs this world, and dominates both the democratic and republican parties you all hold so dear. He is currently perverting the Jewish Zionists to use their endless stream of finances to rule everything you thought was for you: MEDIA, MILITARY, BANKS, and of course POLITICS. 

OBAMA is a shill, no different than BUSH and you all will live to see World War III. 9/11 was an inside job. Get off your knees and fight back 

RON PAUL 2012 - or Gary Johnson if we have to...sigh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody on here ever talk BAD about Obama?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 07:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I see on Reddit is negative statements about Romney, which I understand. But, why nothing about Obama? Why does this site lean so far left that it seems almost to refuse to give any sort of basic criticism to our current president? You would think, even by chance, that at least a few articles would make it to the front page once and a while. Am I the only one who notices this bias?...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/Atheism's Ten Commandments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-14 07:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad Luck Brian feels shifty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-12 10:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This cracks me up every time (Starship Troopers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 08:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your parents are right, modern music is getting louder and more repetitive  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-08 08:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most horribly insensitive, crap propaganda you'll watch all week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 10:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Acceptance of Homosexuality in Christianity - A legit answer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-01 09:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lost appreciation for games - NEED HELP/IDEAS! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-01 02:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lately, every game i play i feel bored and as if i've played it already. I was hoping /r/gaming could point me in the direction of a game they've loved oh so much, but maybe not many people played it. Something different, like Shadow of the Colossus. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I buy a history book made pre-1950?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-30 14:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link; Cost?

 I'm just curious to see the differences between history books written at earlier times in the previous century. Thank you Reddit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question, if Ron Paul doesn't win?.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-28 20:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if Ron Paul doesn't win the nomination/presidency? Do we just wait for all the DoomPaul memes to come true and embrace the end of the world or...? What's the plan? Because I don't see much hope without his truth and honesty in office.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Obama, John would like to have a word with you... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-26 05:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Obama, John would like to have a word with you... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-26 05:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House easily approves Paul's 'audit the Fed' bill in 327-98 vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-25 21:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nintendo Synthesis - the future of handheld gaming (fan fiction/comedy) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-24 22:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nintendo Synthesis - the future of handheld gaming (fan fiction/comedy) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-24 08:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Year: 2064

Grandpa walks into the living room to see his 6 year old grandson is laughing, laying prone in front of some sort of handheld gaming device while his
eyes are in REM. (Rapid Eye Movement)

"Hey buddy whaddya playin there?", asks grandpa looking at his grandson in confusion


Grandson quickly comes out of his REM and looks at his grandpa cheerfully and replies, "My Nintendo Synfesis Gwandpa!" With a lisp :) (Nintendo Synthesis)


Grandpa's confusion quickly subsides with a smile of relief and replies, "ohhh, Nintendo? Shoot, I used to have a 
Game Boy back in the day. Played the heck outta that thing"


"Grandpaaaa, dis isn't da same as a silwy Game Boyy", Grandson says laughingly annoyed.


"Whaddya talkin' abouuut? Lemme see that thing", retorts grandpa with confidence.


"We can pway together!" Excitedly replies grandson. Grandson proceeds to hand grandpa another one of the devices.
The device is merely a 3x3in rectangular chrome device with a rounded spherical bottom. Similar to a three dimensional ellipse 
divided in half with central a flat surface. 

Grandpa examines it oddly, looking on all sides, "Where's the D-Pad?...How do I turn this thing on?"


Giggling, grandson exclaims, "You just have to holwd it with boff hands gwandpaaa"


"Oh, okay", grandpa says as he places both hands on the device, "What're we even 'playing' anyway?"


"Caww of Duty: Stormfront!", excitedly replies grandson as he quickly gets comfortable and places both hands on the device,
at which point you begin to hear a low binaural beat begin to build within the system and slowly growing louder.


"Well CoD's kinda gay -- but What the heck is that sound?", asks grandpa in confusion.


"It's startin' up Gwandpa", replies grandson with a big innocent smile.


As the noise begins to grow grandpa's mind begins to wonder into nostalgic memories, "Oh...well you know when I was your age,
I would play Pokemon none stop. I swear, I had the best line-up ever. My Dragonite was level 100 -- " Suddenly,
within the blink of an eye grandpa is transported to a drop ship transport about to land in the middle of a barren planet war zone. He looks around 
in frantic fear and confusion, seeing he is surrounded by a dozen other future soldiers preparing to fight. Everyone is strapped into their seats with
metal chest harnesses, wearing futuristic black and grey military protective equipment and wielding heavy assault rifles. The ship is severely turbulent 
as it draws nearer to the surface of the battle. "What the hell is happening!? Where am I?!!!", cries Grandpa
to all of the nameless soldiers he is seated next to. All of which seem have their wits about them.


"Private! Get your shit together! Now is not the time to lose it!", commands what appears to be the Sergent of the ship's unit.


Grandpa is shocked in fear facing the Sergent, who returns his body to the upright position of his harnessed seat while someone next to grandpa gestures
the Catholic cross across their chest as they kiss their Christian pendant. Grandson then reveals his smiling face and waves "Hi, gwandpaaa!", says grandson
with cheer.


"Oh my God! What the hell is happeningggg!!!??" screams grandpa.


"We got to take the Cwompound, gwandpa" replies grandson as he rocks his head from side to side joyfully.


"What!!? What the hell are you talking about? What is this!!?, exclaims grandpa in utter fear and calamity.


"Just fowwow me grandpa!" laughs grandson as the ship comes to a sudden halt. 


"OhGodFUCK! What is hap-!" grandpa is screaming as The harnesses suddenly rise, and the side hatch of this ship immediately burst open. The noise quickly grows ten-fold, with near by explosions and dust flying so thick that its barely visible to see more than 20 feet in front of oneself.

"Alright Men! Into eternity we fly!" shouts the Sergent as he throws his hand forward giving the command to charge. Large amounts of similar ships can be 
seen landing, and leaving near their drop zone.The terrain is virtually flat as the dust bowl continues to fog any view besides what lies ahead.
 Hundreds of soldiers are running into the clouds of fog. 
Many of which are being mowed down by continued chain
gun fire and blown to pieces by explosions and artillery. 

Grandpa, standing in the haul doorway of the drop ship stares in disbelief at what he is witnessing when suddenly he feels quick jab to his
right leg and a grab
at his hand from grandson exclaiming, "Come on gwandpa, follow meeee". Grandson begins to run haphazardly into the fray of smoke.

"Wait! NO!" Grandpa yells as he suddenly becomes aware of his grandson sprinting into a firefight. Grandpa proceeds to sprint after him. As he runs blindly in grandson's last known direction,
all he can see is random soldiers faces gliding with him in his run as well as the amount of vigor and strength he now has that was not previously existent in his normal body's elder state. 
This revelation is quickly forgotten as nearly as soon as he sees more soldiers passing by him in the haze, they are quickly swept down by bursts and flashes of light and blasts from
whistling bombs from above. Dirt and debris began to soil grandpa's clothing.
A sudden cut back to grandpa and grandson in the living room shows both of them experiencing REM with grandpa's mouth wide open making odd screaming noises and grandson smiling and giggling.
Cut back to the battlefield, the only usable cover are large boulders that randomly appear through the haze. A large explosion in the distance knocks grandpa down to the ground, the heat from the blast causes his face
to be flushed in even more sweat. Grandpa scrambles on all fours to the nearest boulder that is nearly 12ft high and sizable enough
to cover four men. Large numbers of other soldiers continue to pass by on both sides. Grandpa presses his body tightly against the boulder next to soldiers of which are poised to return fire with no direct leader.
On grandpa's side is a medic attempting to revive an unconscious soldier with CPR and various medicinal shot administrations that only require the grasp of a trigger to instill into the skin. This is to no avail.

"God damn it, wake up!" Screams the medic to the dead soldier, of whom has a severe burns and lacerations to the entire front of the body.

The soldier on grandpa's other side nearest the edge of cover pops out and shoots blindly into the fog screaming, "Motherfuckerrrrsss!".
A stray bullet flies in and goes directly between the soldiers neck and clavicle. He collapses in front of grandpa grasping his neck as blood begins to spray out of his artery
with each heart beat. Grandpa's face is stricken with shock as he lets out a girlish screech.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend showing his respect and admiration for Joe Paterno </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-23 14:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend showing his respect for Joe Paterno </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-23 14:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joe Paterno Statue Terrorist Threat
 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-22 03:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joe Paterno Statue Takedown Terrorist Threat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-21 09:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some say pets look like their owners... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-19 09:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad Jewish Joke Eel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-18 06:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cops are so smart and cool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-18 06:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something else for the ladies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-18 00:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gilbert Gottfried Reads Fifty Shades of Grey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-14 01:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Parents Hate Their Children (38 seconds) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-10 08:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was there a revolt in Ireland recently? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-09 07:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Failed my NCLEX - Now what? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-05 21:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i failed my nclex on 7/2/12 in the state of Pennsylvania. I went to the PA dept of state to reapply for the ATT and it said they "You already have a license of this type". And I wasn't sure if I have to wait a period of time before even apply again. They didn't make the whole 45-90 waiting period very clear. Can someone give me a clear explanation on the process I should go through? thanks :)

EDIT: I called. They said if you do a re-exam you need to send in a physical paper application. False alarm, I still failed... :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Domestic Issues - could use prayer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-05 09:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i found out i failed the NCLEX which is the boards or test you need to pass to become a nurse. It sucks, but its obviously not the end of the world. The most frustrating issue was when i broke the news to my father, he was infuriated and continued to make a bunch of outlandish claims like, "things are gonna be changing around here!" and "You can get your own ride down to Harrisburg next time!" (the place of the test) and "This is bullshit!" - as if my failure is more of a detriment to him than it is me. He's not a christian if that's important, and I hate having issues with my dad. He's always been kind of a douche and often makes me feel like an idiot without considering my side of the story. I wanna tell him off but I also want to respect my parents and unfortunately, I still live under his roof until i can pass this stupid test and get a job. Basically, I would really appreciate prayer for passing the NCLEX test and my relationship with my father. Any advice would be cool too. Thanks.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nurses of Reddit: Is this Pearson NCLEX trick legitimate? (cuz if so, I failed the nclex fml) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-03 23:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I took it yesterday, felt like I did horrible. And I mean horrible. Like, I didn't know anything. 230 questions later I was done. I got online the next day and some people said there's a trick you can do where if you try to register again on Pearson-Vue, if you passed, it won't let you go to the credit card screen. Unfortunately, it allowed me to make it to that screen and I feel like that has all but solidified my failure. Which, in turn, makes me feel like a sack of shite. Mainly because, I'll somehow, have to figure out how to change my study habits to pass next time. Which honestly, studying is the bane of my existence. Is there truth to the whole Pearson trick? Encouragement would be nice too ;P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think I failed my NCLEX </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-03 22:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I took it yesterday, felt like I did horrible. And I mean horrible. Like, I didn't know anything. 230 questions later I was done. I got online the next day and some people said there's a trick you can do where if you try to register again on Pearson-Vue, if you passed, it won't let you go to the credit card screen. Unfortunately, it allowed me to make it to that screen and I feel like that has all but solidified my failure. Which, in turn, makes me feel like a sack of shite. Mainly because, I'll somehow, have to figure out how to change my study habits to pass next time. Which honestly, studying is the bane of my existence. Is there truth to the whole Pearson trick? Encouragement would be nice too ;P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not all Christians are bad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-02 02:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure why /r/atheism hates christians so much. Sure, there can be some seriously ignorant followers who piss you off to the fullest extent, but not all christians are advocates of The Crusades. Not all christians molest children and try to tell you what to do. The message promoted by Jesus in the Gospels of the New Testament was that of peace, love and sacrifice. A lot of christians hold true to that and are great members of the community, helping the poor and needy. I know people like the Westboro baptist church are nuts, and a lot of other christians realize it as well. My biggest confusion with /r/atheism is, what's being accomplished by the top upvoted item being Jesus having sex with a goat? Your subreddit is flooded with this stuff. How is that evidence of people who claim to be critical thinkers, and well educated? Most of the time, rather than a legitimate debate, your subreddit is filled with hate. At times I wish the sub was renamed '/r/trolls'. It's not serving anyone. I suggest we take a step back and consider our actions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Used Car Salesman Romney </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-01 11:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Used Car Salesman Romney </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-01 11:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey /r/Atheism! I've got a riddle for you :D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-01 10:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
What is so simple, any child can understand; Yet, so complex, no wisdom can solve?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Reddit Sucks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-01 00:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grandpaaaa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-29 21:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This pretty much sums this place up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-29 11:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that 9/11 was an inside job by Israeli Mossad :D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-29 10:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Israel's Mossad Do 9/11? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-29 10:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This kid sees the full picture now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-29 06:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Futurama Fry - Why horror movies suck nowadays </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-28 08:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Evil Banks Actually Are (Follow the Money) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-27 22:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disclaimer, this is not my own material I simply felt it necessary to share

1694  Bank of England Established

First Central Bank established in the UK. Served as model for most modern central banks.

1744- Mayer Amschel Rothschild, Founder of the Rothschild Banking Empire, is Born in Frankfurt, Germany

Mayer Amschel Rothschild extended his banking empire across Europe by carefully placing his five sons in key positions. They set up banks in Frankfurt, Vienna, London, Naples, and Paris. By the mid 1800s they dominated the banking industry, lending to governments around the world and people such as the Vanderbilts, Carnegies, and Cecil Rhodes.

1757- Colonial Scrip Issued in US

Debt free, fiat currency was printed in the public interest. As Benjamin Franklin said,

In the colonies we issue our own money. It is called colonial scrip. We issue it in proper proportion to the demands of trade and industry to make the products pass easily from the producers to the consumers. In this manner, creating for ourselves our own paper money, we control its purchasing power and we have no interest to pay no one.

1776  American Independence

1791  Congress Creates the First US Bank  A Private Company, Partly Owned by Foreigners  to Handle the Financial Needs of the New Central Government

Previously, the 13 states had their own banks, currencies and financial institutions.

1816  The Privately Owned Second Bank of the US was Chartered  It Served as the Main Depository for Government Revenue, Making it a Highly Profitable Bank

1832  Andrew Jackson Campaigns Against the 2nd Bank of the US and Vetoes Bank Charter Renewal

Andrew Jackson was skeptical of the central banking system and believed it gave too few men too much power and caused inflation. He was also a proponent of gold and silver and an outspoken opponent of the 2nd National Bank. The Charter expired in 1836.

1833  President Jackson Issues Executive Order to Stop Depositing Government Funds Into Bank of US

By September 1833, government funds were being deposited into state chartered banks.

Jan 30, 1835  Jackson Escapes Assassination. Assassin misfired twice.

1833-1837  Manufactured boom created by central bankers  money supply Increases 84%, Spurred by the 2nd Bank of the US

The total money supply rose from $150 million to $267 million.[1]

1837-1843  Terrible Depression

343 of the 850 banks in the US closed entirely as largest banks consolidated wealth and power.[2]

1861  American Civil War

1862-1863 Lincoln Over Rules Debt-Based Money and Issues Greenbacks to Fund the War

Bankers would only lend the government money under certain conditions and at high interest rates, so Lincoln issued his own currency  greenbacks  through the US Treasury, and made them legal tender. His soldiers went on to win the war, followed by great economic expansion.

April 15, 1865  Lincoln Assassinated

1881- President James Garfield, Staunch Proponent of Honest Money Backed by Gold and Silver, was Assassinated

Garfield opposed fiat currency (money that was not backed by any physical object) and was a strong advocate of a bi-metal monetary system. He had the second shortest Presidency in history.

1907- Banking Panic of 1907

The New York Stock Exchange dropped dramatically as everyone tried to get their money out of the banks at the same time across the nation. This banking panic spurred debate for banking reform. JP Morgan and others gathered to create an image of concern and stability in the face of the panic, which eventually led to the formation of the Federal Reserve. The founders of the Federal Reserve pretended like the bankers were opposed to the idea of its formation in order to mislead the public into believing that the Federal Reserve would help to regulate bankers when in fact it really gave even more power to private bankers, but in a less transparent way.

1908  JP Morgan Associate and Rockefeller Relative Nelson Aldrich Heads New National Monetary Commission

Senate Republican leader, Nelson Aldrich, heads the new National Monetary Commission that was created to study the cause of the banking panic. Aldrich had close ties with J.P. Morgan and his daughter married John D. Rockefeller.

1910  Bankers Meet Secretly on Jekyll Island to Draft Federal Reserve Banking Legislation

Over the course of a week, some of the nations most powerful bankers met secretly off the coast of Georgia, drafting a proposal for a private Central Banking system. Those in attendance included Nelson Aldrich, A.P. Andrew (Assistant Secretary of the Treasury), Paul Warburg (Kuhn, Loeb,   Co.), Frank Vanderlip (President of National City Bank of New York), Charles D. Norton (president of the Morgan-dominated First National Bank of New York), Henry Davidson (Senior Partner of JP Morgan Co.), and Benjamin Strong (representing JP Morgan).

Dec 23, 1913  Federal Reserve Act Passed

Two days before Christmas, while many members of Congress were away on vacation, the Federal Reserve Act was passed, creating the Central banking system we have today. It was based on the Aldrich plan drafted on Jekyll Island and gave private bankers supreme authority over the economy. They are now able to create money out of nothing (and loan it out at interest), make decisions without government approval, and control the amount of money in circulation.

1913  Income tax established -16th Amendment Ratified

Taxes ensured that citizens would cover the payment of debt due to the Central Bank, the Federal Reserve, which was also created in 1913.The 16th Amendment stated: The Congress shall have power to lay and collect taxes on incomes, from whatever source derived, without apportionment among the several States, and without regard to any census or enumeration.

1914  JP Morgan and Co. Profits from Financing both sides of War and Purchasing Weapons

J.P. Morgan and Co. made a deal with the Bank of England to give them a monopoly on underwriting war bonds for the UK and France. They also invested in the suppliers of war equipment to Britain and France.

November 1914  Federal Reserve Banks Open

1921-1929  The Roaring 20s  The Federal Reserve Floods the Economy with Cash and Credit

From 1921 to 1929 the Federal Reserve increased the money supply by $28 billion, almost a 62% increase over an eight-year period.[3] This artificially created another boom.

1929  Federal Reserve Contracts the Money Supply

In 1929, the Federal Reserve began to pull money out of circulation as loans were paid back. They created a bust which was inevitable after issuing so much credit in the years before. The Federal Reserves actions triggered the banking crisis, which led to the Great Depression.

October 24, 1929  Black Thursday, Stock Market Crash

The most devastating stock market crash in history. Billions of dollars in value were consolidated into the private bankers hands at the expense of everyone else.

CONTINUED IN COMMENTS
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Evil Banks Actually Are (Follow the Money) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-27 12:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disclaimer, this is not my own material I simply felt it necessary to share

1694  Bank of England Established

First Central Bank established in the UK. Served as model for most modern central banks.

1744- Mayer Amschel Rothschild, Founder of the Rothschild Banking Empire, is Born in Frankfurt, Germany

Mayer Amschel Rothschild extended his banking empire across Europe by carefully placing his five sons in key positions. They set up banks in Frankfurt, Vienna, London, Naples, and Paris. By the mid 1800s they dominated the banking industry, lending to governments around the world and people such as the Vanderbilts, Carnegies, and Cecil Rhodes.

1757- Colonial Scrip Issued in US

Debt free, fiat currency was printed in the public interest. As Benjamin Franklin said,

In the colonies we issue our own money. It is called colonial scrip. We issue it in proper proportion to the demands of trade and industry to make the products pass easily from the producers to the consumers. In this manner, creating for ourselves our own paper money, we control its purchasing power and we have no interest to pay no one.

1776  American Independence

1791  Congress Creates the First US Bank  A Private Company, Partly Owned by Foreigners  to Handle the Financial Needs of the New Central Government

Previously, the 13 states had their own banks, currencies and financial institutions.

1816  The Privately Owned Second Bank of the US was Chartered  It Served as the Main Depository for Government Revenue, Making it a Highly Profitable Bank

1832  Andrew Jackson Campaigns Against the 2nd Bank of the US and Vetoes Bank Charter Renewal

Andrew Jackson was skeptical of the central banking system and believed it gave too few men too much power and caused inflation. He was also a proponent of gold and silver and an outspoken opponent of the 2nd National Bank. The Charter expired in 1836.

1833  President Jackson Issues Executive Order to Stop Depositing Government Funds Into Bank of US

By September 1833, government funds were being deposited into state chartered banks.

Jan 30, 1835  Jackson Escapes Assassination. Assassin misfired twice.

1833-1837  Manufactured boom created by central bankers  money supply Increases 84%, Spurred by the 2nd Bank of the US

The total money supply rose from $150 million to $267 million.[1]

1837-1843  Terrible Depression

343 of the 850 banks in the US closed entirely as largest banks consolidated wealth and power.[2]

1861  American Civil War

1862-1863 Lincoln Over Rules Debt-Based Money and Issues Greenbacks to Fund the War

Bankers would only lend the government money under certain conditions and at high interest rates, so Lincoln issued his own currency  greenbacks  through the US Treasury, and made them legal tender. His soldiers went on to win the war, followed by great economic expansion.

April 15, 1865  Lincoln Assassinated

1881- President James Garfield, Staunch Proponent of Honest Money Backed by Gold and Silver, was Assassinated

Garfield opposed fiat currency (money that was not backed by any physical object) and was a strong advocate of a bi-metal monetary system. He had the second shortest Presidency in history.

1907- Banking Panic of 1907

The New York Stock Exchange dropped dramatically as everyone tried to get their money out of the banks at the same time across the nation. This banking panic spurred debate for banking reform. JP Morgan and others gathered to create an image of concern and stability in the face of the panic, which eventually led to the formation of the Federal Reserve. The founders of the Federal Reserve pretended like the bankers were opposed to the idea of its formation in order to mislead the public into believing that the Federal Reserve would help to regulate bankers when in fact it really gave even more power to private bankers, but in a less transparent way.

1908  JP Morgan Associate and Rockefeller Relative Nelson Aldrich Heads New National Monetary Commission

Senate Republican leader, Nelson Aldrich, heads the new National Monetary Commission that was created to study the cause of the banking panic. Aldrich had close ties with J.P. Morgan and his daughter married John D. Rockefeller.

1910  Bankers Meet Secretly on Jekyll Island to Draft Federal Reserve Banking Legislation

Over the course of a week, some of the nations most powerful bankers met secretly off the coast of Georgia, drafting a proposal for a private Central Banking system. Those in attendance included Nelson Aldrich, A.P. Andrew (Assistant Secretary of the Treasury), Paul Warburg (Kuhn, Loeb,   Co.), Frank Vanderlip (President of National City Bank of New York), Charles D. Norton (president of the Morgan-dominated First National Bank of New York), Henry Davidson (Senior Partner of JP Morgan Co.), and Benjamin Strong (representing JP Morgan).

Dec 23, 1913  Federal Reserve Act Passed

Two days before Christmas, while many members of Congress were away on vacation, the Federal Reserve Act was passed, creating the Central banking system we have today. It was based on the Aldrich plan drafted on Jekyll Island and gave private bankers supreme authority over the economy. They are now able to create money out of nothing (and loan it out at interest), make decisions without government approval, and control the amount of money in circulation.

1913  Income tax established -16th Amendment Ratified

Taxes ensured that citizens would cover the payment of debt due to the Central Bank, the Federal Reserve, which was also created in 1913.The 16th Amendment stated: The Congress shall have power to lay and collect taxes on incomes, from whatever source derived, without apportionment among the several States, and without regard to any census or enumeration.

1914  JP Morgan and Co. Profits from Financing both sides of War and Purchasing Weapons

J.P. Morgan and Co. made a deal with the Bank of England to give them a monopoly on underwriting war bonds for the UK and France. They also invested in the suppliers of war equipment to Britain and France.

November 1914  Federal Reserve Banks Open

1921-1929  The Roaring 20s  The Federal Reserve Floods the Economy with Cash and Credit

From 1921 to 1929 the Federal Reserve increased the money supply by $28 billion, almost a 62% increase over an eight-year period.[3] This artificially created another boom.

1929  Federal Reserve Contracts the Money Supply

In 1929, the Federal Reserve began to pull money out of circulation as loans were paid back. They created a bust which was inevitable after issuing so much credit in the years before. The Federal Reserves actions triggered the banking crisis, which led to the Great Depression.

October 24, 1929  Black Thursday, Stock Market Crash

The most devastating stock market crash in history. Billions of dollars in value were consolidated into the private bankers hands at the expense of everyone else.

CONTINUED IN COMMENTS
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL - How Evil Banks Actually Are (Follow the Money) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-27 12:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best part of Mario 64 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-26 23:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've finally figured it out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-26 11:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think this might have a double meaning.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-24 13:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never thought I'd say this but FUCK THE POLICE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-24 02:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Playing" with Mario </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-23 10:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Playing" With Mario </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-22 10:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad Luck Brian fapped </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-22 10:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I doubt you wanna hear this confession </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-21 21:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I honestly feel like girls go to third world countries specifically for this reason alone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-21 21:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there suppose to be a terrorist attack at the London 2012 Olympic Games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-20 10:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of crazy youtube sources keep predicting a nuclear and/or biological attack during the 2012 Olympic Games in London. Similar to the signs that pointed towards 9/11 occurring. All for the purpose of increased fear and furthered security to unite the world under one totalitarian big brother governing body. Has anyone else heard this? Please, I'm not trying to be crazy with this. I just want to hear peoples' thoughts on this that may have some sort of related information. 

source: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bqGkNslqVxU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone ever had a spiritual and/or demonic experience? If so, please describe.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-19 21:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is a safe-haven for trolls, but please, no creepy pasta. I'm genuinely interested in real encounters and experiences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I feel after seeing all the Senior Week pictures start to surface on facebook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-17 23:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This will save us all a lot of grief in the end </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-17 23:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are my youtube videos funny? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-17 21:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Father's Day from Charlie and Michael Showalter!! (from Stella) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-17 21:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think about people who sing in public? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-17 10:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about the weirdos and the thespians alike. What's your personal view of someone who openly sings at any given time, without prompt? Even the black dudes who sing to themselves loud as they walk by with their iPhones blaring.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> seriously could NOT get off to this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-17 09:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you explain the examples harshness of the Old Testament to those who will use those to negate the rest of the Bible? (eg. Exodus 21) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-12 09:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many people use old testament verses to put down the bible and it's meaning. I personally feel a lot of the crazier stuff of the old testament like Exodus 21 is specifically addressed to the Hebrews of that time and shouldn't be pulled out of context to shut down any biblical argument. What do you think?

EDIT: I don't know, the one thing I've seen for sure is that people with different views need to meet somewhere more personal than the internet. Not to be rude, but this Christianity vs Atheist is the biggest circlejerk on Reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evil Plotting Raccoon Writes a school paper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-12 08:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does Prometheus tie in with Alien? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-11 10:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw the movie, Prometheus, and even though I can see the events clearly occur before the Alien movie timeline; I'm confused how the movie directly ties in as a prequel. I felt like there were quite a few script holes and plot decisions that didn't make sense. I can't think of many off the top of my head, but the movie left me a bit jaded. 

Any ideas my Reddit friends? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My grandma has cancer. Are the doctors just milking her for insurance money? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-10 22:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandmother has cancer that has metastasized (spread) all through her body including her pancreas, liver, spleen, and spinal cord. She is 87 y.o. Her husband, my grandfather, died of cancer 4 years prior and, even though she is cheerful, has never been in good health since. The clear prognosis (likelihood of the disease progression) is terminal (death). Unfortunately, even with that most definite outcome, the physicians (doctors) insist on continuing to perform procedures; of which will be billed to her insurance company.

She suffers from severe back pain, due to the cancer's spinal cord involvement, and the physicians say they want to perform a biopsy (take out a piece of the cancer for examination) to determine the best method of pain control for her palliative care (care for someone who's dying). I, personally, have never heard of a cancer biopsy being necessary to determine specific treatment for pain. Especially palliative. 

I know I probably just seem angry and accusative, but I would like my grandmother to spend as much time at home with her family as possible before she passes. I don't want to openly know that the doctors and hospital are just trying to gain a profit from her suffering. 

If anyone with personal experience, like someone who encountered a similar situation or someone in the medical field, could shed some light on this it would be much appreciated.

PS - I'm not blood related if anyone wanted to tell me to get early screening etc. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Flextrek Whipsnake! - "When whipsnake strikes, you'll want to be the one wearing It".
 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-10 07:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Ironside's response after being replaced as the iconic voice of Splinter Cell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-09 08:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Ironside's response to being replaced as the voice of Splinter Cell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-09 08:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Sam Fisher younger in the Splinter Cell: Blacklist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-09 07:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see Michael Ironside (voice of Sam Fisher) is being replaced by a different actor in Splinter Cell: Blacklist. What I don't understand is, if the events takes place after Conviction (where Sam Fisher already seemed like he was getting older), why would they replace him with a young actor with a young voice and it even appears Sam's movement is that of young stud. Why wouldn't they just do a prequel or something, when Sam was just starting to kick ass or something. I donno, I just don't like the taste this is putting in my mouth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is to be gained from being an Atheist? And why do people take such Pride in it?

 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-08 10:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like no one knows what's going on. And don't give me bullshit. You can't tell me that our 21st century minds have any iota of a clue to what the fuck all "THIS" is (the universe etc). All that has come to be is new theories, nothing proven. Life after death is NOT proven or disproven. Although, I've heard a ton more stories of near death/ out of body experiences where people say they've seen something (white light, God, whatever). I mean, holy shit, how can one be so arrogant as to utterly deny something that they have no possible way of understanding. Science is great, and has helped mankind tremendously, but to say it negates a spiritual perspective is outright stupid.

If you believe in atheism so much, why do you come to this subreddit just to be reassured that what you believe is right? Your actions are no different than the religious you shoot down (Culminating in the church of atheism).  Also, its become almost an unsaid duty of atheists to put down religion (that just seems low and also pointless). If what you believe is what you believe and that's the end of it, the need for a community to support your belief is erroneous.

Atheism doesn't help anyone either. At least religion or some sort of discipline gives people hope in something more. All atheism does is spread the word of nothingness and self-service and usually just an underlying way of expressing disgust with religion.

There's also this association with being an atheist and being educated. That's just an outright lie because, education (math, science, history etc) and personal beliefs are almost mutually exclusive and being atheist does not necessitate a higher IQ in any sense. 

Take a step back and compare yourself to anyone you know. Your understanding of this world and what's beyond holds no stronger basis than your neighbor. Before you go out of your way to explain to people the lack of an existence of a god/gods, maybe you should step out of your comfort zones and do some searching yourself. Even if that searching is within.

tl;dr - /r/atheism = /r/circlejerk

PS - all those pictures people post of "famous" atheists and their quotes - I've never seen a single one of them smiling 8( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The only way I see USA entering into a war with Iran </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-08 09:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This still confuses me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-08 09:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to make a chicken laugh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-08 09:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a good, convenient, non-acne facial wash? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-07 00:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a male just looking to keep his face clean without using bar soap. 

What I've been doing is using dial soap in the shower to clean off the grease and then a moisturizer on my face to keep it from drying out. 

I just need something that will clean and moisturize without making me break out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IAmA: Bouncer at a bar called Pickles, AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-06 23:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The People I Met In Hell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-06 23:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I feel after I realize a girl doesn't like me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-06 09:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mass Effect - Galaxy Map Music (so relaxing) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 11:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This guy appreciates all memes equally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-02 19:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are other ways to watch television shows... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-02 19:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not sure if these people do this out of their own subconscious of feeling racist if they don't, or if they're actually just packed to the brim with their own liberal bullshit   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-02 18:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I feel about caged up dogs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-02 18:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What I wonder every time I walk by a chained up dog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-02 02:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I feel about this coming election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-02 02:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad Luck Brian visits the Big Apple </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-01 08:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This story isn't quite as magical </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-23 00:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Excellent Dog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-21 14:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you heard about the sequel to the Ron Paul movement coming out in 2016? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-20 11:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think we all would be gone if this were the case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-20 11:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This goes for all you "bar" DJs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-20 10:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good Guy Rabbi - the middle east is great </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-20 01:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good Guy Rabbi - We all know this is true </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-20 01:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Funny song called "Surprise Sex" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 23:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm actually pretty fortunate if I get this many </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 01:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Misunderstood D-Bag - poor Adrian Veidt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 01:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I feel about Max Payne 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 01:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How feel every time I scroll through my MP3 player </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 00:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch 90s Nickelodeon Cartoons online with other Redditors and chat about it, ALL LIVE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-07 09:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boromir - Happens in Every telephone conversation in my Life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-06 10:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad Joke Eel - What's a heroin addict's favorite soda? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-06 01:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hank Hill sells things </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-05 00:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How considerate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-02 05:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good Girl Gina - Let me just sum this one up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-01 05:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What a foolish uneducated theist!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-01 02:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He actually did this during one of his shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-01 01:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whenever I play mini golf  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-30 06:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long's it been? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-28 06:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jimmy McMillan hates spelling errors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-27 22:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If he doesn't get it, he'll die </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-27 22:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What i wonder sometimes when I watch p0rn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-27 22:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Horrifying Houseguest - We thought we were safe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-24 00:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ross the Boss - Everyone LOVES this bartender </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-22 04:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ross the Boss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-22 04:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chihuahua Logic - That's Hot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-22 01:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waking Life (2001) - Animation, Philosophy, Lucid Dreaming. Everything you could possibly ask for in a flick. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-17 10:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Offensive Forrest Gump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-15 03:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ~: The History of YouTube :~ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-15 03:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fabulous Divorced Guy - This guys got it right </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-14 06:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The greatest deception of Barack Obama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-14 04:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Innuendo Garth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-13 10:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joseph Ducreux's rendition "In Da Club" - 50 cent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-13 09:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ghost Recon Future Soldier - Personalization Beta </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-12 16:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GhostRecon:Future Soldier - versus multiplayer gameplay - Map Pipeline Beta - YouTube </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-12 16:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In My Opinion Orangutan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-12 06:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secede - Live at Lab30 (2007) [ idm 1 hr set] (unreleased tracks) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-12 06:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
