<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9154</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World's Longest Tongue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 14:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little Baby's Ice Cream </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 06:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> make it stop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 03:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> feels like. sword is moving through my stomach. and then my 5th or 6th trip to the bathroom the last couple of bowel movements that come out they sting, badly. Some of it is just mucus but it stings when it passes through. 

fucking awful. I fainted on the toilet for 45 minutes. I woke up on the floor with blood and mucus/poop on my leg. and my head hurt. awful make stop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL former Heisman winner   NFL pro-bowler Herschel Walker has D.I.D. (Disassociated Identity Disorder) also known as Multiple Personality Disorder. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 02:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL two members of the musical group LMFAO are descendants of Motown Records' founder, Berry Gordy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 01:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a cat AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 07:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be answering questions for my cat, Fred who wanted to do an AMA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Woman Plans To Sue United Airlines For Forcing Her Autistic Daughter Off A Flight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 20:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what's your Top 5 of everything? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 07:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No categories. Top 5 of everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sleep with one eye open </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 06:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A family walks into a talent agency.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 23:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A family walks into a talent agency. It's a father, mother, son, daughter and dog. The father says to the talent agent, "We have a really amazing act. You should represent us."

The agent says, "Sorry, I don't represent family acts. They're a little too cute."

The mother says, "Sir, if you just see our act, we know you would want to represent us."

The agent says, "OK. OK. I'll take a look."

The father pulls out a watermelon and shoves it in the daughters vagina. The daughter screams in pain from the giant fruit. Then the son takes off his shirt revealing a pink bra and starts fingering himself in the asshole. The mother takes off all of her clothes and starts to finger herself while the father feeds her x-lax pills. The father grabs the daughter and shoves her face right in the mothers butt hole that at that moment exploded with diarrhea all over her face and it filled up her mouth. The the daughter turned to the son and spat the diarrhea all over him. Then the father reaches in the girls vagina and pulls out the now stinky, cum covered watermelon and starts to hump it while the mother begins to shoot her explosive diarrhea in his direction. Then the son begins to rub his cock and cums all over the daughter. Then the father stops humping the watermelon and cums all over her. They continue to cum on her while the mother fills up a plastic kiddie pool with her crap and piss. They all jump in the human excrement and start to fuck each other. Now the pool is filled with cum and shit and piss. 

They jump out of the pool covered in cum and shit and piss and say "tada!".


For the longest time, the agent just sits in silence. Finally, he manages, "That's a hell of an act. What do you call it?"

And the father says, **"The Aristocrats!"**

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kanye West - Hey Mama [Hip-Hop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 23:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 69 boyz - Tootsee Roll [Dance/Hip-Hop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 23:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lefties of reddit.....what's is like living in a right-handed world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 22:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canelo KOs Kirkland with Devastating Right </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 05:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sauron's ring of power is pretty much just a Horcrux </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 02:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's over....but wait </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 01:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your life like pre-reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 00:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ice Cube - Today Was A Good Day [Hip-Hop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 23:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What movie(s) has made you cry? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 22:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] When you were a kid, what did you want to be when you grew up? Did you do that or end up doing something else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 21:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: English Premiere League relegation, how to win league, length of league </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 18:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep in mind I'm American and now nothing on European Soccer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Obama became President of the US because People Magazine thought actor Garret Wang was attractive. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 21:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cat talking with crows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 21:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi Reddit, I just came out to my friends and family as bisexual, AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 15:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another short poem by Google. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 12:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Derby the dog: Running on 3D Printed Prosthetics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 12:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Derby the dog: Running on 3D Printed Prosthetics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 09:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi Reddit! I have Ulcerative Colitis. I was diagnosed when I was 16, about 14 years ago. AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 21:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Takashi Tateishi - Mega Man 2 Dr. Wily's Castle [8bit] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 19:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why should people read books? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 15:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snorkeler Finds Skeleton Tea Party 40 Feet Beneath The Surface </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 23:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Wells Report (a mere 243 pages) on Deflategate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 19:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Human Centipede 3 (Final Sequence) Official Red Band Trailer #1 (2015) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 19:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ellen DeGeneres' last name does not represent her well. She is, in fact, incredibly generous. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 14:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am a mental health counselor/school counselor AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 13:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been in the profession for 3-4 years now. AMA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kingsman: The Secret Service </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 21:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed this is a movie a lot of people enjoyed. Is there something I'm missing with this movie? It's seem really highly rated but when I watch it there's no endearing quality about it, it's just a cheesy humor, action flick with not so great montages of a kid training while we watch the villain plot. Is this like a homage or satire? 

What am I missing? I feel like there's a joke and I missed it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garfield Dog. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salad? Nope. Spaghetti? nomnomnom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now I understand the Guardians of the Galaxy "black light through the ship   Jackson Pollack" painting joke </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 10:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What is the main argument for fracking? What are the positives? Do they outweigh any negatives? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 08:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manny out 9-12 months after shoulder surgery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 06:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Return of the Jedi when Luke burns Vader, the firewood looks like it is cut by an ax not light saber, what are some reasons he would use an Ax instead of Light Saber? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 04:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manny reportedly fought with shoulder injury; The injury kicked up again in the 3rd round. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 08:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by telling my friend his behavior was unacceptable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 03:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So about 6-7 months ago I told my best friend at the time that his behavior was unacceptable when he got drunk: Example: Overly aggressive, violent, angry, mean, physical, arrogant, and insulting when he gets drunk. One night was the icing on the cake for me, and I told him when he was sober how I felt and that I think he might have a problem. Irregardless if he believes that he does, I didn't want to be around him when he drinks anymore because he treats people badly. 

In perfect him fashion, he said he disagrees with everything I said and never wants to talk to me about it again. 

Systematically the few months after that all of my friends stopped talking to me and asking me to hang out. Now i have no friends where I live and it makes me wonder if I had just gone along with it and put up with it maybe I will still have friends. 

None of them have spoken to me at all in the past 4 months.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fishermen cuts open a fish(cod) he caught to find a dildo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 08:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Window Water Baby Moving- Stan Brakhage (1962) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 07:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby Armadillo plays with toy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 05:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hot Dogs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 13:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Some mother's drink their own placenta after birth as a smoothie because it gives them strength, balance, and helps reduce blood loss. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 11:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you call the security guards outside of Samsung? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 10:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guardians of the Galaxy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by getting up to go to the restroom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 07:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened many many years ago when I was in 5th grade but I was reminded of it today when I got a hard on. 

I used to think when I was younger that us men got boners because it meant we had to pee and the stiffy meant the penis was full of urine. 

So one day in class during silent reading time, I had an erection and stood up and walked to my teacher and asked if I may go to the bathroom. I was standing there with my pre-pubescent dick with a pitched tent and my teacher gave me the strangest look. I didn't think anything of it, I thought this was normal and all boys walked around like this when having to drain the snake. 

I went and finished my business and my member was flaccid again so I went back in the room and everyone was still looking at me. Later at recess people kept calling me Masturbating Matt and that set the tone for the rest of elementary school and middle school for me until I went to a high school where no one knew me. 

tl;dr thought my shaft getting rigor mortis meant it was time to go to the bathroom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roommate's dog found my bed. Cat not happy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 05:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help finding Missing person in Texas: First name Thomas from Ohio, need advice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 05:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Missing person somewhere in Texas last seen:

My friend Thomas W. has been missing for over a week. He lives in Columbus Ohio and his last known whereabouts were somewhere in Texas where he was doing a job of some sort. He does not do drugs so this is very out of his character. He is also a father and needs to be found. If you know anything at all please PM me for facebook info.

Or if you know how to check hospitals or some type of database. He's never been in trouble or anything, but has been missing and his family is concerned.

[Current Picture](http://imgur.com/AFeRkJ1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every account on reddit is a bot except you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 13:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favorite excuse you give people for not wanting to hang out with them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 06:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Text]The Power of Reddit   the Internet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 07:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to take the time to thank Reddit and people on here for coming together to help the people in Nepal this past few days. We created /r/NepalEarthquake   /r/LangtangRelief both awesome subreddits. Watching it unfold has been extremely motivating, seeing people work together tirelessly. 

We got all this info from people in Nepal, someone who is even talking to people in Langtang via SAT phone to see what they need food wise. News articles, local contact, helping one another find lost ones or missing ones with a missing/found google doc database. 

I find it fascinating   motivating how beautifully the internet can be used to resource and connect people so quickly. 

The /r/NepalEarthquake subreddit is really awesome seeing how fast people have compiled a compendium of everything so quickly- with the sole purpose of helping one another. 


It's fascinating to see the results of what happens when people work as a part of a global team.

Thanks for listening to my ramble. I just wanted to say thank you reddit. You're awesome. 

TL;DR - Motivated by Redditors working together to help Nepal Earthquake victims. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got my refund check. What's a good way to pay it forward? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 05:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Read a funny post in IMDB comments involving Seth MacFarlane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 00:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's rare. 

**bagpipper-onnen (OP)**: MacFarlane has to be bangin Amanda Seyfriend, he's casting her in everything he does. 

**AckleyKid1990**: Yeah wow he's cast her in two whole movies. That's insane. If that's how it works, Leo Dicaprio and Scorcese must be married with three kids, a poodle, a couple of Prius' and a beach house in Lake Geneva by now.


**theshape26**:Yep, DiCaprio and Scorsese are together. It's a long story. Now, it's never been publicly revealed but from 1973 to 1995, Martin Scorsese and Robert De Niro were an item. Unfortunately, Scorsese caught De Niro in bed with Joe Pesci and they broke up. Scorsese stopped casting De Niro   Joe Pesci's career pretty much died. 

Then in 2001, Scorsese ran into DiCaprio at a party and they started talking. They had met in 1993 when Leo was still a teen, at the premiere of This Boy's Life. They were introduced by... Robert De Niro! 

By the way, for those wondering, De Niro and Pesci broke up in 2006 and in 2011, De Niro started an affair with Bradley Cooper. They also knew each other from before when they briefly talked, at The Actor's Studio when De Niro was a guest in 1998.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am modding /r/NepalEarthquake can someone help me to to setup a system for collaboration on a GIS system (GeoSpatial Information System), to highlight and geotag all media </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 15:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping there is some existing software out there that would accept a google spreadsheet, and render them as points in a map

I'm not familiar with GIS much, wondering if anyone may be able to help?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google 'person finder' tool deployed to help relatives find loved ones in Nepal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 14:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook: Safety Check for Friends/Family in Nepal Emergency Number: +977-4228435 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 14:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nepalese dig for quake survivors as toll exceeds 2,200, big aftershock 6.7 on Richter Scale hits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 14:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good information here on local contacts for help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 12:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NepalEarthquake: News, Updates,   Help  /r/NepalEarthquake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 12:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to help Nepal: 7 vetted charities doing relief work following the earthquake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 12:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nepal earthquake: Over 1900 people killed, 4700 injured; fresh tremors hit Delhi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 12:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You're a ten year old human and you're parents adopt an orphin Rodian named Greedo on the planet Tatooine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 12:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UAB Football Player Raises Helmet at Commencement, Refuses President's Handshake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 10:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I will eat the top rated comment if the Cleveland Browns don't make it to the AFC Title Game from 2015 season. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 09:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> History of the iPhone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 04:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just watched Up the Disney/Pixar movie for the first time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 10:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck you Disney/Pixar. Fuck you. The first ten minutes...really? Well fuck you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what's the best pun you've come up with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 07:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, why do people get so mad when discussing white privilege? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 03:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what would your decoy username be on To Catch a Predator? (in the Fort Myers episode, they used snakesonagirl) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 18:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To Catch a Predator: Decoy Username: Snakesonagirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 18:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fatberg breaks London sewer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 16:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a nightmare you've had that has come true? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 14:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stop using the term IBD please, it hurts us with UC/Crohn's because of the negative stigma and similarities with the far more common IBS. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 14:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I've used that word/acronym with people it ends up being responses like "oh i get that when i eat taco bell, just take some tums or stop eating pizza youll be fine."
We should just called CCD or Colitis   Crohn's Disease. Please it would be a major help if you all in this community could sign my .gov petition and pass it on to people so the government may help us change it as a medical term.



http://wh.gov/iBX6z


Thank you. :)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study finds no association found between MMR vaccine and autism, even among children at higher risk (study of 95,000 children) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 22:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> REPORT: BAY AREA NEEDS TO PREPARE FOR 'MEGA STORM' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 20:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by not honoring the 10 second food rule </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 13:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a cool ranch Doritos chip laying on the ground near my dinner table, must have been dropped on the ground when I had a snack several hours earlier in the day. I ate it. It tasted like cat urine, because my cat had urinated on it. 

Surprisingly, cat urine tastes a lot like cool ranch Doritos, the aftertaste on my breath at least. My own fault. I knew my cat was looking to get back at me for giving him a bath a week ago, I just didn't know this would be his plan. The feud lives on Brian.  

TL;DR: Ate chip soaked in cat urine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Treasure Mountain! My favorite Floppy Disc PC Game when I was 5 years old! I found it!!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 15:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twin Peaks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 16:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have just about finished season one of Twin Peaks. A couple things I would like to ask: 

Among fans of Twin Peaks, is there a running joke about how many times Agent Cooper drinks coffee, or how excited he is every episode when he gets an amazing cup of coffee, minus fish in the one sip he had. 

I can't tell if some of it is bad acting or if it is done purposely, there are some really hilarious lines. I really feel bad for the girl's dad, but ...damn if it wasn't hilarious watching him try to dance to those swing/big band songs that kept coming on. Should I be laughing at that? lol

I have never seen any David Lynch before, so I am new to his creations and style of directing. 

I was told to watch the movie after I am finished with season 2, is this correct? It looks like a prequel though, is it worth watching?



EDIT: Just finished Episode 8 with the cliffhanger of an ending. Wow. Season 1 was marvelous if for nothing else than that wonderful soundtrack of glory. Running theme of the first season: Almost every female relationship the female is being abused somehow. 

I knew I recognized James from somewhere, he was also in A Few Good Men.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists develop mesh that captures oilbut lets water through </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 13:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Western Conservative Summit disinvites GOP gay group </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 16:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you wanted to comically troll your brother, what would you do? (he lives far away) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 04:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just watched first episode of Twin Peaks for the first time.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 13:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Just watched the first episode of Twin Peaks for the first time, why is this guy (on the right) randomly doing a strange wormy jig off camera in the background? It's so random...made me laugh out loud. Is this show full of random quirks like this?

 I was originally recommended to watch this show because I love the X-Files, I recognize the music will be a bit weird because this came out 25 years ago, but it seems to be rich full of randomness that just makes me giggle and I love it. 


Here's the link http://i.imgur.com/ZxXXxOm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by calling a customer a jerk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 01:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work a Lowe's and I was chatting with a customer for about twenty minutes about paint mixtures. We had been joking back and forth, and I called her a jerk out of sarcasm/joke. It was clear it was a joke. She says I need to learn how to talk to people because saying things like that is what gets people killed....... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL There is something called a penile plethysmograph, in which a sensor is attached to the penis while an array of sexual images flashes before his eyes, to gauge arousal, this will happen to Darren Sharper, ex-NFL player after his release from prison. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 03:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by trying to kill a spider in my car </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 05:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in my car driving home from Easter Dinner with my mum and a large white spider started crawling across my windshield. I was almost home so I pulled over and put my emergency lights on. 


After this I tried to kill him with my hands but he foiled my attempts at squashing with my clumsy hands and he landed on the passenger side dashboard. I then got a bunch of paper I had laying around in my passenger sit and rolled it up to swat him. 


For whatever reason he survived it and fell on my passenger seat then he scurried away onto the passenger side ground among all the trash I had laying there. 

The worst possible outcome happened. I lost sight of him. He disappeared. I drove home with my car lights on keeping a watchful eye on that side of the car. Then I got home..not sure if I'll ever drive that car again


EDIT: Spider dead. Went down to my car to try and retrieve my cellphone this morning and I saw him crouched against the weather stripping on the driver's side window on the inside. I rolled my window down and he started crawling out on the outside door frame. I threw water on him. He fell to the ground. I stepped on him. I can drive my car now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Geographic tongue is a condition in which the upper layer of the tongue, which consists of tiny hair-like protrusions-papillae is damaged due to an inflammation. A noticeable characteristic of the condition is an evolving map-like appearance of the affected tongue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 23:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tired of this DDOS crap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 11:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was on An Corp, somehow it stopped, was on UOF, now it's on UO:R almost every night...weirdly in the middle of the night which seems dumb because it's not in prime time but...wtf? I don't understand, why can't they just stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gerry a movie by Gus Van Sant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 04:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else see this movie? It has Casey Affleck and Myatt Damon in it. I made my brother watch it and it was the worst 100 minutes of his life so he tells. What do you all think?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do poor people in Scientology move up the levels if they can't afford it since they're poor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 07:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just watched Going Clear, I understand it's subjective, but this is one question I have had. 


EDIT: Would like to tag as Serious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why would male public toilets in America start being raised 6-10 inches? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 17:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Columbus, Ohio I have found that public toilets have been raised at least 6-10 inches, in several places. I don't know if this is nationwide but what would the rationale for it be? We're not getting any taller on average as American Men.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] As a young kitten in a litter of eight you were sold off to slavers who gave you no pets, let you fend for table scraps, and had no windows in their house. You stayed in a dark, cold room most of the time until a smaller slaver wanted to "play." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 11:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 11:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My best friend has a girlfriend who is from another country (one of the Scandinavian countries i dont want to say which dont want to give away their identity or anything).
She got a school visa to come to school here. She graduated from undergrad, then she got her graduate degree as well. She is currently working at a job, but they will not help her stay by saying they absolutely need her or whatever on her immigration forms for a visa. She has an immigration firm that is helping her with the massive application process but she is going to have to move away in 4-5 months and be deported if she does not figure out another way.


They could get married, theyve been dating for a while, but they don't want to do that because it wouldn't be "sincere." I mean they do love each other, but not ready for marriage and yet neither one wants her to go. She wants to stay, he wants her to stay.


I want to be able to help because I hate seeing him sad. I know her place of employment had to fill out a certain section of her application and they refused to which I guess was the only way she could stay?
Any advice?


EDIT: lives in the United States, South Carolina. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Immigration advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 04:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My best friend has a girlfriend who is from another country (one of the Scandinavian countries i dont want to say which dont want to give away their identity or anything). 

She got a school visa to come to school here. She graduated from undergrad, then she got her graduate degree as well. She is currently working at a job, but they will not help her stay by saying they absolutely need her or whatever on her immigration forms for a visa. She has an immigration firm that is helping her with the massive application process but she is going to have to move away in 4-5 months and be deported if she does not figure out another way. 

They could get married, theyve been dating for a while, but they don't want to do that because it wouldn't be "sincere." I mean they do love each other, but not ready for marriage and yet neither one wants her to go. She wants to stay, he wants her to stay. 

I want to be able to help because I hate seeing him sad. I know her place of employment had to fill out a certain section of her application and they refused to which I guess was the only way she could stay? 

Any advice?

EDIT:  lives in the United States, South Carolina.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone please explain to me, seriously, what is the deal with the film The Room? Why do people love it so much? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 10:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm asking seriously I read the AMA but don't understand a lot of the jokes. What is the big deal with this movie? Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am a former Blockbuster manager. AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 07:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked as a manager of Blockbuster Video from 2005-2010. I started as a CSR for the first year then was promoted to Shift Lead, then Ast. Store Manager. 

I'm not really sure what I would show you as proof, I don't really have anything like an old name tag or anything like that. My knowledge to your questions will have to be the proof lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just bought a Wii U. Did I do the right thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 09:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little Experts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 06:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My 102 year old grandma (august 9th, 1912) loves President Obama. She was absolutely smitten after she got to meet him. She was laughing/smiling because he had just swooped in to give her a little kiss kiss. I love my grandma! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 03:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just listened to a news report, actual news report, of someone reading Taylor Swift's instagram post about her cat clawing her leg. 10 years ago this would not be normal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 01:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stories from Blockbuster Management (Shift-Lead-ASM) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 22:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some funny Blockbuster stories you have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 22:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a former shift lead/manager. I'll post mine in the comment section

Edit: specific walk-in experience stories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend's wife is really sheltered. So for my friend NSFW means not safe for wife. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 04:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If your life was a video game, what kind of game would it be, who would be the main boss and mini bosses? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 04:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hopefully original enough. Who would be your allies, if any? What powers if any would you have? 2D Sonic style? Or 3D? FPS? RPG? Or maybe you're game would be Guitar Hero or Rock Band? Lay out your game in the comments! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My school counseling blog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 02:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://schoolcounselingfilms.blogspot.com/

I'm in graduate school for school counseling so I had to make a blog and this is what I came up with. Still a work in progress but I like the premise. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the strangest movie you've ever cried while watching? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 01:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cried at the scene in 28 days later where Jim finds his parents dead holding a photograph of his younger self. I dunno why, it's just heartbreaking. It's not typically a movie I would cry in like in The Notebook or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best movie hardly anyone has seen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 10:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's what happens to your knuckles when you crack them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 00:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best candy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 08:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could only speak one phrase (up to 10 words) for the rest of your life what would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 08:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has to be in the same exact order anytime you speak, same exact phrasing and words. Anytime someone asks you a question or talks to you, this is all you can say to them in person, phone, internet, school, everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Office cats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 22:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Carolina Aquarium rescued rare 475 pound leatherback sea turtle after it was found stranded </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 11:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christian Men's Shelter in Alaska named, "The Glory Hole" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 11:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No.1 Ladies Detective Agency. I just watched the entire season and absolutely loved it. Who else liked it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 10:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why was it cancelled in 2010? I thought it was excellent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I was ten years old, my friend's family had a house rule called cuddle time.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 07:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted this as a comment on Ask Reddit on a question about what is the strangest house rule you have come across in your life. This is mine. Someone suggested I put it in /r/creepy and while I am not sure if it is up to part with some of the other posts I have seen here and I have no pictures...here is Cuddle time. 

When I was ten years old, my friend's family had something called cuddle time. When cuddle time started, my friend, his parents, his autistic brother, and his other younger brother would get into bed naked and cuddle. I'm not joking. Luckily, I didn't have to and I left the house and haven't spoken with him since. Literally I walked out the door and walked to a payphone and called my mom. Creepiest shit I ever witnessed. It irks me to this day.

I mean...the way it started out was just bizarre. Anyone ever seen Clerks 2? The way Randall looks at Elias when he tells the story of pillow pants? That's how I looked at my friend and his family when he told me it was "cuddle time" 

He started taking his clothes off in front of me, like it wasn't a big deal and it was completely normal and I should join them. In their defense, they said I didn't have to. They said it's just something they do for family unity or bonding or some shit. I dunno. I got the fuck out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wombats are an animal that poop out cubed shit. Makes shitting bricks take on a whole new meaning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 20:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Sunday December 17th, 1995 The Cleveland Browns played their last home game at Municipal Stadium against Cincinnati. The Browns won and afterwards fans tore the stadium apart as they were moving to Baltimore. I got some bench and re-framed it recently, with the ticket stub. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 04:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't the Walking Dead characters wear zombie blood to walk amongst them anymore? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 03:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by eating a piece of chocolate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 08:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Around 6PM today I ate a piece of chocolate. About five minutes later I realized I had to go poop. I went to go poop and it was one of the worst experiences I have had pooping in a long time. I was in there for two hours. 

It felt like having a double edged sword swimming around im my stomach constantly laughing at my plight. The laughing would signify the bubble/stomach groans I often felt in the middle, like my stomach was a goblet of fire. 

To make matters worse I was reading that reddit post that was on the front page a day or so ago asking the question of whether or not a fart can overtake a poop or vice versa in the intestine. I pondered this questions while pooping on my own as I would poop then bubble out some farts, then poop. 

I stood up and was exhausted to the point to where I couldn't stand. I felt 'drunk.' So I laid down. 

Five minutes later I realized I wasnt through pooping. The shear amount of force I put into each strain made me feel like I was just going to shit my colon out. I got through round two seemingly quicker, only about thirty minutes. 

I sat on my bed again. Then realized I still wasn't finished. This time it was mostly urine being forced out but yet a bubble in my stomach caused an avalanche of poop and now red blood to come out. Round three was surely the end? Nope. 

It went on like this for about eight rounds. I went and sat in my chair and watched the movie 42. After it was finished round nine started. 

I've decided not to ever eat again. Obviously, yes, I have Crohn's Disease but this is probably the worst day I've ever had. The most pain. 

I often wonder what would have happened if I didn't eat that piece of chocolate. Maybe my poops would have been spread out over time and not been as painful. I have no idea. 


TIFU by eating a piece of chocolate and then pooped for an entire day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by ordering chinese food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 20:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My name is Sean. Pronounced Shawn. It rhymes with Yawn. Not Seen.

 I drove to pickup my chinese food order which I ordered online from my apartment. It's been really snowy lately so it was a bit of a hassle driving there but I finally arrived. 

Hello, pick up?

yeah

name?

Sean

uhhhh, last name?

*******

internet order?

yeah, am I early or something?

oh, Seen.

what?

your name Seen

no, my name Sean

says Seen on ticket

says Sean on ticket

*takes my credit card*

sure its not Seen?

yeah pretty sure

why it spelled like that

ask my parents

(Asian woman in background saying something, probably talking shit)
*little boy laughs and stares at me*

thanks?

ok bye

bye

-end-

I took my food and went out into my car and drove home, which is only a 5-10 minute drive. I realized they forgot my chicken fried rice, so I drove back. When I got there it was very busy in the back behind the counter like lots of people there. The same kid came up to the counter and said,

 "Oh..Seen again"

"No..Sean...again, you forgot chicken fried rice in bag" 

*I handed him my receipt* 

*He looked at everyone in the back which was about 4-6 people and said "we forgot seen rice" and everyone started laughing.*

They handed me some rice and I left, somehow feeling ashamed because I was born with the spelling of my name Sean. A bunch of Chinese food employees at the China Wok made fun of me for it and had a nice laugh over it. 


TIFU by ordering chinese food...and then became insecure about my name...lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lammily </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 18:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were shown a Boggart (from Harry Potter) what form would it take for you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 14:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who havent seen or read Harry potter, a boggart is an amortal shape-shifting non-being that takes on the form of the viewer's worst fear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 Why do farts smell different if they are essentially the same gas? What is the science behind them.all.smelling.different? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 01:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My cat, Brian, likes to join me when I use the restroom. When I go number two, I run bathwater because it helps me pee/start. He drinks it and then lays down and wades in it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 09:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marvel's The Avengers, Harry Dean Stanton Deleted Scene from Blu Ray, I love this actor, so glad they had him in this movie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 09:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fort Myers, Florida: Man drives neighbors dead body to lawyers office </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 07:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do Octopus have eyes? (2:10 mark) ...just a weird question I feel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 04:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The movie Secretary is more hardcore s m than 50 Shades of Grey, why weren't people salivating over that? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 09:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earthworm Jim, side character in Star Wars: A New Hope </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 08:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black Lab dog body slides in the snow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 06:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
