<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1905</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 100 Worst Atrocities - Population Control, Marauder Style </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 16:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 02:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno, that stud on the left has that Chris Farley thing going on. Pretty sure he's also a famous athlete. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 07:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen them at my local Sports Authority. They seem nice enough with decent quality. It's hard to tell until you try them on and see how they fit and how well they grip.

I think people recommend the Addidas and Nike because it's what they know not necessarily because it's the best shoe.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 01:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depending upon what they are used for it might make more sense to put them on the inside.

Back when I was a kid loading UPS trucks in college we used to two those with our fingers just to mess with them. It made it look like the package was mishandled when it wasn't. 

When you make it obvious that you don't trust the people doing your work they will probably mess with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 23:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am if you want me to be. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 07:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can still buy those on ebay. I think the memory of them is better than the reality. But everyone at school used to have one of those. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 03:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol....That's exactly what being a dad is about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 03:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! You look fantastic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 03:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw this a while ago and was really impressed. Thanks for sharing this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 00:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't Chris Hanson already do this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 03:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm honestly not sure how you could say it was boring. It was predictable for certain. But it was certainly action packed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 02:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typically I'll do some back work like face pulls or rows. I also like doing some ab sets.

But as long as you're not taking up 10 minutes between sets who cares what you're doing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 18:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pacific Beach. It's in front of the Mossy Nissan dealership, I saw it last night on my way to the gym. I had to look twice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 05:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not creepy if you just give advice then back off. You could say something like "I've done the same thing, what worked for me was to lower the hooks".

For the record, I back into the bar too depending upon the rack I'm using because I hate looking into the mirror. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
