<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8344</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If You Were An Iraq War Critic, You're Probably Not Being Asked To Go On TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 06:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sodexo Reverses Course On Health Coverage After Trying To Blame Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 05:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HELP! - I am Old and have no idea what this bitcoin thing is - Is it a good thing for r/assistance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 00:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is post offering a bitcoins and I am dumbfounded. Some think it's good  and some think it's more of an insult to give a starving family 26 cents.

I do not want this subreddit to be a place where  responses to real problems are answered in pennies. But I admit I am totally ignorant to all of this.

What do all think about this? Please help me. I am clueless to all of this. Does this really offer any real assistance or is it just an insult to those in need? I know every penny counts but we are interested in real solutions, not making people beg for scraps. 

It may be a solution to a small sector of people who are into this but is it really something for the /r/assistance community?

Please give me your opinions and advice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cuban-Americans Are Getting Over Republicans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 05:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Town Mayor Blocks Fired Lesbian Police Chief From Getting Her Job Back (UPDATE) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 05:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tea Party Vs. the Republicans - I'm confused - I mean what really is the difference here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 04:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the McDaniel loss last night, I hear all this talk about how pissed the Tea Party is and how they want to split from the party. But as an outside observer,  I'm find myself confused and really can not tell the difference between the two. They have voted the same in all congressional votes. Basically no no and no and yes on Obamcare repeal.

I mean what is really the difference between the two. I just don't see it. One may talk crazier than the other but they both vote for the exact same things.

What is the actual  difference when it comes to how each of them vote or what they stand for?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Town Votes To Give Fired Lesbian Police Chief Her Job Back, Strips Mayor Of Power </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 07:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch John Oliver Verbally Pants Dr. Oz Over Dietary Supplements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 20:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans Finally Admit Why They Really Hate Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 07:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were god, what would you be saying around the water cooler about humans to the other gods? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 09:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean your really honest and candid comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Obama Declare Terrorist Threat Gone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 07:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way I can watch HBO's Bill Maher show and John Oliver's Last Week Tonight without buying HBO? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 02:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't justify paying $16 a month just for these two shows. Is there another way I can still see them. Doesn't matter if it's later in the week than they appear.

I have never done streaming before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My 3 months to HBO is up. Is there a way I can still see Bill Maher and John Oliver? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 01:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't justifying paying $16 a month just for these two shows. Is there another way I can still see them. Doesn't matter if it's later in the week than they appear.

I have never done streaming before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Christie Falsely Claims Democrats Barred Anti-Abortion Speakers From Conventions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 00:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I change the default setting of the size of images that appear when I click on an image link? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 20:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just changed my browser to Chrome and now when I click a link to an image here on reddit the picture is huge. I have to shrink it manually to see what it is.

It's obvious one of my settings somewhere is doing this. Can you tell me what setting I need to change to make these pictures appear a normal size without having to shrink it manually each time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can I get the pictures to be smaller when I click on image links here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 20:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michele Bachmann: Hillary Clinton Should Be Disqualified From The Presidency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 19:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a laugh to make us all feel a little better about being broke </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 08:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What subreddit would I post in to find information about computer devices for people who barely see? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 05:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a good friend who is losing his sight. I'm looking to get information about devices that will allow him to still use his computer. Any suggestions on which subreddit to post in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Obama Is On A Tyrannical Quest For Power, He's Not Very Good At It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 03:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do Japanese fans do after they lose in the World Cup? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 07:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News Suggests Obama Captured Benghazi Suspect To Boost Hillarys Book Tour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 22:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So do you think republicans will spin the capture of the Benghazi ring leader as a something Obama has done bad? - And by "if" I really mean "how." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 20:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They seem to have made anything and everything Obama does some sort of act of Satan. To me the question is not if they will, but how they will. 

How long do you think people are going to continue and fall for this obvious smear campaign?

As of now there hasn't been anything. But I'll bet you I can come here two days from now and that will not be the case.


----------------------

**EDIT:** (2 hours later)

Well that didn't take long:

http://thinkprogress.org/world/2014/06/17/3449917/fox-news-suggests-obama-captured-benghazi-suspect-to-boost-hillarys-presidential-prospects/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do I have to watch Dexter in the order they were made? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 07:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got Showtime free for three months. So I want to watch all the good shows while I can. But the earlier seasons aren't playing at the moment. I even checked On Demand. Can I watch them in any order? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do I have to watch Dexter in the order they were made? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 06:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think we have finally found a way to convince republicans to support immigration reform </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 06:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This One Issue Is Driving Sarah Palin To 'Renounce' Her 'Republican Ties' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 06:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I send a personal thank to folks who contributed on gofundme.com? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 00:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to send out some personal thank yous to folks that contriibuted to the Baes fund raiser. There was a link to click on the first donation that allowed me to do that. Now I can't seem to find it anymore. There are a couple of people I want to thank. How do I do that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attention Congress - This is how you are supposed to do it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 08:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reince Priebus After Eric Cantor Loss: I Don't Think GOP Is Divided </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 01:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Nightmare Continues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 00:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone near Fullerton willing to give me a ride to and from Global Meet up Day tomorrow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 06:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will pay for your gas, buy you lunch and dinner and drinks if you want 'em.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone near Fullerton that give me a ride to Global Meet up Day? I really want to go but have no way to get there and back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 06:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will pay for your gas and  buy you lunch and dinner.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some new and good epileptic jokes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 03:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been epileptic for like 40 years now and I am so sick of hearing the old shake and bake joke. Please for god's sake, tell me some new and better epileptic jokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Key for a 2002 Dodge Neon just spins when I put it in the lock. Where do I take this to get fixed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 02:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I put the key in my 2002 Doge Neon, it just spins and does not lock or unlock the car. I looked at videos online and took off the door panel. The cables going to the lock work perfectly. It's the actual part where you put the key in that isn't working.

I want to get it fixed but fear if I go to the dealer they will way over charge me for a simple job.

How would you smart guys here approach this problem. Or should I say how do you recommend someone like me approach it so I don't get over-charged hundreds of dollars for a simple problem?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Raul Labrador (Tea Party) To Run for House Majority Leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 21:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are all your jokes that have someone's name as an answer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 05:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Examples of what I'm talking about:

--------------


What do you call a one legged woman?


* Ilene

What do you call a one legged Asian woman?

* Irene

Where do these ladies work?

* IHOP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In US, political split outgrows the voting booth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 09:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now Iraq seems to want our help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 08:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraq Said to Seek U.S. Strikes on Militants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 08:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Ron Johnson votes against veterans bill citing cost </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 06:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So do you think that Dave Brat won or was it really Not-Cantor that took the election? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 05:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that the smoke is clearing, it's pretty evident that the sole issue Dave Brat ran on (immigration) was not much of a factor in this election. Virginians actually support immigration reform by a pretty decent margin. 

So could it be that the candidate that actually won was the "Not-Cantor" candidate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Eric Cantor lost - "The media will play up Cantors loss by claiming it was about immigration. They will be wrong..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 04:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Isn't it ironic? - A unanimous no vote turns into a unanimous yes on VA bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 05:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first though after hearing about Eric Cantor's defeat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 03:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In light of the awesome news tonight about Eric Cantor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 02:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rachel Maddow To Politifact: 'You Are Terrible' And Someone Should 'Sue You' (VIDEO) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 07:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] Help for one of the good guys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 06:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being the head mod of r/assistance, I have made it a policy, to make or endorse a request for anyone to avoid any conflict of interest.  But I am making a rare exception because one of our own needs us in the worst way. /u/baes is one of the nicest people I've ever met on reddit.
 
Last year in r/SantasLittleHelpers, I met him and he loved what we were doing and joined in to help in every way he could, even though he was undergoing chemotherapy for the cancer that invaded his life. 

We loved him so much, we made him a moderator in r/assistance and he instantly fit in, continuing the wonderful work he had done during Christmas. But his condition has deteriorated to the point he can barley see the screen anymore. We keep in touch because his wife reads my messages and helps him compose the ones back to me. 

It really saddens me how such a good guy is having to go through so much. And to make it worse, he and his family now face considerable financial troubles. I could go into them but lets just say they need our help in the worst way.

-----------------


**THERE ARE TWO WAYS YOU CAN HELP**

-------------------------


**Make a donation of any amount at:**

* http://www.gofundme.com/9to2is




**Purchase an item off the wish list his wife has supplied:**

* http://www.amazon.com/gp/registry/wishlist/2Y1G39U9MJZQA

This wonderful man has helped so many. Now it is our turn to come to his rescue.  He really needs us. Please find it in your heart to help with **any** amount you can. If you have ever wanted to help someone, this is the guy to help.

I will start this off with a $100 donation. Let's make this one count. He is one of own own. And like I say, one of the good ones.

**And please and send him a message to let him know /r/assistance cares and what a great guy he is:**

* http://www.reddit.com/user/Baes/


Thank you so much,

train_subject8344 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help for one of our own. And truly one of the good ones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 05:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a policy, I rarely make or endorse a request for anyone in r/assistance, more less sticky it to the top of the page.  But I am making a rare exception because one of our own needs us in the worst way. /u/baes is one of the nicest people I've ever met on reddit.
 
Last year in r/SantasLittleHelpers, I met him and he loved what we were doing and joined in to help in every way he could, even though he was undergoing chemotherapy for the cancer that invaded his life. 

We loved him so much, we made him a moderator in r/assistance and he instantly fit in, continuing the wonderful work he had done during Christmas. But his condition has deteriorated to the point he can barley see the screen anymore. We keep in touch because his wife reads my messages and helps him compose the ones back to me. 

It really saddens me how such a good guy is having to go through so much. And to make it worse, he and his family now face considerable financial troubles. I could go into them but let's just say they need our help in the worst way.

-----------------


**THERE ARE TWO WAYS YOU CAN HELP**

-------------------------


**Make a donation of any amount at:**

* http://www.gofundme.com/9to2is




**Purchase an item off the wish list his wife has supplied:**

* http://www.amazon.com/gp/registry/wishlist/2Y1G39U9MJZQA

This wonderful man has helped so many. Now it is our turn to come to his rescue.  He really needs us. Please find it in your heart to help with **any** amount you can. If you have ever wanted to help someone, this is the guy to help.

I will start this off with a $100 donation. Let's make this one count. He is one of own own. And like I say, one of the good ones.

**And please and send him a message to let him know /r/assistance cares and what a great guy he is:**

* http://www.reddit.com/user/Baes/


Thank you so much,

train_subject8344 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When a user deletes their reddit account, does their name still show up on their old posts and comments? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 05:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying figure out if someone deleted their account. Will their name still show up on their old posts and comments or will it say **"deleted"** under the part where it says who made the post or comment?

If they had been banned by the administrators, wouldn't their posts show up in light pink? I know the newer ones will but I'm not sure about the old ones.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think would be the reaction if after all these states have their federal judges strike down the gay marriage ban and then the Supreme Court reverses them all? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 06:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like the gay marriage ban is being struck down in one state after another. There is now a pending case in every single state that has a gay marriage ban. Should this trend continue and it eventually goes to the Supreme Court, how do you think the nation would react if they nullified every decision made by federal judge after judge in  making it clear the ban is unconstitutional? Of course it would be the usual 5-4 decision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama To Endorse Elizabeth Warren's Student Loan Proposal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 04:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did John McCain flip-flop on the Bergdahl deal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 04:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News Is Now Claiming That Bergdahl Is A Jihadist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 23:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> B of A in Talks to Pay At Least $12 Billion to Settle Probes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 07:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rachel Maddow mocks 50-year history of hysteria surrounding anti-pollution laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 06:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Same shit, different day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 05:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[T]his bill could prevent continued production of automobiles ...,  and is a threat to the entire American economy and to every person in America.**

Lee Iacocca, executive vice president of Ford Motor Company, in 1970, on why the government shouldnt regulate airborne contaminants that are hazardous to human health </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My god is there anything republicans won't bitch about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 06:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kings fans are getting too carried away - It can't be a coincidence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 06:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Be able to send a mod message to a user that all mods can see and participate in </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 01:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently a user can initiate a modmail thread that all mods see and can participate in. 

But a mod can only initiate a thread other mods can see. We don't have the ability to include another user in that conversation. 

My reasoning behind this is when we have issues with a user, the mod has to send a personal message to them that only he and the user  see. It would be much more useful for all the mods to see and participate in it. That way all mods know what is going and can offer their input as well. 

It would really help keep the mod team on the same page and for the user to not be singled out by one mod.

I know it can be done. It is exactly what happens when you ban a user. A message is sent from whoever banned the user to the user and to modmail that all the mods and the user can see and participate in.

I think this would help both the mods and the user. Everyone wins.

Thank you considering it. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do I send a suggestion for a tool that would help moderators. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 01:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to ask the administrators to add a tool that would help us. Basically a way we can send a mod message to a user that would start a mod thread all the mods could see.

Just like when you ban a user, that thread appears under the mod that sent it, but all the mods can see it and participate in it.

This way when we have an issue we need to communicate to a user, all the mods will see it and can participate in it. Current we can only do that when the user initiates the thread.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the way to send a message to a user that comes from all the mods? Like how it starts a mod thread when you ban a user </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 00:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you ban a user, it starts a mod thread that all the mods can see and also the person you banned. You have a mod thread with the user and the mods.

Is there a way to initiate that type of thread from a mod so all the mods will be in on something when we send messages to a user?


-------------

**Edit:** The title should read:

 ***Is there a way to send a message...,*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big Earls (Texas Restaurant That Refused 'Fag' Customers) Now Being Touted As Gay Bar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 03:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John McCain: Tom Coburn Is The 'Best Possible Replacement' For VA Secretary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 23:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank God it's Saturday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 22:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The one thing that is missing from this subreddit's header photo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 09:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me right now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 06:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House rejects bid to allow Gitmo transfer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 00:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Set you DVRs - Hillary Clinton is going on FOX News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 05:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton Is Going On Fox News To Promote Her New Book </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 05:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House GOP Backs Tax Breaks That Add $300 Billion To Deficit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 00:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Boehner: 'I'm Not Qualified To Debate The Science Over Climate Change' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 20:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The actual draw down of troops under Obama (graph) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 08:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Defends Controversial Policy of Not Invading Countries for No Reason </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 02:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What your state is searching for more than anything else </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 06:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Delays Homeland Security Deportation Review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 06:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can people still submit link post to my subreddit when I have the box checked that says text posts only? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 05:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run /r/assistance and currently it is allowing users to submit linked posts. It never used to allow that. It is important to us that only text posts be allowed.

I have the box checked under subreddit settings to **text posts only.**

Yet it still gives users the option to make a linked post. We've been text post only for a long time now. I don't know how or why it is behaving this way.

Any guesses?

-------------------------

**Edit:**

Looks like timotab figured it out. It's only letting the mods do it. Thanks timotab! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One Of America's Dirtiest Coal Plants Had Some Dire Predictions. It Was Wrong. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 02:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many subscribers does reddit have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 21:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to know what I can site as reddit's readership. So about how many subscribers and maybe an estimate of their total readership. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has any of you had their Reddit Enhancement Suite disappear? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 01:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wondering if it's just me. I actually still have the little cog wheel button to change my settings, but all of the RES features have disappeared. 

Is it just me or are the rest of you having the same problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House Vows Defense Bill Veto Over Gitmo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 14:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What republicans who believe in climate change are saying to Pat Sajak </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 07:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What republicans who believe in climate change are saying to Pat Sajak </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 05:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something really nice i can send someone who had to put their dog to sleep? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 23:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did this room addition last year for my brother's boss. It took several months and I developed a very special bond with their dog. I just heard they had to put him to sleep. I'm not super close to these folks but my brother told me his bosses' wife told him to make sure he let me know. I thought I would send something like flowers but I wasn't sure that would be appropriate. What do you think? Have any other ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Most Delighful Man In America' Joe Biden Gets Asked To Prom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 04:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate Change Will Hurt Nations' Credit Ratings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 04:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Learn to speak Benghazi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 00:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A salute to Anaheim's version of the great one - Teemu Selanne </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 06:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A salute to Anaheim's version of the great one - Even the LA Kings remain on the ice after winning the series to salute the great Teemu Selanne </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 06:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The California Drought Is Far From Over, And The Entire State Is Suffering </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 06:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Come join us to collect signatures to raise the minimum wage at the Fullerton Costco this Monday at 10:00 AM - We are doing at Costco because they are a great example of how paying a fair wage works </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 03:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What should I put on my protest sign at a raise the minimum wage protest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 02:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a user that needs to sign in and it is telling he has to wait five hours. Is this something reddit does? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 01:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run /r/Assistance and I have a user that needs to communicate with someone right now because they are helping him with an urgent problem.

He made the post with a throwaway account but I have his other account too that he hasn't used for over a year. But now it says he has to wait five hours to sign in to either account. I've never heard of anything like this. Is there a reason they do this and is there anything I can do to help him get around this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need your opinion about this statement for an article I am writing: Not all republicans are racists, but for the most part all racists are republicans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 03:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans Are Already Ignoring The Benghazi Special Committee Theyve Been Begging For </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 00:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Show This To The Next Person Who Says High Minimum Wages Kill Jobs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 23:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Casey Kasem Found! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 09:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today in Fullerton: I either need to move or get a new thermometer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 03:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another Federal Judge Trolls Scalia While Striking Down Gay Marriage Ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 08:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OMG - Stop the presses! This is the the story of the century! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 07:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul Threatens To Hold Up Fed Nominees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 02:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Boehner: Democrats Are Probably Fundraising Off Benghazi 'Just Like We Are' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 02:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is ATT the only cable provider blacking out the Kings/Duck playoff hockey games on NBCSN in the Anaheim area? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 22:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've talked with so many other people and no one but U-Verse subscribers in Anaheim (Fullerton) are being deprived of the game. This is the first time in LA sports history that two local teams are meeting head-to-head in a playoff and the most devoted fans are the only ones who don't get to see it. 

And the only reason is we made the mistake of having U-Verse. ATT has really screwed us big time. I've called them and can't even get an explanation. They say it's because it's on a local channel which is a lie. It was during the regular season but not for the playoffs.

And it's not like there should be some contract dispute that doesn't allow it. DISH, Direct, Time Warner and everyone else but U-verse people get it.



-------------------------------

**EDIT:**

After spending two days on the phone being given every excuse in the world and finally being told it is just blacked for me, and there were no options for me to get it..., for some reason I am now getting it. I think I was more frustrated by them not being able to give me a valid reason and telling me lie after after lie. But I am watching the game right now.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ykpjFjsEdl4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Oliver's take on raunchy political ads - The best one is at the 9:59 mark: Mitch McConnell: No dick is older, whiter or wrinklier - (Very NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 08:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are you folks with ATT U-Verse able to view the Kings/Duck Hockey games on NBCSN? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 23:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The series of the year is being blacked out on my TV (Fullerton, CA) and ATT says it's because they have not negotiated a contract with NBCSN. I think they are BSing me because I still get the channel but it blacks out just during the Kings/Duck game. I near yo folks in Los Angeles are getting it but we in Orange County do not? That does not make sense.

My question to you out there in LA, are you getting the games? And what city do you live in? I am hassling with them right now and need to know whether or not I am going to quit my service.



-------------------------------

**EDIT:**

After spending two days on the phone being given every excuse in the world and finally being told it is just blacked for me, and there were no options for me to get it..., for some reason I am now getting it. I think I was more frustrated by them not being able to give me a valid reason and telling me lie after after lie. But I am watching the game right now.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ykpjFjsEdl4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are any other people who have U-Verse not able to get the Kings/Ducks hockey game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 23:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The series of the year is being blacked out on my TV and ATT says it's because they have not negotiated a contract with NBCSN. I think they are BSing me because I still get the channel but it blacks out just during the Kings/Duck game. People in Los Angeles are getting it but we in Orange County do not? 

My question to you out there is are you getting the games. And what city do you live in? I am hassling with them right now and need to know whether or not I am going to quit my service.

-------------------------------

**EDIT:**

After spending two days on the phone being given every excuse in the world and finally being told it is just blacked for me, and there were no options for me to get it..., for some reason I am now getting it. I think I was more frustrated by them not being able to give me a valid reason and telling me lie after after lie. But I am watching the game right now.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ykpjFjsEdl4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uverse is blocking out the Stanley Cup for people in LA - We are missing half the second round - You suck U-verse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 05:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Kings/Ducks hockey games have been blacked out for my area. (Orange County, California) - Not only that, they blacked out the end of the games before that so I wasted hours watching it only to have the last 30 minutes of the game blacked out. They are not blacking them out on Direct TV or Dish from what I hear. They are just being dick heads.

 

What in the heck is going on? This is ridiculous. This is the first time in history two LA sports teams are meeting each other in a playoff and we in the local area don't get to see it. Seriously I am really frustrated about this.



-------------------------------

**EDIT:**

After spending two days on the phone being given every excuse in the world and finally being told it is just blacked for me, and there were no options for me to get it..., for some reason I am now getting it. I think I was more frustrated by them not being able to give me a valid reason and telling me lie after after lie. But I am watching the game right now.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ykpjFjsEdl4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uverse is blocking out the Stanley Cup for people in LA - I mean this is BS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 05:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Kings/Ducks hockey games have been blacked out for my area. (Orange County, California) - Not only that, they blacked out the end of the game before that so I wasted hours watching it only to have the last 30 minutes of the game blacked out. These games are all sold out long ago. There is no reason to black them out excpet to just be mean.

 
-------------------------------

**EDIT:**

After spending two days on the phone being given every excuse in the world and finally being told it is just blacked for me, and there were no options for me to get it..., for some reason I am now getting it. I think I was more frustrated by them not being able to give me a valid reason and telling me lie after after lie. But I am watching the game right now.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ykpjFjsEdl4
What in the heck is going on? This is ridiculous. This is the first time in history two LA sports teams are meeting each other in a playoff and we in the local area don't get to see it. Seriously I am really frustrated about this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> #Randbrackets, The Fun New Out-Of-Context Game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 04:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All Science Is Wrong, Concludes Esteemed Fox News Panel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 04:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Millions of Americans Who Need Jobs Want Congress to Get to Bottom of This Benghazi Thing First </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 01:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawmaker Ignores His Own Facts To Make Debunked Benghazi Claim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 21:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the Kings Duck game blacked out for you guys too? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 04:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have ATT U-Verse and the game is supposed to be on NBCSN. But the channel is black right now. Are they actually blacking out a sold out game for us? If so, does anyone know where I can watch it on the computer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do men always want to beat up the guy he thinks his girlfriend is cheating with when it's his slut girlfriend who really caused the event? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 03:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, men go nuts and want to kick the shit out some guy messing around with his girlfriend. But more times than not, it is the girlfriend who is responsible for the cheating. Unless it's some case of rape, the girl is the one to blame. Why does he take it out on the other guy? Is this a leftover Neanderthal reaction? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do birds pooping in your pool present any health risks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 05:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simple question I need answered because I am being harassed by my park manager because some birds I fed pooped in the pool. Do a couple birds pooping in a pool really present a health problem?

Edit: I'm talking about a couple ducks. Is it reason to shut down a pool? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Economy is expected to improve as year progresses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 07:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans overwhelming approve of the individual things Obama is doing about Russia/Ukraine - But at the same time they overwhelming disapprove of how he is handling it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 04:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cliven Bundy Says He's 'Just Like Rosa Parks' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 07:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cliven Bundy Says He's 'Just Like Rosa Parks' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 07:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Sterling (LA Clippers own) to Receive NAACP Achievement Award </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 07:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mitch McConnell: 'Every Crazy Liberal' Has Heard Of Me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 04:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress returns to work to do the bare minimum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 20:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> G-7 nations agree to more sanctions on Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 06:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Raise the wage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 06:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans blast rancher Clive Bundy for forgetting to use the usual GOP racial code words </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 01:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US: Russia has days, not weeks to follow accord </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 06:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowdens Camp: Staged Putin Q A Was a Screw-Up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 04:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT][SONG] - "Tune in the news to see who's shooting who" - An old song by a pretty famous artist - It's not a rap song - probably from the 70s or 80s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 00:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember this song from long ago. When I google it all I get is a bunch of violent rap songs. This song is nothing like that. I think it's an acoustical guitar piece by a pretty famous artist from the 70s or 80s. And the song is not violent at all. 

The lyrics may be "turn on the news o see who's shooting who" or "tune in the news to see who's shooting who." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rush Limbaugh Is In Ruins - Bad News Coming From Every Direction - Including The Right </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 23:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There Is An Epidemic Of Republicans Plagiarizing From Rand Paul </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 06:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans Aren't Moving On From Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 23:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Economic Costs of Inaction on Immigration Reform </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 08:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boston Marathon bombings: 'We endure,' Joe Biden says at memorial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 21:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Captain Kirk gets stage three space herpes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 09:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Democrat: 'Not All' Republicans Are Racist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 21:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bush draws boos from conservatives </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 07:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Government Listens To Lobbyists And The Wealthy, Not You And Me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 07:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pastor Banned From Feeding Homeless Because He Doesn't Have A Food Truck Permit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 02:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Computer taking a couple seconds to catch up with my typing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 20:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of a sudden it takes a couple seconds for the keystrokes and mouse clicks to show up on the screen after I enter them.  I have done malware and virus scans. No help there. I have defragemented, and I still have all kinds of space left on my computer. It also doesn't register anything after I get six or seven characters ahead. So I have to type five ore six letters and then sit and wait for it to catch up. And even then some of the words I typed aren't there. 

It is extremely irritating.

I have Windows 7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boston Marathon Survivor Adrianne Haslet-Davis Leaves 'Meet The Press' Set In Tears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 20:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The biggest idiot I've ever seen on Wheel of fortune in my life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 05:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama: Right to vote under threat in the US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 00:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sexy Cat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 07:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservative Newspaper Mocks Female Candidate In Sexist Editorial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 01:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting Walmart Workers Off Food Stamps Would Cost Customers Barely Anything </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 00:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Insane political ad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 23:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What NCIS-type shows would my 91 year old mother love </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 05:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 91 year mom has watched nothing but NCIS for years and years. She is finally sick of it. I mean that's all she watches. I need to find her some shows she will like.

She has watched nothing but NCIS   Dateline. Keep in mind how difficult it is to get her to do anything new. So nothing too complicated and/or hard to get into. Got to be something she will like from the get go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate Passes Unemployment Extension, House In No Hurry To Do The Same </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 03:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NO Spoilers] After watching the first five episodes I have to ask, Why are these people so into buttfucking? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 03:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why hasn't the media covered the discrimination bill passed in Mississippi a few days ago? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 01:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Arizona was going to pass it, it was the lead story for over a week. And they didn't even pass it. Now that Mississippi passed it, I have barely heard a mention about it in the news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When will we get to see House of Cards - Season three? [US] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 09:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long do we have to wait for season three? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas Nullifies all guns laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 07:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think my cat is a republican </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 02:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan Ready To Intercept North Korean Missiles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 21:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2" ABS drain pipe broke under the house where it meets the main 4" sewer line </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 08:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pipe broke and left the inch or so that inserts into the female part of the main sewer pipe. It's flush with the the female sleeve. Here is the generic photo of the connection:

http://cloudfront.zorotools.com/product/full/1CNT9_AS01.JPG

It is a 4" to 2"

I would like to fix this without having to replace the piece above. I just need to get that one or two inch piece out of that fitting so I can put a new pipe in there. Someone  told me to chip it out with a screwdriver but I am afraid I will break the female part in the process.

Another person said there might be some kind of drill bit that looks like a spade that I can use to drill it out. I have no idea what it is called or if it even exists.

At this point I'm not sure how to proceed. I was hoping for some suggestions on how to chip or drill it out with more ease and without breaking the female part of the fitting. Or any other methods you might have up your sleeve.


----------------------------

**EDIT**

Off the advice of a redditor, I used a rubber tee with a clamp and it fit over the female part of the coupling.

It looked like this:

[Rubber Tee](http://i.tfcdn.com/img2/O6qHNVwAY3oleYQhPbEoJTWPIaOkpMBKXz9TrzwxJzexqCQzNzE9tVgvOT9XP1M_t0DfwEDfwFDfwlTf3ALMNjAwtDA1twDSppbxAUaWBuZGhvGmBgYRQKyXVZAOAA**/fvUG-v8A.B)


I had given the wrong size in my post but was still able to find a fitting that worked. It ended up being the 2" opening off of a 3 X 2 tee. But all that matters is it worked. Once again washing clothes without flooding the underneath of my house.

Thank goodness for reddit. :D

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ABS drain pipe broke under the house right at the male part where it inserts into the female main sewer pipe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 06:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pipe broke and left the inch or two part that inserts into the female part of the main sewer pipe. Here is the generic photo of the connection:

http://cloudfront.zorotools.com/product/full/1CNT9_AS01.JPG

It is a 4" to 2"

I would like to fix this without having to replace the piece above. I just need to get that one or two inch piece out of that fitting so I put a new pipe in there. Someone  told me to chip it out with a screwdriver but I am afraid I will break the female part in the process. But at this point I'm not sure I have any other alternative. That is unless you folks out might have one. Or maybe have some suggestions how to chip it out with more ease and without breaking the female part of the fitting.


----------------------------

**EDIT**

Off the advice of a redditor, I used a rubber tee with a clamp and it fit over the female part of the coupling.

It looked like this:

[Rubber Tee](http://i.tfcdn.com/img2/O6qHNVwAY3oleYQhPbEoJTWPIaOkpMBKXz9TrzwxJzexqCQzNzE9tVgvOT9XP1M_t0DfwEDfwFDfwlTf3ALMNjAwtDA1twDSppbxAUaWBuZGhvGmBgYRQKyXVZAOAA**/fvUG-v8A.B)


I had given the wrong size in my post but was still able to find a fitting that worked. It ended up being the 2" opening off of a 3 X 2 tee. But all that matters is it worked. Once again washing clothes without flooding the underneath of my house.

Thank goodness for reddit. :D
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would the US do if Russia decided it would no longer transport astronauts to the International Space Station? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 05:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If tensions grew and a new cold war escalated to the point where the two countries were hurting each other at every step. What would the US do and how would the rest of the  world react  if they refused to transport out astronauts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> God I love this guy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 22:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama: Paul Ryan's budget is a stinkburger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 03:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News: Obamacare Numbers Are 'Phony' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 01:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Havasu Falls: Paradise by any other name - Photo by Cody Lewis (OC) - [5472 x 3648] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 00:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Havasu Falls: Paradise by any other name - Photo by Cody Lewis (OC) - [5472 x 3648] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 00:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Havasu Falls - Paradise by any other name - Photo by Cody Lewis [5472 x 3648] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 23:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Boehner's Replacement For Obamacare: A Promise To Replace Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 21:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans Administration Disability Claims Backlog Drops by 44 Percent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 06:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> March Was First Month Without U.S. Fatalities in Iraq or Afghanistan In 11 Years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 06:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Advances Bill Calling For More Weather Forecasting, Less Climate Change Research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 01:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everything Wrong With Humanity, In One Short Animation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 07:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Statistics and Climate Science: Roger Pielke Missed the Mark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 22:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Florida Republican Fights To Keep Battlefield Focused On The Confederacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 03:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama: Romney Was Wrong On Russia, Still Is </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 03:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Kicking Out Russia, the G8 Is Now The G7 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 02:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Clinton: 'Everybody Can Serve Everywhere' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 04:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blow By Blow: A Comprehensive Timeline Of The GOPs 4-Year Battle To Kill Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 19:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Romney: Obama's 'Naivete' On Putin Helped Lead To Crisis In Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 18:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans hate Rand Pauls libertarianism. They just dont know it yet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 22:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know what the difference is between a pizza and a republican? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 07:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pizza will feed a family of four. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul Compares Republican Party To Domino's Pizza </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 05:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for some sort of sealant to stop water from leaking in my shed from the ground </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 02:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a wood shed, built several years ago resting on a cement slab. There are paver stones that go right up to it. In fact about and inch under. Water leaks under the bottom plate and gets the floor of my shed wet.  Is there a sealant I can buy that will stick to both the shed and the stone an will prevent water from leaking in:

http://i.imgur.com/eUoZWq8.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
