<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject615</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We`re Done! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 06:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 05:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike and Rachel killed me tonight! they were so cute, but then she cheated! I was proud of Mike for not forgiving her right away but then I wanted them back togetherIm so conflicted! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pretty Little Liars 'Scream for me' Thoughts... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 07:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its so obvious Hanna hates Ali. She is avoiding her big time! Im telling youHanna joined Mona. She cant face her. Shes drinking and stressed because shes afraid the girls might find out.
    Rhonda is so cute with her root beer and crunchy cheese doodles.
    I think E. Lamb was fired and pushed out of town by A.
    Poor Ella. I have a feeling they moved the wedding up because she got pregnant. Zach is an Asshole!!!!
    Did Sydney slip up on purpose about NY or by accident. (Id love to hear your thoughts on this!)
    I want to hear what everyone thinks about Alis behavior. All fake?
    I was shocked it was Noel who broke in the Marins house! When Ali first blurted his name out i had a heart attacki thought she was going to say he was A or something tp do with A!!
    Just a side thought..didnt Mona also ride horses? Remember she went with Kate and her friend when Hanna went? 

Thats all i have. Any comments?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 05:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 07:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soooo we still don't know what Parrish is....And he doesnt know what he is either obviously. He was too funny when he was like Im only worth 5 dollars?!??? Loved this episode!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 07:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks you 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 07:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thx a lot!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone found a Teen Wolf S04E06 link? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 06:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 17:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much! I`m going to try it! Have a good one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 16:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the input! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did you think of the new Manhattan tv show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 16:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Itll bring armies to their knees. Cities will disappear in the blink of an eye. The world will be united in peace by the most just and noble country in the history of mankind. Or it will burn to the ground...

Anyone seen it? Is it worth it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 07:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True Blood tonight was ridiculously boring. I mean come on, this is a final season! Dont put us to sleep! I want some action and some oh shit! moments, preferably lots of them!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> True Blood Saison 7 Episode 6 'Karma' Resume </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 07:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 15:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was kinda sure about that...well that`s that! After all they are husband and wife....in real life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poster and Images from "Air" starring Norman Reedus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 15:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
