<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4879</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 05:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot it in people- broken social scene

In the aeorplane over the sea- neutral milk hotel

Illmatic- nas

Music from big pink- the band

Sgt. Peppers lonely hearts club band- the Beatles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 04:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fair enough, but i think the consequences of failing this course arguably outweigh the annoyance of taking and additional half credit, at least in my situation, being an english student. do you need a science credit for a commerce degree? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 04:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, i got 30/60. our marks were also 6 points higher than they would have been, because she boosted them. i might end up dropping psych, im too worried i might fail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 04:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> try redreader beta, not super popular, but awesome nonetheless  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 01:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think you still get the breadth requirement. do you know when the marks will be available? I'm in the same credit/no credit situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 00:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im pretty sure i bombed it, i spent way too much time reviewing lecture notes, instead of studying the texbtook. might drop the course and try to get into a big idea course next year to fulfill the science credit for my degree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone who's taken psych100, got tips for first midter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 00:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> class is taught by prof luby, what do I need to know for the midterm? her outline was incredibly vague </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 05:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is their any way to access the marking scheme short of having an awkward conversation with a ta?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
