<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject374</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 11:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Melbourne is beautiful but it's also intimidatingly huge! I'm nervous about finding a job and meeting new people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 11:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a job lined up - will start applying in May. I'll be staying with a friend and her family for a bit until I get on my feet. Savings - a bit, moving back home before I move so I can save a bit more. I have a handful of friends there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 11:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jigglypuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 11:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now and Then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hiya! I'm moving from Auckland to Melbourne on the 1st of June, I don't have cold feet but I am getting nervous - I'd appreciate any tips you lovely folk may have. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 11:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 10:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finding movie trivia and other info about movies i've watched </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 09:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've done the same with Give Your Heart a Break </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 09:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit..that sounds oddly arousing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit Gleeks - what's your favourite song on Glee? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 09:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 09:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're brave, I wouldn't want glitter getting into my japs eye (if I had one). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 09:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sleepers, Inception, Schindler's List, The Godfather 1 - 2 - 3, The Silence of the Lambs, Saving Private Ryan, Braveheart, Dances with Wolves, The Pianist, Scarface, The Green Mile, Legends of the Fall, About Time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 09:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In West Philadelphia, born and raised... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 09:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ben Folds Five - Brick https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Wt5EHAqhR1c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 08:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Wedding Singer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 08:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta work to pay the bills </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 08:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brothers and I used to get hit with a black leather horse whip. 
I remember being five years old and I was punished for getting sunburnt during a school trip. My mother just watched.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 08:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time, good friends and having hobbies helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 08:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't ride a bike  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 08:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fancy soap - $30 sigh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your theme song and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 08:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 08:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with you on that one buddy!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 08:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad Sam Mendes didn't follow on from Quantum of Solace and kinda rebooted instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 08:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't watched many Bond films but Skyfall is def my fav out of the ones I've seen. Looking forward to Spectre - coming out Nov 2015 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 07:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She didn't charge at all - she's a friend of a friend who just wanted to help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 01:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I reckon the unsub is still out there somewhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 00:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had an experience several years ago when a friend encountered something overseas and brought it back with him, it then proceeded to attach itself to me. 
It would present itself to me as a really strong pungent shit smell right under my nose and no one else could smell it, on three separate occasions - my workplace, outside my friend's house and at my mother's house. 

A psychic who was a friend of a friend told me that it was a trickster and had latched itself onto me because i'm sensitive but don't realise it therefore I can't protect myself. 
I was lucky because this trickster had the potential to do some real damage. She banished it to another plane and cloaked me in protection. 

It was the most bizarre experience I've ever had and I still don't know what to make of it to this day. I sure as hell don't tell many people out of fear they'll think i'm nutso.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 00:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We needed to feed 7 of us, after combining all of our chump change (college/uni students) we went to the gas station and bought a 5 pack of ramen and a pack of precooked Sizzlers sausages. 

We cooked the ramen and sausages, added a bit of chilli powder and ate using what cooking utensils we could find at my mate's flat since he only owned one fork.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 00:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back  forearms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 23:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> March 7th </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 23:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone talking about papercuts in eyeballs. Currently wincing :s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 23:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quirky sense of humour, kind heart and a genuinely caring nature </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 23:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My plans if i'm trying to come up with an excuse to avoid going somewhere  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 23:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> M - Skyfall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 23:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The need to get blood tests done to check my cholesterol levels and the necessity of power naps otherwise I fade pretty quickly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 00:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keanu Reeves </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 23:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are things that I'm working on:

Distractions and realising you just have to keep on going, the world doesn't stop for you so that you can curl up into a corner and cry. Set yourself little goals and then take steps to achieve them. Give yourself a purpose. 

Learning coping mechanisms so that you can roll with the punches also helps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 23:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being two-faced - I tell myself that I do it to try and keep the peace but really I guess I'm just being fake, pretending I like people when I think they're morons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 23:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That and people shooting their snot out of their nose and onto the ground like a nose cannon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 23:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who sneeze or cough without covering their mouths when other people are around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 03:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When are people going to realise that you catch more flies with honey? If you're going to be an asshole, why would we go out of our way for you? I guess there are too many cases of assholes stomping their feet and getting what they want. I get lots of oh yeah well company X is offering me this which is way better...well then sir - why are you still talking to me, why don't you FUCK OFF THEN?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 02:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahahaha desperation... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who work in Customer Service, who are the worst kind of customers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 02:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 01:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who don't take ownership and blame everyone or everything else for their problems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 12:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lee Pace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 12:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smile at strangers without expecting a smile in return  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 12:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beefcake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 12:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to a Dr or dermatologist and ask about isotretinoin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 12:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arrogant know-it-alls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
