<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1185</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 19:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think it's a shame he doesn't write the blockbusters he works on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 19:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Pale Rider. I feel like it's Eastwood's forgotten Western - or maybe that's Hang 'Em High. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 18:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Season 3 was half its length, it would have been the best season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 17:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, less visually interesting. In fact ugly and messy. The action in this episode is actually horrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 17:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I didn't think Charlie Work was all that funny, the plot was a bit stupid and I struggled to suspend my disbelief for a lot of it. Frankly, the cinematography still isn't that great. The show still feels like it's being filmed by three friends for $100 and IMO that's part of the charm, but it doesn't create good looking shots. In fact, a lot of the shots were pretty terrible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 17:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a lot happened in 5a, but they sure made up for it with a lot of great moments. Do you remember the train episode? Jesus! That was awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 17:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Game of Thrones and Homeland experienced a drop in quality. I think the golden age is well and truly over.

I keep looking at shows I thought were great last year and now I'm not too fond Hannibal has forgone story for the sake of artiness, Community found its way further up Dan Harmon's arse, Better Call Saul was tremendously disappointing and I have nothing but low expectations for the next season of Fargo. Also Parks and Rec is over. :'(

I've enjoyed Archer, Daredevil, and even The Walking Dead more than I've enjoyed the aforementioned shows. The Walking Dead!! I think the golden age of television is over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 17:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jon Favreau's dialogue is so underapreciated, I think it's a shame he doesn't write the blockbusters he works on. I imagine his voice working best on Shazam! His dialogue through a teenaged voice would be interesting to hear and I also think Shazam's DC's funnest hero and Favreau is Marvel's funnest director (sorry Gunn and Whedon fans).

Other than that, probably Branagh to Aquaman. If anyone is going to give the Big Orange the respect he deserves, it'll be him. Also, he'll probably add some Shakespearean touches which would be much appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 11:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! I knew this one!

/u/train_subject1185 - 1: Life - 99 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 11:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the right answer. M </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 09:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, but it was months after Peter died when they announced the new Ultimate Spider-Man. I get the sense that Peter wasn't just killed off to be replaced. It makes a lot more sense in the continuity of Ultimate Spider-Man which I'd recommend reading as it's very accessible for a non-comic book reader like yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 09:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's got to earn that paycheck somehow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 09:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything pop culture knows about the character comes from the movies which was a pretty inaccurate depiction of the character back then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 08:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan Ball deserves a mention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 07:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Dollar Trilogy. Clint is a real prick in those movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 07:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was eleven-ish and watched The Good, The Bad and The Ugly with my dad. The finale is almost completely superfluous to the narrative and could have been done in three or four shots, yet Leone takes five minutes to express relationships between characters, build tension, show off some pretty Spanish landscapes and play some kick-ass music. That's when I realised what film was capable of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 07:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's kind of weird because it sounds so fake, yet it's so enthralling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 04:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few months and it's working great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 18:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd prefer to see him take his Hal Jordan into Live Action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 18:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dark Reign and Annihilation would make my day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 17:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why Big Koala instead of Des Kangaroo?
 
I now feel like an idiot. Of course I should run Des Kangaroo. I probably left it out for some stupid reason like the card art annoys me.

I'll add Naturia Beast.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 17:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man, you've been very helpful. I feel like this deck is going to run a lot faster now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 17:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I think that's helped a lot.

-1 United We Stand

-1 Closed Forest

-1 Mirror Force

-1 Kalantosa, Mystical Beast of the Forest

+2 Royal Decree

+2 Mystical Space Typhoon

+2 Effect Veiler


This puts the deck at 42 cards, do you think that may be too big? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 16:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. You've got me all excited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 15:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Sorry to be doubtful, but do you have a source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [R/F] Koalas/Raccoons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 15:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The aim is to try and summon monsters from the extra deck as quickly as possible using the Raccoons' swarming abilities or Obedience Schooled. You can do this by using Junk Synchron to special summon a level two beast from the grave to synchro summon a level 5 *or* XYZ two level 2 beasts to summon Number 64: Ronin Raccoon Sandayu *or* searching for the material for Koala-Koala - with Pon-Poko, the Raccoon Rascal/Baby Raccoon Tantan or Obedience Schooled - and using Polymerization to fusion summon it. Using United We Stand whilst Number 64: Ronin Raccoon Sandayu is on the field can lead to some strong tokens. Tokens from Number 64: Ronin Raccoon Sandayu can have their attack borrowed by Junk Warrior to give it ridiculous attack. You can do a lot of these combos within the first turn creating a FTK.

I have no idea how this stacks up against the current meta, but I've really enjoyed using it and felt like sharing.


 **Monsters [24]**
 
 * Big Koala
 * Junk Synchron x3
 * King of the Swamp x3
 * Tree Otter x2
 * Mogmole
 * Wind-Up Kitten
 * Pon-Poko, the Raccoon Rascal x3
 * Valerifawn, Mystical Beast of the Forest x2
 * Kalantosa, Mystical Beast of the Forest x3
 * Sea Koala x2
 * Baby Raccoon Tantan x3
 
 **Spells [15]**
 
 * Raigeki
 * Polymerization x3
 * Ayer's Rock Sunrise x3
 * Rank-Up Magic Astral Force
 * Obedience Schooled x3
 * United We Stand x2
 * Closed Forest x2
 
 **Traps [1]**
 
 * Mirror Force

**Extra Deck [15]**

 * Master of Oz
 * Koala-Koala x3
 * [Any four level 5 Synchro monsters, I opted for Frozen Fitzgerald, T.G. Hyper Librarian, Armades, Keeper of Boundries and Ally of Justice Catastor.]
 * Junk Warrior
 * Diamond Dire Wolf x2
 * Daigusto Phoenix
 * Number 64: Ronin Raccoon Sandayu x3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 14:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a deck list I could peek at? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 10:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three Photon Satellites and the Calculator or XYZing Number 64 then getting a token with high attack and Junk Warrioring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 10:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mixed them with Koalas and have found that pretty effective. I just use a lot of staple beast cards and support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 09:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robbie Reyes wouldn't be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 09:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two = tons? Okay then. Moon Knight is capable of holding 13 episodes IMO and I think Pascal is a great choice white or not (although, I would have preferred him as Doctor Strange). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 09:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if it's Terry Crews? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 09:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Teen Titans: Year One any good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 09:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Southern Bastards. It's gloriously written and really shows Aaron and Latour at their best. A TV show would be fantastic, but I believe there needs to be more source material for it. Maybe in three-four years. I wish we were getting more than one arc every eight months though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 09:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want change to have a sense of progression. My favorite period of Avengers comics is the 2004-2010 run of crossovers (Avengers Disassembled, House of M, Civil War, World War Hulk, Secret Invasion, Dark Reign and Siege). I love this period as characters grow and change. We got a new Cap, Thor died and had a change of setting, Iron Man battled inner demons and went from being on top of the world to the bottom of it and Hawkeye went from hiding in Eastern Europe to leading the New Avengers and calling out Norman Osbourne on live television. These were clear character arcs that lasted years and as a result felt like advancing seasons of a TV show - exactly how /u/AlphaNeonic seemed to want comics. I just wish some of the actual events had been a bit less crap and the solo books contributed to the overall story arc a bit more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 09:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but the mythology is weaker. Although the fight scenes are why most will watch it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 08:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Raid 2 is a much richer experience for seeing the first one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 08:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Raid  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 16:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a feeling this is becoming the next underrated gem, but who cares when its that good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 16:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Godzilla director? Awesome. I think that movie would have been great with a stronger script. His visuals were awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 16:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ketchup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 15:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everybody should just watch Slow West anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You wouldn't try to adapt the fucking Mona Lisa into a movie.

Don't give them ideas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on, the worst Marvel movies are only mediocre. Nothing as tragic as Green Lantern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather see their Transformers or TMNT than Bay's bastardisation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would it? That's what they did for 50 years before The Dark Knight Returns and that's what they still do whenever Mark Waid or Grant Morrison writes the characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 00:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he wasn't too old, that'd be perfect casting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 14:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, this isn't a dispute. The comics are worldwide - I'm a fan in Europe and I know of many fans in Asian countries where they are translated. The movies are about making money the most efficient way they can and diversity is one of them.

TL;DR - Comics are **global**, movies are about money, you should fact check. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 14:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So pretty much a different deck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 12:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not really doing this, are you? Literally millions of people in China went to see Age of Ultron. Literally millions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 08:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cloak and Dagger appeared in like 2 issues of The Runaways. Replacing them with Doc Strange wouldn't make too big a difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 08:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't want Nico without the rest of the Runaways, but Cho is awesome. You could plop him into most Phase 3 movies and he'd work. Imagine if he was one of Peter's classmates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lightsworn-Timelords? What's that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 05:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever since AMC set up thousands of new cinemas in China. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 05:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. It'd be the wrong decision. If we had to have an Asian hero, I was rooting for The Wasp as she's Asian in teh Ultimate Universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [R/F] Photon Satellite Deck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 04:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The aim of this deck is to to win via three methods.

A) Use a set of Photon Satellites to reach an absurdly high level and attack with the Calculator

B) Use Junk/Road Synchron in combination with the Photon Satellites to synchro summon high level monsters

C) Use the Photon Satellites to XYZ a range of monsters

D) Use Junk Warrior whilst the The Calculator is on the field with a really high attack

**Monsters [19]**

* Photon Thrasher *x2* 
* Road Synchron
* Shining Angel *x3*
* Honest *x2*
* Junk Synchron *x3*
* Ryko, Lightsworn Hunter *x2*
* The Calculator *x3*
* Photon Satellite *x3*

**Spells [16]**

* One for One
* Polymerization
* Accellight *x2*
* Machine Duplication *x2*
* Upstart Goblin *x3*
* Gold Sarcophagus
* Inferno Reckless Summon *x3*
* Photon Lead

**Traps [5]**

* Mirror Force *x2*
* Call of the Haunted *x3*

**Extra Deck [15]**

* Twin Photon Lizard
* Road Warrior
* Stardust Dragon
* Black Rose Dragon
* Goyo Guardian
* Frozen Fitzgerald
* Junk Warrior
* Ally of Justice Catastor
* Underworld Fighter Balmung
* Number 23: Lancelot, Ghost Knight of the Underworld
* Constellar Pleiades
* Number 50: Blackship of Corn
* Evilswarm Exciton Knight
* Grenosaurus
* Wind-Up Zenmaines </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 02:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Asians are a small, small minority.

1 in 19 Americans are of Asian descent. There are 16903324 Asian people in living in the USA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 02:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no reason not to have both - unless you worry about to many people with a similar skillset - but I think it's unlikely they'd want to add another member to the Defenders this early on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 01:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I don't want to bone him then the casting is wrong.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 01:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Race is important to many, many people, but the writer wasn't using it as a case against Iron Fist, he was saying that Iron Fist better use mystical elements to justify choosing him over Shang-Chi. But, the MCU only has one Asian hero - why would one more hurt? I know it would certainly please a lot of people to have Shange-Chi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 01:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arr you flexible on the blue eyes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the director of Swingers comes The Edge of Tomorrow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 21:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITT: People mistaking the Thomas Jane Punisher for the first one.

Edit: to people saying that I'm ignoring the title. People are still referring to the 2000s movies as if they're the only ones. I know this thread is about those in particular, but this the posts in this thread make it very clear that not that many people are aware of the '89 film due to their phrasing, *not* because they're not mentioning the film. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 18:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Likewise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 18:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry - you're right. The superhero genre is extremely constrictive. Definitely check out Understanding Comics as it's really enlightening and has improved my understanding of cinema as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 18:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly believe the *medium* - comics aren't a genre -  is one of the most complex there is and Watchmen only succeeds in that form. Check out Scott McCloud's Understanding Comics.

Personally, I think the only way the movie could have been more successful is if they changed the story to suit the form much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 18:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

I'm a strong believer in, if someone has explained something better than you would, direct the person asking to the person with the answers.

So here are some links to points I generally agree with.

https://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/377635/watchmen_underappreciated_a_victim_of/crkc0tt

https://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/377635/watchmen_underappreciated_a_victim_of/crkg10m

https://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/377635/watchmen_underappreciated_a_victim_of/crkeflu

https://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/2t7vbk/watchmen_look_at_the_bottom_computer_screen_they/cnwwiqt

https://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/377635/watchmen_underappreciated_a_victim_of/crkg10m </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mind the movie (I think it's OK), but it's fundamentally a misunderstanding of the graphic novel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 04:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Summer Wars better than The Girl Who Lept Through Time which is the only one of his folms I've seen and I wasn't too fond.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 04:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Summer Wars better than The Girl Who Lept Through Time which is the only one of his folms I've seen and I wasn't too fond.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 01:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like what Jason Aaron is doing right now, granted, I'm a big Aaron fan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 01:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a big fan of Daredevil and Punisher comics, I think I have a pretty good idea. Daredevil doesn't approve of Frank's methods. They clash as Daredevil tries to save someone from Frank. Frank and Daredevil team up to take down the big bad and Daredevil doesn't let Frank kill anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 01:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daredevil is fantastic, but I wasn't too fond of the last episode. It felt surprisingly superhero-y. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 00:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say so. But also: Zodiac. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 00:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I expect all of Marvel's Netflix series will be grim 'n' gritty, but the ABC shows will stay relatively light (that said, MAOS' finale was somewhat grim). I imagine a few films may be darker, but they'll never get as dark as Daredevil. Doctor Strange and Black Panther have potential to be darker, but as did Iron Man 3 and Thor: The Dark World. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 23:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ehh. Not really a Snyder fan, but I didn't really mind Man of Steel. That said, I'm really looking forward to seeing Cyborg, Aquaman, Wonder Woman and Shazam! on the big screen. I know lots of people love him and that's fine, I just wish they didn't give Snyder so many movies as I don't really like his style. If Terrio can give his movies a tighter structure, then I should be good then, but I still don't care much for his action and I don't think he's very intelligent. Misunderstanding of Watchmen and Superman aside, I feel like he throws in symbolism, but doesn't really follow it through and it kind of bugs me. Was Supeman Jesus, the American Dream or humanity's last hope? I'm unsure because Synder kept telling me he was too many different things without telling me why. If a producer or a writer can help hold Snyder's hand through exploring his themes and ideas, that'll be great.

I just watched Gone Girl and I'm certain Affleck will make a great Bruce Wayne. Still unsure on Batman, but I'll stay open minded. 

I'm a fan of the Marvel formula, but I'd really like them to try something different from here on out and Phase 3 seems to be promising that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 16:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gwyneth Paltrow's strength being dead in a box? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 15:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try Greg Rucka's run. Best Punisher I've read not written by Ennis or Aaron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 13:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Urgh. Civil War. Don't use that as an example of good characterisation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 11:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BKV's Doctor Strange: The Oath

Bendis/Maleev on Daredevil

Christopher Priest on Black Panther </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 03:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd only mind because Clark alreqdy has a love interest and I'd like to see them together for a few movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recommended reading for the Yuuzhan Vong War? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 22:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preferably comics, but I'd happily read books as well. I'd prefer books that are good rather than ones that are just important plot-wise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really, really good. The art is phenomenal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did you think of his other two episodes from S5? Conquer and Remember? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Submersion? I believe that you mean immersion.

I - personally - don't think it affected immersion at all as they put the tribute right at the end of the movie as there was no story left to take you out of. But, different strokes, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm confused. I'm in the UK and I can purchase them. What's your problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me, not many people here know that much about the industry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a fan of the Walker tribute? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preacher? I'm sure that's going to be a TV Series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm expecting the eighth one to be called F8. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably just an attempt to certify what happens in these comics matter. Not sure it does though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marvel could definitely do with a series akin to Star Wars Legacy or Knights of the Old Republic. I think they just wanted to take advantage of the almost completely clear chronology and add some stuff to the original trilogy. Still iffy on Han's wife, but otherwise the stuff they've added has been great and I'm especially looking forward to the Soule/Maleev Lando series. I think they should explore some other genres though. Imagine a neo-noir police procedural in the Star Wars universe written by Greg Rucka or a quirky romantic comedy about two gay Gungans who fall in love in a prejudiced society by Matt Fraction? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dark Horse's Star Wars was great, but I'm loving Marvel's more.  Marvel's feel more like the movies and -generally- the art is better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 19:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I consider this to be a much ignored chapter in Brubaker's Captain America run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 19:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably a controversial opinion on this sub, but I'm not too big a fan of Dickerson as a I think his action is just too clumsy and Too Far Gone is one of the show's messier hours. His action is unclear and lacks any real weight. I think he tries to make it feel "real" and it suffers for it as it makes the show look like a bunch of middle aged guys flailing about rather than the unisex set of badasses Nicotero demonstrates. Maybe the former is more in keeping with The Walking Dead's tone, but it's not really fun to watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 18:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Straight forward? Did you not see What Happened and What's Going On? It's probably the single most pretentious and arty episode of the show and I love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 13:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Does it have influences from that genre? Sure. Does that mean anything? Not at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shut-up ye mutie scum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 11:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really liked the second New Mutants book and the New X-Men that followed. Hellion, Rockslide, Pixie, Prodigy, Surge (what are you up to now Surge?), Wallflower, Icarus , X-23and Dust all stand out in my mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 10:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To Kill a Mockingbird changed my views on masculinity and racism and I think I'm a better person for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we just take a moment to discuss how great Greg Nicotero's direction is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, every episode he directs is a vast improvement compared to the others. The action is cleaner and cooler, some shots are artier and he can use symbolism really well and he always gets really creative with blood and gore. If he directed a movie, I would be first in line to see it. Does anyone have any ideas for pre-existing properties that he would direct an adaption of well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also, Cyclops was right.

Eh. Cap was a dick and all, but I still can't condone everything Cyke has done. At least Cyclops was interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We need more cameos like this. [Minor Thor: The Dark World spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they give Scott something really interesting to do in the next modern movie. I'm loving the arc he's currently finishing in the comics and I'd love to see a cinematic take on that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jackman's Winter Soldier score is great, but I prefer his X-Men: First Class score. Sometimes I'll just blare Magneto out of my speakers really loud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 06:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at 5 Centimetres Per Second  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 05:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 04:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vertigo TV. Not really sure I'd count it as the same thing as DC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agent Carter and Jake Chisel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 23:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brian Michael Bendis wrote Ultimate Spider-Man for 15 years. He's reknowned for having a love it or hate it, naturalistic style of dialogue that tends to bounce back and forth between characters in short sentences. Google some examples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 22:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as it's in Bendis-speak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 22:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree. I believe it to be the episode before where Michael J Fox plays the doctor with OCD and everyone is jealous of him and then they realise he's more troubled than they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 20:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giving people who have prime comics, is a good way to attract more people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 20:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The apps have improved greatly, but they could do with better smart panels for older comics, a higher resolution and two-page viewing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 20:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ending of The Usual Suspects  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 07:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With Batman as a dad? No bloody way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
