<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1905</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 03:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think that races won matters not win rate. You can have a win rate of 100% and only compete once.

I'm not saying that he's not a good rider. But I don't think that he's the most talented rider. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 03:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Win rate doesn't matter really. Ago is the rider with the most wins followed by Rossi. 

The trouble with saying "talent" is that it's really subjective. Races won is really the only metric that we can use. And it's what counts in racing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 05:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Define "talent". If you mean winning races then I think you're wrong. And winning races is all that really matters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 16:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's the data? What does "best" mean? Muscle activation can be measured these days and I would prefer to see this list broken down by some sort of actual data showing how much more activation these lifts provide than their counterparts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 16:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on what you're trying to get out of coaching and what that coach can provide. Are you looking to learn how to program? Are you looking for coaching on your technique?

Don't forget that just because someone is strong doesn't mean they are a good coach.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 03:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree. I'm in San Diego and I can be on pretty quiet roads in less than an hour.

edit: autocorrect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 05:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We seem to be on a good upward trend. Interesting (but not surprising) just how many breweries we had in 1873. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best and worst years for U.S. beer production: 1800 - 2010 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 05:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 01:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the sound of it the horse was hers not some "random" horse if that makes a difference in your reply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 07:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How come he slowed down instead of just accelerating through that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 03:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My shins used to get pretty bloody but once I got better at my form they stopped bleeding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 03:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree. They just aren't passionate about racing and racing does nothing for them in terms of development. I imagine they see it as a waste of time and money to participate in racing. 

Which is a shame because their bikes definitely have the potential to do well. 

I don't think that Ape is tarnishing their image really. They aren't a well known brand and they are getting what they need out of GP by actually racing. They have proven that they can do the WSBK thing pretty well already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 08:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw this parked in the parking lot at work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cool modified bug - Album on Imgur </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 07:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
