<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7840</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 20:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A scientific poll is MUCH more relevant than an Internet poll.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 18:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They would try to match the state demos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 18:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The most recent *actual* poll on NJ has Clinton up 48 points.](http://www.realclearpolitics.com/epolls/2016/president/nj/new_jersey_democratic_presidential_primary-3443.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 05:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RemindMe! 2 days Donation for /r/millionairemakers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 04:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't dislike him personally. He's an affable guy and seems honestly passionate about his issues. But he'll never be able to deliver them. All his radical changes have to get through a congress controlled by republicans where the tax raises needed to pay for them are a non-starter. We'd have 4 years of an ineffectual president with little to no foreign policy experience and the bad taste left in voters mouths would move the presidency back to republicans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 04:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's getting hardly any support. He's getting far less than Obama did at this time in 2007.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 00:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way way behind in the polls. And behind in money. And behind in establishment endorsements. Obama had far more money, endorsements, and better polling numbers at this point in 2007. [And he's the exception to insurgent candidates.](http://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/bernie-sanders-isnt-barack-obama-and-2016-isnt-2008/2015/07/17/5d85377e-2b37-11e5-bd33-395c05608059_story.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 00:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Most see the Post as having a liberal bias.](http://www.rasmussenreports.com/content/pdf/4541) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 23:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I supported Obama in 2007-2008.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 23:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course it's not spent on "luxury."  It's spent on extra field offices and paid staffers and mailers and commercials.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 23:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone doesn't love Bernie HES A SHILL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanderss limited appeal  even to Democrats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Clinton has been in the high 50's for that same period of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 20:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome!  I hope this has opened your eyes a little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 16:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If the Clinton folks weren't in the panic already, they most assuredly are now.

You think a candidate that leads nationally by an average of 40+ points is in a panic?  She's never polled behind Sanders in any state.  In some early states, like South Carolina, Sanders is behind Biden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 16:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Responses are weighed against the demographics of the electorate.  They don't just post the raw numbers they get in response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton leads Sanders by 50 points in Virginia. Leads all republican opponents in Virginia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 21:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take no issue with a politician that evolves and grows on an issue. Even Lincoln did that. 

Also no other sub has individuals as out of touch as this one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Article from the summer of 2012.  The final results in that election prove that the pollsters were still, by and large, accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pollsters don't just use raw numbers.  They use previous statistical information and cross tabs to ensure their information is as accurate as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just trying to bring a dose of reality to the sub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Landlines and cell phones.  The polls are painting a clear picture, you just don't like how it looks-much like the Republicans in 2012. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubt polls at your peril.  Republicans constantly tried to unskew the polls in 2012 and it turns on the polls were pretty spot on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's been running for 2.5 months </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Suffolk poll shows Clinton ahead of Sanders by 45 points. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This will be a fight for the Democratic nomination, and it will be hard to secure it, said communications director Jennifer Palmieri. There are a lot of people Hillary Clinton will need to convince to support her and thats what we expect will happen.

If you think that's an honest statement you're very naive.  There's no way the communications director for Clinton actually believes that.  They're setting expectations high for Bernie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton leads by 45 points, 59 to 14, in latest Suffolk poll. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boston for Bernie rally tonight feels like a disaster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There has been. [Sanders runs behind Biden.](http://www.realclearpolitics.com/epolls/2016/president/sc/south_carolina_democratic_presidential_primary-4167.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He's godlike... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 22:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That post has over 43,000 likes and over 12,000 shares, and less than 6,000 comments.  Even if we assume every single comment is pro-Sanders, I think the reaction is mostly pro-Hillary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I accepted your response and was continuing the conversation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 19:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the guy you originally responded to. I'm a guy starting a new conversation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 19:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The issue is it isn't that simple. It's pie in the sky hopes and dreams. Congress will never have enough democratic socialists to pass what he proposes. The chances are high that at least part of the next term at least one, if not both, chambers will be republican controlled. His plans will never come to fruition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 21:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clinton hasn't campaigned against any republican either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 21:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes no sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 21:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has leads in swing states on all leading republicans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 01:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [They think he's "godlike."](https://np.reddit.com/r/SandersForPresident/comments/3csfev/tough_questions_to_sen_sanders_on_his_gun_votes/csyhvqt) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 23:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's godlike

Do you people even hear yourselves? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stop bed-wetting over Hillary Clinton campaign (opinion) - CNN.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 501 Mile walk | Kevin Doyle's Fundraiser, walking 650 miles to Comic-Con in Stormtrooper armor in honor of his late wife. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 05:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 01:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bad news for Trump and Sanders: If history is any guide, eventually their bubbles could burst.

Duke University professor John Aldrich cautions voters not to get too excited or worried by this summers boomlets from Trump and Sanders.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 00:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "This is what UCLA professor Lynn Vavreck dubs the 'discovery, scrutiny, decline' pattern. Party activists discover a shiny new candidate as an alternative to the races front-runner, usually when the campaign is just beginning. The insurgent faces press scrutiny and then, typically, declines." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Voters' summer flings typically don't last </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 00:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 00:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "This is what UCLA professor Lynn Vavreck dubs the 'discovery, scrutiny, decline' pattern. Party activists discover a shiny new candidate as an alternative to the races front-runner, usually when the campaign is just beginning. The insurgent faces press scrutiny and then, typically, declines." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Voters summer flings typically dont last </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 00:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton leads NC primary by 35. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Bernie Sanderss Momentum Is Not Built to Last </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 14:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Larry J. Sabato's Crystal Ball  Democrats 2016: Not Feeling The Bern </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 14:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.ytimg.com/vi/e__1KU7lg-4/hqdefault.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL tries to decide what's worse, adultery or decapitating someone and bringing their head to the hospital to show the mother of their child? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 22:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 22:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  devoted husbands don't strike me as the abusive type.

Husbands that decapitate other people don't strike me as the devoted type. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 19:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if he wants any chance at winning he needs to do much much better in states not next to his home state. 19 down in Iowa and 40 some down in South Carolina won't cut it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 19:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No he wasn't. Clinton had a three point lead in polls taken at the same time in 2008. Nowhere near 19 points.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton leads by 44 points in Florida primary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 17:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 15:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While it's narrowed, Clinton still has a 19 point lead and leads Sanders in favorability, leadership, honesty, and caring about their needs and problems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 22:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubt polls at your peril.  Republicans doubted polls all last cycle, and there were numerous news stories and websites devoted to "unskewing" them, and it the end it turned out they were right.

Also their likelihood of voting is determined by asking them a series of questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton leads nomination by 41 points in latest poll, beats all Republican candidates by double digits. Sanders lags behind Biden. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 04:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  
 You think that, in my off time, if I wrote articles about how shitty my company's products are, my employment should be protected by the 1st Amendment?
 Are you genuinely selling substandard products to your customers? That is a pretty shitty thing to do.
 

You didn't answer his question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leadership also meaning being willing to change your stance when you're wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama wasn't even close to this far behind in 2007. Not even close.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [At this point in the 2008 campaign Hillary was up 10-16 points on Obama.  Nothing near 42 points.](http://www.realclearpolitics.com/epolls/2008/president/us/democratic_presidential_nomination-191.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That poll references an 18 point lead.  Hillary has a ***46*** point lead in the latest polls.  You don't think those two are significantly different? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 22:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Only down 26 in Iowa!](http://www.realclearpolitics.com/epolls/2016/president/ia/iowa_democratic_presidential_caucus-3195.html)

[Down a mere 41 in South Carolina!](http://www.realclearpolitics.com/epolls/2016/president/sc/south_carolina_democratic_presidential_primary-4167.html)

[Only the barest of bare bones leads in Florida!](http://www.realclearpolitics.com/epolls/2016/president/fl/florida_democratic_presidential_primary-3556.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton up by 32 in New Hampshire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 09:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 16:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Last year President Obama won the popular vote with 65,000 American supporting him and 5,000 vote margin. 

You're missing some zeros.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 03:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you read the article? The whole point was that those strong front runners, even after losing some states, *still won*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 03:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The people that make these predictions for a living say they're very indicative of what will happen.](http://fivethirtyeight.com/datalab/what-to-make-of-the-bernie-sanders-surge/) They pay a lot of attention to these things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 03:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he's behind in every state that isn't next to his home state. Iowa, the first caucus (happens before New Hampshire) down 42. South Carolina, the third primary state, down 41, and behind Biden *who isn't even running.* Florida down an astounding 55 points and again behind Biden. You have your head in the sand if you think these numbers are meaningless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 02:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And is about 40 points behind her just about everywhere else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 02:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Key states like Iowa, where Clinton is leading by 42%? Or how about South Carolina, the third primary state, where she's leading by 41%, and Sanders is 5 points behind Joe Biden who isn't even running? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harmful if Swallowed was hilarious.  Fite me irl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 00:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is they didn't keep it to themselves or their sub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who killed Rodney Marks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rodney Marks was an Australian astrophysicist employed at the South Pole with the Smithsonian Astrophysical Observatory, working on the Antarctic Submillimeter Telescope and Remote Observatory, a research project for the University of Chicago at the Amundsen-Scott South Pole Station.

On 11 May 2000 Rodney Marks became unwell while walking between the remote observatory and the base. He became increasingly sick over a 36-hour period, three times returning increasingly distressed to the station's doctor. Advice was sought by satellite, but Marks died on 12 May 2000 with his condition undiagnosed.

Marks' body was held for nearly six months over winter before it could be flown to Christchurch, New Zealand, the base for American activities in Antarctica, for autopsy. Once in New Zealand, a post mortem established that Marks had died from methanol poisoning.  An investigation was undertaken by Detective Senior Sergeant (DSS) Grant Wormald, of the New Zealand Police.

DSS Wormald stated it was not credible to believe he had accidentally drunk the methanol, when he had ready access to a large supply of alcohol. Marks had recently entered a new relationship, had nearly completed important academic work and had no financial problems. He had promptly sought treatment for an illness that confused him, and there was no reason to suspect suicidal intent.

Wormald indicated that Raytheon and the National Science Foundation had not been cooperative.  Having obtained details of the 49 other people at the base at the time, DSS Wormald told a newspaper, "I suspect that there have been people who have thought twice about making contact with us on the basis of their future employment position".  The whereabouts of the station doctor, Robert Thompson, have been unknown sometime after 2006.

In September 2008, the written report resulting from the December 2006 inquest was released. The coroner could not find evidence to support theories of a prank gone awry nor foul play nor suicide.

The case received media attention as the "first South Pole murder", as suicide was considered the least likely cause of his death.

http://tvnz.co.nz/view/page/410965/2104065 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 15:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I didn't ask how you thought it would turn out, I asked if I was legally able to. If I am legally able to this could work out really well for me actually. Thanks

Sounds like this confrontation is going to go great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
