<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1906</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vatican recognizes state of Palestine in new treaty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These spectacular photos show the breath-taking moment lava burst into the sky as Mount Etna had its largest eruption in months. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No paywall here. This is the rest of the article, aside from the actual decision which op linked above.

"Federal agents do not have unlimited power to search laptops and other electronic devices without a warrant at the border, including airports, a federal judge in Washington said.

U.S. District Judge Amy Berman Jackson rejected prosecutors arguments that a laptop was like any other container that could be searched at the border without a warrant. The border search doctrine had limits when it came to electronic devices, Jackson wrote.

Given the vast storage capacity of even the most basic laptops, and the capacity of computers to retain metadata and even deleted material, one cannot treat an electronic storage device like a handbag simply because you can put things in it and then carry it onto a plane, Jackson said.

Jackson is the latest judge to confront warrantless searches of electronic devices since the U.S. Supreme Courts ruling last year in Riley v. California. In Riley, the justices said police generally must get a warrant before searching a cellphone, acknowledging the vast amount of personal information those devices hold.

Citing Riley, Jackson said she would apply the same approach as the high court and weigh the degree to which defendant Jae Shik Kims privacy was invaded when his computer was searched against the governments national security interests. Kim, a Korean businessman, was traveling home from the United States in December 2012 when a U.S. Department of Homeland Security special agent seized his laptop and sent it away for a forensic examination.

She wrote:
The imaging and search of the entire contents of Kims laptop, aided by specialized forensic software, for a period of unlimited duration and an examination of unlimited scope, for the purpose of gathering evidence in a pre-existing investigation, was supported by so little suspicion of ongoing or imminent criminal activity, and was so invasive of Kims privacy and so disconnected from not only the considerations underlying the breadth of the governments authority to search at the border, but also the border itself, that it was unreasonable.

Jackson tossed out incriminating evidence investigators discovered stored in the laptop, which prosecutors used to charge Kim with violating U.S. economic sanctions against Iran.  

Kims lawyer, David Deitch of Ifrah Law in Washington, said Jacksons ruling made clear that the government will still have all its rights to protect the border if it is doing searches that are designed to thwart crimes that are afoot at the border crossing.

This is a really interesting and unresolved area of the law right now because, as often happens, were taking 17th century concepts of privacy rights and trying to apply them to 21st century technology, Deitch said.

A spokesman for the U.S. attorneys office in Washington said they were reviewing the ruling.

Jacksons decision was the second in the past year in the D.C. federal trial court to address warrantless searches of laptops at airports.
In December, U.S. District Judge Rudolph Contreras rejected a motion to suppress evidence filed by another defendant charged with sanctions violations, Shantia Hassanshahi. Hassanshahi claimed the government lacked reasonable suspicion to seize and search his computer. He also argued the search was unlawful because investigators discovered his phone number using a secret law enforcement database.

Contreras found there was reasonable suspicion to search Hassanshahis computer. Law enforcement had reason to believe Hassanshahi was doing business in Iran, the judge said, including an earlier federal investigation into his activities involving Iran, his past travels there and the fact that he was carrying multiple electronic devices that appeared to be inconsistent with just personal use while traveling.

Jackson said that Kims case was different from Hassanshahis because there was nothing about Kims particular travel plans that would arouse suspicion; he was returning to his home in Korea and he was known to have business operations within the United States.

The next hearing in Kims case is scheduled for May 18."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 14:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of me wants to go all conspiro   believe that this is just a cover for a strategic take over of the territory, because no way can those running our governments be this fucking stupid! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 14:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for thr giggle:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 01:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "REUTERS - Israel has reported an outbreak of H5N1 bird flu virus in the north of the country, two months after declaring a series of similar outbreaks earlier this year had been resolved, the World Organization for Animal Health (OIE) said on Tuesday.

High pathogenic H5N1 bird flu first infected humans in 1997 in Hong Kong. It has since spread from Asia to Europe and Africa and has become entrenched in poultry in some countries, causing millions of poultry infections and several hundred human deaths.

The strain is different to the H5N2 strain that has been spreading in the United States, leading to the death or culling of nearly 30 million birds so far." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bird Flu Confirmed on Nebraska Egg Farm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 01:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bird flu virus re-emerges in northern Israel Report comes two months after a series of similar outbreaks had been resolved. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 01:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 00:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.scientificamerican.com/article/do-plants-think-daniel-chamovitz/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Victoria is bracing for wild winds across the state, blizzards in alpine areas and possible flooding in Melbourne. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 00:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wild weather set to hit Victoria, with blizzards, snow and hail forecast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 00:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 00:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like we got lucky this time:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 00:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is seriously wrong on so many levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 00:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yea this isn't the one they are talking about, thank goodness.

Another source: Rumbling from ocean trenches could be sign that Japan faces mega earthquake
http://theconversation.com/rumbling-from-ocean-trenches-could-be-sign-that-japan-faces-mega-earthquake-41464 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 00:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no, that is far too much responsibility:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 00:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "There was no initial Tsunami risk to the United States, but NOAA reports the potential for a Tsunami hitting the immediate region on mainland Japan"

http://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2015/05/12/magnitude-6-8-earthquake-hits-just-off-japans-coast/

No tsunami threat for Hawaii after 6.8 Japan quake  http://www.kitv.com/news/no-tsunami-threat-for-hawaii-after-68-japan-quake/32975944




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> crap.

RSOE EDIS
Event Report

Preliminary Earthquake Report
Notice! This is a computer-generated report - this event has not reviewed by a seismologist!
EDIS Number:	EQ-20150512-478823-JP Common Alerting Protocol

Magnitude:	6.8

Mercalli scale:	8

Date-Time [UTC]:	12 May, 2015 at 23:13:01 UTC

Local Date/Time:	Wednesday, May 13, 2015 at 08:13 in the moorning at epicenter

Coordinate:	141 48.000, 38 54.000

Depth:	48 km (29.83 miles)

Hypocentrum:	Shallow depth

Class:	Strong

Region:	Iwate
Country:	Japan
Location:	18.00 km (11.18 miles) - of Ofunato, Iwate, Japan
Source:	USGS
Generated Tsunami:	Declare
Damage:	Not or no data
The potential impact of the earthquake
Drivers have trouble steering. Houses that are not bolted down might shift on their foundations. Tall structures such as towers and chimneys might twist and fall. Well-built buildings suffer slight damage. Poorly built structures suffer severe damage. Tree branches break. Hillsides might crack if the ground is wet. Water levels in wells might change.

Strong Quake Shakes Northeast Japan, No Tsunami Risk    
 http://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/strong-quake-shakes-northeasst-japan-tsunami-risk-30995079 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lake Ray Roberts flood gates opened    http://dallas.suntimes.com/dal-news/7/75/115693/lake-ray-roberts-flood-gates-opened </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related: Lake Ray Roberts flood gates opened http://dallas.suntimes.com/dal-news/7/75/115693/lake-ray-roberts-flood-gates-opened

Denton Co. Authorities Warn Residents of Possible Evacuation  http://www.nbcdfw.com/news/local/Denton-Co-Authorities-Warn-Residents-of-Possible-Evacuation-303384211.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More rain could cause brimming lakes to overflow (Tx) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 16:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chemistry of firearms AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 16:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 16:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard someone somewhere describing it as sounding like an explosion. Scary stuff, glad you're ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sources ID Suspected Serial Killer Several sources have identified the man suspected of killing seven people whose bodies were found behind a New Britain shopping center. (Conn) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 16:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PM Tells Cabinet: Give Working People A Chance The PM tells the first full Tory Cabinet in 18 years they no longer have to "trade away" policy but can deliver on their promises. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 15:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 15:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> related:Troubling new research says global warming will cut wheat yields
 http://www.washingtonpost.com/news/energy-environment/wp/2015/05/11/troubling-new-study-suggests-global-warming-will-reduce-wheat-yields/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran stresses end-June deadline as nuclear talks press on </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 15:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google shuts off Map Maker after urinating robot ruins it for everybody Company announces prank has forced it to take a pause as it makes changes to how it approves edits made by users </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 14:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 14:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the article sure makes it sound like Godzilla will be the loser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ice loss in west Antarctica is speeding up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 14:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 14:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second Suspect In Isla Vista Shooting In Custody

http://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2015/05/12/second-suspect-in-isla-vista-shooting-turns-himself-in/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 14:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> related:Three Ukrainian servicemen killed in past 24 hours in east: Ukrainian military

http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/05/12/us-ukraine-crisis-casualties-idUSKBN0NX0YC20150512?mod=related channelName=worldNews </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scores of Russian soldiers killed in east Ukraine: opposition report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 14:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Detroit, Jewish cemetery survives within GM auto plant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 14:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://bigstory.ap.org/article/8d57ab4776514a38a1f5e178f3552d82/detroit-jewish-cemetery-survives-within-gm-auto-plant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 14:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Texas, Arkansas governors declare disasters after deadly tornadoes

http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/05/12/us-usa-weather-tornadoes-idUSKBN0NW19T20150512?feedType=RSS feedName=topNews utm_source=twitter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas, Arkansas governors declare disasters after deadly tornadoes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 14:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> El Nino has emerged, Asia braces for crop damage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 14:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> El Nino has emerged, Asia braces for crop damage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 14:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 14:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yea there's been several aftershocks from this new 7.3 ranging from 5.0-5.6 looks like.  
Death toll at least 36, reports of injurys seem ~1k. 

Reuters is updating pretty well. http://live.reuters.com/Event/Nepal_Earthquake_3

AP too: http://hosted.ap.org/dynamic/stories/A/AS_NEPAL_EARTHQUAKE?SITE=AP SECTION=HOME TEMPLATE=DEFAULT

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 14:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow. Lucky you had the fireplaces. May I ask whereabouts (generally) you live? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 13:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> re South Dakota 

"South Dakota was the center of weather extremes Sunday, with a tornado damaging a small town and injuring at least nine people on the eastern side of the state and more than a foot of snow blanketing the Black Hills to the west."

"Farther north, a late-season snow fell in parts of the Rockies, western Nebraska and western South Dakota.

National Weather Service meteorologist Kyle Carstens said between 10 to 18 inches of snow was on the ground Sunday morning in the Black Hills of South Dakota and totals could reach 20-24 inches by the time the system moves out. Rapid City, South Dakota, had 8-11 inches, accompanied by 20-30 mph winds."

http://www.cbsnews.com/news/tornadoes-flooding-helicopter-rescue-texas-south-dakota-oklahoma-iowa/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Large Tornadoes Ravage Small Towns in Texas, Arkansas, Iowa and South Dakota, Killing At Least 6 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 13:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 12:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/search?q=%23EarthquakeInNepal src=hash mode=photos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 12:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Tyler Moore and his father said they have been coming to the north end of Carolina Beach for the past 15 years and were shocked to see how much was gone.

"We looked down and were not expecting to see the drop off, because normally the sand over here is just about even with the rocks, Moore said, pointing to the sand along the coastline. Now it's probably dropped off 8-10 feet especially up under the pier so it was really a shock. Then we walked down the beach (towards the north end) and to see how much of the beach was gone was really surprising."

"However, Town Manager Michael Cramer said in the grand scheme of things those damages are minimal. 

"Really our storm damage reduction program is having the benefit that we want it to have and that is stopping any of the wave action from damaging business, damaging personal property, or our infrastructure, Cramer explained. So the fact that we have the dunes, that's working, and this is just a normal process of maintaining and keeping those dunes up so we don't have major damage when we have storms like this."

Kramer said the damage that was done is easily fixable. Officials are looking to add a few steps to some accesses that were hit the hardest by the erosion to make it easier for people to get down to the beach. 

Also, the town has contacted a contractor to re-stack the rocks along the 1500 block of Carolina Beach Road North, past the Carolina Beach Pier. Some of those rocks have been disheveled due to Ana's impact."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tropical Storm Ana hit the coast of Southeastern North Carolina hard this weekend, causing severe damage to several beaches in New Hanover County. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 12:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Storm knocks motorists, power in central Ohio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 12:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 12:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDIS Number:	EQ-20150512-478654-NP Common Alerting Protocol

Magnitude:	7.4

Mercalli scale:	10

Date-Time [UTC]:	12 May, 2015 at 09:05:19 UTC

Local Date/Time:	Tuesday, May 12, 2015 at 15:05 in the afternoon at epicenter

Coordinate:	86 9.210, 27 50.568

Depth:	18.47 km (11.48 miles)

Hypocentrum:	Shallow depth

Class:	Major
Region:	
Country:	Nepal

Location:	23.00 km (14.29 miles) - of Kodari, Nepal
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A major earthquake has struck eastern Nepal, near Mount Everest, two weeks after more than 8,000 died in a devastating quake. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 12:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Substantial' El Nino event predicted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 12:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Substantial' El Nino event predicted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 12:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 14:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What'chu talkin' 'bout Willis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 06:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok I'm clueless. what??  I'm just hoping that Junior can be wizarded into ..well what you all do here. It's a personal   original photo. I can't seem to get this submitted correctly, I keep trying to follow the rules, and at this point I genuinely have no idea what it is you are asking...

Any help would be appreciated, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 06:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually don't recall if I posted this here, I had on worldnews, but what with it's being Russia   all..so pardon me if it is a repost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Most Powerful Volcano in Kamchatka Releases Steam and Ash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 06:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 06:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as much wood as a woodchuck could chuck, if a woodchuck could chuck wood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 06:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has some interesting stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "critical" USGS, "In times of crisis, this account helps share critical information with Twitter Alerts. Be prepared" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 06:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photo: Reported gas well explosion in Denton, Texas, near I-35 and Windsor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 06:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 05:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mostly lovely racist sentiments   apparently taco marketing. No thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 05:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can we erect a fence around them ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Magnitude of Largest California Earthquakes Since 1900 pages mapped by Location </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 05:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 05:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why are you yelling at me?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 05:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what does that even mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: Junior the dog, relaxing in a bed of grass. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 05:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 04:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love you! thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 04:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok I'm going to try again heading it as "Junior the dog, unknown  breed, laying down on a bed of grass"

hope that will be ok. Thank you very much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 04:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much. Junior meant a lot to us, so I do seem to get rather emotionally verbose:)  Ok would 'Junior, our rescue dog,laying down on a bed of grass' work? no idea what breed he was; just a darling animal.

( he really was hunting (unsucessfully) for chameleons :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 04:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> arg ok I suck at these submissions, I actually did read the page. 

ok I am sad now:(

Thanks for modding well, I thought I was doing it right. pardon meas I crawl into some corner   weep for a while, then make one more attempt.

ty   gn:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 04:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> great point :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Military Could Step in Over Brazil Drought Chaos An engineer for Sao Paulo states water company said that scenes from the end of the world would ensue if the city ran out of water. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 04:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tornado Warning for Lander County, NV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 03:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 03:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UPDATED: Timeline for severe line of storms headed directly for #DFW area. @NBCDFW @NBCDFWWeather #txwx 

https://twitter.com/BrianCurtisNBC5/status/596488958873243648 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 03:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does she like the color purple? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 03:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'The volcanic eruption warning on Mount Hakoneyama was raised to Level 2 on May 6, meaning that people should stay clear of the crater on the mountain that straddles Kanagawa and Shizuoka prefectures.

The Japan Meteorological Agency had maintained a Level 1 alert although earthquakes around the mountain intensified in frequency and strength over the past 10 days. This is the first Level 2 alert for the mountain since the system was introduced in March 2009....'

From RSOE "An eruption warning has been declared for the volcano, as increased seismic activity under the wakudani hydrothermal field were registered during the past days and could herald sudden phreatic explosions. The Owakudani valley lies north of the central lava domes inside the Hakone caldera. Seismicity started to increase in late April, consisting mostly of swarms of shallow quakes at 2 and 5 km depth. More intense swarms have occurred during the past days, triggering the Japan Meteorological Agency (JMA) to raise the alert level of the volcano to 2. Simultaneously, slight deformation of the ground was detected and it appears that fumarolic activity has increased in the past days. Japanese authorities have closed access to the area, which is a popular tourist destination. After the deadly, sudden phreatic eruption of Ontake-san volcano last year, the risk of such eruptions has been taken very seriously. Whether or not an eruption will occur at Hakone in the near future is impossible to say. Similar seismic crises have occurred in the past with no eruption following. The last known eruption at Hakone occurred in 950 AD." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UPDATE: Volcano alert level raised for Mount Hakoneyama; mayor laments 'blow to tourism' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 03:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nicaragua's Concepcion volcano has experienced more than 60 small eruptions since early Wednesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 02:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 02:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Impact - Did You Feel It? - Tell Us!

http://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/us20002dm8#impact_dyfi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parts of North Texas just experienced the most powerful earthquake so far to rumble through this part of the world: a 4.0-magnitude temblor in Venus, just south of Mansfield and west of Midlothian. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 02:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 02:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/us20002dm8#impact_dyfi   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parts of North Texas just experienced the most powerful earthquake so far to rumble through this part of the world: a 4.0-magnitude temblor in Venus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 02:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 01:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you, how odd it added him as the thumbnail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 01:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point, I was meaning the mother's behavior as being odd, but you are quite correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 20:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.slate.com/blogs/crime/2013/03/13/justin_bieber_swatting_what_to_do_when_the_internet_sends_a_swat_team_to.html

http://www.dangerandplay.com/2014/11/07/avoid-swatting/

ps: just in case you may want to dispose of any illegal substances you might have laying around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you please draw our family pet, Junior? Thanks! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 18:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 18:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> VIDEO (if you dare): Nurse in Bulgaria beating a new born baby in nursery   http://philtrends.com/2015/04/29/viral-nurse-in-bulgaria-beating-a-new-born-baby-in-nursery/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bulgarian Midwife Emiliya Kovacheva Remains in Detention after Severely Wounding Newborn Baby </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 18:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 15:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> who on earth is in that thumbnail? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 15:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that should linked to every pet owners travel schedule and beep like an amber alert on the days the pet owner schedules a visit to the kennel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 08:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you are so lucky if this is the first of which you have heard! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 08:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, really! Kid's mom sounding a little crazy to my ears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 08:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bumped into these: 
http://www.forcesreunited.org.uk/namearchive/units/RAFNames/RAF-Ballykelly.html

http://www.forgottenairfields.com/united-kingdom/northern-ireland/londonderry/ballykelly-s933.html

http://www.sandes.org.uk/news_detail.asp?id=13

http://www.sandes.org.uk/template.asp?pid=52 area=1 aName=

looks as though some may be helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 07:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 07:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MANILA, Philippines (AP)  A Philippine volcano has spewed ash for the second time in less than a week but there were no signs of any imminent violent eruption, the country's chief volcano expert said Thursday.

Mount Bulusan in Sorsogon province southeast of Manila ejected ash 250 meters (825 feet) above the 1,565-meter (5,165-foot) volcano late Wednesday, said Renato Solidum, director of the Philippine Institute of Volcanology and Seismology.

The agency asked local officials to keep people away from a 4-kilometer (2.5-mile) hazardous zone around the crater, he said. He said aircraft should not fly close to the mountain to avoid any sudden explosions and ash clouds.

Solidum said the explosion was due to ground water coming into contact with hot rocks and not rising magma. He says such "phreatic" explosions are typical of Bulusan. The ash explosion lasted about 3-1/2 minutes, shorter than the 5-minute explosion recorded May 1.

A large explosion in February 2011 that shot an ash plume about 2 kilometers (more than a mile) into the sky prompted about 1,200 villagers to flee to shelters.

Bulusan is one 23 volcanoes considered active by the volcanology agency, but it has not had a violent eruption since in 1918.

The country is in the Pacific "Ring of Fire," where volcanic activity and earthquakes are common. In June 1991, Mount Pinatubo in the northern Philippines exploded in one of the biggest eruptions in the 20th century. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philippine volcano ejects ash, but no violent eruption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 07:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 07:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GLENDALE, Ore. -- Fire crews worked through the night after a large fire broke out north of Glendale Tuesday night at Peavine Creek.

Firefighters are currently trying to contain the fire, working since 5 p.m. Tuesday after fire detection cameras spotted the blaze.

Douglas Forest Protective Association says its estimated that 123 acres have already been burned.

According to DFPA there is a fire trail around half of the blaze.

"As we're going along with the fire trail, we're pummeling it with water too so we can work on those hotspots, said DFPAs Kyle Reed. There's going to be a lot of work to go before this fire's contained but there's a lot of good work that's being done out here too."
     
Reed says there will be a 100 percent mop-up before they are done with this fire.

"With it being so early in the fire season, we have to make sure this fire's going to be good not only for a couple days from now or a couple weeks from now, but 2-to-3 months from now when we're in the peak of fire season."

Douglas County is in its third year of drought conditions. Reed says it's important to be careful when burning your debris or even mowing your lawn.

"Stuff that doesn't typically cause fires this time of the year -- we're going to see an increase in stuff like that, so people just need to be cautious when theyre working or recreating in wildlife areas."

The cause of the Peavine Creek fire is still under investigation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wildfire in Douglas County: 'We're pummeling it with water' (Oregon) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 07:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unprecedented Flash Flooding Emergency Hits Oklahoma City; All-Time May Record Busted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 07:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 07:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KFOR @kfor  30m30 minutes ago
Edmond teacher recognized for going "above and beyond" to help students http://link.kfor.com/1P0GiA4  pic.twitter.com/87YwgWrfIO

Details
 KFOR @kfor  32m32 minutes ago
EMSA reports that 12 people are injured, 2 are critical, at a mobile home park on SE 48th. Crews are still searching for missing people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> KFOR @kfor 24m24 minutes ago Tornado warning for Seminole county. No visual confirmation yet, but low level rotation is detected. Take precautions pic.twitter.com/zubYv5rYeA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 07:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 06:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yea, in all honesty those with whom I have spent a good amount of time dealing with..well they have been rather wonderful, arg but the politics... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 05:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GAITHERSBURG, Md. (WJLA) -- A 28-year-old Missouri woman has been charged with sexually abusing a 15-year-old Gaithersburg boy.

Police say Garen Smith met the alleged victim while playing Xbox online. Investigators say she drove all the way from Missouri to connect with the boy.

According to charging documents, the boys mother invited the woman to move into the family's Gaithersburg home.

Smith and the boy shared a room and would push their mattresses together at night, according to records.

On her Facebook page, Smith says she is working on an R.N. degree, but she loves her video games.

Investigators say the alleged victim told them he and Smith had numerous sexual encounters. He said that she frequently said she was afraid of going to jail if anyone found out about what they were doing.

Apparently the mother became suspicious and communicated with police.


(you did see the part that said "the boys mother invited the woman to move into the family's Gaithersburg home.", right?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garen Smith, Missouri woman, charged with sexually abusing 15-year-old Gaithersburg boy she met through Xbox (people are very odd) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 05:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police: Anne Arundel County police officer bites man's testicles Officer charged with assault after altercation on Cinco de Mayo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 05:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spotters report ffunnel cloud crossing Highway 183 approximately 8 miles north of Throckmorton, Texas; moving northeast at 15 mph - @weatherchannel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 05:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 05:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Police: All animals that were on the loose are safe and accounted for after tornado-warned storm damaged Tuttle, Okla., safari - @kfor live video </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 05:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OKLAHOMA CITY - Governor Mary Fallin is in the process of preparing an emergency declaration to sign, Wednesday night.
Severe storms have produced several tornadoes and have caused emergency flash flooding across Oklahoma.

Fallin visited the State Emergency Operations Center to make sure it was fully staff and running smoothly. She will be out in the affected areas Thursday.

Currently, there are no reports of any injuries associated with the storms. Gov. Fallin urges everyone to remain weather aware.

https://twitter.com/cityofokc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gov. Mary Fallin To Sign State Of Emergency Declaration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 05:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 05:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/cityofokc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 05:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OKLAHOMA CITY - Governor Mary Fallin is in the process of preparing an emergency declaration to sign, Wednesday night.
Severe storms have produced several tornadoes and have caused emergency flash flooding across Oklahoma.

Fallin visited the State Emergency Operations Center to make sure it was fully staff and running smoothly. She will be out in the affected areas Thursday.

Currently, there are no reports of any injuries associated with the storms. Gov. Fallin urges everyone to remain weather aware. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gov. Mary Fallin To Sign State Of Emergency Declaration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 05:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 05:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well they may be hunting down /u/MaltedFootball (don't even ask:)

or maybe they should have been given crayons or pastel sticks...idk, I know one of my friends used to tell me about the cougar that was living on her property  (texas). she had her protection ready if ever they were to cause any trouble. I miss that woman! 

Well I somehow have no worries of tigers   lions getting loose out there..oh but thank goodness you didn't mention bears!  
 Hope all will be well   safe , goodnight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 04:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have some extremely dear, long-time, internet friends living out there, and I know how you all prep and stay on top of it all..still I worry for them, and well gee, no wonder I love those people, they are awesome!

I know they know, and really thank you for reminding me that they do, thanks again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 04:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yea but then...https://digitalempire.files.wordpress.com/2011/03/palin3.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 04:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eek! This is not looking well. https://twitter.com/hashtag/okwx?src=hash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 04:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well 16 people not showing up to play pin the tail on the donkey does increase the odds of him being pricked by the tail holding needle...

plus you know the Korean birthday thing is odd to most of the world as you are considered 1 on your day of birth...maybe they fled to find him 16 candles, knowing he never had that particular party experience growing up, and they realized what a big fan he is of the film..ok I made that last part up... Night! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 04:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol say no more:)  Arizona huh? oh my. I always loved visiting that state..~sigh~

(ya know, just ftr, I have met   spent time with any number of Mormons, most of whom I liked much. I just so dislike the takeover of our democratic voting process by religious  /or racial groups..We all have the right to vote as individuals in this country, and bla bla etc etc...ok I'll hush , but look forward a few years and see where that vote may lie. I refuse to wear a burqa, I get claustrophobic.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 03:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow lot of nasty weather out there. If you are in that area , safe staying to you.  Did you post it to oklahoma sub?

still looking like some possibly severe weather out that ways.  http://www.weather.gov/

http://www.weather.gov/Radar

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 03:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wednesday, May 6, 2015 10:38 am
By AD CRABLE | Staff Writer

People living near the Three Mile Island nuclear plant may have heard a loud release of steam at 1 a.m. Wednesday as the plant was shut down after an electrical issue developed in the reactor.
The plant was taken out of service after a problem developed with an electrical component that operates one of the control rods in the reactor.

The control rods control the nuclear reaction in the reactor.
The issue with the control rod presented no danger or issue with controlling the reactor, said Exelon spokesman Ralph DeSantis.
He said the release of steam when the plant was being taken off-line was audible to nearby residents. Any radioactivity in the steam was too low to detect so there was no threat to the public or the environment, DeSantis said.

I suppose it's good they did this in November 2014, just in case   all:
 http://lancasteronline.com/news/local/potassium-iodide-pills-to-be-distributed-to-residents-living-near/article_b8e5bd0e-6c0c-11e4-8739-3b3acadf37c8.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Control rod problem causes shutdown of Three Mile Island reactor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 03:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 03:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok but honestly, please explain how someone name 'Flake' gets elected in the first place..sorry but the odds seem staggering, I don't know the guy, perhaps he is wonderful...though his associates..arhrmm... oh sorry, must be my allergies acting up.

Also:)  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DrbPAt1_vc4  

Those poor animals, I ..oh let me stop, it's just so horrible. I like the song   the show way better than what these excuses for humanity created. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 03:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Violence is like a weed - it does not die even in the greatest drought.
Simon Wiesenthal

So yea, maybe the drought can yell like @$^* %W you! or something??

though...If a drought falls a forest and no one is around to hear it, where are they?.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 01:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm jumping in here to remind you all of the pre-inca system of water management you may have read here at some point. 

Basically the system allowed for catching of rainwater during rain season, but kept it flowing   flowing until the dry season.
http://www.newscientist.com/article/dn27311-preinca-canals-may-solve-limas-water-crisis.html#.VUqkWflVhHw


Also this guy has produced great results using the old system of water management in India:http://www.techtimes.com/articles/41355/20150322/indias-rajendra-singh-bags-nobel-prize-water-saved-thousands.htm

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 01:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 00:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://celebrationsathomeblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/06/donuts11.jpg

better?  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 00:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is a brilliant surgeon, but his views on many things seem rather dated and ignorant. This does not distract from the man he is, I admire much about him..but I would not like him to be the leader of the USA.

 https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/236x/bf/ef/ec/bfefece6435bdc306c737500ca78f371.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 23:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Redditor for 7 days, (last account get banned huh?), and you're a Detroit Lions fan? Well that explains everything, water is just a money making dream for you.

Lions tell me you taste like chicken...https://dwellingintheword.files.wordpress.com/2012/01/lioneating.jpg

'Detroits fight for public water is also the nations
Cutting off water to those who cant afford it has roots in a long-standing, inequitable pricing scheme'  http://america.aljazeera.com/opinions/2014/6/detroit-public-watershutoffsunitednationsprivatization.html  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 23:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh go drown or something.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 23:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can not agree with you on that. We all need water. Let those with little funds die of thirst?  

So many people struggle just to make ends meet, to maintain a roof   a bit of food on the table. Would you have us collect rainwater in every available bucket, resulting in the alarming rise of mosquito borne illness which we are currently seeing running amok in places like Columbia?   http://outbreaknewstoday.com/dengue-cases-top-40000-in-malaysia-colombia-sees-10000-additional-chikungunya-cases-14946/

No. This is not the future I wish for my or anyone else's children.

Privatization of water must not be allowed to happen. Water belongs as a public sector element, and we need those government agencies that manage our current environmental troubles to step up and start doing the jobs they were elected to   for which they are paid.

Selling off water rights to private industry will result in nothing less than a disaster; the type that will make our citizenry rise up in a manner no one wants to ever have to see on a large scale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 22:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author writes "Ive been a full-time freelance writer for something approaching 25 years..."

I found it an interesting description of a writer's life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Littoral Space- My life, standing on the shore. By Warren Ellis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 22:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 21:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dendrophiliacs for starters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 20:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> possibly better explanation:http://abc7.com/weather/mystery-solved-why-does-this-lake-disappear-and-reappear-each-year/698892/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 20:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the news, a lot. 

Figure out which issues are important to you personally. Business   economy? Civil   human rights? Health   welfare? Environment? Military   defense? Science   technology?

Once you have a sense of where you lean on some of the various issues, start looking into where those running for elected office stand.

Educate yourself as best able on things that are important to you, make sure you register to vote, and use that privilege to get those that most agree with your viewpoints elected.

I also want to add that reading one article from one source on one politician is not enough. Read a lot of opinions/article from a variety of sources, and always consider the source when reading what they are saying.

Gee I'm chatty today.  Also Happy Birthday!!!! Thank you for growing into a good citizen!  Give your parents my thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 20:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> odd, they didn't give me a survey. I hate those also, and refuse to take part in them. Thank you for the alternate link. 

Your link looks better   reads more easily as well:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 20:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh good, I was afraid someone would say Maine; moose be scary! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lost Lake shrinking down a hole Lava tube drains lake on Santiam Pass (Oregon) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 19:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 19:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did it fall when no one was there? Did it make a sound? (sorry couldn't resist). Seriously though this may help:

Tree dead or not?  
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=be2QqfmPWtM    TheUrbanForesters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
