<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8603</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I met KC Green about 5 years ago and asked him to draw on my pants. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 04:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 07:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the [link](http://aht.seriouseats.com/archives/2011/04/the-cheeseburger-eggsplosion-a-burger-with-a-fried-egg-center-slideshow.html#show-154032) with more detailed instructions. Not following instructions can lead to disaster! Some disasters can be yummy though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 02:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](http://i.imgur.com/d9rtLfn.jpg) for a long time. Recently switch to [this.](http://i.imgur.com/rvsdTIs.jpg)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Poetry] Honk honk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 01:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Haiku] Renegade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 01:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 23:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah! Caught a picture of you on Saturday! http://imgur.com/Nf9WtTL Great job, btw! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 19:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Your costume was great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Photographer]Megacon 2014 walkaround album </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 08:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 07:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Heres](http://i.imgur.com/Pdix44Z.jpg) my favorite picture I've taken of them. Cracks me up every time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Photographer]Stupid sexy Little Mac </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 06:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 05:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta go fast! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 08:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like "She's so drunk" to me. http://i.imgur.com/26ij3SZ.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 21:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would suggest skipping over Walmart brand paper towels entirely and getting a large pack of a higher quality paper towel like Viva. Less air in the packaging and much more durable and useful for cooking. Anytime I buy a lower quality paper towel, I immediately regret it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 21:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lived in Tallahassee for 4 years (2009-2013) and have lived in Jacksonville before that and currently live in Riverside (4 months), so I think I may be of some help. If you're looking for nice walkable areas to enjoy outdoorsy stuff, both cities have their charms. Jacksonville has the beaches and the restaurants and bars in and around downtown/Riverside are great and improving at a very high rate. Tallahassee's downtown/Gaines street/midtown areas are also seeing a lot of improvement at a similar pace.

I feel that Jacksonville's Riverside is definitely more conducive for family activities with things for children and adults to enjoy, while in Tallahassee it is much more catered to those in their 20s. There may be some areas scattered around Tallahassee but not at the density I think you're looking for.

If you're interested in music and culture, both Jacksonville's Art Walk and Tallahassee's Railroad Square First Friday are both very similar events, but I really enjoy the intimacy of Railroad Square compared to the downtown event in Jacksonville. 

Its definitely a tough choice as both cities are seeing massive improvements and have their drawback in terms of size/neighborhood selection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 07:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very few things qualify as "Fucking bonkers." This is definitely one of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 05:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [No idea whats going on here.](http://i.imgur.com/GjHIBR0.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 05:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Some say it took Leonardo da Vinci 10 years to perfect those lips.](http://i.imgur.com/tj2bJGM.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 18:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC Starbucks only serves their cold tea drinks in Trenta. A Trenta white mocha frappucino or caramel macchiato would be heart attack inducing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 14:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stiff interfacing on the inside or the inside lining of the fabric. You come across it a lot in cosplay. http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Interfacing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 02:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the idea, but this felt like a long Portlandia skit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 00:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah. Didn't realize they had ridiculous pricing on shipping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-25 19:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any particular reason why you just don't have them shipped to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 00:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related fun fact. During the conscription of soldiers for World War 2, there were 9 documented cases of men with 3 testicles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-20 09:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get one of these ASAP http://amzn.com/B0002ITQHS
Do yourself a favor and follow the instructions from now on and everything will be all right. Stray from that and there will be hell to pay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-20 02:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to cry constantly while cutting onions and tried nearly everything that the internet could possibly recommend to stop it. One trip to Harbour Freight and $15 later, haven't shed a tear since. http://www.harborfreight.com/6-inch-ceramic-chefs-knife-98186.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
