<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8959</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gun allegedly used by San Francisco shooting suspect belonged to federal agent, source says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 06:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 06:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How precisely do you splinter a vote before a primary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did Subway take Jared so seriously? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 05:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was obvious he was kidding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 05:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, he doesn't change his mind. He changes the words coming out of his mouth. Hes a politician. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 05:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realize Republicans are literally sucking Netanyahus dick, right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wanted to introduce everyone to my Dark Souls II character, Mr. Covington! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 03:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is an intentional, planned distraction to keep scrutiny off of the GOP and make even the most radical Republican presidential candidate appear completely rational. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 01:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 15:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are "terrified" using any website on the web and you continue visiting it, you need to bring that up to a therapist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 15:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Golfclap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit Revolt: Will Petition Force Pao to Step Down? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 05:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 05:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This submission is racist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 01:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly what it is. Ask anyone who claims he can win what his wife's name is, where was he born, what is his position on drone strikes against American citizens, how much is he worth, what is his stance on Israeli apartheid practices towards Palestinians, who does he think would make a good secretary of defense, what's his position towards affirmative action, what will he do to loosen big banks grip on commodities... You get crickets. Just like Pauls supporters. They couldn't tell you anything about him except he'd audit the fed which most couldn't tell you what that even means and he likes legalization of drugs. Don't hate me for passing this message, it's just the way things appear right now to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 01:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly this. I'm not buying any guarantees in this election. We are one justice away from a major conservative majority. I'm not comfortable enough to say who I may vote for, let alone who could certainly win. Name recognition in reddit cj's aside, where is the data to support these claims? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 01:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Riches buy the companies that build the machines that count the votes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How specifically does gun control impact criminals? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 01:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surfing a wake of light: Researchers observe and control light wakes for the first time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 19:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 17:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Chinese citizens have better protections than US citizens do, it's not a good sign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 09:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the fuck would I help Reddit make money right now? What possible reason would I have to assist a group of money and power hungry people in attaining more money and logically more power? Hell no. They are going to listen to us or they're going to collapse faster than they can say "oops".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 08:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it can be demonstrated to have likely prevented any shooting this year, I'll consider your moderate approach. Otherwise all cute freshman year 101 Pavlov name bombs aside, no amount of regulation is going to address the real crisis, an emerging human condition that relies on libido and base desire and anger and violence when reacting to the world, instead of genuine concern for others. Infringing on a right our Supreme court supports as a constitutional one is not only the wrong approach to fix the issues, it's the issue that specifically led to Maryland failing to elect a shoe-in Democrat governor, Colorado to demonstrate effective recalls against Democratic reps. It will lose us the White House. I'm a nonhetero Democrat and I know this as fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 02:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ghost World, Mulholland Drive, We Need to Talk About Kevin are a few that come to mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 01:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After reading this, I'm glad I went nexus 6 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 00:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did she announce her departure? Nothing else she has to say matters to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone Is Finally Suing Samsung Over Its Bloatware </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 21:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 19:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 19:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think raw strength can trump the magic that protects the hammer from being wielded by unworthy people. The hammer is protected by more than its weight in the comics I've always read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 19:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if the Supreme Court weighs in and rules the Federal laws on marijuana trump the state initiatives? I thought the Supreme Court precedent seems to be Federal law will trump state law in event of conflict. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Is legalized marijuana in the US here to stay or can the Federal government somehow revoke the state laws that legalized it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 19:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charlie as viewed through Google's "dreaming" image scan process. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 18:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WYR live your entire life never falling in love with someone, or fall in love with someone and enjoy 10 amazing years before you catch them cheating on you and they leave you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 09:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 05:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't imagine how difficult it must be as The One. You and you alone carrying the burden of The Truth, tasked with educating us mindless sheep. It must be a living hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Incredible Hulk vs. Wonder Woman in an arm wrestling challenge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 04:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could the restraining order be a test to see how much I really love her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 03:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 03:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By the year 2050, it'll be 25 billion killed in the Holocaust. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 00:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heathers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Victor Victoria (1982) Musical comedy about a woman pretending to be a man pretending to be a woman in order to achieve fame and success on the stage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 00:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox Mulder and Dana Scully are investigating the Bay Harbor Butcher case in Miami. Can they catch Dexter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 22:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WYR live blind with no legs or deaf with no arms? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 16:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 16:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe anyone remembers that show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 15:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically the horny ones all die and teens don't beat him until everyone they know is dead and even then they fail repeatedly to truly kill him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Freddy Krueger enters Supermans dreams. Could he kill Superman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 02:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 00:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't create to profit, I simply enjoy creating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 23:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strip poker in ASCII... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to use a site called TheGlobe, which was sort of an early social media site. I loved it but they closed shop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freakfarm? That sounds like a Facebook game I could get into. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who were around for the early days of the Internet, what website or service no longer exists that used to be huge? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN updated their terms of service to require arbitration, now stripping readers of any right to sue them in court for any reason. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 06:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 03:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The subjectivity of morality when measured against desires for wealth never fail to surprise the shit out of me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WYR have sex with your mother (father for ladies) for one billion dollars or live in absolute poverty for the rest of your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 22:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who are friends with ex wives or ex husbands, what's your secret? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 05:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 00:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WYR create world peace but die doing so or unlock immortality for yourself but no one else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 23:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What non-politician would make a great US President? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 22:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also why if possible :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't I recall hearing about this before? Is this something that happens regularly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do we need a "leap second" added to our clocks at the end of June? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 19:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some Tyler Perry movie with Madea in it. A wedding or funeral or some shit was happening. My ex was forcing me through it, I wanted an airplane engine to fall through the ceiling and crush me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If PC's are better for gaming, why couldn't computers run Arkham Knight when consoles easily did? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 05:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most interesting fact you know? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 02:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can I convince an atheist to agree to disagree? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 00:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WYR post a stupid comment reflecting a total lack of intelligent thought or remain silent and not look like an absolute twat? Either way you live so hopefully this is more suited to your specific set of rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WYR drown in a pool of bleach or get crushed in the back of a loaded, inner-city garbage truck? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Relativitys time dilation may limit the quantum world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 16:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 16:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greece already collapsed. That happened. The question isn't about their collapse. The question is whether or not they intend to dump the EU which would send EU markets sliding into potential recession territory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 16:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tl;dr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 10:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DARPA Attempts to Make Mars More Hospitable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 06:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 02:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Life experience also teaches the beauty of brevity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 01:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no this one is gonna be gold. I'm making popcorn and reading it tonight. Not kidding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Court Allows Nationwide Health Care Subsidies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the strongest survive, why do humans still die? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 06:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 05:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get out and live. Fail. Love. Make an ass out of yourself. Get rich. Break a bone. Get divorced. Rescue a dog. Get dangerously addicted to something then drop it. Lack of life experience is such a glaring, obvious flaw in so many books. My opinion obviously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 05:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She may well lose. It won't be to Sanders.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel I am a velociraptor trapped in a human body. How can I convince society this internalized manifestation of insecurity is something they need to externally respect and accommodate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 18:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 18:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aside from the confederate flag, what are some other symbols we can blame for our shortcomings and rally against in a desperate attempt to pretend we're not horrible people? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 20:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 09:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spanking the Monkey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> D-Wave Systems Breaks 1000 Qubit Quantum Computing Barrier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 09:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 09:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It only works when you look at people over eighty years old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Scientists of Reddit, what fact blows your fucking mind? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 06:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ozymandias develops a plan to kill Batman. Could Batman survive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 17:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Film and comic abilities in play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 05:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without a doubt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 05:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm personally thinking he starts drinking at takeoff and doesn't stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Joker and Sterling Archer are stuck sitting next to one another on a trans Atlantic flight. Who kills who? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 05:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the NSA was smart, they would have built a comprehensive database archiving our every search on the internet then named it something else and pretended like it wasn't their company. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 07:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poe (1995) - Angry Johnny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 07:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If children do not learn to cope with being bullied, how will they develop the skills needed to handle any kind of crisis as an adult? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 04:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could one highly trained, invincible assassin with the ability to teleport anywhere at will theoretically kill everyone on the planet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 00:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How or why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Incredible Hulk vs. Goku and Sagat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 19:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> City street fight to the death </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is one app for your phone that others may not know about but you couldn't live without? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 21:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WYR randomly, loudly poop your pants for life or randomly puke on a person you touch for the next fifteen years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 04:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ms. Piggys been sleeping around and now Kermit the Frog is bloodlusted. What Muppet can stop his killing spree? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 17:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 05:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So...horcrux </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are we just now discovering dust clouds and other atmospheric activity on the moon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 22:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Incredible Hulk vs. The entire US military </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All abilities implied by comic, film or book in play for both sides </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 17:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading OPs unusually limited history, I now actually believe this. I was being sarcastic earlier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 16:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be more likely to believe OP is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 04:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This ignores the environment. Perhaps CT has a nicer, more educated well off population that aren't resorting to guns to settle gang disputes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A small framed deaf genius with no hands vs. A blind idiot bodybuilder with no feet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 04:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cage match no prep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 04:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 04:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'll start with Rover and Snowpiercer, they seem solid glancing online. Definitely working my way through your list! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 04:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen the majority of those and forgot Mulholland Drive on my list, its one of my top picks of all time. Long day I guess. Never heard of Sleep Dealer though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 04:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are great, I have not seen any of these aside from Gilliams work and Oldboy thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Without spoilers, what is the most mind bending, intelligent and/or thought-provoking film you have ever seen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 01:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of my favorites include 
-The 39 Steps
-Beyond the Black Rainbow
-The Royal Tenenbaums
-Primer
-Eyes Wide Shut, 2001: A Space Odyssey
-Enter the Void
-Memento, Inception, Interstellar
-Southland Tales

I'm looking for films that stick with you after you see them, for better or worse. Something that makes you think and consider other viewpoints or something that passes as solid after multiple viewings. Surprise endings are not necessarily key, just a solid, intelligent film would be great. Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 23:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red Corner with Richard Gere isn't specifically a "law movie", there's some mystery to it but it involves an American businessman suddenly forced into the Chinese legal system as a defendant. I enjoyed it, and I enjoyed most of the films in your list. I also like the Pelican Brief, but the book was a bit better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The police forces of the United States launch a surprise, collaborative attack in an effort to seize control of the country. All branches of state and local law enforcement are in this united force. How far would they get in their takeover? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Military is against this operation. Military officials who are serving law enforcement roles or vice versa are actually sleeper cell policerevolution spies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time travel has been proven to be theoretically possible by current understanding of the quantum relation of atoms and their responses to observation. So technically time travel can be considered logical. Just wanted to throw that out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every single person who downvotes submissions in this subreddit team together against a six year old girl with a fly swatter. Who would win? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Primer (2004) - Intelligent independent sci-fi thriller about a team of engineers working out of their garage who accidentally create a time machine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 02:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Deathmatch] Harry Potter vs. Luke Skywalker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 00:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can I get rich without putting much time, money, effort or work into it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 08:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every subreddit is now a sovereign country whose subscribers are the military. World war erupts. Who comes out victorious? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 05:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All existing alliances and likely alliances are in play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 04:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate McDonald's so I don't eat there. I don't stand in the lobby and yell at everyone and try to shut them down or change them. I simply don't fucking go there. See how that works? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 04:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not one mention of Prescott Bush? Seriously? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 01:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starving children in Africa have no idea what suffering truly is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: You can avoid being offended by certain subreddits by pouring gasoline on your computer and setting it on fire! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 00:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 00:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean you had to see sentences you don't agree with and take the time to look at the next sentence? Your life must be a living hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Krispy Kreme apologizes for 'KKK Wednesdays' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 06:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ryu vs. Iron Man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 08:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> City street fight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
