<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5807</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists make breakthrough in understanding how to control intense heat bursts in fusion experiments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 21:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in 2005 a thirty-foot-high trash avalanche at a Landfill in Indonesia killed 143 people and destroyed 71 houses. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 21:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That's not God you just spoke to; it was a dream. "All humans are endowed with brains innately primed to daily generate god concepts in dreaming." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 15:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have used stem cells to create custom red blood cells tailored to individual patients. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 21:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Psychology retractions have quadrupled since 1989 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 04:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A quantum effect helps protect plants during photosynthesis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 17:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Intimate partners with low self-esteem stay in unhappy relationships </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 20:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 21:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is clearly satire, just to make that fact plain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Terrible, Horrifying, Painful Truth About All Those Corporate Scientist   Science Writer Shills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 21:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Computer games can be used to watch for early signs of cognitive decline in the elderly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 03:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Incarceration has little effect on crime rates. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 05:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When scientific findings challenge a person's social identity, they are more likely to try to attack or discredit the science. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 16:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Cannabis use in patients with a psychotic disorder has a long-lasting negative effect on illness outcome, particularly when persistent. Treatment should focus on discouraging cannabis use. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 01:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Athletic performance fluctuates based on circadian rhythms. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 02:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds that NFL players who started football before the age of 12 are more likely to have thinking and memory problems as adults, regardless of the time they actually spent playing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 18:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On the Existence of Low-Mass Dark Matter and its Direct Detection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 04:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is glass a true solid? New research suggests it is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 19:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chewing a piece of gum removes up to 100 million bacteria from your mouth, a similar amount to flossing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 19:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If models bear out, the average child of the next generation will live for over 100 years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 20:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study shows that the incidence of lung cancer is lower at higher elevations. "For every 1,000 m rise in elevation, lung cancer incidence decreased by 7.23 cases per 100,000 individuals." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 00:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 21:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to see Hai exercising; I've been worried about his health. Hopefully Balls will get him to hit the weights, too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A review finds that prison inmates suffer from deficits in executive cognitive functions. The researchers suggest that the prison environment may deteriorate those functions, potentially making inmates more prone to future criminality. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 21:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do we breathe oxygen and not some other gas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 17:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You Have More Musical Talent Than You Think. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 20:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cold is contagious: In a new study, when subjects looked at someone dipping their hands into ice water, their own hands actually grew colder. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 23:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fast-food consumption in children linked to poorer academic outcomes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 21:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA Study Proposes Airships, Cloud Cities for Venus Exploration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 02:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Most Radioactive Places on Earth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 21:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Biggest Junk Science of 2014. A familiar face to /r/skeptic earned the top spot. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 17:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10 Ways That Brain Myths Are Harmful </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 18:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the first time, researchers have tallied the number of microorganisms that Americans unintentionally consume every day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 17:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analysis of comet water from the Rosetta mission contradicts the theory that water on Earth had a cometary origin. Instead it's now more likely that Earth got its water from asteroids. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 17:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 19:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original for good measure! 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4sT99Y4AnmA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 19:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, my baby. Hello, my honey. Hello, my ragtime gal.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4sT99Y4AnmA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How One Woman's Discovery Shook the Foundations of Geology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 19:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "83% of the Psychology/Education articles with four or more experiments that were published in Science (20052012) have an excess of success, which suggests that their results are too good to be true." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 01:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A study conducted in Chicago found that giving disadvantaged, minority youths 8-week summer jobs reduced their violent crime rates compared to controls by 43% over a year after the program ended. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 20:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hype around cannabis as a treatment for cancer is undeserved </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 04:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have used carbonate to boost silver's antimicrobial activity 1000x. The change could make it much easier to spread clean drinking water throughout the third world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 22:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obesity-attributable absenteeism among US workers costs the nation more than $8 billion annually </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 00:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists get the first, up-close look at what a nuclear meltdown looks like. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 19:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Many Possible Melodies Are There? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 18:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
