<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4458</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I bought a pretzel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 02:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 01:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I say just cover the game as a whole like what makes this particular smash different overall, make brief comparisons to other smash games it shares similarities to and maybe even game feel/speed/etc? I feel like you could do that for all iterations of smash games and give the newcomers who don't doesn't know the difference between each iteration a brief overview of what the composition of that particular smash game is. Not sure if I made sense there but hopefully you got the gist of it haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 23:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't done too much research but I feel like it is. I'm still interested in getting it since it looks impressive. Either that or transistor.

EDIT: guess there's way more to be excited about than I thought </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 23:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> binding of isaac for $1, the hd remake is coming out soon for about $15 preorder but if you're on a budget I strongly recommend. I believe if you preorder the remake while having a copy of the original you get 33% off the game so if you plan to buy both I guess you save like 4 dollars on the remake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 22:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 9 volt playable character </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 00:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just PMed you asking about details but I guess you're planning a small meet up. Just let me know time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 23:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in c9 but I'm down as well. Just pm me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help opening up ASUS U47A to clean internal fan! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 06:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not exactly sure if that title helps with identifying the model but I've tried opening up this laptop and I'm too scared to go any further.  Tried finding similar model tutorials online but nothing really comes close. Some help would be appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
