<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5096</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 09:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've watched that ending a dozen times and his face doesn't change at all. the only thing to give a hint is the sound of boots on pavement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> question about the ending of The Drop. spoilers maybe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 05:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so the woman says she'll go get her jacket and he's waiting there. and then we hear really loud footsteps sounding like running. did she go to the cops?

aquarion, blassreiter, gankutsuou, gad guard, kite, md geist, now and then, shigurui, slayers, xxxholic, 009 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 23:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it fell less than a foot. I bet he plays soccer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 09:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how did you try to do it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 13:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's because it's rare </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 07:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when I was in middle school our DARE officer got suspended for using cocaine. I've cheated so many drug tests during high school and i'm sure that cops get more leeway than I did. these guys must be retarded

just tape the synthetic piss it to your thigh because they make you hike up your pants to your knees, and also pee on the outside of the bottle because sometimes they smell it. and make sure to follow the directions to have it at the right temperature. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 05:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'd give her a night. I have no standards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 05:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want know what she said just after the video ended. "the fact that women have been shut out of dangerous..." 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> i give up trying to make an alright pirate deck. can someone please share theirs with me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 21:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 14:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I call bullshit. not that you did this, only that alcohol is solely to blame.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 07:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't get me wrong, fuck republicans and all that. but if this senator was republican this post would be on the front page with 3000 comments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 03:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant wait to be outraged by the verdict that they're too young to know that stabbing someone causes death </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 01:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you. hope you have a nice day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what's the name of that subreddit where some guy posts random sequences of numbers and theres a conspiracy theory about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 01:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 21:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live near seattle and i'm pretty sure I've had this beer before. it came in a golden or yellow 24oz can and was really good. too expensive for me though (around $3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 17:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nope, I can't. well actually I can get one but not two </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 22:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did anyone actually think that putting any kind of smoke in your lungs is healthy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 12:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> was he still on dope then? he looks pinnned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 20:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the driver is a Saudi so he'll probably beat the worker too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 11:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you. hope you didn't do that on my account. too bad shroom season is still a few months off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 11:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you don't happen to know what episode that was do you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 06:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, death for yelling and screaming the morning after new years on the train. completely justified in my opinion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 10:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I had to punch you and knock you out because I was concerned for your health because you might have been smoking marijuana" 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 10:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a handle or a fifth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 17:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because a shaman is a great authority on western culture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 22:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a hard reset is always holding down all the buttons at once. usually fixes most problems </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 06:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, that's the job he took </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 04:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no doug Stanhope?

edit: no doug stanhope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 12:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually while I was off on the shoulder, two other crashes occurred. I think a presidential candidate was in town 

but is that your way of saying giving a ticket to someone who just crashed their car is justified? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 09:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forget, there was an unlit underpass and traffic was going smooth up until then where traffic stopped. completely my fault as I told the cop. traffic was about 50mph until the unlit overpass where traffic was stopped. my fault  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 09:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "this guy is making too much sense, better downvote him rather than talk to him" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 08:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gathered that. I also got a ticket after I was in an accident. 

don't just ignore an opinion you don't agree with or so you can meet your quota without feeling bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 08:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> driver got in an accident, give him a ticket too. and you wonder why people hate cops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 01:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> can the other guy see when i'm fucking about with the features on the board? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 00:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 22:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you don't have siblings. i'm kinda in the same boat and Christmas was hell. seriously I have never wanted to kill myself more than during holidays </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 06:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you know, you're probably right and I can't find where it was mentioned before. probably just a conspiracy theory or something. but i'm sure i'm read something bout it on reddit. anyways thanks for being cool about me being wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 04:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just look at any of the times it was posted on reddit. usually one of the highest comments explains it. how I heard it was fake was on reddit so i'm sure you can find it if you look </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 03:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anyone know if this is fake like the American south episode or if it's real this time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 00:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> probably empty and in the trash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 15:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't make it that far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 11:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how many dogs have UPS, FedEx and Postal worker killed combined? FUCKING ZERO. cops are pussies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 09:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my problem with feminism is that feminists never focus on actual problems but instead only stuff they think affects them. there are plenty of problems concerning women in the middle east and i'd be 100 percent behind any feminist who addresses them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 08:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "police officers don't meet the same consequences that the general public would experience in the same scenario"

how many dogs have UPS or FedEx or USPS drivers killed? zero. cops? too many to count. i was a seasonal driver helper and got bitten by a dog. didn't even report it. there should be a cowardice test along with the other ones

if a post office worker kicked a dog that was biting him, he would lose his job. but a cop shooting a golden retriever? guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 05:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yea, never realized until now how autistic George costanza was </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 18:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's not that. just that once hard a was allowed to be sold in grocery stores liquor stores couldn't compete.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 17:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once tried to have a civilized conversation with someone there, but it was like talking with a cop... oh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 17:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> washington </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 08:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not that much drinking in either of them. but thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 07:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish my state still had liquor stores. just bought a ten dollar handle of vodka that cost me almost twenty with tax. and had to wait in line with judgmental assholes. I worked an overnight shift you cunts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 07:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my buddy was the first legal weed bike dealer in Washington state. his pack consists of weed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 06:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's because those states have already legalized medical marijuana for awhile now. nobody is going to buy a $40 gram if they can get a $10 gram or $15 dollar (medical) of same shit. 

two things I hate about this subreddit - people just can't connect two simple dots. and this post has 200 upvotes but only 10 comments. people think upvoting a post within this little subreddit of people who already smoke weed is helping the cause </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> looking for anime with lots of drug use or heavy drinking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 06:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's gotta be English dubbed. and preferably action with cool fight scenes. thanks

on a side note, also looking for action anime with art style similar to afro samurai or redline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> looking for a dubbed anime with lots of drug use and or heavy drinking. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 04:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pretty much any anime with drug use fits the bill but action is a bonus. i'm looking for something where drinking is more than just a quirk like eating a lot or sleeping a lot and defines the character. or really any anime where drug use is common </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 00:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 steps on how to use a dildo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 06:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you write really well. write the next game of thrones. George r martin probably gets hella bitches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anime with lots of drug use or heavy drinking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 15:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> looking for any anime with lots of drug use </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 15:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 06:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah I've worked UPS driver helper a couple seasons and at the start of a day when the truck is fully loaded, some packages will get stepped on to get to ones in the back. it can't be helped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 19:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is the zoo decklist he posted the best one? is there a better zoo deck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 02:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol that's the definition of the word, retard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 01:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was right.  http://www.ushistory.org/franklin/philadelphia/fire.htm

I won't bother to call you a retard, but why do foreigners always care so much about America anyways? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 00:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> didn't benjamin franklin invent firefighters? what did the rest of the world do before, just watch shit burn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 19:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what does getting shot feel like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 06:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the art and the that title "master of disguise" sounds badass

also its just 1 health off from being a yeti but its special is really useful when I get a 8/3 bloodsail raider (which is a 2 drop) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 05:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got from rank 20 to 16 today with just this deck. I played a few hours today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 04:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have those and I really want to enchant my first legendary, but yeah I really want a blade furry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 04:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> give it a shot man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 08:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> does the producer have tits?

DN episode 9 next </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 06:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he broke through the autism spectrum into infrared colors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 12:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there's a weakened version of 211? that seems unbelievable because it would be more expensive to dilute the shit than change the label on the cans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 09:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the alcohol tax in washingoton state forces me to. i'm not made out of money, cutie. I drink steel reserves like a champ. i'd rather drink whiskey but I can't afford it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
