<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject138</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The boozing starts from 7am. Though large amounts are often drunk, the sessions are orderly, even sociable. A skinful later, and always before nightfall, enough is enough and they rest. They are the chimpanzees of Bossou, south-eastern Guinea, and their secret is finally out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 03:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Spanish bullfighter gored in the testicles by a bull he was fighting has left hospital. The huge black fighting bull thrust its left horn into Marco Galans groin, lifting him in the air, after he thrust two spears into the animals back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 02:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu said on Tuesday he hoped Arab states could press the Palestinians to return to talks to reach a two-state solution to the Israeli-Palestinian conflict. Netanyahu, speaking to a strategic conference near Tel Aviv, blamed the Palestinians for the 14-month impasse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 02:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israelis and Palestinians would gain billions of dollars from making peace with each other while both would face daunting economic losses in case of other alternatives, particularly in case of a return to violence, according to a new study released on Monday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 13:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans shift strategy in effort to increase logging - This year, the Republican-led push is focused on excluding certain projects from an environmental review and by making a lawsuit to stop a project potentially much more expensive to file. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 13:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A guitar once owned by John Lennon - which mysteriously disappeared in 1963 - has been located and will be auctioned in November. Lennons 1962 Gibson guitar was used on many of the Beatles early hits like Love Me Do, I Want To Hold Your Hand and She Loves You. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 12:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The regional president of the northern Italian region of Lombardy has refused to accept any more migrants in to the province in comments backed by other regional leaders. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 12:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video footage reveals the devastation inside the cruise ship in China which capsized in a freak storm on the Yangtze river last week. Rescue teams use circular saws to cut through muddy mangled metal in the hull as passengers' personal belongings lie strewn around. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 12:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkish President Tayyip Erdogan said on Monday no party had won a mandate to govern alone in a parliamentary election and urged all political parties to work towards preserving an environment of confidence and stability in the country. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 12:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 02:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The party that controls the laws also controls the people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A major new study from NOAA finds more evidence that we may be witnessing the start of the long-awaited jump in global temperatures. As I reported in April, many recent studies have found that we are about to enter an era of even more rapid global warming. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 02:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warmer, Lower-Oxygen Oceans Drive Marine Species toward the Poles - In order to survive, a number of species may move closer to the poles, though there is no guarantee these new habitats will be hospitable, the researchers said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 02:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newly discovered vessels beneath skull could link brain and immune system - I thought the body was mapped and that these discoveries ended somewhere around the middle of the last century. But apparently they have not. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 02:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two blasts ripped through a Kurdish rally in Turkey on Friday, killing two people and injuring more than 100 in what President Tayyip Erdogan described as a "provocation" designed to undermine peace before Sunday's parliamentary election. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 02:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She Killed Her Rapist, and Now Shes Running For Political Office in Mexico City - In December 2013, the resident of the tough Mexico City barrio of Tepito was jailed for nearly three months for killing her rapist, stabbing him 14 times to stop what was described as a brutal sexual assault. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Pakistani court has freed eight out of 10 men charged with organizing the shooting of schoolgirl activist Malala Yousafzai, police said on Friday, a move that will raise further questions about the nation's heavily criticized justice system. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Data stolen from U.S. government computers by suspected Chinese hackers included security clearance information and background checks dating back three decades, U.S. officials said on Friday, underlining the scope of one of the largest known cyber attacks on federal networks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The presidential candidacy of Ben Carson, a tea party star who has catapulted into the top tier of Republican contenders, has been rocked by turmoil with the departures of four senior campaign officials and widespread disarray among his allied super PACs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michelle Duggar Defends Smearing Transgender People As Pedophiles: Its Just Common Sense - Jim Bob interrupted to clarify that Michelle said pedophile, which requires the perpetrator to be of a certain age, but Josh was younger  a child preying on a child, not a pedophile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 03:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Global warming has not undergone a pause or hiatus, according to US government research that undermines one of the key arguments used by sceptics to question climate science. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 03:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hackers breached the computers of the U.S. government agency that collects personnel information for federal workers in a massive cyber attack that compromised the data of about 4 million current and former employees, U.S. officials said on Thursday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 03:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The record-breaking drought in Californiabrought about by a severe lack of precipitation, especially mountain snowshas exacted a $2.7 billion toll on the states economy because of agricultural losses, researchers said Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 03:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plutos moons have been tracked closely for the first time, showing that they tumble unpredictably rather than keeping one face fixed on their host planet. Astronomers also observed that Pluto, whose status was downgraded to a dwarf planet in 2006, might be better regarded as a binary dwarf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 03:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The FBI's investigation of bribery and corruption at FIFA includes scrutiny of how soccer's governing body awarded World Cup hosting rights to Russia and Qatar, a U.S. law enforcement official said. Russia and Qatar have denied wrongdoing in the conduct of their bids </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 03:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The American Red Cross vowed to help Haitians rebuild, but after five years the Red Cross' legacy in Haiti is not new roads, or schools, or hundreds of new homes. It's difficult to know where all the money went. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 03:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A regional Costa Rican court has recognised Central Americas first same-sex civil union, despite opposition from the Catholic Church and conservative politicians, local media reported on Wednesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 03:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear Class of 2015: Youve Been Scammed! - Does this really sound like an education to you or does it sound more like a Ponzi scheme, like youve been scammed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 03:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The string of massive snowstorms and bone-chilling cold on the US east coast, as well as flooding in Britain and record temperatures in Europe, are linked to rapid ice loss in the Arctic, new research appears to confirm. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 02:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Days after the launch of two newspaper database projects aimed at tracking killings by police officers, two Democratic senators announced Tuesday that they will introduce legislation that would require all states to report to the Justice Department anytime a police officer is involved in a shooting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 02:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Large Hadron Collider (LHC) will start smashing particles together at unprecedented speed on Wednesday, churning out data for the first time in more than two years that scientists hope might help crack the mystery of "dark matter". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 02:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Data collected by NASA's Alice instrument aboard the European Space Agency's Rosetta spacecraft reveal that electrons close to the surface of comet 67P/Churyumov-Gerasimenko -- not photons from the sun, as had been believed -- cause the rapid breakup of water and carbon dioxide molecules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 00:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't worry, FIFA  Putin has your back - Judah says Putin is nervous that the corruption scandals could lead to the cancelation of the World Cup. There are also a growing number of people calling for a boycott of the 2018 World Cup. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 05:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> According to an analysis done by The Washington Post, police across the country have fatally shot at least 385 people so far this year - a rate that comes to more than two a day and is twice the number counted by federal authorities. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 05:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bird flu is raging through poultry farms across the United States. It's the largest outbreak in U.S. history, affecting 20 states and tens of millions of birds. The disease is particularly ravaging farms in the Midwest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 05:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You live in an alternate universe where religion never developed but everything else is the same. What do people scream out during sex in this universe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 05:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What We Now Know About The Men Who Led The Impeachment Of Clinton - Almost 17 years later, with the federal indictment of Hastert for illegally concealing up to $3.5 million in hush-money, we finally have a more complete understanding of the men who led this effort. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 10:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you're still looking for somewhere exotic to go this summer and don't mind a vacation that comes with a heavy dose of socialist propaganda and leader worship, North Korea says it's just the place for you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 10:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Key Patriot Act anti-terror provisions, including bulk collection of Americans' phone records, expire at midnight unless senators come up with an 11th hour deal in an extraordinary Sunday afternoon session. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 10:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maine Gov. Paul LePage (R) pledged on Friday to veto every single bill sponsored by Democratic state lawmakers until they allow his constitutional amendment banning the income tax to pass through the legislature. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 05:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netflix documentary explores the choices made by the stars behind Internet porn's biggest genre - While some people may see teen porn as a simple fantasy, there are thousands of real 18- and 19-year-old girls who provide the content that feeds online porn sites. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 05:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A deadly virus with no known cure  Middle East Respiratory Syndrome, or MERS  has infected 13 people in South Korea since mid-May. The fast spread of the disease, from the first case confirmed on May 20 to more than a dozen by Saturday, is prompting criticism of health officials </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 05:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CBS' Bob Schieffer Retires Sunday As Last Of The Old-School TV Anchors - Schieffer leaves CBS with impressive stats. He's one of the few reporters to have covered the White House, Congress, the State Department and the Pentagon. He's interviewed every president since Richard Nixon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 05:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over the last 15 years, thousands of former high-ranking intelligence officials and operatives have left their government posts and taken up senior positions at military contractors, consultancies, law firms, and private-equity firms. In their new jobs, they replicate what they did in government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 04:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former U.S. House of Representatives Speaker Dennis Hastert was indicted on Thursday on federal charges, including for lying to the FBI, relating to an alleged effort to hide $3.5 million in payments to a person to conceal past misconduct. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 04:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When rival biker gangs in Waco, Texas, fired hundreds of rounds at each other, leaving nine dead, 18 hospitalized, and 170 arrested, are we to anticipate the perpetrators mass exoneration because its just too hard to figure out who fired the bullets that actually killed someone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 04:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Real Anti-Poverty Movement Cant Be Led By Millionaires - A strong anti-poverty movement will be led by the people who understand what poverty really is, why it happens, how we could create workable solutions. A strong movement will be made up of the people who are poverty experts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 03:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexican President Enrique Pena Nieto misrepresented to authorities the circumstances under which he acquired one of his properties, public documents reviewed by Reuters show, a discrepancy that could add to the controversy surrounding his personal finances. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 03:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The corruption charges engulfing world soccer's governing body have heaped shame and humiliation on the game, FIFA President Sepp Blatter said on Thursday, although he flatly rejected calls to resign over the widening scandal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 03:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alabama Chief Justice Roy Moore, a rabid opponent of marriage equality, told the Family Research Councils Tony Perkins on Tuesday that he believes Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg should be impeached for officiating the marriages of same-sex couples. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 01:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The prosecutors seeking to send Timothy Tyrone Foster to death row went about their job in a curious manner. During jury selection, they highlighted each black prospective jurors name in greenon four different copies of the jury listand wrote that the green highlighting represents blacks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 01:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate Change May Have Souped Up Record-Breaking Texas Deluge - Ekwurzel added, When you have a warmer atmosphere, then you have the capability to hold more water vapor. When storms organize, theres much more water you can wring out of the atmosphere compared to the past. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 01:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heaviest Downpours Rise across the U.S. - While rainfall in the region is consistent with the emerging El Nio, the unprecedented amounts suggest a possible climate change signal, where a warming atmosphere becomes more saturated with water vapor and capable of previously unimagined downpours. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 01:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Court of Appeals for the Eighth Circuit has blocked a harsh abortion ban in Arkansas that seeks to ban the procedure after just 12 weeks of pregnancy, significantly before the point of viability that serves as the current cut-off point for legal abortion services under Roe v. Wade. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 00:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have pieced together the worlds earliest murder mystery, showing that an ancient human appears to have met their end after being bludgeoned to death and thrown down a cave shaft. The skull, which has two holes above the left eye, belonged to an early human closely related to Neanderthals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 00:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the U.S. can arrest FIFA officials in Switzerland, explained - There are few secrets so poorly kept that billions of people know them, but FIFA's sketchy practices were one of them. Leave it to the soccer-indifferent Yanks to finally point out that the emperor's clothes appear to be stolen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 00:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Defense Secretary Ash Carter on Wednesday called for an immediate end to island-building by China and other countries near the South China Sea, urging the participants to stop militarizing the dispute and find a peaceful solution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 00:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Internal Revenue Service believes the theft of about 100,000 taxpayers' personal data from its computer system originated in Russia, CNN reported on Wednesday. The tax agency's criminal unit is leading an investigation into the cyber attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 00:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Smart Should the President Be? - Whats more, IQ correlated positively with a measure of presidential greatness based on multiple rankings and ratings of presidents leadership abilityand the relationship went in a straight line. The smarter the president, the better, roughly speaking. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 00:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Testing is underway on NASA's next mission on the journey to Mars, a stationary lander scheduled to launch in March 2016. The lander is called InSight, an abbreviation for Interior Exploration using Seismic Investigations, Geodesy and Heat Transport. It is about the size of a car </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 23:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia's army is massing troops and hundreds of pieces of weaponry including mobile rocket launchers, tanks and artillery at a makeshift base near the border with Ukraine, a Reuters reporter saw this week. Many of the vehicles have number plates and identifying marks removed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 23:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA's CloudSat has imaged the eye of a category 4 typhoon, a feat the space agency likened to a "golfer hitting a hole in one." Its cloud-penetrating radar has a field of view of just .5 square miles, making it a challenge to zone in on such a tiny, fast-moving target. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 22:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three people have been confirmed dead after record rainfall across the south-central United States led to flash flooding over the weekend across Texas and Oklahoma. In Claremore, Oklahoma, a firefighter was killed early Sunday after he was swept away during a water rescue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 22:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An anti-immigrant Arizona sheriff is asking the public to help with his legal fees while he waits for a decision on a contempt of court hearing about his departments systemic racial profiling of suspected undocumented immigrants. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 21:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 21:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a matter of fact I do get wood over guys but that's because I'm bisexual and how were you to know that? But fuck Pattinson, especially after Cosmopolis. Anyway, he doesn't look like a bottom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The governor of Texas on Monday declared states of disaster in 24 counties, citing the severe weather and flash flooding that have killed at least two people. The state has been pounded by tornadoes, heavy rainfall, thunderstorms and flooding that forced evacuations and rooftop rescues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 21:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 16:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess we could argue this all day,and truthfully, I wouldn't kick her out of my own bed for eating crackers, but seeing her in any movie immediately ruins it for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 14:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If her acting were better I wouldn't be forced to notice her looks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 13:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Emma Watson had a pointy chin and could only open her eyes halfway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 10:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kristen Stewart - I cannot find her even remotely attractive in any role, but especially the pasty chick in the Twilight series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 09:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've asked several times for sources on that subreddit and I'm either ignored or directed to the individual's blog where I'll also find no sources or citations. Additionally, they'll cite wikapedia, which is a good starting point for sources relating to a topic, but I don't trust the website for consistent accuracy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 07:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/askhistorians - The crap they post there for answers to historical events/people make working historians cringe, plus if you ask for citations or where they got their information, it's treated like you've made a personal attack. If a citation is provided it's usually from a history channel show, which is a whole new level of crappage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 06:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked at a restaurant in the Omni Hotel, San Diego, that was owned by a guy who donated so much to the George W. Bush campaign he was rewarded with the ambassodorship to New Zealand. Meanwhile, waiters/waitresses at his restaurant were forced by management to participate in a "fake-a-break" program. Employees that worked more than six hours were forced to choose between working through a thirty minuted break or taking that break during the busy period and losing out on tips. If anyone spoke out about the "fake-a-break" program, they were harassed by management. While stealing hours from his employees, the restaurant owner enjoyed a fat government paycheck with perks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Domestic dogs may have a pedigree that dates back almost 40,000 years to when modern humans started colonising Europe and Asia, new research has shown. Previous studies suggested that the ancestors of modern-day dogs diverged from wolves no more than 16,000 years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 02:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a former Virginia lawmaker made a bad situation even worse, in 1 picture - The image shows Morrissey, who is white, and Pride, who is black, in what some reporters have described as period dress  without mention of the fact that said period would appear to be the antebellum South </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 02:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stable Antarctic Ice Is Suddenly Melting Fast - Sea levels worldwide will rise higher than anticipated, thanks to a new once-stable region of Antarctica that is suddenly melting, and at a fast rate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 02:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research published in the journal Science on Thursday found the Southern Antarctic Peninsula (SAP) ice sheet is losing ice into the ocean at a rate of 56 gigatons each year  about 8,500 times the mass of the Great Pyramid of Giza. This adds around 0.16mm per year to the global sea level. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 02:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey's state intelligence agency helped deliver arms to parts of Syria under Islamist rebel control during late 2013 and early 2014, according to a prosecutor and court testimony from gendarmerie officers seen by Reuters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 02:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> During a campaign appearance in Beaumont, Texas, presidential hopeful Sen. Ted Cruz (R-TX) wondered why the left  including the media was so obsessed with sex when the terrorist group Islamic State, known as ISIS or ISIL, is executing gay people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 00:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arizonas legislature has decided to try to plug a $1 billion budget deficit in part by kicking people off of welfare after just 12 months, the strictest time limit in the country. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 00:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate change: Americans crowding into future heatwave zones, study says - The study highlighted the Houston-Dallas-San Antonio and Atlanta-Charlotte-Raleigh corridors as the places where the effect looks to be greatest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 00:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Florida man who flew a gyrocopter onto the grounds of the U.S. Capitol in April faces up to 9-1/2 years in prison after being indicted by a federal grand jury on Wednesday. Douglas Hughes, a 61-year-old mail carrier from Ruskin, Florida, was indicted on six charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 23:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News, which is hosting the first Republican debate of the 2016 campaign, will require participants to place in the top 10 in an average of the five most recent national polls in the run-up to the event, according to details obtained by The Washington Post Thursday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 23:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Tuesday, a pipeline along the coast of California just north of Santa Barbara ruptured and spilled an estimated 21,000 gallons of crude oil. A significant portion of this oil ended up in the ocean, creating a four-mile-long slick along the coastline. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 23:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New cell phone video of the arrest of Freddie Gray, the unarmed black man who was critically injured in April in the custody of Baltimore police and later died, shows officers lifting his limp body into a police van face down and head first at the first of four stops </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 23:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New York Times put a 1,700-word piece on its front page Tuesday that accuses the EPA of violating federal laws on grassroots campaigning. The paper ran the story despite knowing the accusation is not true, a fact that is buried deep in the article. How is that journalism? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 23:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New York Times put a 1,700-word piece on its front page Tuesday that accuses the EPA of violating federal laws on grassroots campaigning. The paper ran the story despite knowing the accusation is not true, a fact that is buried deep in the article. How is that journalism? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 23:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aid Burst Lifts People out of Extreme Poverty - Giving some of the worlds poorest people a two-year aid packageincluding cash, food, health-care services, skills training and adviceimproves their livelihoods for at least a year after the support is cut off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 23:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paracetamol is the painkiller considered safest for pregnant women. However, researchers investigating reproductive defects in baby boys such as undescended testes say there may be a link between low levels of testosterone and paracetamol intake. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 23:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photographs showing a North Korean missile launched from a submarine were manipulated by state propagandists and the country may be years away from developing such technology, analysts and a top U.S. military official said on Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 23:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Osama Bin Laden Loved Reading Conspiracy Theories and Noam Chomsky Books - It's fun to imagine Bin Laden reading to pass time in hiding, stretched out on an IKEA PONG and eating white cheddar Pirate's Booty. Notably, he doesn't read any fiction or pop nonfiction. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 22:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A mysterious robotic space plane launched its secretive mission for the US air force on Wednesday, its fourth long orbital flight in five years. The X-37B launched from Cape Canaveral, Florida, for the reusable spacecrafts fourth mission. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 22:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State insurgents stormed the historic Syrian city of Palmyra on Wednesday, fighting off pro-government forces who withdrew after evacuating most of the civilian population, state television said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 22:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 16:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forrest Gump - "Life is like a box of chocolates, motherfucker...." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This past weekend, against the steel gray sky of the Puget Sound, hundreds of climate activists took to the water to surround Shells Polar Pioneer, the 307-foot-tall flagship of the companys newly resurgent Arctic drilling fleet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 12:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraqi forces said they fought off an overnight attack by Islamic State militants near the city of Ramadi, which the insurgents overran at the weekend in the most significant setback for the government in a year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 12:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you do the maths puzzle for Vietnamese eight-year-olds that has stumped parents and teachers? - You need to fill in the gaps with the digits from 1 to 9 so that the equation makes sense, following the order of operations - multiply first, then division, addition and subtraction last. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 12:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress wants to cut President Clintons pension, federal allowance - The House Oversight committee Tuesday passed unanimously a measure to limit the federal taxpayer dollars former presidents receive for their various expenses. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 12:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran's Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei said on Wednesday Tehran would not accept "unreasonable demands" by world powers during negotiations over its disputed nuclear programme, and ruled out letting inspectors interview its atomic scientists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 12:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu has ordered the suspension of a controversial measure banning Palestinians from riding the same buses as Jewish settlers when returning from Israel to the West Bank. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 12:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marco Rubio Refuses To Answer A Basic Question About The Iraq War - Repeatedly pressed by host Chris Wallace on whether in hindsight the Bush administration should have invaded Iraq, Rubio continued to dodge the question. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 12:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A senior NATO official said on Monday it was still unclear whether Russia was prepared to take steps to support the Minsk agreement to ease the conflict in Ukraine, adding that Moscow would face more sanctions and isolation if the deal collapsed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 12:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are ignoring the new machine age at our peril - About 47% of total US employment is at risk from technologies now operational in laboratories and in the field. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 11:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A debate over the Iraq war triggered by Jeb Bush's wobbly response to questions about it spilled into a major gathering of Republican 2016 U.S. presidential hopefuls on Saturday, reflecting divisions about whether the conflict was worthwhile. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 11:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teenagers in Montgomery, Georgia celebrated their fifth integrated prom this year  thanks, in part, to photographer Gillian Laub who spent 12 years documenting the towns struggle to confront deep-seated racial tensions  and ended up transforming the town through her images. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 10:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cambodia has deported a fugitive Russian tycoon living illegally in the south-east Asian country after he was accused of embezzling $175m in his homeland. Accompanied by Russian authorities, Sergei Polonsky was put on a flight to Moscow via Vietnam on Sunday morning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 10:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Antarctic ice shelf roughly half the size of Rhode Island will disintegrate completely within the next few years, according to a NASA study released Thursday. In 2002, two-thirds of the Larsen B Ice Shelf  which had been intact for more than 10,000 years  broke up in less than six weeks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 01:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. industrial production fell for a fifth straight month in April, weighed down by declines in mining and utilities output, pointing to a lack of momentum in the economy at the start of the second quarter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 01:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Alabama taught its children to be racists -- and what will it do with science? - Fourth graders until the '70s learned how living on a plantation was "one of the happiest ways of life." Just imagine yourself, the 1957 edition says, on your family plantation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 01:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In U.S. cities, Republicans are looking for a few good losers for 2016 - The goal isn't necessarily to win these races, but to improve the performance of the Republican ticket overall and build a base for success over the longer term. That could help the party's presidential candidate as well </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 01:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two men who had been colleagues at the former FTSE 100 mining group Eurasian Natural Resources Corporation have been found dead at a hotel in the US. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 01:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Maryland governor Martin OMalley, who is poised to launch a White House bid this month, reaffirmed his strong opposition to capital punishment Friday following a federal jurys decision to sentence to death one of those convicted for the Boston Marathon bombings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 00:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Texas legislature early Friday failed to advance a proposal to prohibit local officials from granting marriage licenses to gay couples, a measure viewed as an effort to preempt an expected U.S. Supreme Court ruling next month regarding gay unions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 00:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A decade-old oil leak where an offshore platform toppled during a hurricane could continue spilling crude into the Gulf of Mexico for a century or more if left unchecked, according to government estimates obtained by The Associated Press that provide new details about the scope of the problem. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 00:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Australian government is undertaking frantic diplomatic efforts to avoid the Great Barrier Reef being listed as in danger by the UN, amid rising international concern over the opening up of a vast region in the state of Queensland for gigantic new coal mines. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 02:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Countries Grab Farmland beyond Their Own Borders - In the past 15 years companies and government groups in investor countries have grabbed 31.8 million hectares of land, the area of New Mexico (column on right), according to the Land Matrix Global Observatory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 02:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama said Fox News vilifies the poor. Jon Stewart presses his point. - "Are these glaring contradictions a product of a lack of self-awareness or cynicism or stupidity or evil? I don't know anymore," Stewart said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 02:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AFL-CIO chief: White House trade bill argument is unadulterated horse waste - "If the president wins this fight, Democrats will be in the minority for a decade or so" on Capitol Hill, Trumka said during a hour-long conversation at The Washington Post's offices. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 02:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iranian naval vessels fired shots at a Singapore-flagged tanker in the Gulf on Thursday, in what appeared to be Iran's latest attempt to settle a legal dispute by force with passing commercial vessels, U.S. officials said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 01:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The speaker of the Missouri House just resigned after sexting with an intern. Heres what you need to know. - The revelations came after Missouri Southern State University ended its internship program at the state Capitol a month early, even as the university did not specify why it did so. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 01:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A day after his Republican colleagues on the House Appropriations Committee voted along party lines to cut about one-fifth of Amtraks budget, House Ways and Means Chairman Paul Ryan (R-WI) incorrectly claimed that Congress had already funded implementing the safety system it mandated in 2008. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 00:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The car-tire-size opah is striking enough thanks to its rotund, silver body. But now, researchers have discovered something surprising about this deep-sea dweller: It's got warm blood. That makes the opah (Lampris guttatus) the first warm-blooded fish every discovered. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 00:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philadelphia train crash engineer lays low as scrutiny heats up - A portrait of the engineer at the helm of a speeding Amtrak train that derailed in Philadelphia began to emerge on Thursday as the man's lawyer said his client could not remember the crash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 00:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican Jeb Bush reversed course on Thursday and said that based on information now known, had it been up to him he would not have waged war against Iraq, putting some distance between himself and his brother, former President George W. Bush. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 00:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul is about to have a shining moment on the Patriot Act - It's the sort of good government, Mr.-Smith-goes-to-Washington stuff that even people outside of politics eat up. This is the way politics should be, they shout. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 02:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dawn Spacecraft Images Reveal "Ice Rinks" on Ceres - The presence of exposed ice on Ceres would be a surprise, because ice should be unstable on the dwarf planets airless surface, turning from a solid into a gas and drifting into space rather than sticking around. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 01:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The White House on Tuesday said it strongly supports a bill that would end the National Security Agencys mass collection of Americans phone records, a program recently ruled illegal by a federal appeals court. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 01:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Water, the weirdest liquid on the planet - Think about it for a moment: in front of you is a solid, floating on its liquid. Solid wax doesnt float on melted wax; solid butter doesnt float on melted butter in a hot saucepan; rocks dont float on lava when it spews out of a volcano. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top U.S. and Russian officials said they hoped to work together on contentious issues such as the conflicts in Ukraine and Syria but offered no sign of concrete progress after more than eight hours of talks on Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Navy says one of its fighter jets has crashed in the Persian Gulf, and the plane's two pilots ejected and were rescued without serious injury. The Navy's 5th Fleet said the F/A-18 Super Hornet crashed shortly after taking off Tuesday from the aircraft carrier USS Theodore Roosevelt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sea Level Rise Is Happening Faster Than Anyone Thought - The study, published Monday in Nature Climate Change, found that sea level rise has been speeding up over the past two decades compared to the rest of the 20th century. This contradicts previous satellite data dating back to 1993 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dane County District Attorney Ismael Ozanne announced Tuesday that he will not bring criminal charges against Madison, Wisconsin police officer Matt Kenny for shooting and killing 19-year-old Tony Robinson Jr. on March 6. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA laboratory experiments suggest the dark material coating some geological features of Jupiter's moon Europa is likely sea salt from a subsurface ocean, discolored by exposure to radiation. The presence of sea salt on Europa's surface suggests the ocean is interacting with its rocky seafloor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama, Warren feud breaks open as trade legislation blocked by Democrats - Now, in a battle few saw coming three years ago, President Obama and Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) are locked in an increasingly personal dispute over a mammoth global trade deal that the president is trying to finalize </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A group that wants to kick Andrew Jackson off the $20 bill and replace him with a woman has, after months of collecting votes, chosen a successor: Harriet Tubman. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 23:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea announced on Saturday that it successfully launched an underwater ballistic missile from a submarine, further raising concerns about its military capabilities and raising tensions in the region. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 13:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Universities 'censor' bad ideas all the time, Tim Wilson. It's called learning - In fact, the word censor comes from the Latin to assess. In universities  whether in the sciences, social sciences or the humanities  people voice their ideas by submitting them for peer review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 13:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malaysian police say more than 1,000 migrants from Myanmar and Bangladesh have been found "illegally" trying to enter the country at the popular resort island of Langkawi. The 1,018 migrants, many thought to be members of Myanmar's long-persecuted Rohingya Muslim community, landed on Langkawi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 13:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Moroccan F-16 warplane that is part of the Saudi-led force carrying out air strikes in Yemen has gone missing, Morocco's military said on Monday, and Iran-allied Houthi rebels and Saudi forces traded heavy fire across the border. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 13:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 07:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn you...this was my go-to answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker Gave Corporations Cash To Create Jobs, Forgot To Check If They Created Jobs - The group also gave loans and tax credits to companies that did not meet its requirements, and did not even attempt to fact-check claims by the companies about the number of jobs they created. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 23:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The European Rosetta spacecraft began to listen out for its robotic lander this morning amid hopes that the comet-riding probe may soon have enough solar power to wake from hibernation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 23:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Barack Obama, co-opting Nike Inc's famous slogan, told Democrats on Friday to "just do it" and support a trade deal with Asian countries that the shoe company said would help it create up to 10,000 U.S. jobs over 10 years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 23:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United States said on Friday it has asked Beijing to investigate reports that China interfered with Internet content hosted outside the country and used it to attack U.S. websites. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 23:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Justice Department waded anew Friday into fraught big city police-community relations, with new Attorney General Loretta Lynch declaring the subject "one of the most challenging issues of our time." She announced a wide-ranging investigation into Baltimore's police. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 23:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bring on the Class War: Bernie Sanders Dreams of a Revolution in 2016 - In his view, the electoral system is set up to deter those outside the political process from getting involved, insulating those inside the process from any inconvenient consequences of democracy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 03:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hawaii is on its way to having the greenest grid in the nation. The state legislature sent a bill to the governors desk this week that moves the renewable portfolio standard (RPS) up to 100 percent by 2045 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 02:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 02:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Children, can you say cronyism?
  
Very Good!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After spending months distancing himself from his familys political legacy, Jeb Bush surprised a group of Manhattan financiers this week by naming his brother, former president George W. Bush, as his most influential counselor on U.S.-Israel policy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 02:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Defense Secretary Ash Carter flatly denied Thursday the frenzied Internet speculation that a U.S. military exercise in Texas is part of a hostile takeover or other nefarious Pentagon mission. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 02:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shell Plans to Drill in the Arctic This Summer and It's Already Failed a Coast Guard Inspection - It will be the multinational oil giant's first attempt to drill there since the ill-fated summer of 2012, when Noble Discoverer was plagued by engine trouble and the drill platform Kulluk ran aground </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 04:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> According to the Republican candidates for president, our country faces two mortal threats. One is Hillary Clinton. The other is radical Islam. And its not enough to target jihadists with military force, as President Obama has. The Republicans say we must go further. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 03:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prick a finger and have the blood checked for parasites - by smartphone? Scientists are turning those ubiquitous phones into microscopes and other medical tools that could help fight diseases in remote parts of the world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 03:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a friend told you that we were all living in a giant hologram, youd probably tell him to lay off the kush. But incredibly, physicists across the world are thinking the same thing: That what we perceive to be a three-dimensional universe might just be the image of a two-dimensional one </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 02:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On paper and in speeches, Republicans boast that Congress' first budget since they won control of the Senate and House last fall will eliminate red ink within a decade. Actually, it will do nothing of the sort. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 02:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SpaceX plans to launch a dummy almost a mile into the sky on Wednesday, in a test of the private spaceflight companys new emergency abort system, a first step to safeguarding against shuttle disasters for missions with people on board. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 01:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heres what Americans *dont* want to see in a president - Well, also if someone is a "leader in the Tea Party movement" -- the trait that makes the most people very uncomfortable -- but that's somewhat subjective. (We granted Ted Cruz the title, which we assume he'd accept.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 01:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The IRS issued $5.6 billion in potentially bogus education tax credits in a single year - more than a quarter of all education credits claimed by taxpayers, a government watchdog said Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 01:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have stumbled upon the oldest known ancestor of all modern birds after breaking open a lump of ancient rock near a town in north-eastern China. They discovered the fossilised remains of the prehistoric bird, complete with exquisitely preserved plumage, in silt rock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 00:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The federal Office of Management and Budget has granted U.S. Agriculture Secretary Tom Vilsack the authority to transfer an additional $330 million in emergency funds for the agency's handling of the quickly spreading avian influenza outbreak, USDA agency sources told Reuters on Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 23:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astronomers have discovered a baby blue galaxy that is farther away in distance and time than any galaxy ever seen. It's among the universe's first generation of galaxies, from 13.1 billion years ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 23:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's Why Elon Musk Might Have Just Really Pissed Off Your Utility Company - "Here in the Southeast a lot of utilities are looking at imposing charges and fees on their customers who want to go solar. The more options customers have, the less they're going to be willing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 23:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 Tools the Police Are Using in Their War Against Activists - It is, in fact, no longer unusual but predictable for peacefully protesting citizens to face military-grade weaponry and paramilitary-style tactics, as the counterinsurgency school of protest policing has become the new normal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 23:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Traffic Around Mars Gets Busy - Traffic management at Mars is much less complex than in Earth orbit, where more than 1,000 active orbiters plus additional pieces of inactive hardware add to hazards. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 23:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA's Dawn mission will host the flagship event for its "I C Ceres" space festival at the California Institute of Technology in Pasadena on Saturday, May 9, from 10 a.m. to 4:30 p.m. The free event is intended for all ages. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 23:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican Mike Huckabee announced a run for his party's 2016 presidential nomination on Tuesday with a fiery, populist speech aimed at energizing support from the Christian right and blue-collar Americans struggling to make ends meet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 23:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Huckabee kicks off his 2016 bid with a violation of campaign finance law - And then he added, to laughter, "Now, rest assured, if you want to give a million dollars, please do it." It was mostly a joke. It also violated campaign finance law. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 23:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last week, the House Subcommittee for Transportation, Housing, and Urban Development approved a bill that cuts funding for affordable housing for the lowest income households. The move by House Republicans imperils a crucial resource that can help address homelessness. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 00:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since at least 2007, the FBI has been able to recognize the voice of Elton Simpson - one of the men suspected in the Texas shootings outside a contest featuring cartoons of the Muslim Prophet Muhammad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 00:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Severe Chlamydia Outbreak Hits Texas High School That Focuses On Teaching Abstinence - Since Crane High School only has about 300 students, that means about one in 15 kids there has been infected. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 00:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NATO launched one of its biggest-ever anti-submarine exercises in the North Sea on Monday, inviting non-member Sweden for the first time, amid increasing tensions between Russia and its northern neighbors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 00:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Porn Stars Share Their Most Embarrassing Sex Stories - I think one of the funniest scenes I've ever shot was a Spongebob parody. I was Sandy the Squirrel and the guy was "Spongeknob Squarenuts." We were doing the voices, badly, and it was so hard to keep a straight face. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 00:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Supreme Court won't hear a dispute over statements that law enforcement officials in Queens, New York, made before telling suspects about their Miranda rights against self-incrimination. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 23:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Israeli group that collects testimonies from combat soldiers has published accounts from last year's Gaza war alleging indiscriminate fire killed Palestinian civilians. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 23:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astronaut Samantha Cristoforetti fired up the first espresso machine in space over the weekend. She posted a selfie on Twitter from the International Space Station on Sunday, sipping from a cup designed for use in zero-gravity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 23:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Supreme Court has turned away a challenge to New Jersey's ban on so-called gay conversion therapy for patients under 18 years old. The justices did not comment on their order Monday. It followed similar action last year that left California's therapy ban in place. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 23:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 05:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything from Suzy Solar, but Judge Jules also does a nice monthly set that he puts on his website for download. If you want some real hands-in-the-air or uplifting trance, try Aly   Fila's Future Sounds of Egypt pod cast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 04:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Condsidering the zeal with which you attack major corporations, federal agencies, and politicians, do you ever fear repercussions? Do you have any sneaking suspicions that you"re on a no-fly or watch list? Has the harassment extended to the show's writers, producers, or directors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new petition filed with the US Securities and Exchange Commission accuses Royal Dutch Shell of misleading investors about the risks of drilling in the Arctic Ocean and alleges the company is unprepared to handle a major oil spill. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 08:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SpaceX is just days away from shooting up a crew capsule to test a launch escape system designed to save astronauts lives. Buster, the dummy, is already strapped in for Wednesdays nearly mile-high ride from Cape Canaveral, Florida. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 00:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamist rebels and the Syrian army fought fierce battles in Latakia province overnight close to President Bashar al-Assad's ancestral home, the army and rebels said, after weeks of insurgent gains in the country's northwest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 00:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doctors Disagree With The Baltimore Police About Freddie Gray's Spinal Injuries - Freddie Gray didnt stand up in the back of that van and twist his back, Belk said. What it would take to break a persons spine is heavy trauma. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 00:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate change could drive up to a sixth of animals and plants on Earth to extinction unless governments cut rising greenhouse gas emissions, according to a U.S. study published on Thursday. Species in South America, Australia and New Zealand are most at risk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 00:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Images from NASAs New Horizons spacecraft suggest that Pluto has a polar cap made of some kind of ice. The pictures, taken over the past few weeks and released on April 29, show Pluto with its largest moon, Charon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 00:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When a man in Colorado contracted the plague from his two-year-old pit bull terrier and spread it to four other people last summer, the resulting outbreak was the largest in 88 years  and the first known dog-to-human transmission of the disease </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 00:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Friday, the Sanders campaign announced that it has raised more than $1.5 million online in the 24 hours since he announced his candidacy. It is a surprisingly heavy haul for a candidate whom some in the Democratic chattering class have cast off as a gadfly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 00:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The electric car company Tesla has announced its entry into the energy market, unveiling a suite of low-cost solar batteries for homes, businesses and utilities, the missing piece, it said, in the transition to a sustainable energy world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 23:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than one in four U.S. renters have to use at least half their family income to pay for housing and utilities. That's the finding of an analysis of Census data by Enterprise Community Partners, a nonprofit that helps finance affordable housing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 23:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkish police fired tear gas and water cannon at hundreds of stone-throwing May Day protesters on Friday, after they defied a ban and tried to march on Istanbul's Taksim Square. Europe's biggest city was under a security lockdown as thousands of police manned barricades and closed streets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 23:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iowa Governor Terry Branstad declared a state of emergency on Friday due to a rapidly expanding avian flu outbreak, soon after state agriculture officials announced four new poultry farms had initially tested positive for the virus. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 23:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It only took two weeks for the Republican-led House in North Carolina to introduce and pass a bill gutting the states environmental law. The House passed the SEPA Reform Act on Wednesday after allowing total of one minute of public comment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 00:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia's military may be taking advantage of a recent lull in fighting in eastern Ukraine to lay the groundwork for a new military offensive, NATO's top commander told the U.S. Congress on Thursday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 00:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Character Assassination Of Freddie Gray - What is consistent, however, is police departments selective release of information that paints people injured or killed by police in a bad light  and mainstream medias decision to buy into it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 23:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The private spaceflight company Blue Origin launched a surprise test flight of its suborbital New Shepard spaceship on Wednesday (April 29), a mission that successfully demonstrated the space capsule but failed to recover its reusable rocket booster. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 23:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Given the NYPDs pervasive lack of transparency, there will probably never be a public accounting of why they so dramatically shifted gears last night in deciding to aggressively corral, arrest, and terrorize demonstrators marching in solidarity with the protests in Baltimore. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 23:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The leading American professional group for psychologists secretly worked with the Bush administration to help justify the post-9/11 US detainee torture program, according to a watchdog analysis released on Thursday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 23:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To fight infections, hospital workers can hit the hand sanitizer a hundred times or more a day. Now, the government wants more study of whether that is safe and how well it actually fights the spread of germs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 22:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A nearly $612 billion defense policy bill headed to the House floor is at odds with the White House, a Shiite cleric in Iraq, anyone who wants to bar lethal aid to Ukrainian forces fighting Russian-backed rebels - and a bird known for its strutting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 22:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With no information about where the tip had come from or why officials had decided to make it public, it was hard to stave off the suspicion that Baltimore Police Commissioner Anthony Batts was trying to distract from the real issues at hand (the death of a black man in police custody) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 00:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korean leader Kim Jong Un ordered the execution of 15 senior officials this year as punishment for challenging his authority, South Korea's spy agency told a closed-door parliament meeting on Wednesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 00:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
