<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6188</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A U.S.-led coalition dropped new leaflets over the de facto capital of the Islamic State group in Syria, promising those below that "freedom will come" to the region. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 11:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU foreign ministers to discuss Tunisia terror attack: Prime minister Habib Essid in Brussels to discuss security after incident saw 38 die. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 11:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 10:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if he made TMZ, he must be!

Actually, I just don't get why someone would throw away their reputation for a pair of sunglasses. I think we all know that there are cameras everywhere now, don't we? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Indian Navy hopes to develop high-energy lasers and high-power microwave weapons in the near future that can destroy targets with minimum collateral damage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 10:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 10:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is good news for those of us living nearby. Don't know if it will help to lower prices in the area, but the more options, the better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Foodland announces return to Ala Moana Center in 2016: When the reconstructed Ewa wing of Ala Moana Center opens in the fall, it will include the return in 2016 of a longtime, local retailer as well. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 10:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vanderpump Rules' Jax Taylor surveillance video: Watch him steal sunglasses from Sunglasses Hut in Honolulu. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 10:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Foodland announces return to Ala Moana Center in 2016: When the reconstructed Ewa wing of Ala Moana Center opens in the fall, it will include the return in 2016 of a longtime, local retailer as well. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 10:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game changer in fight against rhino horn poachers: Rhinos wearing satellite tracking collars with spy cameras implanted into their horns could help turn the tables on poachers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 10:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little-known Ontario company fills worlds museums with beloved dinosaur skeletons. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 10:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While their repair backlog continued to grow, along with outstanding rent arrears, TCHC brass spent 18 months and $240,000 on consultant studies to determine whether their pay and perqs were high enough. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 10:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 07:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did the fly, fly? 

Because the spider, spied her... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 06:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who knew that you could bee so sweet!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Professional surfer and three-time world champion Mick Fanning was attacked by a shark during the J-Bay Open Sunday off South Africa, prompting organizers to cancel the competition. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 06:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for ahmet145 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for Zicara </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for alansmith005 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for gsticher61 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for DRD1176 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for mariegnunez1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for Dinosaur2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ah , think of the smell.

I'm sure the animals will get used to us... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edmonton researchers develop pill that allows celiac sufferers to eat gluten. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 04:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Timbuktu's historic tombs restored in show of confidence for war-ravaged Mali: Local and international project in city of 33 saints reconstructs 14 Sufi mausoleums smashed up by al-Qaida backed extremists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Yorks Kennedy airport builds worlds first animal terminal  complete with flat-screen TVs: The $48m terminal, to be named The ARK, will handle more than 70,000 animals every year and have showers and access to massage therapy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A former African leader will be held to account before an African court for the first time today when Hissene Habre, the fallen dictator of Chad, stands trial for allegedly presiding over the deaths of 40,000 people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Civil service loophole? Records show county bending contract employee rules: Over the past two years, Mayor Billy Kenoi has spent more than $1.5 million on contracted employees, using an exemption to sidestep state civil service laws that require employees be hired based on merit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A pedestrian suffered life-threatening injuries Saturday afternoon after she was struck in a Kahului parking by a vehicle operated by an 11-year-old boy, police said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edmonton researchers develop pill that allows celiac sufferers to eat gluten. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A social media strategy that has replaced the official names of some federal departments on their Facebook pages with slogans has an Ottawa public affairs digital strategist puzzled. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, looks about right:~) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chemical pollution from M6 lorry fire thought to be behind mass fish deaths: Environment Agency found about 150 dead fish in the river Penk and more in the river Sow, near Stafford  identifying the tarmac-melting fire as the likely cause. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 02:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 02:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And in observance of Ocean Day, because life's a beach, I'll meet you all over at the sandbar!

*big wave* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Monday here in Tokyo, but we don't care because it's a national holiday: Marine Day ( Umi no Hi), also known as "Ocean Day" or "Sea Day! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 02:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 01:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I've never been to Moanalua Gardens

I'll never forget when I first came to Japan and people kept asking me where the [Hitachi tree](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Moanalua_Gardens) was, and I was like, *Whaaaaat?!"

Then, I was watching TV on Saturday night (Mr. Excitement, right?) and Hitachi sponsors a show and I saw [this.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q8SQNMclNGY)

Went back to Oahu and my memories of Moanalua grew fonder 'cause one of my kids was born at Kaiser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Japanese salmon and trout fishing boat from Hokkaido was seized by Russian authorities Friday for breaching the fishing quota, the Hokkaido government said Saturday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 16:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Fisheries Agency plans to conduct research on coral resources in waters around Okinawa Island starting in August following the poaching of jewelry coral in waters near Japan by Chinese fishing boats. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 15:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Fisheries Agency plans to conduct research on coral resources in waters around Okinawa Island starting in August following the poaching of jewelry coral in waters near Japan by Chinese fishing boats. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 15:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Japanese salmon and trout fishing boat from Hokkaido was seized by Russian authorities Friday for breaching the fishing quota, the Hokkaido government said Saturday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 15:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Womans necklace containing fathers ashes returned following robbery. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 15:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The advent of competition and new technologies is forcing politicians across Canada to re-evaluate their cities taxi industries and to wonder just how many cabs they want on the roads. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 15:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the U.K., community renewable energy pushes for more power: Buoyed by Pope Francis new encyclical, community groups have been trying to tackle climate change on their own. But theyre not having an easy time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 15:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Big Data can help save the environment: Journalists, scientists   techies must work to translate data into the knowledge needed to address climate change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 15:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As Rotary celebrates 100 years in Hawaii, the clubs international president stops in Hawaii to offer congratulations and to check on some of local Rotarians service projects. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 15:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The estimated cost of Michigans new prison food services contract with Trinity Services Group is $13.7 million more over three years than the problem-plagued Aramark Correctional Services contract it replaces. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 15:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This weekend, Moanalua Gardens is once again the gathering place for hula. The annual event features traditional and contemporary dance, and this year the Prince Lot Hula Festival also includes a few new things. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 15:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 15:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  to do something you can do for free in your living room while getting head and watching television?

...while eating pizza...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 15:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As you already know Surfer, I've been a fan and supporter of yours here for a long time now.

I really like your pics and can't really come up with anything you haven't done, 'cause you already cover so many bases...

...

....

,,,,

...unless.....in about three weeks....do you think you can snap the ever elusive hatter running rampant on the sands of Waikiki?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> City Hall officials asked an East Pilsen theater not to allow a benefit concert by Chief Keef who was supposed to appear by hologram to help memorialize a toddler killed in the aftermath of a shooting, according to a spokeswoman for Mayor Rahm Emanuel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 14:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 69-year-old El Cerrito man was accused of practicing medicine without a license after he changed a Southern California cancer patients prescriptions, giving her an array of powders and expired drugs and a baggie of dirt, authorities said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 14:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for infozone24 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 14:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for emceesingapore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 14:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for ernestoolivares01 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 14:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for wefornews </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 14:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A jury has begun deliberations in the case of a lottery security officer who allegedly fixed the Hot Lotto game in 2010 to get himself a winning ticket for a $14 million jackpot and then tried to cash it anonymously. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The German interior minister has said Germany can cope with the growing stream of refugees entering the country. His remarks came as suspected arsonists set fire to a future home for asylum seekers near Karlsruhe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taiwan's ruling Nationalists on Sunday nominated pro-China Hung Hsiu-chu as its candidate for presidential elections in January 2016, ending months of division in the party following heavy losses at local elections. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saskatchewan stripping laws impact Swift Current theatre festival: organizer is defending shutting down a burlesque dancers onstage rant about the provinces stripping laws. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nanowires give 'solar fuel cell' efficiency a tenfold boost: Researchers make important step towards a solar cell that generates hydrogen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microplastics at 'alarming levels' in Canadian lakes and rivers: Microbeads just tip of plastic iceberg floating in Canadian waters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 12:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microplastics at 'alarming levels' in Canadian lakes and rivers: Microbeads just tip of plastic iceberg floating in Canadian waters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 12:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 06:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet pic.

I spent a lot of time in the Kailua / Lanikai area and how I do miss those sunrises...and sunsets too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 06:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to disappoint, but I travel light. The zebra head's staying in Japan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seattle-area billboards aim to counter negative views of Islam: A national campaign aimed at countering negative perceptions of Islam has put up four billboards in Seattle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 06:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Travelers might find it easier to pass through agricultural inspection stations on the Big Island after Senator Brian Schatz fought to increase funding by $1 million in the Agriculture Appropriations Bill. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 05:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia's Energy Ministry has signed a contract worth up to 47.3 billion rubles ($830 million) for the construction of energy infrastructure to Crimea as Russia strives to end the peninsula's dependence on Ukrainian supplies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 05:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fracking to be allowed in protected wildlife areas after Government u-turn: Ministers say it would be "impractical" to introduce a complete ban on fracking in Sites of Special Scientific Interest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 05:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate change mitigation could be the greatest global health opportunity of the 21st century. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 05:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British Columbia's police watchdog is investigating its second police shooting in three days after officers killed a distressed man in Surrey early Saturday, sparking alarm from civil liberties advocates. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 05:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Origin of Italo-Canadian term mangia-cake is in dispute. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 05:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan is conducting a reshuffle of goods in its consumer price index basket that will ditch items on the kids menu in exchange for hearing aids to reflect changes in consumer spending caused by its rapidly aging population. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 02:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 01:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here I thought you were going to say $69! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 01:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "May I have a serving of your finest multiple orgasms and by the way, what's that come to?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for liveuniver311 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 01:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for ISNTD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 01:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At the height of the summer vacation season, the touristic coasts of the southeastern Mexican state of Quintana Roo have been swamped by atypical amounts of gulfweed algae whose removal has become an emergency. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 00:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than 35,000 Cubans for whom deportation orders have been issued could be repatriated to the Caribbean island as a result of the renewal of relations between the two countries, U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement, or ICE. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 00:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When the Hawaii Island Humane Society suspended adoptions of dogs to Big Island rescue organizations this week, individuals went underground to adopt animals themselves and turn them over to the organization that transports the dogs to shelters on the mainland. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 00:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A court hearing ended early after a certified Marshalese translator could not be found for a 37-year-old man accused of shooting two people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 00:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran's Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei said Saturday a landmark nuclear deal won't change his country's policy toward the "arrogant" U.S., making his first public speech since the Islamic Republic's historic pact with world powers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 00:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One congressmans fight to keep fracking waste out of drinking water. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 00:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Green globs of little critters in the ocean are responsible for half of the cloud droplets that cover the Southern Ocean during the summer, a new study finds. This link between the critters and clouds provides needed insight for predicting the effects of climate change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 00:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Britains largest police force has launched an investigation into allegations that its officers used a secret Facebook group to air racist views about ethnic minorities. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 00:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudi Arabia has arrested 431 people with suspected links to the Islamic State group and in the process thwarted a wave of suicide bombings that were to target mosques and security forces, the interior ministry announced on Saturday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 00:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prime Minister Shinzo Abes support rate fell nearly 10 points to 37.7% in a Kyodo news agency poll released on Saturday, the first since his ruling bloc pushed forward legislation marking a dramatic shift in the nations post-war defense policy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 23:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Child in Quebec shaken-baby case dies, father may face more charges. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 23:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than four years after an earthquake and tsunami triggered a meltdown of three nuclear reactors in Japan, lessons learned are still being put into place at nuclear power plants in Canada. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 23:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scottish councils could lose out on 44 million of scarce income under UK government plans to scrap subsidies for wind farms. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 16:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's how you can make meat way more sustainable: You can be a carnivore and an environmentalist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 16:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Canadian military's new top commander has delivered a clear, tough message, saying bullies and abusers have no place within the ranks and, where they exist, they'll be weeded out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 16:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Canadian military's new top commander has delivered a clear, tough message, saying bullies and abusers have no place within the ranks and, where they exist, they'll be weeded out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 16:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calgary pilots Segways to help change outdated pathway bylaws. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 16:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nineteen NYPD officers face departmental charges after city investigators uncovered dozens of instances where crimes were misreported at a Bronx precinct. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 16:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for JerimireSerd </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 16:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for selzbusinesshouse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 16:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for Idontknowwhour1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 16:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for allahbarkatlocket </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 16:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for moviesonline94 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 16:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Master navigator Nainoa Thompson was honored for Excellence in Exploration at the 2015 Peter Benchley Ocean Awards ceremony this week in Washington D.C. Thompson, mentored for decades by master navigator Mau Piailug, became the first Native Hawaiian in 700 years to practice long-distance wayfinding. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 16:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A South Korean government spy was found dead Saturday in an apparent suicide alongside a note that seemed to comment on the recent revelation that the spy agency had acquired hacking programs capable of intercepting communications on cellphones and computers, police said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 15:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A proposed class-action lawsuit filed in an Ontario court Friday alleges the federal government fails to provide adequate care to mentally ill prisoners while relying far too heavily on solitary confinement as a way to deal with them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 15:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hamas chief Khaled Meshaal has met Saudi King Salman during a pilgrimage to the kingdom, state news agency SPA said Saturday. He headed a delegation from the Palestinian Islamist movement in a two-day Umra pilgrimage to the Muslim holy city of Mecca. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 15:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Islamic State (IS) group used poison gas projectiles in attacks against Kurdish-controlled areas of Syria and Iraq in late June, Kurdish militia backed by UK groups monitoring the Syrian conflict have said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 15:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Nations see Nexen oil spill as just the beginning: Just as news of as the massive Nexen oil spill in Alberta broke, the provinces premiers were concluding a deal on Canadas national energy strategy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 14:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Nations see Nexen oil spill as just the beginning: Just as news of as the massive Nexen oil spill in Alberta broke, the provinces premiers were concluding a deal on Canadas national energy strategy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 14:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada's provinces reached a long-sought deal on Friday over an energy plan for the country, agreeing broadly to curb greenhouse gas emissions while also promoting the use of pipelines. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 14:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada's provinces reached a long-sought deal on Friday over an energy plan for the country, agreeing broadly to curb greenhouse gas emissions while also promoting the use of pipelines. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 14:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 12:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet pic! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 11:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I've faced exactly the same annoying problem with loudspeakers in India with loudspeakers and it's usually different religious communities or political parades.

And we have to put up with the noise during the political seasons here in Tokyo too. 

Not only in front of the train stations, but roaming trucks as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 10:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stuck in Tokyo and because there's no pot, I drink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for arabtechnoo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 06:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for worldinsuranceinfo4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 06:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for summermelody </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 06:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for moldinspection1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 06:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for getfixr </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 06:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
