<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3651</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shark attack incidents have fallen by over 91% since 1950, due to public information campaignsnot culling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the paper is live, it'll be here: http://www.wiley.com/WileyCDA/PressRelease/pressReleaseId-119242,descCd-release_additional_material.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cancer survivors face potentially discriminatory challenges when trying to adopt children, new study shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a link to the paper...but it's entirely behind a paywall (even the abstract...)

http://pediatrics.aappublications.org/content/early/recent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nixon's healthcare plan shared some common ground (and much rhetoric) with Obama's Affordable Care Act according to a new study published in the journal Pediatrics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 14:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't know how to read. Let me help:
The scientists ran an in-depth statistical analysis to find out whether pesticides, human land use or other factors may have contributed to declining bumblebee populations over the past century. And the answer is clearly nowe checked this carefully, Pindar says. They are impacted by climate change and these effects are already very large and widespread.

That's a quote in this article, from the lead author on the new study, published in the most prestigious scientific journal in the world. They confirmed through statistical analyses that climate change and NOT pesticides or land use were to blame.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 21:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/mesopotamiae: not the bee keeper we deserve, but the beekeeper we need right now.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 21:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah...not according to the *real* scientists (nice try, though) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 21:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monsanto isn't a vague boogie monster? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 21:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed. The study was literally published in the top scientific journal in the world (give or take "Nature" journals). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bumblebee drones don't have feelings anyway. Also, drones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giant pandas are only able to survive on bamboo shoots because they move slowly and conserve energy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New jumping soft robot combines the advantages of hard robotics with the more malleable properties of soft robotics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bumblebees are clearly liberals, looking for excuses to tax the rich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists confirm that worldwide bumblebee populations are dying out due to climate change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers identify new spectrum disorder: ALPIM Syndrome. The disorder helps explain some of the physical symptoms behind certain kinds of panic attacks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 19:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lake Erie is in trouble. NOAA report warns that the impending algae bloom could be so severe that it'll pose risks to swimmers and boaters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 18:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People are wiling to take the stairsbut only when the escalator is at least 100% farther away, new study shows. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
