<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6084</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 22:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's why they're called Secret Service agents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 21:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Women copied her hair and clothing styles (especially when she lowered the neckline on her inaugural gown by 2.5 inches)

Scandalous! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the myth that the Great Wall of China is visible from space originated before anyone had ever been into space, and dates back even as far back as the 18th century. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 05:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 21:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bird red blood cells do, and these guys found what look like nuclei, so they found something that once contained dinosaur DNA. They were just a few million years too late. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A google search for "bird erythrocytes" shows that they do have a nucleus, and that it's only in mammals that they are missing. TIL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new test that requires less than a single drop of blood can tell a person every virus they have had over their lifetime. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 06:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that hops are not only used for their flavor in beer: they have an antibacterial effect, which promotes the activity of yeast over less desirable microbes during fermentation, which would otherwise ruin the brewing process. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 10:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Steven Spielberg wanted to direct an episode of Twin Peaks, but David Lynch put the kibosh on it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 08:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 07:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the paper.](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0124256)

It's better than the write-up: I didn't know the jellyfish "twitch" their tentacles alluringly as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Australian species of jellyfish actively hunts its prey. The Irukandji jellyfish uses structures in its tentacles to attract small fish, which it then stings and consumes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 07:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL of "The Green Man", a man severely disfigured as a child who would take long walks only at night in western Pennsylvania. Urban legends at the time said he glowed green, whereas in fact he was real person who was liked by his family and neighbors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 17:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All these wacky bribes uncovered so far have been in relation to the World Cups in South Africa and Germany. Imagine what went on for QATAR to be awarded the World Cup! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ability to learn a foreign language during adulthood is strongly associated with a variation in a particular gene: the FOXP2 gene, which has been previously been implicated in disordered speech and language. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 17:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [MRW seeing this.](http://i.imgur.com/0hTvUkx.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do we feel about the Fallout 4 announcement? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 10:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure you've all seen it. Something like that might soon come for us Mass Effect fans. Discuss.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 08:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is the Materials and Methods section of their paper.](http://stm.sciencemag.org/content/7/290/290ra89.full#title9) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The antidepressant Zoloft and heart drug Vascor are shown to be effective treatments for Ebola in mice, after testing thousands of existing medicinal compounds, showing the effectiveness of large-scale testing of drugs for unrelated conditions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 03:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most comprehensive map yet of the human epigenome has been published. Among the findings: methylation patterns differ so much among organs that it can be matched with organ type. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 19:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 15:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a fantastic piece of work! Well done indeed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The evolutionary advantage of homosexuality in fruit flies has been discovered: females with the genetic changes associated with the trait display higher reproductive rates. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 14:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rick Santorum: Climate scientists are like flat-Earth believers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 16:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Isis in Palmyra: Civilians rounded up and forced to watch execution of 20 men at amphitheatre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 05:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowstorm masks in Montreal, 1939. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 13:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that there is a plant that grows and even flowers completely underground, in Western Australia. The "underground orchid" was only discovered because of the smell it was giving from the ground alerted a farmer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 10:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 09:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is an EXTREMELY HARD platinum. Hawking would be proud! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 09:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russell Crowe, you're drunk. That's an Aussie Burger and we all know it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The gut bacteria of pandas are not very well suited to bamboo, their main food source. In fact, they seem to be more suited to a meat based diet. The imbalance may in fact be responsible for these endangered animals' apparent reluctance to have sex. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 05:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that George Lucas offered David Lynch the opportunity to direct The Return of the Jedi. Lynch refused, saying the movie should reflect Lucas' vision of the script. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 08:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have figured out how to brew morphine using the same kit used to make beer at home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 07:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 22:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If nothing else that is one well-written and entertaining wiki page. Good job OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 00:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's life trying to, uh, find a way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 00:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprisingly, there are several other bands from Saudi Arabia on that site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple of random examples:

[Danish](http://da.wikipedia.org/wiki/Smoking)

[Portuguese](http://pt.wikipedia.org/wiki/Smoking) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that a tuxedo jacket is called a "smoking" in French, Italian, Portuguese, German, Polish, Russian and other European languages, because of its similarity to Victorian smoking jackets. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 18:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't, the photos we have of the landing sites were [taken from a satellite currently in orbit around the moon.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Third-party_evidence_for_Apollo_Moon_landings#Photographs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 17:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The way the police knee him in the back is something they should not do. 

No shit, and yet it seems to be the go-to move whenever we see videos of rough arrests.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 17:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I for one did *not* see that coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 22:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess this is ironic, in the Alanis Morissette sense of the word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 21:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has an appeal left and will probably be executed on his own later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 20:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the record, the correct breakdown is:

8 executed (1 Indonesian, 2 Australians, 3 Nigerians, 1 Brazilian, 1 Ghanaian)

(source: OP's link - it may well have been updated since it was first posted)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dandelions produce rubber. Scientists have identified the key components involved in the production of rubber in the plants, bringing closer the biotechnological synthesis of rubber. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 19:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 23:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Link to the study in Nature Neuroscience.](http://www.nature.com/neuro/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nn.4011.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The neurons responsible for the sensation of hunger have been identified. Mice with this brain circuit activated reduce feeding, "resulting in the same outcome as dieting but without the chronic feeling of hunger" according to a co-author. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 22:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the largest opinion gap between the US public and scientists is in whether genetically modified foods are safe to eat, with 88% of scientists in agreement compared to 37% of the public. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 21:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 19:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This kid is about 77 now. Probably still cuts a rug, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A retrovirus in the human genome is expressed in 3 day old embryos, which are bundles of 8 cells, and appears to protect embryos against foreign viruses at this stage of life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 17:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists can now tell where a dust sample comes from in the continental U.S. based on the DNA of the fungi in it. The research has applications in forensic science. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that a crease in the earlobe may be indicative of heart disease and/or diabetes. This is called "Frank's sign" and notable individuals with it include Steven Spielberg. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 17:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 20:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a different cop, folks. The one you're thinking of is unarmed and locked in Charleston County Jail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that married women drink more than their unmarried counterparts, whereas the opposite is true for men, according to a 2012 study. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 20:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that giant tortoises from the Galapagos can survive without food or water for up to a year. In the past, buccaneers, whalers and fur sealers would store them live in their ships' holds as a fresh meat source that doesn't require feeding. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 11:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 04:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the world returned to a more basic state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 04:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have [dealt successfully with another revolting ideology](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Laws_against_Holocaust_denial). It *should* be easy to enact similar laws against radical islamist hate speech, but don't hold your breath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 04:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mark Stein was very [prescient](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/America_Alone). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that aluminum was once so rare that Napoleon III would serve his state dinners on aluminum plates. The rank-and-file guests had had to settle for dinner served on gold or silver plates. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 11:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that sometimes a group of ants will get separated from their main foraging party and begin to follow each other in a continuously rotating circle. Eventually they all die of exhaustion. This phenomenon is called an "ant mill". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 23:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 10:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the internet and a robot are a better alternative to trying getting a date, your country's gonna have a problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police officer explains why he hit homeless man with his car </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 23:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 18:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is the paper being discussed](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0003347214004643), in case that link is problematic, as it was for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chimpanzees in the wild 'talk' to each other about their favorite fruits and the trees where they can be found. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 17:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 19:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, "cuddling". [Just ask these penguins.](http://www.nbcnews.com/id/24585481/ns/technology_and_science-science/t/seal-caught-tape-molesting-penguin/#.VLv6Ro_PF2M) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 06:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heartbreaking. We have police dash cams, why not body cams? This is a great example of why they're needed, we get to see the humanity of the vast majority of police and the work they do, and make sure that those who abuse their power are held accountable. It's a win-win for everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 19:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure the racist cartoon analogy is appropriate. A religion is not a race. It is a set of ideas, and satirising ideas is fair game, no matter how "offensive" that may be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 18:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems to be an english language thing in general. Unless I'm mistaken none of the papers in the UK, Australia etc. are reproducing the cartoons. In Canada, ALL of the french media in Quebec are showing the cartoons, but the english media in the rest of Canada (and in Montreal) are not. What that all means I'm not sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 07:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure either but I think M. Night Shyamalan has optioned it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 17:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This comes to mind.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VRIUbFLjtX0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 17:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy promoted his snuff film before it was even made. Surprised it took them 8 days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Dominant Life Form in the Cosmos Is Probably Superintelligent Robots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 01:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 00:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely fascinating, all of this, but this part doesn't seem to have any backup based on the links provided, and seems anecdotal (thus the highlighting), can someone help?

December 3rd

The second data leak. This one garnered less press but contained was considerably more dangerous... **I've heard** that much of this information was available because an IT director was comprised apparently he had no background in IT and was actually a marketing exec who reached the position (and thus higher salary) through corporate politics. You can see for example is was good at naming files.

(this is not to detract from the link at all, I'm just curious)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two scientists have set the world record for time spent living underwater: 10 weeks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 14:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Morning work start times should be delayed to ensure adults get an adequate amount of sleep, according to a new study. For every hour that work started later in the morning, sleep time increased by approximately 20 minutes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 21:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 15:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Top ten jobs that attract psychopaths:](http://www.forbes.com/sites/kellyclay/2013/01/05/the-top-10-jobs-that-attract-psychopaths/)

1. CEO
2. Lawyer
3. Media (Television/Radio)
4. Salesperson
5. Surgeon
6. Journalist
7. **Police officer**
8. Clergy person
9. Chef
10. Civil servant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ancient origins of drinking alcohol: A paleogenomic study reveals it begain around 10 million years ago when primates began eating rotten and fermented fruit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 15:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 18:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's the "Gangstas in Space" DLC (?). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 18:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a pretty interesting infographic about this [in this article by none other than Bill Gates.](http://www.gatesnotes.com/Health/Most-Lethal-Animal-Mosquito-Week?WT.mc_id=MosquitoWeek2014_SharkWeek_tw WT.tsrc=Twitter) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 16:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, [here](http://www.plosone.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0004741). This doesn't detract from OP's link, however. For a start it uses a completely different technique (EEG vs. fMRI).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada's Sudbury Basin, the world's second largest impact crater, was formed when a comet struck 1.8 billion years ago, according to an analysis of the geochemistry of the crater. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 18:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
