<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1576</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 23:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe that Louis Armstrong is not on these lists!  Come on folks, he invented Jazz singing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 23:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big upvotes for Blossom Dearie and Cecile McLorin Salvant.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 23:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree Anita and Ella were the great Verve rivals, and as a pure Jazz singer Anita might have had an edge.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 21:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that makes it right then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 21:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the mod of the /r/badlawyer subreddit I can attest to this.  Really it's fraud, perjury, theft, and violence that will get you tossed.  Amazingly though, there is a former major crime prosecutor in Cleveland who while coked up shot his girlfriend at close range; went to prison for 7 years; and, who was reinstated.  Amazingly the same court disbarred a longtime civil attorney who didn't file and didn't pay income taxes (no fraud involved.)   Go figure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 21:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great suggestion by /u/Ihearcolor -- I'd also suggest that you stay close to us.  Do the daily check-in and share here with us.  We're not like the rest of Reddit.  This is a full on support subreddit and snark-free zone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 20:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're doing it right double-D! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats, Republicans Open Huge Rift on Their Opinions of the Supreme Court | There's been a 17 percentage point approval drop among Republicans and a 29 percentage point increase among Democrats since September, Gallup says. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He opened Pandora's (Sarah's) box. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawyer is entitled to only $100 for ex-client's post on ripoffreport.com, appeals court says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama echoes Reagan on Iran </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, he always writes like that--but, there's some information there that's not being covered anywhere else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sarah Vaughn

Rosemary Clooney

Ella

Louis Armstrong

Johnny Hartmann

Nat King Cole

Frank Sinatra

Nina Simone

Julie Christy

Tony Bennett (with Basie)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the irony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rick Santorum attacks Scott Walker as not anti-gay enough, while Walker backtracks on bigoted Boy Scout remark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You pull this sort of shit with the feds you get an obstruction of justice charge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out-of-state charter school scam artist fat cat booze heir joins Responsible Ohio at the trough </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawyer Donald Franz 'mocks size of client Mike Rutkowski's penis' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Technically, Ted Cruz And Greg Abbott Should Be Disbarred </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lanny Davis: Why is the media picking sides on polling? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio man accused of bashing neighbors' windows, throwing meat-wrapped brick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker 2012 Campaign Inquiry Ended by Wisconsin Court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Iran deal is a disaster for Benjamin Netanyahu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McCain: Trump 'fired up the crazies' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL--in Cleveland we have a couple of days off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a great Heineken t-shirt that said, Grab a Heinie.  I loved it.  It became a paint t-shirt when I stopped drinking.  Then a rag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's what I did when I was learning (and I'm far from a master)--off the bike in off season focus on abs and squats.  Strengthen your core muscles, but get super strong at the hover squat position by sitting on a stool and rising and holding at 4 inches, 6 inches, and then controlled seating (not collapsing back onto the stool).  Then as you ride, learn to jump up from the saddle and use your body weight to push the pedal down, alternate with sitting and riding at a higher rev.  Then back up on the pedals.  This should become instinctive.  Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hooray!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, bad role model. I'd find a new sponsor.  BTW, I have a co-sponsor that I totally admire but this is his Achilles.  Since he's my co-sponsor this issue bothers me not at all.  It's his character defect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is great.  We get lots of username changes for this stated reason.  It's sort of like losing the beer t-shirt after being in recovery for some time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio Politics Now: Republicans want investigation, prosecution of Planned Parenthood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know the way, /u/gonegirl1022--focus on not drinking TODAY, and plan to make the same decision tomorrow. Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you ride a bike, don't think about your destination instead think about how beautiful the ride is, how great the pedal stroke feel is, how you want to be right where you are right now--then lean in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gay marriage ruling leaves U.S. firms unclear on spousal benefits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/bigndfan175 is Bonus Buddha Baby! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Boy who wouldn't hoe corn.](https://youtu.be/1M9-2t5csY4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Optics.  He's failing at optics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is so true that anniversaries, mile marker celebrations are super important for the reasons you stated, Slip.  I like to point out to newcomers with 7 days, 14 days, 30, 60, 90 days that their achievement of those milestones lend credibility to what they say about the journey that someone with years (and in your case, decades) can not have.  But, as always you paint a poignant picture, my friend.  Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An attorney convicted of a false statement to conceal his travel to Cuba was disbarred by the New York </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prosecutors Drop Ridiculous 'Fleeing Police' Charge For Cautious Driver. But Not Before Exposing A Bigger Issue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Put-in-Bay cop fired again | Volusia County sheriff gives deputy Steve Korossy the boot same day former island police sergeant indicted; watch his 'Strange island arrests' video here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, ELECT ME and I'll take you to war in the Middle East. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he can spread around that Adelson money that he and Menedez are picking up?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations on 600 days!  It gets real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/megame23 -- at this [link is a post called the Baby Steps.](https://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/)  It lays out how I stopped drinking and how I got sober.  When you're up to it, maybe there are some ideas there that will make sense to you.  Good luck, I hope you join us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/Jadiki to r/stopdrinking.  I thought I'd share the [link to the Baby Steps post](https://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) with you.  It's what I did to stop drinking and to get sober.  I try to share it as part of the "handshake at the door" to the SD sober journey.  Good luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, yes, the courage of media whoredom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Fran Supervisor Who Told Off Fox Reporter Speaks Out: Theyre a Propaganda Machine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christie says he will lobby Booker to oppose Iran deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Cruz's presidential campaign disclosed Wednesday that it spent about $5.5 million in three months, burning through more than half the money it raised in the same period of time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And his Dad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what Obama asserted was the only alternative offered by critics of the Iran-Nuke Deal.   How cool would that be?  War with Iran, sheesh, these people are idiots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Cruz Foresees Military Action Against Iran </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a great essay on political trolling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I tell it like it is." Chris Christie made this his campaign slogan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 10:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 10:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fear

Amends 

Dry People, Dry Places

Fitness

Work

Dating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 10:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not drinking TODAY no matter what; honestly, keeping SOBER in Cleveland Thursday.  Beautiful weather today, and I'm happily bike commuting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 03:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not let's see, what might be Sen. Menedez's position on the Iran Nuke deal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sheldon Adelson, Bill Richardson help Sen. Robert Menendez fight corruption charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 03:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 02:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of the quote from Ralph Waldo Emerson that was in my first comment at the original Honesty Week post:

"Speak what you think today in hard words and tomorrow speak what tomorrow thinks in hard words again, though it contradict every thing you said today.

From this I take: judge the truth to yourself and speak it to yourself and if necessary to others; but be open to the idea that what you take as fact may not be fact and so you have an obligation to correct not only your mistaken belief, but speak the truth to others even at the cost of pride and ego. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 02:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $1.8 from Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's official haul: $1.9 million </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 02:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cruel Truth About Rock And Roll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 00:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incredibly smart post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/0_000--let us know what we can do to help you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Straus warchest hovering around $8 million </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former San Antonio district judge Angus McGinty sentenced to 2 years in prison in bribery scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Claims His Wealth Exceeds 'TEN BILLION DOLLARS' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go into lakewood park and walk due north to the lake.  Unfortunately, there is a lot of construction there now, so I don't know how close you can get to it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sorry that this was your experience.  When I got sober in 1986 (for the first 15 years) the only "loss" I thought I had sustained was my relationship with my first wife who had been my childhood sweetheart.  I did lose that relationship but like JBH I was able SOBER to sit down with her one time and express my sincere regret.  Unlike JBH it was way too early in my recovery and I'm afraid it sounded like nothing but words, meaningless words.  And the damage I had done by then was not repairable with words.  As JBH points out, honest words gain credibility with honest actions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democratic House Members Accuse Benghazi Panel of Abandoning Duty | The committee assigned to investigate terror attacks is instead generating anti-Hillary Clinton headlines, the lawmakers say. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not going to drink TODAY in solidarity with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, awesome!  I see where Slip has already added you to DINOs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bridgegate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL, I'm amused and all you had to do was describe the idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for being having the courage to be honest.

I would encourage you to go back through your post and comment history and try and get as honest a grip as you can on why you decided to stop drinking and stay stopped.  Why was it important in the first place?  And now, what do you think you're missing? 

You know if you ever read [my Saturday Share](https://www.reddit.com/r/stopdrinking/comments/25u6cc/saturday_share_im_train_subject1576_and_i_am_an_alcoholic/) how relapse worked out for me, so I'm not going to lecture you.  I will say that if I knew then what I know now--I would have begged my friends to lock me away until the impulse passed.  I barely averted death, for what?  To pour alcohol down my face!  What a waste.

My friend, I understand the impulse.  If you spend anytime sober you probably can't avoid the thought that you're missing something.  New craft beers, fine wines, parties, events, sophistication--in my experience it was all tears and ashes and tragedy.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Akron man accused of stealing $20 worth of feminine hygiene products at knifepoint </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man accused in triple-fatal crash on Rt. 80 in New Jersey had 19 past traffic violations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Latest: GOP's Christie says Obama lied about Iran deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Vilsack On Food Stamp Lawsuit: 'Gov. Walker Hasn't Read The Law' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 19:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [My wife loves Firefighters, and she's a lawyer not a firefighter.](https://www.ffcommunity.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge Joseph D. Russo disputes prosecutor's complaints about old cases </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 19:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hang on to the hope, it lights the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This "terrible," "awful" deal is all about engagement with historic enemies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Double-D this is a delight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not good with internet hugs; but I will offer you some hope.  

My marriage was past due for divorce when I returned to sobriety in 2009.  We both had had destructive affairs. My HS sophomore son was trying to figure out if he was gay; my HS senior daughter was pregnant.  I was losing my professional license AND going to federal prison.  

Flash forward nearly 6 years, we are still married and very close and affectionate.  Life is complicated and relationships are complex.  My son is an award winning professional actor, comedian, and college student; my daughter is a college student; and, my grandson who lives with us, is the light of my life. 

What changed?  

Me.  I changed.  I got sober and stayed sober.  I dealt with my legal consequences honestly.  I went to counseling and stuck with it.  When my daughter needed recovery I was at every family night.  I did not change my wife or kids, I changed ME.  And as I changed everything around me changed.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News wore Jon Stewart down: How 16 years of debunking right-wing lies exhausted the last honest man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am half-way through this bio-history by Tim Weiner and it is bringing it all back into sharp focus and with almost all of the mysteries surrounding these years--solved.  Riveting is not too strong a word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The darkness that consumed Nixon: Why Tricky Dick could never do him justice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overdue process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What is wrong with citizens expressing their concerns about the military potentially infringing on their rights?

None whatsoever.  

But if this is the first you've heard about it, then you have been living overseas or off the grid.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is really strange.  When the folks (including CJ Maureen O'Connor) claim judges need a pay raise because they are overworked and underpaid, Judges like Russo graphically illustrate why this is bullshit.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Missed it; thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the splintered GOP field helps Donald Trump get into first place, in 8 charts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Re-Re-Re-Reintroducing Hillary Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is right.  Here's what I KNOW happened: he enters a guilty plea to a federal felony and as part of the pre-sentencing process there is a standard psychological assessment that turns up paranoid and delusional disorders that are concerning to US Probation and the Bureau of Prisons.  As his behavior under their supervision becomes more bizarre--instead of sending him to prison the US District Court seeks a mental health assessment and recommendation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Department disputes right to racist emails of US District Judge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Department disputes right to Cebull emails </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No sign of man who jumped off break wall in Lakewood Park into Lake Erie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McCain: Obama, Kerry 'Made a Worse Deal Than Even We Had Feared' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump: I don't know why I'm meeting Ted Cruz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge Orders Anti-Obama Filmmaker D'Souza Receive Psychological Counseling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of the major steps forward in my life when I got sober.  I decided that I would "give in" to the world as it is; not as I would have it be.  When I did this everything got better.  As a metaphor, it's like a lot of athletic endeavors: when you ski, road cycling, play tennis--if you let go and lean in, counter-intuitively you gain control.  I had to stop "forcing" myself on the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawyer admits to stealing cameras in landlord-tenant dispute </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama offers some praise of Putin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2nd St. Bernard employee witness against Dave Peralta fired </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clarence Thomas's Unusual Evolution | The silent justice has always marched to his own drum, and in the past year that drumbeat has become more distinct and strange. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Operation Jade Helm 15 Gets Underway in Texas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Haste, Hustle and Scott Walker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker Wants Boy Scouts to Stick to Policy of Banning Homosexual Troop Leaders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Republicans Scrap Breast-Cancer Vote Amid Abortion Dispute </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 12:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 12:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not drinking TODAY no matter what happens good or bad; another SOBER hump day in Cleveland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pastor's daughter, 16, falls more than 100ft to her death from giant swing thrill ride at Christian summer camp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pastor's daughter, 16, falls more than 100ft to her death from giant swing thrill ride at Christian summer camp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, /u/swiggitty -- I'm glad you came out of lurk and posted.  Welcome to the sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What worked for me was getting a support network in place BEFORE I set out to confess my sins, or make amends.  The wisdom of others was essential to me in avoiding unnecessary pain on those I hurt.  I'm not saying that I was taken off the hook in any respect--but, I found effective ways of getting honest and making appropriate amends.  Hard on myself, easy on others was a good rule of thumb for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Horizons (Tribute) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kentucky Judge suspended a week for jailing a woman who cursed her </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rusk County (Texas) Clerk Resigns Over Gay Marriage Ruling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Honesty, Confession and Good Judgment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You probably can't read the new posts and comments on /r/stopdrinking for anytime without coming across a slew of posts in which newcomers talk movingly about shame, guilt, remorse, and regret over past misdeeds.  Most of our misdeeds, as bad as they were, harmed only ourselves, but usually we hurt close family, friends and co-workers.  If you are anything at all like me you wanted a clean conscience and you felt the immediate compulsion to run out and confess and apologize.  STOP.

Honesty does require amends, often confession or apologies but as I said yesterday in my [Brutal Honesty post](https://www.reddit.com/r/stopdrinking/comments/3d67e1/brutal_honesty_is_not_honesty_its_mostly_just/) don't confuse honesty with brutality.  Our need to get honest is not a license to HURT others.  Ever.  

So how do we move forward to right past wrongs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AA meetings helped save my life, but I augmented them with seeing a psychologist in my early days sober.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you made it into the lifeboat.  When I came back from a relapse in 2009 I was losing my professional license, and going to prison.  I got sober and changed my entire life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not go to an AA meeting?  I would if I felt like you feel, in fact I go when I'm feeling great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 22:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, /u/Kev131 -- did I share the [Baby Steps post with you?](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/)  Maybe something in what I did to stop drinking and get sober will be helpful to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 22:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/Allied_Biscuit to /r/stopdrinking  Maybe you aren't an alcoholic but living without booze makes a lot of sense.  One of my closest friends in the World is a leading Class Action attorney and philanthropist--a total teetotaler.  Like you he had a family history of alcoholism and he CHOSE to not drink.  And yet he is the life of any party he's at.  So at this [link is the Baby Steps post](http://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) which summarizes what I did to stop drinking and stay stopped.  Maybe something there will be helpful to you.  Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 22:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, ha, ... perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Door-Knocking Iowa Home-Schoolers Courted by Republican Suitors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 21:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Navy pilot sentenced to 50 years in prison on child porn and other charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 21:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 21:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry.  I probably wouldn't have posted the link at all but one of the newer mods took down my link to the TimesDispatch story about the Circuit affirmance of the corruption conviction as off-topic.  This article points out why it is totally on-topic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 21:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful comment.  It gives me goosebumps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 21:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surly Long Haul Trucker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cuyahoga County prosecutor seeks to move old cases from Judge Joseph D. Russo's docket </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 21:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Iran Deal Upends U.S. Politics | Five ways Tuesdays announcement reshapes the terms of the domestic political debate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 21:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parents plead guilty to neglect after police find dead bug in disabled son's breathing tube </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 21:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great update.  Good luck on the interview! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome /u/Garrosh1981 to r/stopdrinking--I did (and do) the [things I describe at the Baby Steps post.](https://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/)  I see you're hesitant about AA meetings, so was I.  I'm glad I went though.

Good luck to you and welcome aboard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love traveling sober.  I hit up AA meetings wherever I go: Cape Cod, Florida, Chicago, NY, Toronto, even...just out of town.  It's a remarkable way to get out of the tourist or travel bubble and feel at home anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News' Pastor Robert Jeffress: Jesus Wouldn't Protect Undocumented Immigrants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much the standard advice for newcomers to /r/stopdrinking who don't really know if they want "to quit drinking" and who consider themselves "borderline" is--don't quit.  Quitting drinking implies permanence.  Instead STOP drinking for 30, 60 or 90 days and see if abstinence helps you get some clarity about your relationship with alcohol.  

Of course, many of us feel tremendous empathy for your horrible childhood, but it's not that unique in reality.  There are those of us with much better and those of us with much worse upbringing. Many of us can wallow in the misery of the memory of rotten parentage.  The question really is: what do you want to do with your life.  Personally, I chose to live and free myself from the legacy.  I do something I call [the Baby Steps every day](https://www.reddit.com/r/SDCleveAkron/comments/2i427b/the_baby_steps_where_to_start_stopping/) to stop drinking and to get sober.  Thus far I'm in a far better place than I've ever been.  Come jump in the lifeboat, if only for a month or two.  Begin with a decision not to drink TODAY, only.  Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In recovery, (for me, AA meetings) there are systematic ways of approaching the changes I needed to make and a process for making amends to the people I hurt.  Meditation is a huge part of that process in my experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great comment.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep using this forum for this confessional or any other sober purpose; we are your support community focused on helping one another stop drinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calif. man accidentally shoots self in chest at gun range </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 19:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 19:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She made them smaller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 19:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most major banks will give you a passbook savings for $20. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 19:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ordering the Happy Meal Deal at McDonalds the same as declaring War on Wendys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Graham: Iran Deal 'Akin to Declaring War' on Israel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 18:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carly Fiorina: U.S. broke every rule in Iran negotiations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 18:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex Savannah-Chatham cop Khaalis a "dirty cop" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 18:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 18:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it actually fit you, worth $25. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disbarred 2X </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 18:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 18:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, perfect! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alabama mayor convicted of stealing from city is re-elected. But how? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 17:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 17:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A nuclear war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this [link is a post about dreams and an email exchange that I had with leading dream researchers that might answer your questions.](https://www.reddit.com/r/stopdrinking/comments/2dit1m/what_do_drinking_dreams_mean/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> big thumbs up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's [my post from the /r/alcoholism sidebar on this question.](https://www.reddit.com/r/alcoholism/comments/2v573a/the_where_why_and_what_should_i_expect_at_my/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rape kit testing linked bicycle-riding man to four rapes since 2005, prosecutors say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harvard Law Graduate Matthew Muller Arrested In Kidnapping Cops Said Was Hoax </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Losing the war with Iran | A nuclear deal will be the regimes greatest victory over America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Save a dollar a day.  When you have $20 put it in an interest bearing account.  When you have $500 add it to a market-indexed fund.  Forget that you have this money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After a Church of Scientology-backed group helped organize a campaign against it, Gov. Greg Abbott vetoed legislation that would have given Texas doctors more power to detain mentally ill and potentially dangerous patients, according to records obtained by The Texas Tribune. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Scalia: Why he's a bad influence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican lawmakers threaten to kill agreement | Obama will need to rally at least 34 senators to his defense as Congress reviews final agreement. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The White Castle Story: The Birth Of Fast Food   The Burger Revolution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate your post and observations.  Like a lot of things in early recovery, sustained time sober often results in an epiphany or sudden alterations in perception.  While I might not have appreciated why such a big deal is being made about this or that among my support group--time sober and suddenly I can see how huge an idea is and how it really plays out in my own life.  At least that's how I experience some of these things.  I needed to keep my eyes open.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas judge will perform same-sex weddings  but only if couples acknowledge his anti-LGBT beliefs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Museum teams unearth 4,000-year-old home in Sheffield </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 13:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The homeless man who graduated Harvard Law with John Roberts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 13:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fact checking Christie on Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 13:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For just $2,700, Christie will take a photo with you at 2016 N.J. fundraiser </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 13:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tex. police chief investigated for underage solicitation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 13:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High-flying, beer-swilling El Chapo mocks clueless authorities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 13:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abbott's NH Courtship Dovetails with State Politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 12:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why this congressman has almost $20,000 in landscaping gifts on his finance reports </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 12:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obamas calling for sentencing reform. Will it happen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 12:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At La Raza's Democratic Forum, Donald Trump Is the Piata </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 12:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 12:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not drinking TODAY no matter what happens good or bad; staying honest in Cleveland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 12:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great!. Keep doing what you're doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 11:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honesty is freedom in our relationships.  Good work, my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 11:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not drinking TODAY no matter what happens good or bad.  I am with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 11:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thx! I  never alter titles.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 10:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was exactly the title of the article at the time I posted it.  I do not alter headlines.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The federal judge hearing a racial-profiling case against Sheriff Joe Arpaio refused Arpaio's demand that he recuse himself because he asked about Arpaio's investigation of the judge's wife. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 02:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
