<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3482</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraq launches Tikrit operation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 08:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraq launches Tikrit operation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 08:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 17:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't a joke.  Erdogan has high ambitions.

http://www.nationalturk.com/en/syrian-president-al-assad-on-erdogan-tayyip-thinks-he-is-a-caliph-27722

http://www.todayszaman.com/columnist/abdullah-bozkurt/turkey-caliphate-and-erdogan_368278.html

http://www.al-monitor.com/pulse/originals/2014/04/saudi-wahhabi-leaders-see-turkish-caliphate-threat.html#

https://www.opendemocracy.net/john-lubbock/turkey%27s-new-caliph-understanding-erdo%C4%9F%27s-hegemony </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 07:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do a good amount of physical exercise during the course of my job and like to work outside in my yard.  Keeps me from having to go to the gym.  I also don't like sweet foods so I snack on fruits a lot. That helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 00:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erdogan wants to establish the new Islamic caliphate in Istanbul.

Assad: Erdogan thinks he's Caliph, new sultan of the Ottoman Empire

http://rt.com/news/assad-interview-exclusive-syria-265/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 19:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For about 16 years now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 19:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off, spell his name correctly.  It's Leonard Nimoy.  Secondly, there is absolutely no reason for anyone to be unfamiliar with Spock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 19:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 18:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UFOs at the White House. Like this one: 

1952 Washington, D.C. UFO incident: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/1952_Washington,_D.C._UFO_incident </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 18:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Murray </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 07:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I somehow rig the $800 million dollar Powerball drawing so I win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 07:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Water bear is best. Has eight legs and never dies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 07:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on what "Things are getting increasingly more difficult" means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 06:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many subreddits, so little time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 06:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My jokes are funny, I don't care what anyone else says. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal Communications Commission Meeting: Live </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 18:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 18:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Federal Communications Commission Meeting:

http://www.c-span.org/video/?324473-1/fcc-meeting-open-internet-rules </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 05:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dogs' problem turned out to be an easy fix, but, I meant I  hope *your* dog pulls through alright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senior State Dept. official arrested for allegedly soliciting sex from a minor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 05:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 04:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know how scary that can be. My dog started to have seizures out of nowhere.  Found out it was the RAID ant spray I was using.  I hope she pulls through ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 04:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Due to an ice/snow storm I got to go home 4 hours early from work.   I had a great nap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 06:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There will be an Islamic caliphate centered in Istanbul, Turkey.  Erdogan and Sheikh Yusuf al-Qaradawi are making great progress in setting this up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 19:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turkey was home to the 4th and last Caliphate, abolished in 1924.  The last was Abdulmecid II of the Ottoman Dynasty. He was replaced by Mustafa Kemal Ataturk, know as the Father of secular Turkey 1923. He sought to westerize the country which conflicted with conservative Muslm beliefs.  This lead to an identity crisis for the country: go back to our roots in a glorious caliphate that was admired, or become a secular western country.  The man elected as the 12th President, Recep Erdogan,  doesn't like the secular model and is trying to return the country to a caliphate, with himself as the caliph. He views ISIL, and similar groups, as his way to achieve that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 18:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't want to have to run after him.  Takes too much effort for that.  Just shoot his ass, that'll stop him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 01:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An instant mind-reading device. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 01:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't necessarily think they are.  There have been some ugly babies in our gene pool.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 01:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since Turkey is going to be the center of their eventual caliphate, I'd restrict them to Turkey, but they must allow for people to come and go as they please.  Not everyone supports sharia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 22:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not for years.  I must say, I do miss him cooking for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 21:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Treeninja.  It's a game I play with my niece.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 21:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watch ufo "documentaries".  It's ridiculous, but I do it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 21:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Star Trek replicator.  We still don't have it and my microwave will not synthesize meals on demand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 21:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chili-cheese dogs.  If you serve hamburgers you should also serve hot dogs.  They go together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 21:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'd be signing up for a chunk of alone time.  I don't like being around people for too long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Egypt says it bombed ISIS targets in Libya after killings of Christians </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 08:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Egypt says it bombed ISIS targets in Libya after killings of Christians </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 08:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 10:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Additional confirmation: http://www.cnn.com/2015/02/12/europe/ukraine-conflict/index.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine crisis: Putin announces ceasefire deal at Minsk talks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 10:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 18:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Central heat/air and mild weather in winter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 08:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bras.  Since I have to be constrained in one for at least nine hours a day I am damn well going to be in a well-fitting, comfortable one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 07:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 07:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eyeball jewelry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 06:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're dark purple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 05:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching a youtube video and eating delicious grapes while my dog snores beside me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 22:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UPDATE:

Apsara Authority declared that it had arrested two more foreigners for taking nude pictures at Preas Khan temple yesterday.

According to the declaration, Apsara Authority with the cooperation from Tourist Police Unit in Siem Reap and Heritage Protection Division in Siem Reap had prevented the act of taking nude pictures at Preas Khan temple around 10:00 am on 06/ Feb/ 2015. The foreigners are Lindsey Kate ADAMS, 22 years old and Leslie Jan ADAMS, 20 years old. Both of them are American.

Mr Koy Sao (Judge of Siem Reap Court) had declare on Saturday that the court decided to imprisoned them 6 months with 1,000,000 riel fine for each and banned them for re-entering Cambodia for 4 years, as they were charged of

trafficking pornography and exposing sexual organs

in Article 39, paragraph 3 of the law on human trafficking and sexual exploitation in Article 249 of the Penal Code.

However, the punishment was suspended in accordance with Article 107,109,111 of the Penal Code.

Mr Koy Sao added,  Both of them confessed that they had taken nude pictures at the temple.

Both of them will be expelled from Cambodia tonight by bus from Siem Reap to Bangkok, Thailand.

http://cambodiaexpatsonline.com/newsworthy/two-naked-american-sisters-arrested-siem-reap-cambodia-t3872.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 22:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a new development Friday night, the Washington State Patrol said the boyfriend  a 38-year-old man from Miami, Okla.  had been arrested by authorities in Oklahoma late Friday and was booked in jail to await extradition back to Washington. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 07:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tldr: Brian Williams' apology was NOT sincere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 19:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd need to research whose financial investments are threatened by an analysis of data comparing the health of children vaccinated with those not vaccinated.  I doubt a credible study exists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 08:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a beautiful little child. Congratulations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 10:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be kin to [this guy](https://c1.staticflickr.com/5/4019/4251885937_b84e8c0f0a_z.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 22:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alrighty then, in that case, let me refer you to Wilmington, N.C. (great, safe community) or Virginia Beach, Va. (great weather, more jobs). The further south you go, the bigger the mosquitoes and higher the humidity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 21:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on what you mean by "mild weather'.  You do know we have high humidity and get hurricanes here, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 23:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ghost ship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 06:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a beautiful place.  You really have a green thumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 08:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm late fifties worrying about nothing and enjoying this fine bottle of Pinot Noir tonight.  You kids shouldn't worry so much about your bills.  They'll get paid, one way or another,  Worry about the man or woman you're sharing your life with, if you have one.  If you don't have one, get a dog.  Or a cat. Or something that's alive and needs you.  Just be glad for this moment, this very minute you're alive.  It's fucking glorious, man.  So many people didn't wake up this morning, but you did.  Worry only gets you high blood pressure and long-term drug dependence, problems with loved ones, intestinal issues and surgery for bleeding ulcers.  Choose to be happy no matter your present conditions.  Go listen to some Pink Floyd and have a nice glass of wine with a friend.  Or alone, either way.  Life is good and it's good to be here on this Earth with all its' beauty and nice clean air and water.  Plus!, we have the benefit of Mexican food.  Holy hell,  we don't need anything else to be happy, unless it's a good blackberry margarita outside under the big umbrella with some fabulous Mexican food.  Life is so good.  I'm so glad I have it.  I might be a fucking hippie in my mind though, so there
 is that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 06:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stary Olsa from Minsk, Belarus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 10:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suspect arrested after photos of slain woman posted online

http://www.cnn.com/2014/11/05/us/washington-murder-suspect/index.html?hpt=hp_t2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 18:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NBC should find a more trustworthy replacement for her.  She can no longer be trusted to follow simple instructions for the protection of others and doesn't set a good example at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 12:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're wrong; it is great.  Very nice when viewing silent underwater scenes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 23:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ["Today you, tomorrow me."](http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/elal2/have_you_ever_picked_up_a_hitchhiker/c18z0z2) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 09:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice storm, great pics.  I especially like #6. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 07:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's gorgeous, love your hair! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 18:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who purposely harm children or animals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Branson's stunning new vacation policy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 18:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 05:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/jdZwEGc.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 18:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trade-in  your old games at Walmart.  You get a gift card that you can spend any way you want.  I used mine for gas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 21:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are some  articles that refute that premise:

http://www.universetoday.com/107172/why-our-universe-is-not-a-hologram/

http://sciexplorer.blogspot.com/2012/04/holographic-universe.html

http://www.colorado.edu/philosophy/vstenger/Fallacy/FTCosmo.pdf

Honestly, I'm not convinced by them either.  Perhaps this is a question better suited 
for /r/askscience? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extent of Antarctic sea ice reaches record levels, scientists say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 04:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 17:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been paying $18 a month for basic tv for over two years now.  I had it shut off earlier this week and was surprised to find I receive even more channels without it.  With broadband I have no reason to spend the extra money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 08:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.nbcnews.com/id/26887181/ns/us_news-life/t/father-abandons-kids-under-safe-haven-law/#.U_BLaWMvD9o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 07:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 05:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should start asking for donations to help pay for the damages to the ~~Quik-Mart~~ QuikTrip.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 00:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell that to the senator who tweeted "Fuck you" to the Governor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 00:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are local police afforded more personal body armour and weaponry than military forces fighting in war-torn countries?  Shouldn't we be looking at the types of people being hired as police personnel if they're so very willing to follow orders and shoot at innocent civilians?  Who hires these aggressive people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 18:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yours are all anti-Israel in nature, so it doesn't help at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 17:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That bear has better posture than I do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 04:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ferris wheels.  It's just not the same when you aren't 4 ft. tall anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 04:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genuine love for other people in all shapes and sizes.  They aren't cutthroat, sleezy and they won't steal from you or stab you in the back.  They'll help take care of you when you get some dread disease and will come to your parties when asked.  They give nice gifts.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 04:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elora Danan or Alora Dannon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 01:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you like ISIS, Hezbollah, PLF, Al-Aqsa, Al-Qaida  and Hamas to rule the world? Would that be better for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 10:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, it's beautiful.  You did a great job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 20:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they aren't always nice tags. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 11:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His pipe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 07:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://tunein.com/radio/Chicago-Police-Scanner-s95537/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 01:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "They took all the trees
 And put 'em in a tree museum.
 Then they charged the people
 A dollar and a half just to see 'em. 

 Don't it always seem to go
 That you don't know what you've got
Til it's gone.
 They paved paradise
 And put up a parking lot."

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xWwUJH70ubM
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 20:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the point of having it operate so differently on this one subject?  Who's going to decide what's important enough for threads like this and what isn't?  This defeats the purpose of the way reddit operates.  If I wanted randomized, I'd choose randomized.  I cannot tell what's new and what isn't.  I prefer it the regular way.  If I get overburdened with content of one kind or another I just scroll down and skip it.  This takes away choices and I do not support it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 05:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article:

"A #BBCtrending investigation has found that many of these images are not from the latest conflict and not even from Gaza. Some date as far back as 2009 and others are from conflicts in Syria and Iraq."
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 09:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A sweet potato ate my baby! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 10:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tastes metallic, like copper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 17:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A proud dad is a proud dad in any culture.  They both worked hard for this day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 07:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like it's this one: http://www.kmart.com/northwest-territory-front-porch-tent-18%27-x-12%27/p-089W005579974001P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 16:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few drinks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 02:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We believed you, but you threw us to the dogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 02:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've found it very useful and I'm sure getting my $10 worth this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 01:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A third eye on the back of the head, like my mother has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 07:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/europe 

/r/NeutralPolitics

/r/PoliticalDiscussion 

/r/photoshopbattles 

/r/NetflixBestOf 

/r/technology 

/r/TechNewsToday 

/r/Cordcutting 

/r/Frugal 

/r/gadgets 

/r/OldSchoolCool 

/r/scifi 

/r/uspolitics 

/r/WorldPolitics

/r/PostCollapse 

/r/gardening 

/r/homestead 

/r/JusticePorn

/r/DIY 

/r/ArtisanVideos 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 04:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US has counties larger than that.  It's only 998 sq. miles, so I don't think it could ever be considered a separate state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 04:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't do that anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 04:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any of these: http://www.karmawhores.net/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 03:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superiority complex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 02:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're minor things, but everything helps.  After baking something, leave the oven door open so the heat escapes and helps warm up the area.  Also, I cut the leg off a pair of pantyhose and secure it around the end of the dryer vent hose.  The hose in the floor next to the washer blowing out. That heat is also used to heat the area.  I figure, I have to pay once for that heat, why not use it as efficiently as I can  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 05:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chacarron.  Go ahead...say it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 05:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I do not believe all people worship the same god.  There is only one God and only one book He says is given by His inspiration, is profitable for doctrine, for reproof, for correction, and for instruction in righteousness.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 02:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no lost knowledge, it's been written for thousands of years.

The Bible has nearly 800 references to Jerusalem- called the City of our God (Ps. 48:1,8) Jerusalem is Gods city, the city of Zion, he has invested his name there (Daniel 9:19).

Jerusalem is called the city of the great King (Matt.5:35). YHWH is called the God of Israel, He is not called the God of any other nation in this manner, The God of Jerusalem is key to the Jewish people, to Jesus and to the end of the age.

Zion is called the city of God. Isa 60:14: and they shall call you The City of the Lord, Zion of the Holy One of Israel. It is where the Lord has and will dwell again. Joel 3:21: for the LORD dwells in Zion. When the temple permanently replaced the tabernacle and was built in Jerusalem it became the place of his dwelling, his presence was there, thus name Zion.

Ps. 132:13-14: For the LORD has chosen Zion; he has desired it for His dwelling place: This is My resting place forever; here I will dwell, for I have desired it. Ps. 87:1-3: His foundation is in the holy mountains. The LORD loves the gates of Zion more than all the dwellings of Jacob. Glorious things are spoken of you, O city of God! Selah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 18:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the video:  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EIGcpnDvmsg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 06:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She probably can't find a bra that fits her.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 18:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a horse when I was a kid, a gelding.  Silly thing would fight the dog for leftovers (especially spaghetti) and tried several times to come into the house through the back door.  He could drink Pepsi from a bottle and hardly spill a drop.  He also bit me when I wanted to go left and he wanted to go right.  He bucked my sister off into a ditch filled with tadpoles and she came up with green slimey hair and tadpoles dripping off her face.  I gave him a treat for that one. He was a boss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 09:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why didn't more women have alien babies in the X-Files?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
