<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1094</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free marijuana for all: Oregonians exercise the right to Weed the People </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 16:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tunisia has declared a state of emergency, just over a week after 38 people were killed in an attack in the resort city of Sousse. The last time Tunisia declared a state of emergency was in 2011, in the uprising which overthrew President Zine al-Abidine Ben Ali. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 15:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton warns that a Republican president would repeal Obamacare "I'm so thrilled that we're at a point where all the calls about 'Repeal! Repeal! Repeal!' mean nothing ... If the country elects a Republican president, they will repeal ACA. That is as certain as I can say it," </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 14:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian President Vladimir Putin called for dialogue based on equal treatment and mutual respect with the United States on Saturday in a congratulatory message to President Barack Obama marking U.S. Independence Day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 13:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seabirds may navigate by scent: When scientists magnetically disturbed Corys shearwaters, the birds still managed to find their way. But when deprived of their sense of smell, the shearwaters had trouble homing in on their final destination. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 19:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Namibian seal cull: 80,000 seals pups to be massacred in 'cruellest slaughter in the world': African nation is the only country that allows the killing of nursing baby seals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 18:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Healthy people given the serotonin-enhancing antidepressant citalopram were willing to pay almost twice as much to prevent harm to themselves or others than those given placebo drugs in a moral decision-making experiment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 17:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside Kobane: How Islamic State conducted its terrifying 'killing rampage' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 17:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump: A farce to be reckoned with "The one thing Trump can accomplish is to bring the Republican campaign down to his level. A party that allows such a travesty deserves to lose." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 17:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 15:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2015/150703/ncomms8580/abs/ncomms8580.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The brain of a 15 million year old monkey has been visualized for the first time. The 3D computer model shows that the brain is much smaller and has more folds than expected, supporting the idea that brain complexity can evolve before brain size in the primate family tree. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 15:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Miami defendant sobs in court as he realises he and the judge attended the same school </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 15:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surprise! Donald Trump is wrong about immigrants and crime. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 15:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The drugs that protect people who have unprotected sex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 13:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This astronaut is sacrificing his body to go to space for 1,000 days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 16:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wozniak Says Scene in Jobs Trailer Is Fiction, Loves It Anyway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 16:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A study in the New England Journal of Medicine reports that taking daily shots of liraglutide can help overweight or obese patients lose weight -- a lot of it. Patients taking the medication lost an average of more than 12 pounds, twice as much as those on a placebo, after 56 weeks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 16:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BMW will test a vehicle powered by hydrogen fuel cells for the first time on public roads this month. Fuel cells produce electricity by reacting hydrogen with air, enabling longer travel than battery-driven vehicles while emitting only water vapor rather than carbon dioxide. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 16:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Home-brewed heroin is near after scientists nail down poppy morphine gene </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 16:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'We Are Already In a Cold War': Former US National Security Advisor Zbigniew Brzezinski believes the West should stand up to Russian President Vladimir Putin in Ukraine. "We should make it more costly for the Russians to use force," he tells SPIEGEL ONLINE in an interview. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 16:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: People whose parents are distantly related are, on average, taller, smarter and better educated than those whose parents are close relatives. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 15:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yanis Varoufakis: I'd rather cut off my arm than accept yes vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 15:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis tweeted Thursday that mankind should "stop spoiling the garden God has entrusted to us, so that all can enjoy it," echoing the main theme of his recent 'green' encyclical Laudato si'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 15:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dogs diagnose cancer using smell alone: Anecdotes of dogs that can sniff out cancer have been doing the rounds for years, and now the urban legend is being subjected to scientific scrutiny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 15:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia warns against colour revolution in Armenia: In a veiled warning to the West, Russia cautioned on Thursday against any attempt to spark a new "colour revolution" in Armenia by exploiting protests against electricity prices for political ends. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 14:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gerrymandering didnt make politics this vicious. But vicious politics will soon make gerrymandering so much worse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 14:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 14:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Approximately 1.3 million Indian soldiers served in World War One, and over 74,000 of them lost their lives. But history has mostly forgotten these sacrifices, which were rewarded with broken promises of Indian independence from the British government" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the Indian soldiers of WW1 were forgotten </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 14:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese scientists are using animals to try to predict when an earthquake may strike. Seismologists in Nanjing, the capital of eastern Jiangsu province, have set up seven observation centres at zoos and animal parks in the region </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 14:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Countries who treat their women equally have better womens soccer teams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 14:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We can't print drachmas, says Greece's finance minister: With speculation swirling that Greece might be forced out of the euro and have to print its own money after a weekend referendum, its finance minister on Thursday said the country no longer had the presses to make drachmas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 12:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 12:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0127900 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 48 million-year-old Jesus lizard probably walked on water, scientists say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 12:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Solar Impulse breaks solo record: At 76 hours into the journey, he broke the record for the longest ever non-stop solo flight without refuelling. The previous mark was set by the American Steve Fossett in 2006. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 12:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Romania, vazuta prin ochii lui Toma Coconea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 11:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Denmark to cut asylum-seeker benefits under new leaders: Single asylum-seekers without children will get an integration benefit of 5,945 kroner a month before tax, instead of the current 10,849. Married couples with children will be able to get 16,638 kroner monthly, instead of the current 28,832. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Past research shows men find female faces more attractive at peak fertility. A new study shows an increased redness of womens face skin at the most fertile point of ovulatory cycle, but just under the threshold for detectability, ruling out skin colouration as a driver of the attractiveness effect. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State weaves web of support in Gulf Arab states </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nicholas Winton, a humanitarian who almost single-handedly saved more than 650 Jewish children from the Holocaust, earning himself the label Britains Schindler, has died. He was 106. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A blind teacher in southern France was baffled to be called in to supervise students during a an exam. Despite her appeals that she wasn't est suited, her school forced her to do it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study found that people who walked for 90 minutes in a natural area, as opposed to participants who walked in a high-traffic urban setting, showed decreased activity in a region of the brain associated with a key factor in depression. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 16:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Huckabees claim that New York City shootings are up because of Mayor de Blasios policy: He earns Four Pinocchios. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 16:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Danish court on Tuesday stripped the citizenship from a Danish-Moroccan bookseller jailed for inciting terrorism, in the first case of its kind in the country. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 16:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Older athletes can be much younger, physically, than they are in real life, according to a new study of participants in the coming Senior Olympics. The study found that the athletes fitness age is typically 20 years or more younger than their chronological age, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 15:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberia said Wednesday a teenager who died of Ebola fever had spread the virus to at least two more people, confirming the first outbreak of the tropical disease for months. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 15:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New Horizons spacecraft has made its last planned targeting manoeuvre as it bears down on Pluto. The probe is due to scream past the dwarf world on 14 July at almost 14km/s and at an altitude of just 12,500km. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 15:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Greece went bust </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 14:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brain chemical turns tree ants into aggressive soldiers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 14:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Relentless Terror: The Everyday Horrors of the Islamic State. Eighty lashes of the whip for alcohol. Amputation for theft. Crucifiction for robbery. These are only a few of the draconian punishments employed by the IS, according to documents and the testimony of witnesses obtained by SPIEGEL. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 14:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Huckabees claim that New York City shootings are up because of Mayor de Blasios policy earns him Four Pinocchios. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 14:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Online Anonymity Box Puts You a Mile Away From Your IP Address </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 13:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mozambique has decriminalised homosexuality in its new penal code, making it one of a few African countries where same-sex relationships are legal. The revised code, in force from Wednesday, drops a colonial-era clause outlawing "vices against nature". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 13:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Syrian rebel group operating around Damascus has executed 18 alleged members of the Islamic State group in a video mimicking the extremist organisation's own productions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 12:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hitch in U.S. training program for Syrian rebels: Little interest in fighting ISIS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 10:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man in wheelchair robs New York bank, gets away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 10:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Top predator' humans causing catastrophic ecosystem shifts: study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 18:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than 12,000 children have been rescued in the past three years from gold mines in northern Tanzania, according to children's rights groups who fear thousands more youngsters are being forced to work in hazardous conditions for a pittance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 18:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bangladesh might exile Rohingya refugees to a remote, flood-prone island: The remote island, Thengar Char, disappears completely under several feet of water at high tide, and has no roads or barriers to flooding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Britain and the Netherlands have become less friendly places for migrants due to the impact of far-right parties and austerity measures, with both countries falling out of the top 10 in an index released on Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jimmy Carter: Why I believe the mistreatment of women is the number one human rights abuse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ten photos showing the power of the weather </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because his luggage smelled like weed, Charles Clarke lost $11,000 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drug cops took a college kids life savings and now 13 police departments want a cut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tepco ordered to pay over suicide linked to nuclear evacuation: It is the second time that a court has determined there was a link between the nuclear disaster and a suicide, and ordered the utility to pay damages. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google AI chatbot threatens human master: A chatbot has learned how to hold a conversation by analysing millions of movie scripts, allowing it to muse on the meaning of life, the colour of blood, morality and even get angry with its human inquisitor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An international team of scientists has discovered the deepest underground dwelling centipede. Recorded as deep as -1100 m the new species was named Geophilus hadesi, after Hades, the God of the Underworld in the Greek Mythology. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Sudans army raped then burned girls alive inside their homes during a recent campaign notable for its new brutality and intensity, a UN rights report said on Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LiquiGlide: Nonstick coatings leave zero waste behind - YouTube </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://circ.ahajournals.org/content/early/2015/06/25/CIRCULATIONAHA.114.010636.abstract?sid=85dd7dfa-509b-434c-9233-7a7a6b1e700f </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sugary drinks linked to 180,000 deaths a year, study says: The study found that the beverages would be responsible for 133,000 deaths from diabetes, 45,000 from cardiovascular disease and 6,450 from cancer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A kilo of Cocaine costs $1,500, in Colombia, $12,000-16,000 in Mexico and $77,000 in Britain according to the accountant of Colombias Medelln drug mob </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 15:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The world's 400 richest people lost a combined $70 billion on Monday as equity markets around the globe were hammered on fears about Greece and declines in China fueled by leveraged investors exiting the market. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 15:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Single cells made to levitate, just like frogs and mice: A technique previously used to levitate animals and fruit has been scaled down to work on cells, and could help diagnose cancer or test new drugs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 15:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists discover dramatic climate change in the Sahara reduced the largest freshwater lake on Earth to desert dunes in just a few hundred years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 14:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Courts ruling on gerrymandering is a victory for voters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 14:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most internet anonymity software leaks users details: Services used by hundreds of thousands of people in the UK to protect their identity on the web are vulnerable to leaks, according to researchers at QMUL and others. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 14:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greece Can Stay in Euro Even With 'No' Vote, Schaeuble Tells Lawmakers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 14:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicanism is dead. Maybe. "Only a semi-mystical Republicanism, deluded by its own dogma, cannot see the future. Thats why it may not have one." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 14:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ebola Survivors May Be the Key to TreatmentFor Almost Any Disease </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 13:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Partners who become romantically involved soon after meeting tend to be more similar in physical attractiveness than partners who get together after knowing each other for a while, according to new findings published in Psychological Science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 11:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The hardline Islamic State group has beheaded two women in Syria, the first time it has decapitated female civilians, the founder of a group monitoring the war said on Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 10:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: Melting Arctic sea ice could be disrupting the oceans circulationwith potentially major consequences </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 17:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An exhausted army of immune cells may not be able to fight off infection, but if its soldiers fight too hard they risk damaging the very body they are meant to be protecting, suggests new research from the University of Cambridge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 17:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taking a nap may be an effective strategy to counteract impulsive behavior and to boost tolerance for frustration, according to a University of Michigan study. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 16:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sanders says hes no Johnny-come-lately to big issues of the campaign "'It is fair to say, Is one a Johnny- or a Mary-come-lately to the issues, or have you been there for the stretch? And I think if you look at my record, Ive been there for a long period of time.'" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 16:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rich countries are very, very far from raising the billions they promised to help poor countries fight climate change, jeopardising the prospects of reaching a global warming deal at Paris, the worlds rising economies warned. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 15:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope 'plans to chew coca leaves during Bolivia visit' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 14:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Israeli government wants to force-feed Palestinian prisoners who go on hunger strikes, an extreme medical procedure that Israeli doctors say they will refuse to perform because it is unethical and inhumane. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 13:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey mulls bombing ISIL without sending troops to Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 13:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Around 30 percent of China's Ming-era Great Wall has disappeared over time as adverse natural conditions and reckless human activities -- including stealing the bricks to build houses -- erode the UNESCO World Heritage site, state media reported. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 12:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Isis fighters have killed 74 children, part of more than 3,000 people the group has 'executed' in areas of Syria it has held over the course of a year, according to a report by a group monitoring the Syria conflict. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 12:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> France has deported 40 foreign imams for "preaching hatred" in the past three years, a quarter of them in the last six months, Interior Minister Bernard Cazeneuve said on Monday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 12:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Russian lawmaker, who has strongly backed anti-gay legislation, said Facebook should be shut down in Russia over its support for the US Supreme Court's decision to legalise same-sex marriage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 15:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Israeli think tank says the worldwide Jewish population is nearly as large as it was before the Holocaust. When factoring in individuals with one Jewish parent and others who identify as partially Jewish, the figure approaches 16.5 million -- the Jewish population on the eve of World War II. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 14:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dalai Lama gives Glastonbury his verdict on Isis: 'unthinkable' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 12:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Violent videos show apes may have sense of right and wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 11:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austria's finance minister said on Sunday that Greece's exit from the eurozone "appears almost inevitable", after EU leaders refused to extend Athens's desperately needed bailout. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 11:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A German woman tried to end an affair she was having by faking her own death using tomato ketchup as blood and sending the images to her lover. Her internet lover reportedly refused to let things lie and bombarded her and her husband with explicit images, according to local media. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 15:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraqi forces have arrested Abd al-Baqi al-Saadun, one of the most senior officials from Saddam Hussein's regime still at large, Prime Minister Haider al-Abadi said on Saturday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 15:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scalia tried to make the court a conservative stronghold. He failed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 14:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flying paint tin ruins Maserati interior, insurance write-off leads to $90,000 payout "The driver swerved to avoid a dog and the tin of paint he'd set on the back seat flew through the air dislodging the lid," </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 09:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study claims 1 in 4 cancer research papers contains faked data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video: Monkey uses a tool  to pick her nose </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Many conservative Republicans now deny the existence or danger of human-caused warming and routinely question the motives of scientists who speak up on the issue. For a conservative to stray from skepticism is regarded as ideological betrayal." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The global reach of the legal highs industry has been laid bare by a UN study that shows new psychoactive substances  as they are officially called  being reported for the first time in countries as far afield as Peru and the Seychelles. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 14:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its time for conservatives to end the denial on climate change "Many conservative Republicans now deny the existence or danger of human-caused warming and routinely question the motives of scientists who speak up .... For a conservative to stray from skepticism is regarded as ideological betrayal" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 14:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These Three Maps Show How Drugs Move Around the World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 12:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diagnosing Ebola in minutes: Researchers from Harvard Medical School have shown that a new, commercially developed rapid-diagnostic Ebola test performed at bedside was as sensitive as the conventional laboratory-based method used for clinical testing during the recent outbreak in Sierra Leone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 10:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barack Obama interviews Sir David Attenborough at the White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 09:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The decline of religion in the West </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 09:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our eye sockets give us a wider field of view than other apes: The unique positioning of our eyes within our skulls may have played a part in our early evolution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 16:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monster black hole wakes up after 26 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 16:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple co-founder Steve Wozniak says humans will be robots' pets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 15:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At current pace, it will take 30 years to rebuild Gaza, says senior UN official </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope: Worldly pastors talk too much, listen little </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huckabees claim that global freezing theories from the 1970s shows the science is not as settled on climate change gets four Pinocchios </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The famous lemurs of Madagascar face such severe threats to their survival that none of them may be left in the wild within 25 years. That stark warning comes from one of the world's leading specialists in the iconic animals. Deforestation and hunting are taking an increasing toll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 13:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CEO pay at USs largest companies is up 54% since recovery began in 2009: The average annual earnings of employees at those companies? Well, that was only $53,200. And in 2009, when the recovery began? Well, that was $53,200, too. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 13:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giant Galaxy is Still Growing: For the first time a team of astronomers has been able to track the motions of 300 glowing planetary nebulae to find clear evidence of this event and also found evidence of excess light coming from the remains of the totally disrupted victim. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 12:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oslo creates world's first 'highway' to protect endangered bees: Oslo's "bee highway" aims to give the insects a safe passage through the city, lined with relays providing food a shelter -- the first such system in the world, according to the organisers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 11:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds significant spike in number of stay-at-home dads in Canada: Men had to step up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 10:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Female genital mutilation: Why Egyptian girls fear the summer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 10:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ISIS offers sex slaves to winners of Koran memorization contest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 18:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists Can Spark Their Own Lightning With Rockets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 18:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lone Russian Lawmaker To Oppose Crimean Annexation Charged With Embezzlement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 17:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [All Spoilers] The science behind the most horrific deaths in Game of Thrones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 17:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Kurdish militia leading an attack on ISIS strongholds in Syria so far has no plan to extend the assault to the group's de facto capital of Raqqa city, and such an advance should be led by Syrian rebels, a Kurdish leader said Wednesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 17:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putins approval ratings hit 89 percent, the highest theyve ever been according to measurements from the Moscow-based Levada Center, the only independent polling organization in Russia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 17:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A mushroom used for centuries in Chinese medicine reduces weight gain in animals, say researchers in Taiwan. The study, published in Nature Communications, suggested Ganoderma lucidum slowed weight gain by altering bacteria in the gut. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 16:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tsipras turns on creditors: He said that this never occurred with equivalent measures put forward by Ireland and Portugal when they were negotiating bailouts. Either the creditors did not want a deal or were serving "special interests", he added. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 16:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World's first full-color, flexible, skin-like display developed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 15:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis said Wednesday that it may be "morally necessary" for some families to split up, marking a change of tone in the Catholic Church's attitude to troubled marriages. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 15:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla says its drivers have traveled a billion miles. "For some perspective, a billion miles is about as far as 4,200 trips to the moon. It also adds up to some 570,000 tons of saved carbon emissions, thanks to the Model S's electric battery, Tesla says." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 15:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Officials in western Canada are urging people not to flush their pet goldfish down the toilet because they're surviving and multiplying at an alarming rate. Environmental officers in the province of Alberta say they've found goldfish the size of dinner plates in the region's storm ponds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A team of researchers has created a new implantable drug-delivery system using nanowires that can be wirelessly controlled. The nanowires respond to an electromagnetic field generated by a separate device, which can be used to control the release of a preloaded drug. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 14:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lindsey Grahams zombie claim about no fugitive being arrested after a failed gun background check gets four Pinocchios </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 13:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Improved ability to control attention could lead to reduced worry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 11:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martellus, Henricus. (Map of the World of Christopher Columbus), 1489. [1484921] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 18:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State militants have blown up two ancient shrines they consider sacrilegious in Palmyra, a 2,000-year-old UNESCO World Heritage site in central Syria, the ultra hardline Sunni Muslim group said on Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 18:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man builds giant computer at home: James Newman is building a 14m (45ft) computer processor in the lounge of his bungalow in Cambridge. Mr Newman's 16-bit "mega processor" will contain 14,000 individual transistors and 3,500 LED Lights. So far the project had taken him 3 years and cost about 20,000 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 18:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disabled people pilot a robot remotely with their thoughts [+video] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Medical marijuana 'edibles' mostly mislabeled, study shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interstellar: Christopher Nolan on science behind the film </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syria's economy cut in half by conflict </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK university college rewrites 650-year-old dress code to fit transgender students </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video: The US Army is being equipped with these futuristic hoverbikes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astronomers have solved a mystery over small, unusually hot blue stars, 10 times hotter than our Sun, that are found in the middle of dense star clusters. They found the so-called blue hook stars throw off their cool outer layers late in life because they are rotating so rapidly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An analysis published in JAMA Internal Medicine found that 75% of American men and 67% of American women ages 25 and older are now overweight or obese...and a depressing sign that campaigns to get Americans to eat healthier and exercise more may be failing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 16:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Iraq worth the fight? After years of war and chaos, its people no longer know </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 15:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Economic inequality is greatest threat facing many nations, report says: Uneven economic growth does not reduce poverty as quickly as growth that is spread across societies, the CRI said. It also warned that worsening inequality can lead to or exacerbate conflicts and reduce social cohesion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 14:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Pregnancy wi-fi' router causes controversy in China "Qihoo 360 unveiled the device which has three settings it describes on its website as wall penetration, balance and 'pregnant women'. The third setting reduces radiation emitted by the router by 70%, the firm claims." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 14:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps politics by hammer "he believes that everything crossing his mind is worthy of expression, without being edited or organized for the benefit of others. So we get a spew of Trumps gut feelings. They tend to be resentful of outsiders; immigrants are depicted as 'rapists' and drug runners." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 14:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gel that can instantly stop bleeding heads to vet surgeries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 13:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two fearless women lead Romania anti-corruption crusade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 12:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate change threatens to undermine the last half century of health gains </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 11:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A self-described atheist from the southeastern Turkish province of Adyaman has been forced to leave his hometown after receiving death threats for removing the term Islam from the religious affiliation section of his national identity card. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 11:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Map: Where Europe is growing and where it is shrinking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 10:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Early man from Romania had close Neanderthal relatives, DNA shows: DNA testing of an ancient jawbone has confirmed that a man who lived in Romania about 40,000 years ago descended from a Neanderthal ancestor just four to six generations  less than 200 years  before him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 17:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greece's economy minister Giorgos Stathakis has told the BBC that he believes Greece's new proposals to balance the government's books have broken the deadlock with its creditors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 16:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Glows in the Dark and Dispenses Cyanide? Certain species of millipedes do, first to warn off predators and then, if necessary, to dispense with them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 16:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fetus Found Inside 17th-Century Mummified Monk's Coffin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 16:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rumor: Apple developing iPhone display with integrated Touch ID fingerprint scanner, eliminating home button </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 16:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASAs New Horizons captures the first color movies of Pluto and Charon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 15:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toshiba Working on Unbreakable Encryption Technology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 14:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Pauls ridiculous story of an elderly man imprisoned for dirt on his land gets four Pinocchios "this story is about much more than an elderly man simply putting dirt on his land. Pauls storytelling of government gone amok has run wild on its own." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 14:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin Tells Russians That Its Their Holy Duty to Be Patriotic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 13:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The secretary of Russia's security council said Monday it is impossible to stop Russians from going to fight in Ukraine because they are guided by "emotions." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 12:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Few Echo Popes Environment Plea in Sunday Sermons: Around the world, few priests used their pulpits on Sunday to pass on the popes message on climate change, pollution and global inequality. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 11:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 8 Million Dog Mummies Found in Mass Grave: In ancient Egypt, so many people worshiped Anubis, the jackal-headed god of death, that the catacombs next to his sacred temple once held nearly 8 million mummified puppies and grown dogs, a new study finds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 15:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 15:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0128129 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Memory problems? Could be all that trans fat youre eating: A study published in PLOS ONE links worsened memory function to higher consumption of trans fatty acids. "On average, men ages 45 and younger recalled 86 words. But those who had the highest intake of trans fat recalled 12 fewer words." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 15:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The truth about bees: All of our ideas about bees are based on one species, the European honeybee. Most of the others are nothing like it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 15:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The fish that can vanish in 2 seconds flat: it has evolved the ability to become almost invisible. The fish can camouflage its body patterns and shape to match its marine surroundings in seconds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 14:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warring forces in South Sudan have carried out horrific crimes against children, including castration, rape and tying them together before slitting their throats, the UN has said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 14:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Belgian Prime Minister Charles Michel has recognized on the behalf of the Belgian government the killing of Ottoman Armenians in eastern Anatolia from 1915 as genocide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 14:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats are more liberal today than at any point in the last 15 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 14:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The women whom science forgot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 09:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pirate Bay's Peter Sunde says Australia's proposed website blocking scheme won't deter downloaders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 09:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US climate change skeptics and deniers said Thursday that Pope Francis was wrong to urge action against global warming because continuing to burn cheap fossil fuels could actually help the poor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 18:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austria First to Say Game Over for Greece: With the Greek gov't approaching the June 30 expiry of its euro-area bailout and no alternative financing in sight, Austrian Finance Minister was the first to declare the effort to broker an aid deal has failed The game is finished, he told reporters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 17:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Austrian city of Salzburg unveiled Thursday gay-themed pedestrian traffic lights after the flashing signals specially installed in Vienna for the Eurovision Song Contest proved a hit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 17:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have found physical differences in the brains of people who respond emotionally to others feelings, compared to those who respond more rationally. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 17:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's How NASA Will Grab an Asteroid Using a Spiky Robot Gripper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 16:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Kerry Praises Pope Francis Climate Change Encyclical </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 16:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a Billionaire Heiress Cracked the Premier League Boys Club: Katharina Liebherr, the only female owner in the English Premier League, orchestrated the most successful EPL season for once-struggling Southampton. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 15:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French warn Britain: Brexit could be your Waterloo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 15:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This new NASA/ESA Hubble Space Telescope image shows a gathering of four cosmic companions. This quartet forms part of a group of galaxies known as the Hickson Compact Group 16, or HCG 16  a galaxy group bursting with dramatic star formation, tidal tails, galactic mergers and black holes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 15:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 15:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the peer-reviewed journal entry: http://cancerres.aacrjournals.org/content/75/12/2478.abstract?sid=8cf28fc0-5927-4cab-b177-4c3a3e0cecb2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newest miracle food is avocado, which has potential cancer-busting properties: scientists have found a fat in avocados that combats acute myeloid leukemia, a rare and deadly form of cancer, by targeting leukemia stem cells while leaving healthy cells unharmed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 15:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alzheimers spares long-term musical memory: scientists have pinpointed the location of musical memory for the first time and shown that this area of the brain remains largely intact despite progressive degeneration of the brain in Alzheimer patients. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 14:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A growing online craze among some fitness communities, fetishists and chronic disease sufferers for buying and drinking human breast milk poses serious health risks, British experts said on Thursday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 14:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neuroscientists have discovered that artificially stimulating a positive memory can cause mice to snap out of depression-like behaviour. "Turning on" the memory for just a few minutes eliminated signs of depression. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 14:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps Mexican rapists rhetoric will keep the Republican Party out of the White House "That plays well with many far-right Republican primary voters desperately clinging to an America that no longer exists. But such rhetoric is the death knell for the GOP  and the party knows it." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 14:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside 'Hackerville,' Romania's Infamous Cyber Crime Hub </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 09:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> European countries have spent 11.3 billion euros in the last 15 years on deporting illegal migrants and another 1.6 billion euros on border control around "Fortress Europe", journalists said in a study published Wednesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 09:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a scientist in a parking lot may have influenced the Pope and climate change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 08:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A dispute has been tee'd off between Switzerland's ambassador to Venezuela and a neighboring elite golf club, after a banner appeared at the diplomat's residence warning that golf balls injuring or killing anyone inside would violate the Vienna Convention. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 08:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Highly trained, respected and free: why Finland's teachers are different </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 17:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greek Exit Would Shake, but Most Likely Not Shatter, Eurozone: Many analysts believe that changes in the European financial system could contain the fallout if Greece defaults on its debt at the end of the month. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 17:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
