<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8395</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 17:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot. That was done on a Nikon D7000 with nauticam underwater kit in a local pool for a music video I shot. We only used one light above the pool and the grader brought down the exposure so to not got the tacky feeling of it being set in a pool. He deserves as much credit as I do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 17:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the heads up. I see those comments a lot as well and my work is growing ever so slightly so I am hoping to be able to craft a few variations of my showreel to show my experience in said areas.

I also see what you mean by coming across as amateur. At the moment I am still in film school and don't want to come across as too presumptuous by labelling myself as a 'Cinematographer' or 'D.O.P' especially as it is a title I have barely scratched the surface of. But in my next reel i'll cut it out. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first Cinematography reel. Would really appreciate some tips from experienced professionals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 21:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 03:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Filmed with C100 with 6 stops of inbuilt ND filters. 100-400mm Canon lens with 1-9 Variable ND filter as well. 
Shot on ProRes 422 HQ.
25fps, 5.6 f-stop, 1/50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video of the Solar Eclipse in Falmouth, Cornwall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 03:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 10:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ummm for black and white scenes and daylight dancer scenes I used a Canon Mk ll with a L series 50mm 1.4 I think. Underwater scenes I used a Nikon D7000 with a standard 50mm. The DJ gig I used a Canon Mk lll with 50mm L series 1.4. For the dancing event I used a standard 70-200mm 2.8 lens and 50mm L series with the mk lll and with the horse documentary I used a C100 with the 50mm L series and the 85mm 1.8. I think thats roughly right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 10:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yeah, I have been getting into projecting my videos at events recently and have had some good surfaces to work with. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 10:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That means a lot, thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first cinematography showreel [01.51]. Looking for advice and comments from veteran filmmakers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 14:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'V For Vendetta' symbol (potato quality) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 02:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
