<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7821</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 03:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Perfect example ](http://www.nerdacy.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/1x05_Charity_Drive_10.png)



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 05:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no cop should be pulling anyone over unless they are guilty of a crime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 04:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EVERYTHING was insensitive in the 1970s...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) NBC says they're distancing themselves  

2) Trump acting like he's doing his civic duty to be a public servant 

he's marketing himself (brand) by using the political stage like he was pimping goods on QVC. who needs NBC when you're getting every major news outlet instantly hyping you for free. 

   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game Fuel 

Used it again for WOW tie-in... 

God (marketers), please bring it back full time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did various Halo matchups with Mtn Dew   doritos... very extreme

1st thing I thought of w/ the Red Bull was how they were up their old tricks again...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 18:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> even their sisters?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 07:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, while I understand why, please investigate Lee before you write him off as some racist or redneck...

He was a great man, a general not a politician. Simply put: he hated slavery but backed his home state of Virginia who could have sided either way...He deserves a school or two named after him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 15:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/BillMurraySightings/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 04:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/396807/serious_chain_restaurant_employees_what_should/

might as well read the original </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 04:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> REMINDER: he was athletic   trim for most his life BEFORE the fat pic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 20:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the uppity / clueless ones do...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 22:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if we're playing against other 360 players, I assume there'll still be tons of glitching...right? 

every time I try to play, it's glitch-fest in full session.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 17:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when the white walkers take them over,   they will, they'll get their due justice... there's no one left there to grieve for when it happens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 07:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kept renting this game so much, they sold it to me for a discount... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 07:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> which one is Mr. Cherry?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 07:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 800 4my XBOX

http://support.xbox.com/en-US/ [show]

@XboxSupport </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 02:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ had to look up support site. found several threads with several answers from Kevin (I believe) following them through the process  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 03:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have they created a virtual lobby for players yet? You still get kicked to lobby after every match? It'd be nice to be able to stay with a group for a while (eliminate the quitters; keep players playing instead of cranking up a match each   every time...). Basic matchmaking 101.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 07:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> almost like deer hunting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 20:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes... it plugs in between controller - right ear bud. has a very thin mic that extends towards mouth. I have no complaints now... crystal clear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 19:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ALL SPOILERS: applies to ALL things Game of Thrones (BOOKS   TV) 

I even put a disclaimer in brackets as an opening before you read anything else saying it was strictly applying to the TV show. Anyone who proceeded should be caught up enough to not be timid about a post. 

EDIT: TIL if you are afraid of getting any spoilers, don't click any links that say "ALL SPOILERS" because it has spoilers   lots of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [All Spoilers) Question about Fighting Pits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 17:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Haven't read books, only watched show)

When Daenerys finally OK'd the fighting pits, she did so because they were now "free" do so. The logic used to defend them was that it was tradition   these fighters wanted to do it. 

Yet, 2 episodes ago, we saw a slave trader selling people who were chained up   told to fight to their death.  They did so right in front of the Queen who was in attendance (begrudgingly). What gives?


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 17:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> w/ software updates (via XB1) it's better than it was at launch (be sure to update controller when it's plugged in)

I bought one a month ago through MSFT store for $47. 

It's comfortable. In fact, very comfortable (I use it for more than XB1 now). I have it on for hours   never bugs me (rare for a headset)

Sounds great (no surround; only stereo). It's Polk, they make some of THE best speakers around. 

Yes, the built in mic isn't as great as others... So, register it @ Polk's site w/ the yellow paper that's packed. 

Then look at their support page. Find the email they post to like EVERY complaint about mic sound. Email them w/ address, Serial Number, phone # etc...

I did it, got a new (free) mic in 2 days shipped (free). 

Some say their 4 shot now comes w/ headset adapter, mine didn't. I actually like the adapter, has a great mic   awesome cord to connect to controller (the material is soft   doesnt' seem to get in the way).

It's a great headset. Especially at that price, it's THE best XB1 wired headset I've used. You can spend $250+ on a wireless Turtle Beach w/ surround, but that's up to you. Enjoy. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 17:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had 3 Jolder's (1/ damage)... After playing w/ BTRD this week, I only have 1 J.Hammer left 

BTRD  J.Hammer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 19:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Parents you have been warned. Please consider the life long implications of what names you give your children. There is an impending Y2K-like time bomb waiting to explode in the healthcare system because of all these "cute" names parents are coming up with these days. Giving your kids three middle names, double hyphenated last names, siblings with phonetically similar names, or naming twins almost the exact same thing WILL result in errors in their medical records. Oh, and quit using symbols, apostrophes, and other non alpha characters. They don't play well with today's electronic health records.

it's a shame, but good luck getting jobs. Your kids wont' get good jobs with names employers can't pronounce. They won't even make it into an interview.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 18:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> countless cops kill unarmed, presumed innocent citizens / year   they keep their job... yet, this guy may lose his  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 03:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel this is THE worst song ever, yet, I still crank it when it comes on the radio... seriously, it's horrible. EVERY time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 06:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you'd think there's enough musicians / producers / rappers / etc in ATL to fund this...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 02:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That long neck sleeve restricted him... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 01:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 800 4my XBOX

http://support.xbox.com/en-US/ 

@XboxSupport

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 01:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://bfy.tw/7eY  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 01:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> honestly, he didn't do it. They (whoever made the decision) did it. they were making a spot for a bigger/better video game reviewer... 

it's not fair, but it's also not his fault. 

good luck with your career.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 18:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [disappointed if anyone other than this guy](http://www.comicscontinuum.com/stories/1106/06/nathanfillionindex.jpg)



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 06:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 800 4my XBOX

http://support.xbox.com/en-US/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 05:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noble sandwich co has a great (cheap) breakfast. I prefer the porkbelly to the bacon though... 

BTW: their grits/ham hocks is the best thing on the menu.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 21:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $15/mo is too expensive for HBO w/out middle men... I pay less than that   have to share w/ my provider. 

If they offered $5/mo, who would still share their password? It's the price of a couple candy bars a month... get your own account.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 17:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things like this are FAR more important to address...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 18:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought one, love it. Sounds / Feels great

Register it on Polk's site   go to their support page for the free additional mic adapter... doesn't come with it. they shipped it w/in 5 days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 17:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://gizmodo.com/you-can-take-this-little-wind-and-solar-powered-home-an-1706538003 

^ good writeup about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ecocapsule </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 17:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 03:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure that armor is a level 100 jock cup  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 01:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xtf3NlYhB_U 

EDIT: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EQJklN4e6XM better video 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 02:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when I bought the books from Google play, I got a confirmation email sent to my gmail

now, that email is deleted from my records as well. 

it'd be great if Google had admitted mistake   sent out email saying it did. I'd accept that. *BUT* to cover up their tracks? *WTF* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
