<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6418</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did Jon decide to leave Game Grumps only 2 weeks after they made the t-shirt commercial? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 14:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't they have scratched making more Jon merchandises if he was going to leave? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 13:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe gimr requested, and red bull provided? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 14:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hbede p der var nogle som havde erfaringer her som kunne fortlle noget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 14:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tnkte at det var lettere at finde danskere som
Har flyttet til England her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 14:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Det behver ikke at vre London som sdan. Faktisk har jeg det fint mes mindre byer hvis der er arbejde for mig der.

Er frdiuddannet ingenir s hber p en ok ln? Er ikke sikker om det vil give en ok tilvrelse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 14:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Helt sikkert. Er bare ikke sikker p hvordan jobmarkedet er der? F.eks. For ingenirere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 13:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hele England, KBH, frdiguddannet kandidat indenfor en ingenirretning, skal bare have ca. 3 mellemstore kasser med, ingen kledyr eller kreste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flytte permanent til England fra Danmark, hvor meget kostede det jer ca.? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 13:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Et estimat med flybillet, lejlighed, alt andet som man ikke ummidelbart tnker p? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 01:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Denmark the Saudi ambassador blocked an entire floor in a hospital so that his mother (who does not have a Danish citizenship nor has ever paid taxes here) could be there in peace for her cancer treatment. This meant that many Danish citizens could not receive their cancer treatment because the beds were "occupied". Remember this is Denmark which is supposed to have free healthcare for its citizens who pay between 38%-45% in taxes to get free healthcare. There was also stories about several of the nurses going down with stress and some who quit because the family treated them "like slaves".
The ambassador later claimed that it was okay because "he paid for all the treatment". That doesn't change the fact that doctors could not check up on other patients because the Saudi ambassador demanded his mom get first priority and again many patients were denied a place in the hospital because the beds were "full".

Even more fucked, most media here were completely silent about this. Why did most media not write about this? I wonder. Also it later was revealed the person who ran the hospital had been invited home to the ambassador for dinner.

And they say Scandinavia isn't a corrupt place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 13:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao, so now you've resorted to personal ridicule, eh? Believe in whatever you want, I've said my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I wouldn't, because it would take the spot from somebody else who was legally entitled to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thousands of people die in the US every year because they don't receive treatment that they could have otherwise received in Europe. The same would probably happen to me.

If every US citizen with a medical problem was allowed to travel overseas and get free treatment, the quality of healthcare in European countries would greatly decrease or just wouldn't be able to cope with all the patients and in the end it would result in native Europeans not receiving treatment because of the decreased quality or lack thereof.

The same goes for immigration. Countries can't handle the level of immigration currently without it decreasing various aspects of the welfare. This world is not some rainbow utopia where everybody can live happily ever after. When you get older, you will realize that things are not as simple as you think they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I have problems receiving healthcare in the US, I shouldn't come crying to Europe and expect them to solve my problems. I should deal with my problems in my own country.

So yeah, I do believe in that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I wasn't born there and I don't need to emigrate to the West. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's not my problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 12:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Women in Europe didn't have the rights they have now back then. But with hard work that changed.

Running away from your country because it doesn't give women rights is never going to make that place any better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 11:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why not campaign against the Saudi flag? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 11:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The confederate flag happened before the 19's so I think that's old too then. Also if the confederate flag is only a symbol in the south then Americans in the north shouldn't have a say either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 11:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So turn a blind eye on everybody else and be good pals with them, huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 11:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not murders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 11:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the government about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If people are so passionate about taking down the confederate flag, who don't anybody care that the Saudi flag represents the murders during the Islamic conquest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 10:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
