<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9503</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Liar's 'Tell' | Ekman argues that the GAO failed to consider the most up-to-date and pertinent research on the subject." But his critics say the worlds most famous lie detector has been stretching the truth a bit himself. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 02:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can MSM Handle the Contra-Cocaine Truth? | What kind of journalist obsesses over dissecting the work of another journalist while the U.S. government gets away with aiding and abetting drug traffickers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 21:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 21:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesterday I thought the OP and many commenters had said everything that needed to be said, but then my half-asleep musings in the night brought up some more.

He needs to know how important humor is, both in relationships generally and in sex specifically.  In both cases there will be little awkward moments and laughing is the best way to get trhough them.

Talking openly is really key to both relationships and sex.  Being able to say "I've never done this before' or 'I'm pretty nervous, let's slow down and talk for a while' will stand him in good stead.  Also 'I really like it when you move that way' and 'Would this be even better if I were a little slower?'

Without getting too technical and jargony, an acquaintance with the stages of arousal,  la Masters and Johnson, would be useful.

He needs to know that women are for the most part more varied in their sexual response than men.  Many don't orgasm from PIV sex alone and it's unlikely with a girl during her first time.  In fact, he would do well to see that she orgasms first and waits to enter until she invites him in.  Frank talk would help here, telling her that that's what he wants, that they have plenty of time, that they can wait for another time.  You could watch some movies with him with those scenes of ripping off clothes, falling into bed and having stupendous simultaneous orgasms, and let him know how unrealistic they are.  

You're doing a great job and I hope his first time is wonderful for them both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frida Berrigan on Operation Kid Freedom: Making Our Communities Safe for Children to Take Risks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 20:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Finland's Schools Are Top-Notch | Finland has built a school system that has over time strengthened educational equity. Teachers have time to work together with their colleagues during the school day. Play constitutes a significant part of individual growth and learning in Finnish schools. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 20:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who Stills Profits in Era of Obamacare? The Middlemen | Our health care system is filled with good people who feel they are bringing real value to the system, but they are just feeding off needless complexity while the rest of us struggle to pay our insurance premiums and medical bills. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 05:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking at Productivity as a State of Mind | Workers effectively hired capitalists to make them work harder. They lacked the self-control to achieve higher earnings on their own. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 04:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Ray Rice and Successful Ways to Combat Gender Violence | Fan-Shen, FAR Out and Sista II Sista are examples of how we can address abuse in our own communities. By organizing community responses, they demonstrate how everyday people can break through the isolation and secrecy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 15:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 03:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start with "Spanish" then "Advanced".  I haven't used the others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its All for Your Own Good | People speak in terms of autonomy, but what they are doing is making a rapid, intuitive judgment about welfare. I must say that I find all of this remarkably tone-deaf to concerns about autonomy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 23:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brave New Phone Call | Ray Ozzies new app Talko hopes to give people their voices back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 21:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not so foolish | We are told that we are an irrational tangle of biases, to be nudged any which way. Does this claim stand to reason? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 19:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Personhood: A Game for Two or More Players </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 04:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 16:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michel Thomas is not just about teaching phrases.  His is very much a grammatical based approach.  He puts it in context much better than conjugation charts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's poverty in the UK, but we are better off calling it inequality | The tax and benefits systems are propping up incomes of shareholders in companies that pay too little. Money that could and should go to employees in return for their labour instead goes to owners in return for their capital. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 02:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Preparing To Asset-Strip Local Government? The Feds Bizarre New Rules | The international bankers got away with asset-stripping Greece. Why not make the US itself a wholly-owned subsidiary of private banking interests? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 18:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article by Ellen Brown: [Preparing To Asset-Strip Local Government? The Feds Bizarre New Rules](http://www.commondreams.org/views/2014/09/09/preparing-asset-strip-local-government-feds-bizarre-new-rules)

What is the justification for removing all municipal bonds from the HQLA requirements? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Profiting from America's Misery | Self-indulgent capitalists have turned much of America against its own best interests by promoting a winner-take-all philosophy that reaps great rewards for a few people at the expense of everyone else. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 18:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Driving American Politics Underground | Politics is no longer the business of our traditional political institutions, which are used to crush any vestiges of civic life that calls on its citizens to share among all its members the benefits, sacrifices and risks of a nation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 17:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Aren't Women Advancing At Work? Ask a Transgender Person. | Having experienced the workplace from both perspectives, they hold the key to its biases. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 21:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So Bill Gates Has This Idea for a History Class . . . | It begins to be a question of: Is this Bill Gatess history? And should it be labeled Bill Gatess History? Because Bill Gatess history would be very different from somebody elses who wasnt worth $50-60 billion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 20:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Conversation Corporate Education Reformers Want Versus The One They Get | Beltway-inspired wonks are calling out the tone police but its got little to do with honesty and facts. In these calls for taking the politics out of the debate, what you find is itself a rather political agenda. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 18:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 06:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're just playing bookends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NATO and Ukraine: A Warning byVeteran Intelligence Professionals for Sanity | The images released by NATO on Aug. 28 provide a very flimsy basis on which to charge Russia with invading Ukraine. Sadly, they bear a strong resemblance to the images shown by Colin Powell at the UN in 2003. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 18:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 17:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it you think should be done with poor black and Latino students? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Crime of Overbilling Healthcare | These ripoffs are not just clerical errors or computer malfunctions. The frauds are designed with corporate interests in mind to filch your wallet directly or under the nose of unobservant insurers, from the design of billing statements to manipulation of codes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 18:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Segregation Now ... | While segregation as it is practiced today may be different than it was 60 years ago, it is no less pernicious: in Tuscaloosa and elsewhere, it involves the removal and isolation of poor black and Latino students, in particular, from everyone else. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 04:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Building Better Teachers | Mastering the craft demands time to collaborate-just what American schools don't provide. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 02:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 02:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article:
 Calling economists rational fools, Amartya Sen observed: The purely economic man is indeed close to being a social moron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want better, smaller government? Hire another million federal bureaucrats. | Americas Leviathan by proxy consumes as large a share of the nations gross domestic product as many supposedly more statist European governments do. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 21:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inequality and the USA: A Nation in Denial? | "The United States, in sum, doesnt just have the worlds most unequal major developed economy. The United States has the most people in denial about the inequality they live amid." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 17:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ferguson Everywhere Now | Whoever thinks Ferguson and Gaza are disconnected doesnt understand that we are in a desperate struggle against the poison of dehumanization. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 17:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Engineering the ocean | Once you know what plankton can do, youll understand why fertilising the ocean with iron is not such a crazy idea. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 04:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its Time for a Post-Piketty Vision of Shared Wealth | If de-growth on a global level is inevitable sooner or later - and there is enough evidence to suggest that it is - then the implications are dramatic for how we achieve a just and sustainable world for as many as nine billion people by 2050. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 21:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its Time for a Post-Piketty Vision of Shared Wealth | If de-growth on a global level is inevitable sooner or later - and there is enough evidence to suggest that it is - then the implications are dramatic for how we achieve a just and sustainable world for as many as nine billion people by 2050. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 18:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Save the Life of the Next Michael Brown | "Any form of oppression is ultimately about power - who has it and who doesnt - and becoming aware of which side of that equation were on is hard. It often causes defensiveness. But we can see defensiveness instead as a call to listen more deeply." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 18:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Numbers for the 'Entitlement' Bashers | Social Security and Medicare are more properly defined as "earned benefits." The super-rich feel they deserve all the tax breaks and the accumulation of wealth from the productivity of others. This is the true threat of entitlement. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 19:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saving Horatio Alger | Wide-ranging discussion of social mobility and wealth distribution in America. | "There are forces at work in America now that put the country at risk of creating an ossified, self-perpetuating class structure, with disastrous implications for the very idea of America." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 19:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And 'Rithmetic | "Because everyone knows that the subject matter itself isn't that hard. What's hard, virtually impossible, is beating it into the heads of youngsters who hate every step. Give me a kid who wants to learn the stuff -- well, twenty hours or so makes sense." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 21:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We Don't Need No Education | At least not the traditional, compulsory, watch-the-clock-until-the-bell-rings kind. As a growing movement of unschoolers believe, a steady diet of standardized testing and indoor inactivity is choking the creativity right out of our kids. The alternative: set 'em free. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 06:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lunch with Raghuram Rajan, Indias central bank governor | Central bankers have had enormous responsibilities thrust on them to compensate, essentially, for the failings of the political system. And my worry is we dont have sufficient tools to do that, but were not willing to say it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 07:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> America Is Not For Black People | "There are reasons why white gun's rights activists can walk into a Chipotle restaurant with assault rifles and be seen as gauche nuisances while unarmed black men are killed for reaching for their wallets or cell phones, or carrying children's toys." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 06:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Be Polite | The good thing about politeness is that you can treat people exactly the same. And then wait to see what happens. You dont have to have an opinion or make a judgment. I know that doesnt sound like liberation, because we live and work in an opinion-based economy. But it is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 04:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Hidden Ways Urban Design Segregates The Poor | "There's a name for uncomfortable benches, hard-to-reach parks, and ubiquitous surveillance: disciplinary architecture." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 03:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The end of neighbours | We are now more insular and more ignorant of the other guys thinking. There is greater mutual ignorance than a generation ago between people who live in close proximity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 05:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corporate America Hasnt Been Disrupted | "By a wide range of measures, the advantages of incumbency in corporate America have never been greater." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 18:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Biggest Lie About Net Neutrality | "One of the most persistent lies told in Washington is the notion that common carriage is a heavy-handed regulation that transforms innovative businesses into antiquated, government-run utilities." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 17:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 1% May Be Richer Than You Think | The more money that you have, the easier it becomes to hide that and avoid taxes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 04:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beyond the Minimum Wage: Whats Really Keeping Hourly Workers in Poverty? | "These low-quality jobs also impact the broader community because employers shift costsparticularly for health care for their workersto our already overburdened public systems." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 17:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside Our Profoundly Unequal New Normal | Increasing inequality accentuates the reluctance of the elite to pay taxes that can partially equalize opportunity by funding public expenditure on the human capital of all childrenbecause their own children have the most to lose from such spending. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 22:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are fish far more intelligent than we realize? | Part of the reason that cod fisheries are collapsing is that we keep fishing out the largest fish, which are the most knowledgable ones - we take away the animals that know where the resources are, and it's shifting their migration patterns. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 22:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Facts that Poverty-Deniers Don't Want to Hear | 1. We Spend Relatively Little on Poverty Programs. 2. $100 Shrunk to $57 for the Median American Family -- In Just 6 Years. 3. Kids and Seniors Get the Worst of It. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 20:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New Face of Richard Norris | For fifteen years, Richard Norris had a face too hideous to show. Then, one day, a maverick doctor gave him a miracle too fantastic to believe. Richard got a face transplant, a new life, and a new set of burdens too strange to predict. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 20:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Founders On Depression | Once youve been depressed once, you know that depression is not sadness - its just numbness. [x-post from r/technology] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 23:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Founders On Depression | Once youve been depressed once, you know that depression is not sadness - its just numbness. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 22:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Money Talks | The language of money is a powerful tool, and it is also a tool of power. If we allow ourselves not to understand this language, we are signing off on the way the world works today, on the prospect of an ever-widening gap between the rich and everyone else. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 06:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are 7-segment lights still so cost-effective that we can't get rid of them? They're about as state-of-the-art as uppercase-only TTYs from the '60s. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 02:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now Then -- the hidden systems that've frozen time and stop us changing the world | "Taken together the cumulative effect is that of a giant refrigerator that freezes us, and those who govern us, into a state of immobility, perpetually repeating the past and terrified of change and the future." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 17:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Close the tax loophole on inversions | "To be clear, there is nothing wrong with cross-border merger activity; our economy is stronger for our investment overseas and for foreign investment in the United States. But these activities should be based on economic efficiency, not tax savings." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 16:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Be Good [2011] | Derek Parfit is perhaps the most original moral philosopher in the English-speaking world. He believes there are true answers to moral questions, as there are to mathematical ones. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 22:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With New Obamacare Rulings, One Thing Is Certain: We Need Medicare for All for Life | "Thinking that my fellow Americans in another state may suffer more than I because of some decision their elected officials made about creating a state exchange is troubling, to say the least." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 19:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wrong Answer | In an era of high-stakes testing, a struggling school made a shocking choice. | In depth account of the Atlanata cheating scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 23:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malaysia Airlines Flight 17: The Problem Isnt Conflict, Its Violent Conflict Management | This global pro-violence worldview will shoot us all down from the sky unless we reject the outdated, illogical idea that violence is an acceptable, or possible, means for achieving peace. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 16:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside the Artificial Brain Thats Remaking the Google Empire | Google is not really a search company. Its a machine-learning company. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 18:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waking Up To Our Broken Education Policies | Grievances with inadequate and ijequitable funding and lack of democratic control are whats driving the debate -- not teachers unions, Diane Ravitch, or the inner dynamics of the Democratic Party. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 18:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Uncle Sam Have a God Complex? | No one elected Uncle Sam to play God. But a dire shortage of democratic constraints has enabled the U.S. surveillance state to keep expanding with steely resolve. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 17:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Behind 'Smokescreen' of Charity, Global Financial Elite Pillage African Nations $60bn Each Year | "Millions of ordinary Africans are certainly poor, but they are being kept so by a combination of bad policies and immoral or criminal activities perpetrated by elites inside and outside the continent." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 17:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the World Cup Can Teach Progressives About Corruption | 'Apart from passionate support for their national sports teams, hatred of government corruption and crony capitalism is one of the few issues that unite all social groups in developing countries.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 17:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ever Wondered Why the World is a Mess? | "It is not by chance that all mainstream media worldwide have the same reading of the world. Information today has basically eliminated analysis and process, to concentrate on events." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-13 18:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Busy NYC Restaurant Solves Major Mystery by Reviewing Old Surveillance | 26 out of 45 customers spend an average of 3 minutes taking photos of the food. 14 out of 45 customers take pictures of each other with the food in front of them or as they are eating the food. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 19:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Co-Founders: Thanks, But No Thanks | Its pretty amazing that a company that doesnt think twice about tackling absurdly challenging scientific projects (eg driverless cars) is brought to its knees by the prospect of dealing with the byzantine regulation around healthcare. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 22:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 22:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this interview is a week old, but I just discovered it and went to post it on /r/politics.  Looks like the bot doesn't allow anything from Salon, even though I can't find any other source.

So is the bot in error?  Could the bot be made smarter so as to allow original content from Salon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Hobby Lobby Lesson: We Need To Fight For Single-Payer Health Care | Because the ACA still requires that private companies enforce what should be considered public policy - health care - the ACA will always face potential legal contention with the personally held religious beliefs of employers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 18:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cory Doctorow: Thomas Piketty's Capital in the 21st Century | There's one criticism I have a lot of time for: Suresh Naidu's critique of the politics of Piketty's analysis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 19:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americas CEOs: In a Class All by Themselves | Corporations elsewhere in the developed world pay their top execs far less than what U.S. corporations pay, and these corporations seem to be competing - and thriving - quite nicely in the global marketplace. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 17:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five Facts for the Dangerously Deluded Education Reformers | 1. Privatized Education Steals from the Poor, Gives to the Rich. 2. Testing Doesn't Work. 3. The Arts Make Better Scientists. 4. Privatization Means Unequal Opportunity for All. 5. Reformers Are Primarily Businesspeople, Not Educators. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 17:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 06:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate the supportive comments but am surprised by the number of unsupportive ones. Some are even condemnatory.

Hard to believe it would have been like this before becoming a default subreddit.  Maybe it's time for /r/TrueTwoXChromosomes.

**Edit:** Wow, I didn't know it existed.  How do I request to join? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saddhu in Goa 1975 [1443x970] [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 18:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 23:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No help, just this picky suggestion: ~~depreciated~~  deprecated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buying Up the Planet: Out-of-control Central Banks on a Corporate Buying Spree | The Chinese central banks holdings are created out of thin air no less than the Federal Reserves dollars are. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 18:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 07:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, because it deals with the social effects of technology.  You may want to exclude the politico-economic aspects of technology from this subreddit, but others of us don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 22:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michel Thomas teaches grammar in useful ways, without concentratiing on rules (at least in Spanish). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear Marc Andreessen | We could make the choice to pay for universal health care, higher education, and a basic income tomorrow. Instead, youre kicking the can down the road and hoping the can will turn into a robot with a market solution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 08:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Teaching Class | Teaching college is no longer a middle-class job, and everyone paying tuition should care. | The sanctity of teaching ought to be an argument for compensating teachers fairly, not for shutting underpaid teachers up.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 01:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Krugman: Does Timothy Geithner Pass the Test? | We clearly had the borrowing capacity to spend more on fighting unemployment. Whatever Geithner may say, its clear that a lot more could also have been done to reduce the burden of mortgage debt. Yet we didnt do what needed to be done. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 03:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No Money, No Time | The poor were so focused on operating under scarcity that they couldnt think their way through to a strategy -- or, indeed, even realize that an opportunity to do so was available. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 03:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IoT: Get Security Right The First Time | Let's start building security into the Internet of Things now, before everything becomes connected -- and hackable. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 17:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Yorks Single Test for High School Defined My Life | I applaud the desire to fix an admissions system that is clearly flawed, but I caution against hasty implementation of even well-intentioned changes. I am simply asking for more time before rushing unfinished legislation into law. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 03:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Life, After | An accident in February cost the TV reporter Miles OBrien his left arm. He soon discovered that every movement, no matter how small, requires rethinking. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 17:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 16:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The comments haven't addressed the issue that the exchanges are in breach of contract by not providing timely or accurate information.  What about that aspect? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fast money: the battle against the high frequency traders | A 'flash crash' can knock a trillion dollars off the stock market in minutes as elite traders fleece the little guys. So why aren't the regulators stepping in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 06:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brazils billion-dollar gym experiment | Whether in Europe, Africa or anywhere else, the people most active in their leisure tend to be relatively well-off young men. The academias are full of older, lower-income women. This programme is a marker for change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 19:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 20:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm just referring to languages that don't distinguish inclusive from exclusive, such as English and Spanish.  I'm sure there are gender differences also in whether a person says *I* or *we* when their partner is not present.  What I'm wondering is if the language used influences this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using 'we' when the person included in the 'we' is not there </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 23:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, I leave my wife in our room and go to the hotel desk where I say 'We need such-and-such."  There are regional and cultural differences in using the singular or plural in such cases but I also suspect that different languages may be more inclined to use one or the other.

Is this true?  What is this phenomenon called so I could research it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Too Big To Comply? NSA Says Its Too Large, Complex to Comply With Court Order | In an era of too-big-to-fail banks, we should have known it was coming: An intelligence agency too big to rein in - and brazen enough to say so. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 18:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austerity and the Employment Rate | It is tragic to realize that too many economists and policy makers have not learned what Keynes explained in The General Theory of Employment, Interest and Money in 1936. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 18:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time for Congress to Investigate Bill Gates Role in Common Core | The Common Core standards were developed and imposed without regard to democratic process. The largest contingent of the drafting committee were representatives of the testing industry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 17:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What John Browne (BP's former chief executive) Learned by Being Outed | Since my outing in 2007, many societies around the world have done more to embrace people who are lesbian, gay, bisexual or transgender. But the business world has a long way to go. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 01:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 23:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other quotes from the 'conversation':

*  When you write you should pretend that you, the writer, see something in the world that's interesting, that you are directing the attention of your reader to that thing in the world, and that you are doing so by means of conversation. 

*  The controversy between "prescriptivists" and "descriptivists" is like the choice in "America: Love it or leave it" or "Nature versus Nurture"--a euphonious dichotomy that prevents you from thinking.

*  Overcoming the curse of knowledge may be the single most important requirement in becoming a clear writer. 

*  You've got to show people a draft. Even if you're writing for laypeople, your reviewers don't all have to be laypeople; a colleague is better than no one. I'm often astonished at things that I think are obvious that turn out to be not so obvious to other people.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Writing In The 21st Century | A Conversation with Steven Pinker | Debunking stupid rules is not the same thing as denying the existence of rules, to say nothing of advice on writing. The Sense of Style is clearly prescriptive: it consists of 300 pages in which I boss the reader around. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 23:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My State of Emergency | Reflections on life, death, and Obamacare inside Oaklands main trauma ward. | You might think that cynicism would be rampant among ER staff who confront these issues day in and day out, but you would be wrong. Optimism runs deep here, as does pride. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 07:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Open Letter to My Waiter from Your Princessa | You may have meant no harm, but your attitude toward me as a woman is what perpetuates this culture where violence is stemming   fear is growing. In everyday experiences I question my decisions in order to protect myself from potential harm from men. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 17:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How mistakes can save lives: one mans mission to revolutionise the NHS After the death of his wife following a minor operation, airline pilot Martin Bromiley set out to change the way medicine is practised in the UK  by using his knowledge of plane crashes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 07:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 03:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More quotes:

* Everybody is dealing with how much of their own aliveness they can bear and how much they need to anesthetize themselves.


*  The problem of the alcoholic is not alcohol but sobriety. Drinking becomes a problem, but actually the problem is whats being cured by the alcohol. By the time were adults, weve all evolved ways of deadening certain feelings and thoughts.


*  Anybody who writes knows you dont simply write what you believe. You write to find out what you believe, or what you can afford to believe.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Art Of Non-Fiction: Adam Phillips | Long, fascinating interview with a psychoanalyst | It is very difficult to surprise oneself in ones own mind. The vocabulary of ones self-criticism is so impoverished and clichd. We are at our most stupid in our self-hatred. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 03:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate Change, Economic Inequality Are One Debate, says Sen. Warren Both issues show clearly that 'we have a rigged system, where a handful are able to reap benefits at the cost of everyone else.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 18:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear White Ladies | I am hard on you because I believe that you are smart and awesome enough to break the cycle of White women talking over, taking over and generally pushing Women of Color aside. For the sake of #allwomen just shut up for a few minutes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 04:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toward the Total Paralysis of an Unequal Society | Thomas Piketty recommends a global wealth tax to help reverse inequality. But a financial transaction tax would be easier to implement, more efficiently regulated, and a source of massive revenues at little cost to financial traders. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 18:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> #YesAllWomen Changes the Story | The history of feminism is one of punctuated equilibriums in which our conversations about the nature of the world we live in suddenly lurch forward. I think we are in such a crisis of opportunity now, as the whole construct in which we live is brought into question. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 18:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 02:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you and I are the only ones who thought so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Youre Right, I Didnt Eat That | I wanted to say that as a complex living organism, the human body is on for twenty-four hours a day, ready to betray you at an astonishing speed for minor transgressions if you do not respect its hypersensitivity to what goes in and out of it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 19:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 23:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I notice nobody has mentioned culling some of those photos.  Selection and organization are needed to make all those GB usable.  Nobody but you cares that you have 62 GB -- they just want to see the exceptionally good stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Of Brains   Minds: An Exchange | Patricia Churchland, reply by Colin McGinn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 02:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An astonishing record - of complete failure | In 2008, the consensus from forecasters was that not a single economy would fall into recession in 2009 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 02:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Europe works | Mobility is everything in a region where nations live in fruitful proximity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 23:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Impossibility of Growth Demands a New Economic System | Salvation lies in collapse. To succeed is to destroy ourselves. To fail is to destroy ourselves. That is the bind we have created. The mathematics of compound growth make continuity impossible. [x-post from Politics] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 17:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Impossibility of Growth Demands a New Economic System | Salvation lies in collapse. To succeed is to destroy ourselves. To fail is to destroy ourselves. That is the bind we have created. The mathematics of compound growth make continuity impossible. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 17:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We (and This Includes You, Democrats) Have Blown a Huge Hole in the Safety Net </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 18:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Social Immune System | The entirety of the political debate, as conveyed by the media, amounts to: What can we afford? This is a condition seldom placed on military spending. Were stuck in a society with a defective immune system, and reaping the consequences. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 17:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New Feminist Road Map | Feminism is an endeavor to change something very old, widespread, and deeply rooted in many, perhaps most, cultures around the world, innumerable institutions, and most households on Earth -- and in our minds, where it all begins and ends. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 18:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Practical Choice: Not American Capitalism or Welfare State Socialism but an Economy Thats Working for a Few or Many | While median per capita income in the United States has stagnated since 2000, its up significantly in Canada and Northern Europe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 18:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Radical Seed Grows in Jackson, Miss. | We are in a place that is at the bottom. Thats where you start. You start where the sickness is. In this setting, worker-owned cooperatives seem to offer a potent combination. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 18:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evidence that the Meritocracy is Made Up of Poor People | Ample evidence exists to show a correlation between wealth and unethical behavior, and between wealth and a lack of empathy for others, and between wealth and unproductiveness. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 18:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who Betrayed The Legacy Of Brown V. Board? | So 60 years after Brown v. Board, heres what passes for advancements in civil rights: grand gestures of progress - honoring a mixed race president - that amount to empty symbolism, while more direct harm is done to minority school children every day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 20:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schooled | Cory Booker, Chris Christie, and Mark Zuckerberg had a plan to reform Newarks schools. They got an education. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 19:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's Call Out Institutional Insanities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 17:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Darwins unexploded bomb | New evidence strongly suggests that the very different kinds of society seen...in the worlds great civilizations differ not just because of their received culture but also because of variations in the social behaviour of their members, carried down in their genes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 05:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Six Principles of the New Populism (and the Establishments Nightmare) | Republican populism is growing, as is the Democratic version, because the public wants it. Populists on the right and left are also coming together around six principles. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 19:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Four Biggest Right-Wing Lies About Inequality | The rich and CEOs are Americas job creators. People are paid what theyre worth in the market. Anyone can make it in America with enough guts, gumption, and intelligence. Increasing the minimum wage will result in fewer jobs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 17:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trailer Parks Lure Wall Street Investors Looking for Double-Wide Returns | We like the oligopoly nature of our business. It costs at least $5,000 to move a home, a sum that trailer dwellers rarely accumulate more than once. Were like a Waffle House where everyone is chained to the booths. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 18:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Regime Change in America: This Land Isnt Your Land, This Land Is Their Land | An Empire in Decline (City by City, Town by Town) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 18:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lifes restlessness | Why does life resist disorder? Because ever since the first replicating molecules, another kind of stability has beckoned. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 23:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Working the Dark Side | The media still call it the Abu Ghraib scandal, as though, oops, the awkward repercussions for Team Bush were the torture photos primary horror. No one talks about the Auschwitz scandal. The depth of our moral wrong has yet to be plumbed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 18:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corporate Oligarchy or Peoples Democracy: Countering the Elite Agenda | The call that many liberals are making to overturn the Citizens United and McCutcheon rulings and overhaul campaign financing are misguided. The issue is not campaign finance reform, but democracy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 18:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everything that is wrong with American capitalism, in one headline | Suppliers are not supposed to be able to trade customers as if they were a commodity. And yet, this is the situation we are in. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 01:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hello, Stranger | Commuting is associated with fewer positive emotions than any other common daily activity. By avoiding contact, were all following a collective assumption that turns out to be false. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 17:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can Thomas Piketty Re-Write the American Dream? | Piketty's goal is as ambitious as his research - to change the way wealth is distributed. So far, it's a message that a lot of people like to talk about, but very few want to hear. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 16:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tony Blair's speech on the Middle East | It is in fact a struggle in which our own strategic interests are intimately involved; where there are indeed people we should support and who, ironically, are probably in the majority if only that majority were mobilised, organised and helped. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 21:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Rightwing Supreme Court Is Wrong: The Original Intent of the Constitution Was Progressive | The U.S. Constitution was a bigger break away from any prior constitution than any constitution in history, before or since, has been. It was truly a revolutionary, progressive, document. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 16:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elizabeth Warrens Needed Call for Student Loan Reform | This year, commencement speakers should address the problem located on the very campuses that host them, challenging students, lawmakers and administrators to ensure that higher education remains an engine for growth, not a dead end of debt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 17:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Indictment of the Invisible Hand | Pikettys book is an indictment of laissez-faire market theory. One sign of how ineffectual the economics community has become is that it is unable to see the true fruits of the work, even as it praises Pikettys extraordinary empirical contributions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 18:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Krugman: Worried About Oligarchy? You Ain't Seen Nothing Yet | 'Even those of you who talk about the 1%, you don't really get what's going on. You're living in the past.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 18:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Growing-ups | The origins of the many prejudices against todays emerging adults are complex, but maybe one key reason is that many of their elders still use old yardsticks to measure their progress. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 06:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Hollow Center of Common Core | Those who think that inching subject-matter standards ever higher is the key to a quality education are concentrating on the wrong issues and the wrong processes. Until we get our priorities in order, higher standards will be nothing more than a distraction. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 18:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 00:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We as a nation should strive to be .1%-ers.

And all our kids will be above average. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Piketty in Washington: How to Reverse the Increasing Concentration of Wealth | A rare laugh erupted in the audience when Piketty noted, in French-accented English, that the consumption data of the upper income groups did not include their consumption of politicians. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 16:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Raising a Moral Child | To get 3- to 6-year-olds to help with a task, rather than inviting them to help, it was 22 to 29 percent more effective to encourage them to be a helper. Cheating was cut in half when instead of, Please dont cheat, participants were told, Please dont be a cheater. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 17:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evidenced-based tips, some counter-intuitive:  [Raising a Moral Child](http://www.nytimes.com/2014/04/12/opinion/sunday/raising-a-moral-child.html?emc=eta1 _r=1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Close the Billionaire Tax Loophole | Billionaires are exploiting a tax break to pass their fortunes along to their heirs and laying the groundwork for dynasties. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 16:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 02:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check [UUA.org](http://www.uua.org/) to see if there's a Unitarian Universalist community within reach.  You would meet thoughtful, welcoming people who are relatively non-judgmental and also appreciate Buddhist ideas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Wall Street Second-Chances Rule: Scandal Makes the Rich Grow Stronger | Money and influence reserve a permanent place at the trough of money. It's usually absurd to hope that any kind of setbacka loss, a harrowing proximity to eight insider-trading convictionswill leave a mark. They never do. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 16:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
