<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2450</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 16th Century mass grave linked to campaign of Michael the Brave discovered in Romania </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 04:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China's Foreign Ministry has lodged a protest with the United States for its condemnation of the deportation of a group of Uighurs from Thailand last week, as state television showed pictures of some being returned with hoods on their heads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 04:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mass extinction event from South Africa's Karoo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 03:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mass extinction event from South Africa's Karoo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 03:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two environmental groups filed a petition Thursday to put the Midwestern moose  which roams Minnesota, North Dakota, Michigan, and Wisconsin  on the endangered species list, citing climate change as a leading cause of population decline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Libyan political leaders have reached a new version of a U.N.-brokered peace deal, putting pressure on the Tripoli leadership to sign on and build a unity government in hopes of ending the country's chaos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A man in Alabama collapsed and died after officers sprayed him with pepper spray while arresting him after a chase, Tuscaloosa police said Saturday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 01:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than 10,000 fish died in temporary holding tanks in Brazil during construction of what is being touted as the world's largest freshwater aquarium </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Rodham Clinton has won the endorsement of the American Federation of Teachers. It's the first major labor union to make an endorsement in the 2016 presidential campaign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China's Stock Market Selloff Explained in Six Charts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 23:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unarmed Black Man Allegedly Strangled To Death By White Cop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 23:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of gay rights supporters marched through Taipei on Saturday, months ahead of elections that are likely to usher in a pro-gay party and could make Taiwan the first place in Asia to legalize same-sex marriage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 22:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twenty gay and lesbian couples got married in a mass wedding on an Acapulco beach on Friday, one month after Mexico's top court all but legalized same-sex marriage nationwide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 11:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US torture doctors could face charges after report alleges post-9/11 'collusion': Following repeated denials that its members were complicit in Bush administration-era torture, leading group of psychologists faces a reckon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 04:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Uninsured Rate at 11.4% in Second Quarter: Lowest since survey started in 2008 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 04:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For 17 months, a member of the North Carolina Board of Elections appointed by Gov. Pat McCrory demanded regular updates about the confidential investigation into $235,000 in political contributions to the campaigns of the governor and dozens of other elected officials </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 01:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For 17 months, a member of the North Carolina Board of Elections appointed by Gov. Pat McCrory demanded regular updates about the confidential investigation into $235,000 in political contributions to the campaigns of the governor and dozens of other elected officials </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 01:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Albuquerque to pay $5M to settle lawsuit in police shooting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 01:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A right-wing radical group says all refugees entering Hungary illegally should be deported for reasons of national security and says it will hold anti-immigrant protests at refugee camps and along the border with Serbia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 20:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lebanese militia group Hezbollah said on Friday that the Syrian army's resistance to recent large-scale rebel attacks had disproved predictions that President Bashar al-Assad's days were numbered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 20:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders Is Taking Back One Of The GOPs Favorite Insults </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 19:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Permanently Protects More Than One Million Acres Of Public Lands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 19:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Obama designated three new national monuments, permanently protecting more than one million acres of public lands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 19:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Human rights groups call for inquiry into why GCHQ spied on Amnesty: Letter to Guardian from Amnesty, Liberty and Privacy International follows revelation from Investigatory Powers Tribunal about UK monitoring agency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 19:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis on Thursday urged the downtrodden to change the world economic order, denouncing a "new colonialism" by agencies that impose austerity programs and calling for the poor to have the "sacred rights" of labor, lodging and land </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 04:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. regulators on Thursday took DuPont to task for a massive gas leak last year that killed four workers at a plant in Texas, placing the chemical company in its "severe violator enforcement program" and saying the accident shows it has a "failed safety program" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 04:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. regulators on Thursday took DuPont to task for a massive gas leak last year that killed four workers at a plant in Texas, placing the chemical company in its "severe violator enforcement program" and saying the accident shows it has a "failed safety program" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 04:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Utah hunter who killed the first gray wolf seen near the Grand Canyon in seven decades won't face criminal charges because he thought he was shooting a coyote, U.S. Fish and Wildlife announced Thursday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 04:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Utah hunter who killed the first gray wolf seen near the Grand Canyon in seven decades won't face criminal charges because he thought he was shooting a coyote, U.S. Fish and Wildlife announced Thursday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 04:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Puerto Rico's Debt Levels Compare With Those of U.S. States: These charts help explain why Governor Alejandro Garcia Padilla called the island's debt "not payable" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the FBI Wants "Special Access" to Your Smartphone: And why security experts warn that this is a terrible idea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Court Decision Aside, Lethal Injection Looks Increasingly Unsustainable: Pharma companiesand maybe, eventually, the Supreme Courtwill ensure that it only becomes harder to execute people with drugs in America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Republican-controlled House scrapped a vote on permitting the Confederate flag at Park Service-run cemeteries on Thursday, a retreat under fire that only escalated a ferocious attack by Democrats complaining the banner celebrates a murderous, racist past </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Republican-controlled House scrapped a vote on permitting the Confederate flag at Park Service-run cemeteries on Thursday, a retreat under fire that only escalated a ferocious attack by Democrats complaining the banner celebrates a murderous, racist past </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN investigates claims Sanjay Gupta misled viewers in Nepal report: Report disputes facts surrounding the networks star correspondents emergency medical intervention on an earthquake victim in April </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 04:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first statewide police body-cam law comes with a major caveat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 03:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first statewide police body-cam law comes with a major caveat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 03:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first statewide police body-cam law comes with a major caveat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 03:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Your Child Coloring with Asbestos? Cancer-causing asbestos fibers were found in several childrens crayon brands and a couple crime kits, all sold in the U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 03:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Your Child Coloring with Asbestos? Cancer-causing asbestos fibers were found in several childrens crayon brands and a couple crime kits, all sold in the U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 03:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nuclear weapons lab lobbied with federal funds to block competition for lucrative contract: Report peels back part of the veil surrounding a defense corporations capture strategy for the Obama administration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 03:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 01:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Auschwitz remains as a reminder of Nazi war crimes not as a tribute to their regime or politics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kenyan Leaders To Obama: We'll Throw Rotten Eggs At You If You Talk About LGBT Rights Here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 01:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal law enforcement officials warned Wednesday that data encryption is making it harder to hunt for pedophiles and terror suspects, telling senators that consumers' right to privacy is not absolute and must be weighed against public-safety interests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 00:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JPMorgan Chase will pay $136 million to settle charges that it used illegal tactics to go after delinquent credit card borrowers, the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau announced </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 00:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attorneys in federal cases stemming from crimes on American Indian reservations have new guidance on what's needed to prove a defendant is Indian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 00:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 00:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't find swastika flags in German national cemeteries. History doesn't mean you have the right to offend the majority of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exxon knew of climate change in 1981, email says  but it funded deniers for 27 more years: A climate expert with the oil firm for 30 years, shows concerns over high presence of carbon dioxide in enormous gas field in south-east Asia factored into decision not to tap it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 00:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wolves and Monkeys: Unusual Hunting Buddies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 23:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A French court has suspended a ballot by the far-right Front National party on whether to expel its honorary president, Jean-Marie Le Pen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 20:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EPA Slams House Republicans For Trying To Gut Environmental Protections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 19:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The House has voted to ban the display of Confederate flags at historic federal cemeteries in the deep South </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The House has voted to ban the display of Confederate flags at historic federal cemeteries in the deep South </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Louisiana Justice Refuses To Obey Supreme Court, Writes Opinion Implying Gay People Rape Their Children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Louisiana Justice Refuses To Obey Supreme Court, Writes Opinion Implying Gay People Rape Their Children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkmenistan's oil and gas ministry has accused Russian state gas company Gazprom of failing to pay for deliveries in a sign of friction between the two major gas producers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia has vetoed a U.N. resolution that would have condemned the 1995 massacre at Srebrenica during the Bosnian war as a "crime of genocide" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Decoding the brain: Scientists redefine and measure single-neuron signal-to-noise ratio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Decoding the brain: Scientists redefine and measure single-neuron signal-to-noise ratio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside the GOPs Effort to Close the Campaign-Science Gap With Democrats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First female nominee fails to win seat on Afghan supreme court: Conservatives attacked nomination of Anisa Rassouli, with one MP objecting on grounds that menstruating women were not allowed to touch Quran </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 16:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women less likely to be shown ads for high-paid jobs on Google, study shows: Automated testing and analysis of companys advertising system reveals male job seekers are shown far more adverts for high-paying executive jobs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 16:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women less likely to be shown ads for high-paid jobs on Google, study shows: Automated testing and analysis of companys advertising system reveals male job seekers are shown far more adverts for high-paying executive jobs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 16:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Bernie Sanders really a socialist? Or just redefining socialism for America? The Democratic candidate describes himself as one, but it can be hard to detect the traditional hallmarks of socialism at his increasingly popular rallies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 16:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a potential blow to President Mahmoud Abbas, a Palestinian appeals court ruled on Wednesday in favor of maintaining parliamentary immunity for his rival Mohammed Dahlan, who has been charged with corruption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 16:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colombia's largest guerrilla army is declaring a monthlong, unilateral cease-fire. The Revolutionary Armed Forces of Colombia says in a statement that it will halt hostilities as of July 20 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 16:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mapping drought's impact on electricity generation: Natural gas, wind and solar fill some of the hydropower deficit in California </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 04:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tiny sponge fossil predates the Cambrian explosion: The finding questions accuracy of long-standing evolutionary theory, paleontologists say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 03:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tiny sponge fossil predates the Cambrian explosion: The finding questions accuracy of long-standing evolutionary theory, paleontologists say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 03:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A federal appeals court on Tuesday kept alive a legal challenge brought by former students who sued Arizona over a ban on ethnic studies in public schools and who will have a new chance to argue the law discriminates against Mexican Americans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 03:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A federal appeals court on Tuesday kept alive a legal challenge brought by former students who sued Arizona over a ban on ethnic studies in public schools and who will have a new chance to argue the law discriminates against Mexican Americans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 03:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A massive sheet of rock fell from the vertical face of Half Dome in Yosemite National Park, making one of the most popular routes attempted by climbers in North America even more challenging </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 02:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A massive sheet of rock fell from the vertical face of Half Dome in Yosemite National Park, making one of the most popular routes attempted by climbers in North America even more challenging </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 02:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton, whose admitted violations of state securities laws will go before a grand jury this month, has also figured in a federal investigation of a Dallas-area technology company suspected of defrauding investors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 01:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton, whose admitted violations of state securities laws will go before a grand jury this month, has also figured in a federal investigation of a Dallas-area technology company suspected of defrauding investors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 01:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 01:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is original reporting from TPM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After days of dodging questions about whether Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker (R) was involved in a failed proposal to dismantle the state's open records law, the governor's office confirmed Tuesday that his office was involved in the measure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 01:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Survival of endangered African penguin chicks increased by 18% following a trial three-year fishery closure around Robben Island in South Africa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 01:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is The U.S. Better At Womens Soccer Than It Is At Gender Equality? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 01:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going for as much as $4 per ounce, breast milk is a hot commodity that is emerging as a surprisingly cutthroat industry, one that states are seeking to regulate amid a battle for control between nonprofit and for-profit banks that supply hospital neonatal units </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio Gov. John Kasich said Tuesday it's too early to worry about whether Donald Trump might bump him from the first GOP presidential debate if Kasich decides to run </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Temperature a dominant influence on bird diversity loss in Mexico </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Temperature a dominant influence on bird diversity loss in Mexico </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video: This town has been on fire for 50 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greenland Experiences Sudden Onset of Melt Season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greenland Experiences Sudden Onset of Melt Season: Two maps show Greenland's sudden, rapid meltdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WHO incapable of reacting to crises such as Ebola, says report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United States said on Tuesday it was falling far behind plans to build a Syrian opposition force to battle Islamic State, disclosing that just 60 fighters were in training after U.S. vetting thinned the number of recruits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fellow Republicans have stopped GOP presidential candidate Sen. Lindsey Graham from using an annual foreign aid funding bill to block work on a U.S. Embassy in Cuba </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fellow Republicans have stopped GOP presidential candidate Sen. Lindsey Graham from using an annual foreign aid funding bill to block work on a U.S. Embassy in Cuba </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A support ship in Royal Dutch Shell's plans to drill in the Arctic this summer has returned to port after a hole was found in its hull </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A federal appeals court on Tuesday upheld a ban on government contractors donating money to federal candidates or political parties, a prohibition that has been on the books for 70 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A federal appeals court on Tuesday upheld a ban on government contractors donating money to federal candidates or political parties, a prohibition that has been on the books for 70 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Government-backed experts say former Guatemalan dictator Jose Efrain Rios Montt is mentally incompetent, potentially derailing a trial on human rights charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 05:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gee how open minded of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Negotiations between Lufthansa and unions collapse: Recent talks between German flagship carrier Lufthansa and various labor unions have collapsed. In the absence of a settlement, strike action may follow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 05:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Negotiations between Lufthansa and unions collapse: Recent talks between German flagship carrier Lufthansa and various labor unions have collapsed. In the absence of a settlement, strike action may follow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 05:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supercharged Tuberculosis, Made in India: A patient with extensively drug-resistant TB flew from Mumbai to Chicago, and the deadly disease could become an infamous export due to problems in India's public health system </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 04:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Africa's Congo Could Lose Vast Forests: The Democratic Republic of the Congo needs aggressive protections against foreign investors who want to turn the second-largest forest stock on Earth into farmland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 04:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why "Color Cures" for Mental Illness Endure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 04:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro on Monday said he was calling in the country's ambassador in neighboring Guyana for consultations amid an escalating row over oil exploration in a disputed offshore territory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, for making Jindal sympathetic by making a racist comment./s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calling income inequality "the great moral issue of our time," Democratic presidential candidate Bernie Sanders urged a boisterous crowd of thousands in Maine on Monday to help him transform America by restoring a thriving middle class </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abnormally warm ocean temperatures are creating conditions that threaten to kill coral across the equatorial Pacific, north Pacific and western Atlantic oceans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker Tries To Use A Back Door To Get Rid Of Wisconsin's Living Wage Law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 02:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Walker Tries To Use A Back Door To Get Rid Of Wisconsin's Living Wage Law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 02:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Louisiana Gov. Bobby Jindal is suggesting Jeb Bush is out of step with Republican principles in the party's presidential race </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 02:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After 44 years, halting progress on workplace disease: OSHA has made limited headway against substances that sicken and kill America's workers; the agency's stormy history helps explain why </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 01:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After 44 years, halting progress on workplace disease: OSHA has made limited headway against substances that sicken and kill America's workers; the agency's stormy history helps explain why </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 01:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI Director James Comey called Monday for public debate on the use of encrypted communications, saying Americans may not realize how radical groups and criminals are using the technology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI Director James Comey called Monday for public debate on the use of encrypted communications, saying Americans may not realize how radical groups and criminals are using the technology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transparency Program Obscures Pharma Payments to Nurses, Physician Assistants: New data on drug and device company payments to doctors largely excludes nurse practitioners and physician assistants, though they play an ever-larger role in health care. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Studying brain scans and cerebrospinal fluid of healthy adults, scientists have shown that changes in key biomarkers of Alzheimer's disease during midlife may help identify those who will develop dementia years later, according to new research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Studying brain scans and cerebrospinal fluid of healthy adults, scientists have shown that changes in key biomarkers of Alzheimer's disease during midlife may help identify those who will develop dementia years later, according to new research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump is doubling down on his description of Mexican immigrants as criminals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump is doubling down on his description of Mexican immigrants as criminals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secretary-General Ban Ki-moon says an independent review of the 1961 plane crash that killed U.N. Secretary-General Dag Hammarskjold puts to rest claims that he was assassinated after surviving the crash but leaves many questions unanswered about a possible aerial attack or other interference </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 18:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some White House Republican hopefuls want curbs on legal immigration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 18:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican 2016 presidential hopefuls Scott Walker and Rick Santorum are suggesting a potentially controversial way to boost Americans' job prospects: admit fewer legal immigrants into the United States </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 18:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astronomers proposed a novel explanation Monday for the strange appearance of the comet carrying Europe's robot probe Philae through outer space: alien microscopic life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 18:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patients of a Detroit-area doctor received "stunning" doses of a powerful, expensive drug, exposing them to life-threatening infections, an expert testified Monday as a judge heard details about a cancer specialist who fleeced insurance companies and harmed hundreds of people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 18:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patients of a Detroit-area doctor received "stunning" doses of a powerful, expensive drug, exposing them to life-threatening infections, an expert testified Monday as a judge heard details about a cancer specialist who fleeced insurance companies and harmed hundreds of people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 18:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mass shootings begat mass shootings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 17:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A molecule that accumulates in the blood with age may be linked to cognitive decline, said scientists Monday who mooted hopes of a memory-restoring treatment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 17:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A molecule that accumulates in the blood with age may be linked to cognitive decline, said scientists Monday who mooted hopes of a memory-restoring treatment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 17:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hungary's parliament on Monday approved amendments tightening the country's asylum system. The plan, sharply criticized by the U.N.'s refugee agency, was approved by lawmakers from the governing Fidesz party, its Christian Democrat allies and the far-right Jobbik party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 17:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perry joins Donald Trump critics as Santorum praises focus on immigration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 05:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gun-shaped iPhone cases: an accident waiting to happen? Online retailers have reportedly been selling iPhone cases shaped like guns. The police response has been overwhelmingly critical </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 04:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Egypt journalists face jail for reporting non-government terrorism statistics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 03:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State suicide bombers and fighters attacked the center of Iraq's northern oil refinery town of Baiji overnight, forcing the army and Shi'ite fighters to pull back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 21:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Turkish army has called a meeting of troop commanders stationed along its fortified border with Syria to discuss a possible intervention in Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 21:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colombian authorities will this month begin the grisly task of carrying out what could be the largest exhumation of unmarked graves in the conflict-torn country's history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 21:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington state is under a federal court order to fix hundreds of barriers built under state roads and highways that block access for migrating salmon and thus interfere with Washington tribes' treaty-backed right to catch fish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 20:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington state is under a federal court order to fix hundreds of barriers built under state roads and highways that block access for migrating salmon and thus interfere with Washington tribes' treaty-backed right to catch fish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 20:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A hilarious Monty Python sketch helps explain why Greece is in a huge crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 20:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A hilarious Monty Python sketch helps explain why Greece is in a huge crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 20:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arizona prison hit with 3rd disturbance by inmates in 4 days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 04:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malaysias Attorney-General said a special task force investigating state investment company 1Malaysia Development Bhd. obtained documents in its probe related to alleged transfers of funds into Prime Minister Najib Razaks bank accounts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 04:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a sudden reversal amid a stinging backlash, Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker and GOP legislative leaders said they agreed Saturday to completely remove a part of the proposed state budget that would severely roll back open records laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 01:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a sudden reversal amid a stinging backlash, Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker and GOP legislative leaders said they agreed Saturday to completely remove a part of the proposed state budget that would severely roll back open records laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 01:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a sudden reversal amid a stinging backlash, Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker and GOP legislative leaders said they agreed Saturday to completely remove a part of the proposed state budget that would severely roll back open records laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 01:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The president of the Serb-run part of Bosnia claimed Saturday that the Srebrenica genocide was a "lie", a week ahead the 20th anniversary of the slaughter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 22:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkish nationalists protesting China's treatment of ethnic Uighur Muslims attacked a group of Korean tourists in the heart of Istanbul's old city on Saturday, mistaking them for Chinese nationals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 22:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tens of thousands Hondurans poured onto the streets of the capital Tegucigalpa on Friday to demand the resignation of President Juan Orlando Hernandez in the biggest demonstration yet against the country's leader over allegations of corruption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 05:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans have no shame. They claim hypocrisy at every chance and never admit they are the hypocrites.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mass arrests in The Hague as clashes over death in police custody continue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Enjoy your ride': Baltimore police check vans after photos show sign inside -- Officials launch internal investigation after message appears in vehicle images on Facebook following death of Freddie Gray in custody </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yemen's dominant Houthi group and its army allies said on Saturday it had shelled various areas in Saudi Arabia's Jizan and Najran, killing and wounding several soldiers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veteran far-right French politician Jean-Marie Le Pen announced Friday he is taking legal action in a bid to prevent the National Front (FN), the far-right party he founded, from changing its statutes and scrapping his post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opposition mounted Friday to a surprise Republican budget measure that would exempt from Wisconsin open records laws nearly everything created by state and local government officials, including drafts of legislation and communications with staff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opposition mounted Friday to a surprise Republican budget measure that would exempt from Wisconsin open records laws nearly everything created by state and local government officials, including drafts of legislation and communications with staff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opposition mounted Friday to a surprise Republican budget measure that would exempt from Wisconsin open records laws nearly everything created by state and local government officials, including drafts of legislation and communications with staff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oil and natural gas fracking, on average, uses more than 28 times the water it did 15 years ago, gulping up to 9.6 million gallons of water per well and putting farming and drinking sources at risk in arid states, especially during drought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 22:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The month of June saw 677 murders in El Salvador, more than in any other single month since the end of the country's civil war </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 22:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Sen. Mike Enzi has introduced a constitutional amendment to redistribute power from the federal government to the states </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 22:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clashes with police erupt as rival rallies begin in Athens: Dozens of young protestors engaged in a violent scuffle with police ahead of competing "no" and "yes" rallies in Athens. Sunday's bailout referendum will go ahead as planned after a legal bid to stop it was rejected </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 22:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State group militants have destroyed six archaeological pieces from the historic town of Palmyra that were confiscated from a smuggler, the group said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 22:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is It Time to Start Shutting Down Law Schools? No one wants to go to law school, yet new ones keep popping up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 22:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Erosion is eating away at Alaska's northern coast at some of the highest rates in the nation, threatening habitat and infrastructure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 22:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rosetta spacecraft spots enormous sinkholes on comet 67P </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 22:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany appoints senior judge to inspect list of NSA targets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 22:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 10 Most Underrated Law Schools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 04:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hidden China Stock Debt Revealed in Online Loans at 22% Interest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 04:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Officials say firefighters are trying to extinguish a blaze at a prominent black church in South Carolina </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 04:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Officials say firefighters are trying to extinguish a blaze at a prominent black church in South Carolina </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 04:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Honduran authorities have issued an arrest warrant for federal lawmaker and Congress vice-president Lena Gutierrez, along with 15 other people accused of defrauding the country's health ministry, the head of the supreme court said on Tuesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 04:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 03:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elected officials can not be fired. They can be impeached or removed for cause. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Obama administration dealt a setback to Royal Dutch Shell's Arctic oil exploration plans on Tuesday, saying established walrus and polar bear protections prevent the company from drilling with two rigs simultaneously at close range, as it had planned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 03:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Obama administration dealt a setback to Royal Dutch Shell's Arctic oil exploration plans on Tuesday, saying established walrus and polar bear protections prevent the company from drilling with two rigs simultaneously at close range, as it had planned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 03:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost a third of American adults own a gun, but the rate varies widely by state and tops out at almost 62 percent of people in Alaska, new survey data show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 03:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pink salmon are providing researchers with sobering hints to how carbon dioxide-induced acidity could affect freshwater fish species by the end of the 21st century </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 03:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report examines rise in right-wing murders in Brandenburg: A report has found that the state of Brandenburg has witnessed twice as many right-wing deaths than previously assumed. Politicians have deemed the trend "shameful" as Germany awaits 450,000 asylum seekers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 03:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brazilian police assumed control over one of Rio's most dangerous neighborhoods Tuesday, replacing the army in a key test for how to suppress crime ahead of next year's Olympic Games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 02:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brazilian police assumed control over one of Rio's most dangerous neighborhoods Tuesday, replacing the army in a key test for how to suppress crime ahead of next year's Olympic Games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 02:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rally in Madrid against law on right to protest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 02:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Puerto Rico's financial future hung in limbo Tuesday as economists and officials warned that the U.S. territory could head down Greece's path if it is not allowed to declare bankruptcy as it struggles with $72 billion in public debt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 02:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Environmentalists Tuesday called on California Gov. Jerry Brown to halt plans for months of hydraulic fracturing in the waters off Southern California, warning that it could lead to chemical pollution or an oil spill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 02:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A federal judge ruled Tuesday that a Maui County ban on the cultivation of genetically engineered crops is pre-empted by federal and state law and invalid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 02:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia's Rosneft charged over pipeline leak that caused oil to come out of taps: Environment watchdog investigates RN Yuganskneftegaz for water protection violations due to leak at Nefteyugansk that threatens to enter Ob river </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 22:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia's Rosneft charged over pipeline leak that caused oil to come out of taps: Environment watchdog investigates RN Yuganskneftegaz for water protection violations due to leak at Nefteyugansk that threatens to enter Ob river </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 22:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 22:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are at least [42 million people in this country who consider themselves at least part Black/African-American.](http://www.infoplease.com/us/statistics/us-population-by-race.html) This does not include others who are deeply opposed to the Confederate flag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously you don't care but tens of millions of people care deeply about removing this symbol of racism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The GOP May Regret Its Lasting Battle Against Gay Marriage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The US Justice Department on Tuesday moved to seize $34 million from a senior Chad diplomat who it said took bribes from a Canadian oil company </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nepal presented a preliminary draft of its first republican constitution on Tuesday, but the country's top court has questioned the legality of the document that was rushed through after devastating earthquakes spurred politicians into action </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At Georgia's iconic Stone Mountain  where the Confederacy is enshrined in a giant bas-relief sculpture, the Ku Klux Klan once held notorious cross-burnings and large Confederate flags still wave prominently  officials are considering what to do about those flags </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At Georgia's iconic Stone Mountain  where the Confederacy is enshrined in a giant bas-relief sculpture, the Ku Klux Klan once held notorious cross-burnings and large Confederate flags still wave prominently  officials are considering what to do about those flags </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
