<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4484</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 22:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not, post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 22:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have to trust wikipedia, check the source, which is an optics center that deals exactly with satellite imaging:

"If a multispectral image consists of the three visual primary colour bands (red, green, blue), the three bands may be combined to produce a "true colour" image....In this way, the colours of the resulting colour composite image resemble closely what would be observed by the human eyes. "

http://www.crisp.nus.edu.sg/~research/tutorial/opt_int.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 19:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It does not mean that the the colors and saturation are how you would "truly" see them with your eye.

You sure? It's how wikipedia defines it:

"This means that the colors of an object in an image appear to a human observer the same way as if this observer were to directly view the object"

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/False_color#True_color </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 18:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I believe that particular image that referenced (this one [RES ignored duplicate link]) is actually fake.

It's not really "fake", it's just a composite image where they picked the best satellite images and stitched them together. According to NASA, it's even true-color.

Source: http://visibleearth.nasa.gov/view.php?id=57723 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 18:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's a good picture to scale](http://i.imgur.com/ruUcaID.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 18:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, Stephen went the extra mile with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 18:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are basically the main characters for most of the book, but yes, I guess they are difficult names. What I mean is that it's a pretty superficial question covered in the first few pages, which was probably all he read to come up with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 18:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure that question is covered about 5 pages into the book, he sure didn't put a lot of effort into this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 20:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These were previously at a zoo in Europe, but they weren't breeding so it was decided to move them back to their natural habitat to see if that would get the breeding going.

There's an episode of a show called Last Chance to See (also a great book by Douglas Adams) with Stephen Fry that explains and shows the move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 14:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it a porpoise? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 14:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is some truth to that, the math that determined catch rates in gen 1 sometimes favored great balls over ultras.


[
"Under certain situations, a Great Ball is more effective than an Ultra Ball. In particular, Pokmon with high catch rates, no status, and above  HP may guarantee capture with a Great Ball but fail to do so with an Ultra Ball. "](http://bulbapedia.bulbagarden.net/wiki/Catch_rate) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
