<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8834</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 01:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And any one of you would do the same exact thing given his situation. Akron Beacon Journal, or ESPN? Please tell me you wouldn't. I don't blame him one bit. If you can forgive LBJ, then you shouldn't hate Windhorst at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 21:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did he actually say? Anyone have a link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 02:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a post that Broussard made earlier that has since been deleted that said LeBron was going to Cleveland. Wish I would've screen grabbed it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 01:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was multiple posts from Broussard and @Probballdraft that have since been removed. Wonder why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 19:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is dialogue between Garen and Darius. I know that much at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 17:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No need to be an ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [W] Invite to Torrentleech. Former member who's account was deleted due to inactivity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 04:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to have an account at Torrentleech from back in 2008 and had it all the way up until last year when after a few months of inactivity got it deleted. If anyone has an extra invite to spare I would forever be in your debt. Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 17:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've actually had it happen to me only once, and it was $20 after making a withdrawal from the bank. They must've realized their mistake because it was taking out of my account a day later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 14:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did not expect to hear anything about the vestibule for the rest of my life. That place ate up a lot of my time when I was a teenager.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 06:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ben Tate is also a Cleveland Brown now. Can't discount that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 16:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was talking about Vi, not Yi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 02:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long does it usually take for them to finish? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 23:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason your link isn't working for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 21:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I missing something, because I thought the WiiU wasn't doing very well as of right now. I am the only one I know that has one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 22:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vi, Garen, Pantheon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 23:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like OP delivered  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 19:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not really </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 18:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was how I felt the entire last week when I was reading Words of Radiance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the Entire Human Population Died off Tomorrow, Would Chimpanzees Eventually Evolve to Become Human Again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 05:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 18:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serenity  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 04:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope this is the case. It was probably my favorite part about Dark Souls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 04:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure it was sarcasm, but I could be wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 09:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just kicked me out in the middle of champ select. Hopefully the downtime isn't too long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-12 02:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he was a sociopath I don't think he would care enough to lie to them about it though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 13:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we are talking about both next gen consoles, I was actually pleasantly surprised by Dead Rising 3 as well. I put a lot of time into that game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 14:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see nothing wrong with this picture. Also, your boyfriend looks like a skinny/hairy version of Ryan Gosling. Also, I hate cats. That is all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 14:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stardust is a pretty good one to watch in almost any situation. Also, the Star Trek (2009) remake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 18:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that spreading it across the menu is a better idea. I was just stating that raising the price of one burger on the menu is not a good indicator of how to compensate for the raise increase.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 18:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am for raising the minimum wage, but I don't like this argument either. By raising the cost of the Big Mac $1.28 on top of what it already is, you cannot expect the same amount of people to buy it. Then, you would have to raise the price of other items to compensate even more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is Your Thoughts on the Polk TSi Series? (New AV setup) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 21:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everyone; first post here. I recently purchased a home theater setup and was looking for some feedback. Haven't even installed everything yet. 

* Center: Polk CS10
* Front: Polk TSi300 Floorstanding
* Surround: Polk TSi100 Bookshelf
* Sub: BIC America F12
* Receiver: Harmon Kardon AVR1700

I just noticed this sub today, and was looking to make sure I made the right choices. Any help at all is appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 15:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am confused as to why this is funny? Help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 15:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am still undecided between the SC-2010 and the Remington R5. I'm glad to see though that the grip actually does something in this game though compared to previous ones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 18:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of dog is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 16:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless this is offset by a reduced retail price, I will most likely not be getting this game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 21:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone got video?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 17:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...what thread? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-27 16:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Allahu akbar"

A lot of people would flip their shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 21:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gone in Sixty Seconds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 17:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get that line from the show Castle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 18:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would hold onto the last two, but the first one would be right before I played the lottery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-02 15:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Followed and liked. Would be nice as I was actually planning on not renewing my XBL sub this year. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-02 05:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snoop, you ever try Molly? If so, are you sweating? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 14:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had an original Wii that had a bad video chip, and the screen started pixelating. Nintendo sent me a new one out no questions asked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 06:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one who thinks $28-$30 for a tank top is pretty ridiculous?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 20:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> World War 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
