<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9737</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 02:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you! :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, maybe you should see things from her perspective bro   stop looking into things so much. I got the impression you just want to control the relationship, not fix it.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahaha that was perfect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 05:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Important dates to Remember: 
First black president's date of inauguration: uhh...
Gay rights: June 26th 2015
Says a lot about this country </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 05:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mm.. Nothing like a visually pleasing graph. This sounds super racist but actually I'm referring to the pleasant color tones! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 05:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 05:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No wonder why it took years to colorize this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The six letter F-word.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dude. Break dancing goblins in 1901. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 04:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 06:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Singing, dancing, and yes, acting out, the opening scene in Kingdom Hearts 1.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 21:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start researching the place you're going, what you will want to do there, and always keep in mind what season you will be traveling in. At first do a lot of general research and then do the nitty gritty: how are you going to get to point A to B, B to C, etc.? Food expenses? If you choose to travel with a tour group, hotel costs and meals may be included. Try looking up various routes to your destination via different airports in your area. Sometimes, this can save you a lot of money. Borrow luggage from someone to also save money... And lastly, consider a companion   a great camera.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
