<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject6381</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got to use my cast iron skillet for the first time last night, made rosemary chicken with baby russet potatoes and cremini mushrooms! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 13:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I always check this subreddit and admire the shape the girls are in, I'm not exactly where I want to be yet, but I feel I'm at a point where I can share! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 10:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian woman abandons the anti-vax movement after all 7 of her kids get whooping cough </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 18:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Balsamic glazed salmon peppered with freshly chopped oregano, on top of oven roasted baby potatoes and butternut squash! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 14:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 22:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I have relevant story for this! He actually did do competitive swimming for almost 10 years and he was quite good. The toe of course was no actual help with his swimming, essentially negligible. 

Well at one of the competitions he was in, one of the other swimmers noticed his freaky little toe and ran to the official and insisted it was cheating and he should be allowed to participate with an "advantage" like that. Official walked over and looked at his one connected toe and laugh, basically told the kid to shut up and that it was in no way an actual advantage haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 22:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if I do it, I'll be sure to provide pics of the process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 22:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly what I think of!! I loved commander keep! Still run it on a Dos simulator from time to time :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 22:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> his mom had the option of separating them at birth, the bones are completely separate it's just the skin that holds them together. But she thought it was "unique" and kept them joined hahaha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My boyfriend has two conjoined toes, sometimes I draw this little character on them when I'm bored. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 17:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 17:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care to see more of her, but the picture you posted is very clearly shopped. I don't know how you can't tell... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 05:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> be a use its clearly been edited, this is "realgirls" shopped pictures shouldn't be in here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 02:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work at a Tim Hortons and I've had customers complain to me about this several times. I agree that it is completely stupid to advertise their products on the menu board full of THEIR PRODUCTS, but I have had customers even yell at me regarding this. I feel like it's worth mentioning that we in store can't do anything about this. It's all down from corporate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 21:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "dat assss" - Florida man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a limit to the amount of sounds that your ears can "hear" at one time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 20:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a point at whixh you could be hearing so many noises at once that your brain couldn't process all of them? Would you lose sound quality at some point with your brain trying to process several sounds at once? And could you potentially have your hearing damaged this way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 19:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posted it, check my profile! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
