<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1885</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 19:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to think of it as sharing what I have to offer (   ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 19:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted this at like 3 am last night but thought more people would see it if I deleted and reposted during the day. So you're right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 17:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If fucking only. This was my friend's conversation actually, and he said the most they ever talked about was homework. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lol be my sperm donor lol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 17:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 05:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Nick! I was lucky enough to be in the audience in Bloomington, IN last month to hear you lay it to our governor for an hour and a half. I laughed/clapped my ass off. I've been trying to apply paddling my own canoe to my every day life. My friends and I actually waited in the lobby to try to get you to read part of a script we were working on. My question is, how can someone make an impact on people they don't know? How did you know cancelling your Indianapolis show would make as big of an impact as it did? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 19:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought of myself as a big macho scary movie fan until I watched the canal alone at 3 am. The final scenes had me with my blanket up to my eyes, which were as wide as they could be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 20:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prepare yourself. [Eric Wareheim's CREEPIEST music video.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aV7VNhzFLOQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 14:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay don't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spanish Book Snapchats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 05:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What my teacher wrote could be the grade and the number. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 21:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible for someone [19F] to become addicted to my [19M] orgasms? [3 months] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 18:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible for someone [19F] to be addicted to my [19M] orgasms? [3 months] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 09:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible for someone to become addicted to orgasms? (X-post from /r/sex) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 09:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible for someone to become addicted to orgasms? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 09:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 01:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if i'm both? por que no los dos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 06:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you scare the shit out of me as a child? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 22:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do I get rid of the virus on my computer?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 18:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think I'm stupid? Hostess had the blood buy back system implemented immediately after twinkies came back into business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 23:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll use your children's umbilical cords as straws as I drink your blood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who are at least semi-famous on a social network site, (ex. twitter, vine, instagram) how do you deal with the hundreds of replies directly to your phone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 19:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you finish the sentence, "If I've said it once, I've said it a million times, --"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 19:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you finish the sentence, "If I've said it once, I've said it a million times, --" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 19:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 18:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew what this was immediately, this is that weird egg movie where they fly logs like planes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 19:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Gordon, why didn't the duck cross the grill? He didn't want to be a roast duck. Also, how do you feel about using cream of potato in gravy for biscuits? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 02:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the summer off the coast of South Carolina, my father and I witnessed a red ball appear floating miles at sea from our condo balcony around 11:30 at night. Of course we thought it was a flare and wondered what we could do to help this lost ship, but the red ball remained visible for a few seconds until going out. About 15 minutes later, the same red ball appeared, then split into two floating balls out at sea. Have you ever heard anything like this before?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me peeing into the shower stream to hide the sound of me peeing in the shower has the same logic as money laundering </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 21:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 20:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eating biscuits and gravy covered in mustard changed the way i looked at both individually. Imagine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 01:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may or may not have went through a phase where I would create fake pizza coupons, then when the driver shows up i tip them and they don't know the company well enough to not accept it. I also created a bunch for drive throughs and would say i took an online survey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 20:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can already feel the welt from reeming my knee on a brass jawbone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 19:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no! It's "idle-glass-of-water girl!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spider-Man sounds like the perfect villain for Ant-Man if he didn't already exist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 19:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 21:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr. Nobody. I know sometimes when a movie is overly complicated just to be complicated it adds the feeling that the producing team is trying too hard, but with Mr Nobody I felt as though i was trying to solve a mystery called what the fuck is going on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 19:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you quit Franklin and Bash, besides the fact that every episode is essentially the same? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Things You Wish You'd Say To Your Ex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 19:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 09:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was eleven I wrapped my pecker in scotch tape, starting at the head and spiraling down. Once I got to the base and the now purple crooked toothpick was beginning to hurt, I knew mistakes had been made. So um, scotch tape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 00:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Riff Raff. I bought my girlfriend a ticket for her and myself to see him 2 Christmases ago, thinking he was funny in anything I'd seen him in. He had FOUR OPENERS, then I realized I thought he was funny because he was joking with his routine and lifestyle but when he came out and danced in his dumb clothes it wasn't a joke anymore. Plus he poured Croc into my underage girlfriend's mouth. Riff Raff if you're reading this I hate you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 19:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit! Now I have to clean my closet to look for them :c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a past fad you still stand behind? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 19:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 06:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On toga day of my senior year, a strange autistic kid asked me if togas were flammable. He then asked the teacher for a lighter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks, I wouldn't want to slip </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 01:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 01:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was it like going through that woodchipper? Were you okay?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 15:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rick and Morty season 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 21:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you know William "Bill" Robinson? He was my great grandfather from Indianapolis, and was also a Pearl Harbor surviver.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 04:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you know your city is a level in Sniper Elite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 21:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohai johnny, how did you get into making YouTube videos? Also what country are you from? Thanks, you're my favorite customer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 21:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to move shoes from one place to another, it looks like lifting shoes will be your only option </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 18:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If me creating an earth in my head and imagining life on that planet is the same as us existing, do the people I gave free will to in my brain fall out of existence as soon as I think of something else? Are we just waiting for someone to forget about us? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 20:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Working in the year 1 AD probably made this way less special  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 23:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why, what is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 20:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your arms fling up like a happy dandelion of love, good work pal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 16:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched her eat a plate of pretzels out of the bag with a little cup of ranch next to her to dunk them in. I had looking past her chubbiness until then. I'm shallow guys hi  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
