<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject4130</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 343 propaganda.

I'm sure it's so they can push their evil halo killing agenda on you through an app you don't even have to download. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 19:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally all friendly AI turns to God mode Dubbo's with scarab guns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 19:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even though i hate Jeb. I really don't trust anything from salon. They're the people that said burning cars and private property is a legitimate political strategy. They are the most unabashedly large liberal site I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 06:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's more than a legend... He's a...


*myth* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 04:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to assume it was posted because this kid was a fan of halo who was apart of a halo community and thus posted it a halo sub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 04:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good art. But I don't think that's how he'd look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 02:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never dyed!? Coulda fooled me damn I thought you had it blonde in one and red in the other, but after a second glance it was the lighting. Alright, I gotta ask. Who the fuck is Felipe?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 01:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anytime. Honestly I rarely comment on these at all. You have no reason to have low confidence. Just diet at a surplus, hit the gym, and then jaws hit the floor. You have great style too. You a natural redhead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 01:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure how to go about it. But it'll take a few discussions with the users and mods on this and other subs to come up with a gameplan to raise awareness. Movements are like a snowball; starts slow and small but if you keep pushing it, it grows and grows, then you don't have to push it anymore, and it gets faster and bigger as it rolls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 00:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ your probably the most gorgeous person I've seen on here. I don't say that often, and I never thought I would. You seem like a goddamn barbie doll. If you put on more weight you'd be a solid 11/10.

Damn. So on a scale of 1-10, you're a 9 and I'm the 1 you need...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 00:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's even an MS product. Shame really </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 00:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I'm aware, most of Bernie's support and notice came from Reddit being rabid about socialism. We need to do the same, and coordinate. 3k dedicated people is enough to get the same support for Rand. Only Rand has a legitimate chance at getting the nomination AND the presidency. We just need to gain the rabid internet support and the Facebook Republicans. We have a serious shot.

Coordinating officially with his campaign wouldn't hurt either. People just need a a little Rand spark. I'm willing to help coordinate and come up with a legit game plan, we can dominate social media for Republicans/libertarians similar to what Sanders is doing for liberals. It just depends on the willingness of those here to do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 23:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well they can do it forever. People might pass through there, but that company is created specifically for halo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now that The Halo Channel is on Android and iOS. Can we get remote file downloading, stats, and (H5) file share/browser access on mobile? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 23:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus, a reliable schedule of weekly content from both the community and 343? Also, mobile forum access would be GOAT. Mobile Beyond Entertainment forum access would be GOATier since they're pretty much the defacto competitive forum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 23:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Works great for me on mobile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 23:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Works great for me. Honestly it has a great set up, it's responsive, and works really well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 20:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to think this is the guy I saw on Sadik's Instagram today. His arms got so small with age
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Socialism and marxist ideologies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got them. You can workout normally, eating is the issue. And for me it's only because out hurts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 00:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the same thing happen. I strained my tricep doing skullcrushers, stopped working tri's but kept working everything else. Pain kind of went away but not fully.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's nice to see halo reach around here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 14:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank Mr skeltal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 04:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want a sexy calander </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 01:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a horrible comparison. Absolute trash. Just because the scenario isn't a starving child doesn't mean we can't feel bad for someone who has worked so hard on something for his idols to literally disapprove. 

What you're saying is just a stupid reason to dismiss what someone is going through. "Oh you lost a family member? There's starving kids in Africa, you shouldn't be sad". Or if a rich parent won't give approval or love to his son, "there's people worse off, get over it." Emotions are emotions and problems are problems. Just because someone somewhere is in a worse situation doesn't invalidate any other emotions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders is polling as well against Hillary Clinton as Barack Obama did in 2008. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 14:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is a good thing. There needs to be a check on what is usually unchecked. Directly by the people. 

This won't turn into the Tea Party challenging taxes every day because they simply won't have a case. But it will prevent the IRS and political leaders from abusing the IRS and targeting specific groups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 05:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realize what the northern army did right? They raped, pillaged, and destroyed the south, specifically on Sherman's March. The Union Army was in no way as "heroic" as the confederates other than the fact Lincoln freed slaves to weaken the south. 

Lee was an admirable man if you read up on him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 04:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the difference between /r/communism and/r/FULLCOMMUNISM? 

no this isn't the setup to a bad joke. I'm curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 04:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wtf does butterface even mean? Your fine. Like real fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 03:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. What? Capitalism has been around longer then communism, and outlasted communism in nearly every sense. Even China had to adopt capitalist ways to get where it's at economically. There is no sound argument for communism, please leave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 03:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chicago has the tightest gun laws in the US. His point is ridiculous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the first pic you look depressed, annoyed, and negative. No one wants to be around someone who won't give them good emotions, at the end of the day that's what interactions are about; making people feel good emotions and "vibes" about you. That pic screams "I'm a drag and no fun to be around" and has a salty vibe. It simply doesn't put good emotions into those who see it. Plus it's just a horrible selfie with bad lighting. T

he next one is generic with no personality whatsoever, and the other one makes you look feminine and desperate for attention. 

My advice: 

- smile or add personality without it. 

- get a buddy to take your pic in better lighting. Preferably when doing something fun that demonstrates high value where you can get a good face shot

- have a pic of you and your buds at the club, with some personality.

- spice up your bio with something a little less generic. Like it was said before, everyone is on Tinder to have fun. So put some legitimate things about yourself and a witty remark that will make you stand out from the thousands of other guys these girls see. They have more options than you do and are more selective. 

- maybe another more masculine pic with your pet. 

- just stand out, be fun and exciting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 19:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To clarify, the first pic compared to last pic is your progress? And what weight did you start at? Plus, what are your goals?

If so, and your goal of to get big and cut, yes, it's bad progress. Really bad. You may have defined out a bit, but you need to get significantly bigger so bulking is a must. It seems you don't have the diet in order at all. You need to eat at a large caloric surplus to gain weight and it doesn't look like you have been doing that. Simply just working out doesn't cut it, diet is just as vital as training. So I think you just need to her serious about your diet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 19:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do some lifting and get toned. Looking great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 17:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That really isn't a lot of progress for 3 years. You need to do a relatively clean bulk, and get on a lifting program. You should be about 190-200 by now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 17:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PEWPEWPEWBWAPBWAPBWAP.

MURICA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 07:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking commie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 06:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John Wayne makes that pic. But still needs more Reagan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 03:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greatest sci Fi universe ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 03:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This came first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 03:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sick shit bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 00:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, *nothing* stops the Chief when he wants to do something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 20:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Montages, machinima, map features and reviews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 15:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was gold </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 15:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ***SURRENDERTHATAI!!*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 19:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pics. Let's see that physique. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 04:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/dadbod </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 04:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an everyone wins mentality we put in by giving everyone a trophy
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gays Need the Freedom to Discriminate : Anything Peaceful : Foundation for Economic Education </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 06:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comments salty as shit. Damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 06:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. That's awesome, we have identical builds. Also very similar to my goals, I started a month ago, currently at 157, hope to be 220 in 3 years. How was your diet/training? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 05:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use bodyspace. Calculates everything, keeps track of workouts, and whatever program your on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 05:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hamplanet to hottie. Niccceeee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a lot of those men it wasn't about slavery, it was about fighting for their home and state. This mentality extended up to General Lee. Many felt they had no choice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 06:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But HEY! At least you didn't have to own land to vote! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 06:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He expanded the electorate substantially for the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both. This is pretty interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa. Do you have a sause? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full what he said

 Oh, yeah. Thats like getting hate mail from(Adolf) Hitler. Theyre literally terrible human beings. Ive read their newsletter, Ive visited their website, and theyre just rotten to the core. For an organization that prides itself on Christian values  I mean, Im an atheist, so what do I know?  they spend their entire day hating people. They can all suck my dick as far as Im concerned." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It won't. That was a cold blooded attack on innocents by people that despise us. Not a war between uniformed brothers that understood each other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lee wasn't even a slave owner. He didn't agree with slavery either, the only reason he fought for the CSA was because his loyalties were to his state and way of life over his nation. This was the case with the overwhelming majority of CSA soldiers who were only in the war to fight for their home and from foreign aggressors. My biggest fear with all of this is that we will begin to condemn the soldiers and their memorials along with the flag.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He isn't a good president. Neither was Bush, or Clinton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jackson has a pretty good rep and did a wonderful job. The only stain and huge wrongdoing being the Indian thing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 17:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can do that all you want. But until you can come up with logical reasoning, it means nothing. He is a frontrunner in key states whether fox wants to acknowledge it or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 16:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unions between people have always been a thing. But *marriage* has not, like I've said before **semantics**. His economic policies will work and I'm glad he'll be president. People will vote for him over Hillary if he gets the nomination. Just because someone doesn't want the government regulating marriage doesn't mean they're socially backwards. He's stated he wants the government out of people's lives in every way for a while now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 16:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He isn't. But I pay close attention to his ideas and what he says. It's a step in the right direction where basically anyone else in the Republican race is a step back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 16:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is a conservative but he isn't for unequal rights for people. But the institution of marriage has been around since before our government and has been a religious thing. It's *semantics*, marriage has been between a man and a woman and first defined that way by religion, the government just gave them benefits and prevented gays from having the same ones (bad). Paul just says gays should have the same rights, but it shouldn't be called marriage because that word implies sanction by god. Which gays *may* not have.

All in all, he wants the government totally out of it unless enforcement of the contracts so this issue wouldn't even be relevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 14:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a massive oversimplification of the last century. But in short, we've never had true free markets, there have always been a large element of government favoritism. 

The idea that it was hands off economics that led to the depression is a huge myth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 14:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they are equal rights. Marriage isn't a right defined in the constitution. It isn't a right to be regulated, registered, and defined by the government. It *was* a religious institution before it was a government one, and it was around before our government decided to regulate it. This is his point, he doesn't want to spite anybody. Paul has held you'd position for awhile now, you honestly think a libertarianesq like him wants to have his life regulated and registered by the government? Fuck no

Like I said before, he wanted to be married. The only way to do that was to actually get married. He's advocating for most of the benefits instead of taxes to be covered in a legal contract between two people without state intervention unless it's time for it to be enforced or annulled.

What you're essentially saying is equivalent to saying people can't support civil rights because they're white, or more accurately, proper immigration reform because they live comfortably in the US.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because people that had ran our country were deeply religious. I'm not trying to justify those laws, rather argue for them to be removed entirely and replaced with legal contacts. 

Religious people want the right to the word *marriage* and LGBT want equal benefit from the government in regard to the act of marriage. There's no reason one can't be called marriage and the other a civil union. You could argue that it's "separate but equal" but it's really not, it's legal semantics and that's it. And like it or not, marriage is a religious institution that's been around for millennia and has been defined as between a man and a woman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can be involved in the same way you'd enforce any other contract between two consenting adults, you don't need overarching regulations for that. A contract is basically a set of obligations and terms between parties enforced by the government, and marriage is better off that way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 06:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would have those things related to children, finances, death, and property covered in a contract without government interference. The only time the government would get involved is when the contact needs to be enforced or annulled.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 06:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a libertarian so I vehemently disagree with his economic positions so my vote goes to Rand. But I respect his integrity if that counts for anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 06:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not true at all. One can get married and enjoy the benefits and advocate for change. Why? Because the change he advocates for affects his marriage and would make the institution itself far better off. You can't blame him for taking advantage of the only way to get married, like literally everyone else. The  government doesn't need to be involved in everything. 

Your logic relies on the idea that he would want these benefits from the government at the time he got married even though he received them. He wanted to be married and committed to someone he loves, not the benefits that entails. We know this is true because his position has been constant and he's willing to make a change that affects his marriage here and now. He still says this at risk of losing christian GOP votes that he will need for the primary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 06:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is ridiculous. So straight married people aren't allowed to support equal rights to people? That is so stupid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 06:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neo-Cons mainly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 04:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humans. You just never know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 04:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except the Libertarian party or Sanders </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So he was canned for good reason. I mean what the above article said made him seem like a straight asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SIR. 

SIR Ian McKellen

Fucking casual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Famous words of Hillary Clinton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the type of guy that gives Republicans a bad name </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the II's have the XP. But I think physically they are on par </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'd be a toss up in a 1v1 equal everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 18:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. I need pics of your body, 220 lbs muscle puts you at absolutely ripped. Cover the tattoo, but please post before and after </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 02:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we get the story behind this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 02:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A. taking a picture of your nude underaged children.

Also, I really wish people would stop taking nude pictures of their kids..

I ran around nude in a cowboy outfit and rode a tricycle nude when I was about 3. My mom took a picture because I was being a funny and adorable toddler, I wasn't being sexualized, i turned out fine, and ended up with a funny picture. Stop demonizing a normal part of childhood. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 22:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. Did you listen to hunt the truth? The ending had me surprised as fuck, they totally played Ben  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 21:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You and Pepsi should team up and do am AMA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 21:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem like some reddit god. What the shit is up with you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out all of the Halo books. Fall of Reach and everything that follows is pretty phenomenal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The forerunners. Blinded and corrupted by a millennia of absolute power, yet so majestic and wise at the same time. The universe has real world allusions to things like NSA spying. I will never stop being entertained by that lore and universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 15:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is NICE. Do you do a muscle group split? I'm mirin your back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 15:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pics or didn't happen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 15:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't expecting that. Yeah I'd smash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 15:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't you just love when SJWs become so SJW that become racist bigots. It's like a circle, circle of Justice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 07:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Halo all the way. It's incredibly rich and lucrative, with deep lore. It will always be my first love. Second will be Doctor Who. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 00:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is dope. If I had money, I'd buy a copy. You're a great artist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 19:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's Johns last name? Or do glassed planets have bad records? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 06:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please be halo centric in many ways. I can't even imagine RT OE RvB without Halo undertones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 06:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to join as a libertarian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 00:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/govschwarzenegger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 01:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're probably right honestly. I just wanted to see what others have dealt with having been at it longer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 01:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO Calum is a modern day Arnold. So he is better, but Sadik still looks great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 07:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
