<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1529</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Slovenia turned itself around: Another Balkan country didnt need an EU bailout to get its crisis-ridden economy back on track. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Slovenia turned itself around: Another Balkan country didnt need an EU bailout to get its crisis-ridden economy back on track. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California Gov. Jerry Brown has approved legislation recognizing the states professional cheerleaders as employees who are entitled to minimum wage and overtime, following high-profile lawsuits alleging labor violations in California and elsewhere around the country. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 21:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good golly, brah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bush says never make nuclear deals with dictators. His brother and father both did. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama: $80 billion spent on incarceration could eliminate tuition at public universities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama: $80 billion spent on incarceration could eliminate tuition at public universities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Middle East Allies See Heightened Peril in Newly Empowered Tehran </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kids expecting aggression from others become aggressive themselves: Children taught to be vigilant for hostility from others are prone to aggressive behavior </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican leaders delayed a House vote Tuesday on a bill raising money for breast cancer research over anger that some of the funds would go to a group that has worked with the Planned Parenthood Federation of America, which supports abortion rights. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican leaders delayed a House vote Tuesday on a bill raising money for breast cancer research over anger that some of the funds would go to a group that has worked with the Planned Parenthood Federation of America, which supports abortion rights. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Numbers Behind Hillary Clintons Economic Vision </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The European Commission is frowning on Hungarys project to build a fence on its border with Serbia to quell a spike in refugee crossings, but doesnt plan to stop it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok so then explain to me what FWIW means? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 10:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know there was a stove business... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 21:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you should pop over to /r/gaybrosgonewild in that case...haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 06:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly ashamed this still goes on in a supposedly "civilized" Internet forum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 03:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What use are reading comprehension skills? The curtains are just fucking blue, why can't you people study something useful like STEM?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Jeb Bush has right  and terribly wrong  about worker productivity: Some workers need more hours, but that's partly because others are working too many. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 23:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Central Intelligence Agencys health professionals repeatedly criticized the agencys post-Sept. 11 interrogation program, but their protests were rebuffed by prominent outside psychologists who lent credibility to the program, according to a sweeping new report. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Central Intelligence Agencys health professionals repeatedly criticized the agencys post-Sept. 11 interrogation program, but their protests were rebuffed by prominent outside psychologists who lent credibility to the program, according to a sweeping new report. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philadelphia police investigate violent arrest after video of beating emerges: Video depicts as many as 26 officers kicking and punching Tyree Caroll, 22, who was initially stopped for riding his bike the wrong way down his street </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the second time this year, the House used overwhelming bipartisan unity Friday to approve health legislation, this time voting to bolster biomedical research and streamline how the government approves drugs and medical devices. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the second time this year, the House used overwhelming bipartisan unity Friday to approve health legislation, this time voting to bolster biomedical research and streamline how the government approves drugs and medical devices. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China and Russia Lay Foundation for Massive Economic Cooperation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China and Russia Lay Foundation for Massive Economic Cooperation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal Reserve chairwoman Janet Yellen has repeated her view that the central bank is likely to start raising interest rates this year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Senate introduced a bipartisan bill on Thursday that would prevent criminal prosecution as well as liability and asset forfeiture for banks that do business with a state-sanctioned marijuana business. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Immigrants who were detained at a suburban Denver facility while they awaited deportation proceedings are suing the private company that held them, alleging they were paid $1 a day to do janitorial work, sometimes under threat of solitary confinement. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German authorities are set to officially recognize as "genocide" the colonial-era crackdown in Namibia by German troops more than a century ago in which over 65,000 ethnic Hereros were killed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German authorities are set to officially recognize as "genocide" the colonial-era crackdown in Namibia by German troops more than a century ago in which over 65,000 ethnic Hereros were killed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bush's Super PAC announced Thursday that it raised over $103 million in the first half of this year  a massive haul that makes Bush's operation by far the best-funded of any presidential candidate, Republican or Democrat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bush's Super PAC announced Thursday that it raised over $103 million in the first half of this year  a massive haul that makes Bush's operation by far the best-funded of any presidential candidate, Republican or Democrat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge pushes to speed up release of force feeding videos at Guantnamo Bay: Judge Gladys Kessler accuses Obama administration of launching baseless legal challenges to delay court-ordered release of tapes showing shocking treatment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan Seeks To Export its New Sub-Hunting Plane: Tokyo has ambitions to become a global supplier of military hardware. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three Senate Republicans, including vulnerable incumbent Mark Kirk of Illinois, helped Democrats advance a repeal of the so-called global gag rule that restricts U.S. funding to humanitarian organizations that provide abortions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kremlin critics say a climate of fear is growing in Russia after the upper house of parliament drew up a list of "undesirable" civil rights organizations and two similar groups decided to close. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Morocco Is Running Out of Time: Unemployment and stagnation are fueling extremism  and the king's gradual reforms aren't cutting it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hackers stole Social Security numbers and other personal data for about 21.5 million people in breaches of the U.S. governments personnel office, the Obama administration said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bumblebees being crushed by climate change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia is top threat to national security, US general says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Florida's congressional districts rejected as gerrymandered: GOP accused of ignoring constitutional requirements approved by voters in 2010, possibly affecting 22 of 27 districts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Florida's congressional districts rejected as gerrymandered: GOP accused of ignoring constitutional requirements approved by voters in 2010, possibly affecting 22 of 27 districts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obamacare has saved women more than $1 billion on birth control </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two senior senators  one Republican, one Democrat  proposed on Wednesday that the government largely end the taxation of United States corporate profits overseas, but with a mandatory, one-time tax on such profits to pay for an expansive highway and infrastructure program. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baltimore police chief fired in wake of scathing report on Freddie Gray protests: The report cited evidence that Anthony Batts had instructed officers to refrain from arresting rioters involved in looting during the April demonstrations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study estimates the number of deaths that can be linked to differences in education, and finds that variation in the risk of death across education levels has widened considerably. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Delays in efforts to form a coalition government in Turkey are buying time for President Tayyip Erdogan, heightening the chances of a snap election which could see his AK Party regain its majority and leaving the opposition floundering. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crowdsourcing brain data with hundreds of adults in a short period of time could be a new frontier in neuroscience and lead to new insights about the brain, neuroscientists have shown. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. National Security Agency tapped phone calls involving German Chancellor Angela Merkel and her closest advisers for years and spied on the staff of her predecessors, WikiLeaks said on Wednesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. National Security Agency tapped phone calls involving German Chancellor Angela Merkel and her closest advisers for years and spied on the staff of her predecessors, WikiLeaks said on Wednesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton's campaign is telegraphing that it is "worried" about an insurgent Bernie Sanders. But should it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Right Way to Buoy Chinas Stock Markets: Rather than relying on its own companies to expand investments, China should welcome more foreigners. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
