<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject5015</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 01:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does this say there's 134 comments...http://gyazo.com/7cbb3af22d63e270350b215de138b47b </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 20:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta say I agree, on the fence because of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 18:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to keep a cool head at all. These men have had training, even the cop has been in life threatening situations before, and you can tell they're still visibly shaken by whats going on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 18:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was the first thing I realized, it looks almost like a painting edited in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 18:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't tell if you're baiting or just a college kid who thinks he's morally superior to everyone that's made a big mistake in their life. Either way, you're making some pretty huge assumptions from one video and an article. Then again this is Reddit, we do love making assumptions and judging people based on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 18:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought you were talking about the cop or the nurse since I didn't finish the video...i'm pretty slow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 21:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 01:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> +1 also been noticing bad AA after patch. had to turn on MSAA x2 and lose like 5 fps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 20:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 19:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is pretty off topic but does anyone know the default hotkey for the Quickplay Action? I've searched an searched but I can't find it in the keybindings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 06:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a power hungry control freak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's already hackers on GTA V Online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 20:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy http://socialclub.rockstargames.com/member/360madden?headSearch=true was in my online game today teleporting around and killing everyone with rocket launchers. Oh yeah and he was invincible. Just a heads up. Already submitted a ticket to R*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 04:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with simon on this one. He really grew on me by the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 20:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know why his account was shadow-banned/deleted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 20:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not an unpopular opinion, i'm not sure where you're getting that impression. Even though I did play with a level 6 for one of the heists who could communicate and play alright I still feel like a minimum level would be a good idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 20:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played with one friend for all the heists, finding two other randoms and for the majority of it I found people that could communicate or if they couldnt communicate they were usually still pretty alright at the game and could listen to instructions. Got all of the heists done this way. Maybe it's because im playing on the PC though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 20:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humane labs raid was really really fun too. Also enjoyed the stealth setup. Series A funding was definately the worst, just a bunch of missions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 00:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any idea how this happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NSFW?] I really can't tell if this is intentional or not. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 23:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 06:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hannibal Buress was only a guest on the show, which runs for 30 minutes, she could have come to watch the rest of it and just not found Hannibal funny. http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Russell_Howard's_Good_News </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PC][GMT] 2 people with microphones (preferably) or text chat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 22:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey,

Need 2 English speaking peeps to do some heists with. Me and my friend are on the last heist, have done the first setup. Much prefer it if you have a microphone and are willing to communicate, but text chat can work as well. 20/20/20/40 split.
We would be up for completing the last heist within the next few hours. Cheers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DONNIE DOES | Sneaking Into Hong Kong Sevens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 06:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 19:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His character is in an NPC corp so i guess he went on an alt? We were bashing a NC. r32/r64 because we didn't want to wait for HERO's leadershit to transfer it, one hour in divinerapier warps 100 off the POS. He burns around for about 30 seconds. 5 minutes later an NPC corp character lights a cyno off the pos and we get hotdropped by the NC. (we had a few dreads on field to speed it up). I remember people in HERO defending him too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 18:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If someone asks just say you're friends with the person. Don't draw attention to yourself and don't give away more information than necessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 15:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is DivineRapier confirmed as a spy yet? He's done some extremely shady shit in the past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 17:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Helium also has the same effect and is used for suicides, partially too because it's freely available (they sell it in cans for blowing up balloons). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 15:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Download from one site, upload to another. That's I think the easiest way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 16:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/Documentaries/comments/317g3n/escape_from_the_maze_2009_the_maze_prison_in/cpzx6pi?context=3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 15:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/trackers/wiki/rules

 3.OBVIOUS OR IMPLIED INVITE REQUESTS ARE NOT PERMITTED.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 19:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PGP

Do you think HERO has access to the PRISM metadata? I'm confused as to why you think you need that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 18:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 14:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you might still win the award for most hilarious warning though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 14:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice video although I wish people would stop cutting these off right when the enemy team reacts in all chat, that's my favorite part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 01:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only time my relatively small corp almost killed a Titan...too bad their ishtar fleet was just a few jumps out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 22:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was posted in an april fools prank thread a year or two ago (2), and someone that worked at a zoo basically replied saying that they get dozens every year, and that it's a huge waste of their limited resources. I felt bad after that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 17:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You will truly be remembered as a dank memer. *tip*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 17:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10/10 would read again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 19:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny, someone suggested something like this in the 'what niche private tracker communities would you like to see" thread, think it was top upvoted too. I would love to see something like this too! Would even be up for starting it but I really have 0 experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 01:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does it say month tradeban? I assumed tradebans are permanent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 19:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait don't dogs have really sensetive hair too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 19:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOOOOWWWW CAN HE SLAP!

OOOOWWWW, CAN HE SLAP!

ftfy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 19:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.bbcamerica.com/mind-the-gap/2013/09/26/british-dental-care-the-tooth-of-the-matter/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 19:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 9/11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 19:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let others determine your worth and you're already lost, because no one wants people worth more than themselves. 
 Peter V. Brett, The Warded Man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 18:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Zen master was asked what he would do if he knew the world was going to end in 30 minutes. He said meditate. Not contact his family, or try and stop it, just meditate. 

I of course being completely undisciplined and having no idea how to meditate would end up panicking and trying to stop it, and failing horribly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 18:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Journal of a Nazi soldier that didn't believe in/want to fight for the Nazi's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 17:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Destiny confirmed legit streamer and sensitive flower </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "You and I are all as much continuous..." - Alan Watts [1920x1080] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 20:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 19:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finger lickin' goodness! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 17:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're on a windows pc press windows key + r, type 'msconfig', go to the startup tab, uncheck what you don't want to startup, press apply, okay.

This is a pretty simple question too, not trying to be acidic but you could literally just google 'how to turn off startup programs for windows'.

Also if you're on a mac: http://www.maclife.com/article/howtos/how_remove_startup_items_os_x this was the first thing that turned up on google. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/Rathadin provides an in-depth explanation as to why blu-ray discs are not lossless, and why we will not be seeing lossless video for years to come. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 17:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/Rathadin provides an in-depth explanation as to why blu-ray discs are not lossless, and why we will not be seeing lossless video for years to come. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 16:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 03:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't tell if bullshitting. 99% possibility of cow shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont know if this is exactly what you're looking for but they say somewhat broadly what they defined as positivity and toxicness in their blog post, http://idibon.com/toxicity-in-reddit-communities-a-journey-to-the-darkest-depths-of-the-interwebs/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If i'm understanding it right, you guys are (very basically) good at processing large ammounts of text and offering very specific insights into it? I'm curious about the split between machine learning and human intervention, if you could provide some more information on that? How advanced the machine learning is and where the human has to step in, for example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you buy Skippy from there, is it reasonably priced? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "You are that vast thing that you see far, far off..." - Alan Watts [1280x582] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 23:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 17:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Practice is probably the most important thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 15:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That cat is so chill. My cat would be a million miles away the second I picked up the bag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 02:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I just wanted to thank you for posting this, used it in this composition: http://wattsquotes.tumblr.com/post/114543432379/you-are-that-vast-thing-that-you-see-far-far-off, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Reality is only a Rorschac ink-blot, you know." - Alan Watts [1280x720] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 21:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 07:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no words for the ammount of stupidity in your comment. He's made over 20 million dollars for charity, been on the BBC,CNN,WSJ etc.. He visited Liberia to raise awareness and funds for Ebola. If anyone's scamming anyone, it's you with that comment. http://www.savethechildren.org/site/c.8rKLIXMGIpI4E/b.9248995/k.7CEB/After_Ebola.htm http://www.charitynavigator.org/index.cfm?bay=search.summary orgid=4438

You don't have to like how he does it, but you cannot deny that he has a good heart and has probably saved thousands of lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 23:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You literally donate directly to save the children, only reason not to is if you don't have the cash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 22:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuck the haters #2legit2quit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 22:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's obviously fake but it's hilarious. It's even more hilarious watching people trying to 'share the truth', this is what Athene does, anyone that's followed him for long enough knows that. He's raised over 20 million dollars for save the children (http://www.savethechildren.org/site/c.8rKLIXMGIpI4E/b.8157995/k.7191/Athene_and_Gaming_for_Good.htm) You don't have to like how he does it, but you cannot deny that he has a good heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 17:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how he takes his paw off the cooler..."Can you fuckin' not" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 22:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is on the London Tube too which is why she's not looking directly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 20:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking Steven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 22:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you motivate yourself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 22:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome, cheers for the info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 19:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes anybody that has a sense of humor laugh. You evidently do not. I would much rather walk round a fence to get my keys than spend 30 minutes taking off buble wrap and styrofoam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 19:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you shed some light on how you don't get into shit for impersonating a cop? Don't some tourists go away thinking that the NYPD cops drink? I'm genuinely interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 18:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it's not the seedboxs fault then, either change provider or ask wcd to try and get cloudflare to unblock it (doubtful). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 23:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 23:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish there was a video for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 23:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to reddit, where everyone makes assumptions and then judges you based on them. It's how we caught the Boston bomber.... *cough*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 03:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it seems really dumb for him to call you something like that...people like drama way too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 02:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming from someone that's English, just don't call someone a child of a chap... or you might get punched... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 02:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From one of the top comments 'reasonable people don't like racist douchebags or what they have to say.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 02:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people think it's fake on every video like this that is posted. On videos like this though, it dosen't matter, the message stays the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 02:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peoples attention spans are getting lower and lower....it's the only way to get them to watch. On the other hand though I agree with you, I would much rather watch the raw footage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 02:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/GlobalOffensive/comments/2ze70l/if_anyone_got_some_teambiceps_drinks_from_pashas/cpi85u8

A mistake on the manufacturers part is always a lot more likely than some kid having access to a can sealer   label printer at home and putting a bloody worm in it to laugh on stream when he eats it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 02:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck...guess I shouldn't go to any stores or bars anymore before I get to know them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 02:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why assume that it was intentional/ill-willed? See the comments above, 99% of the time it's an accident on the part of the manufacturer, reddit fucking loves drama and it's stupid how little they examine a situation before discussing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 01:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Pascha calling him a terrorist was just a knee-jerk reaction to someone wearing a headscarf, probably a muslim/sikh or something like that. Reddit fucking loves drama, and they can ignore any and all assumptions just to eat it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 00:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So sexy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 20:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for doing this! Will send you one a bit later on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 18:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might seem like that but we can never really know because we don't have the raw footage availible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 16:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a jumper that I wear with a ferrari logo just because it's extremely comfortable....maybe don't judge everyone by the clothes they're wearing lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 15:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah. Announcer dude was actually my secondary school PE teacher....scariest PE teacher ever but also the nicest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 20:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last month reddit had 151,712,210 million unique pageviews...not quite the secret club some people think it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 19:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Video wasn't appearing for me until I turned off my adblock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 19:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could just ban people IRL I disagreed with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 21:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone transcribe this for me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 19:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I get that, the title just makes it seems like this is some sort of official thing. I thought it was common knowledge that you can find 99% of popular tv shows online for free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 18:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? This isn't its website, it's fan made and probably illegal. They would never just put all their episodes online for free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 19:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes yes, you are correct correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 14:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 13:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is pretty late.. but i'm wondering if you have any formal education in computer science/RE or if you're self taught? RE has always interested me but i'm not sure I would be able to get a formal education in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 03:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a real sheriffs car, they had the cop close by because obviously he couldnt just leave his vehicle there, see https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3yvQk0WF6eM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 03:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, just a video that has yet to be DMCA'd: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3yvQk0WF6eM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 19:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first thing they'll do when they see a crash is call for an ambulance... no need to waste an operators time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 11:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck is this AMA.  fucking brutal man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 07:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That ending. What the fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 05:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god i need a fit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bank (Rmi Gaillard) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 18:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 04:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has some inside info. RIP in pieces private trackers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 03:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me only if it's freeleech. My only reason for downloading one would be to watch something in my native 1920x1080, which is a big plus. I usually delete them after a week or so because they're so big. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 01:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shitty camera? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 01:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really good video, horrible title (youtube title, good job OP at changing it.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 21:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i3.kym-cdn.com/photos/images/original/000/738/036/b29.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 00:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On average they get 15 common colds a year, versus the 4 of an adult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 23:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of what you said plus a big factor for me is seed retention. If I find a movie on a public tracker that has little to no seeders I can almost gauranteed download it from a private tracker using my entire bandwidth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 22:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're probably right, SMFC is more beliveable. Good call. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 22:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made my flair global just for you. Anyone that lets someones flair influence their opinion on their post deserves to be lied to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 19:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/Destiny/comments/2bla2t/here_for_bungies_new_game_wrong_subreddit_visit/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 08:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And OP not ordering! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 08:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmm... looks so moist! Nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 08:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From a (fellow?) Greek, beautiful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 23:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> best 1 is ggn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guardian's destroyed Snowden laptop to feature in major V A show | Hard drive used to store top-secret NSA documents that was smashed on insistence of prime minister to be part of exhibition that questions privacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 02:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
