<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3533</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is receive all still broken? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 03:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boyfriends receive all works(on iOS) but mine always says connection lost to the point of no response from server. I'm on Android. Did they fix this or is it broken for android only? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 17:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's about a 30 mile commute mostly on free way. So would hybrids in general be bad for long commutes because of the battery? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 05:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanna spend less than 10k, and I'd use it as a college student commuting would. I was looking at Toyota Pruises and I saw one for 9.5k with 95k miles and it was an 07 Prius, would that sound about right/legit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 01:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the advice. I was planning on bringing my boyfriend and his dad to a meet up if I ever decided to use Craigslist. 

May I ask how much did you spend for that car and the mileage on it? Are cars with about 100k - 200k miles good? And did the car you buy last?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First time Craigslist buyer, need some advice! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 22:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to buy a car and I'm looking at ads on Craigslist, would you recommend I buy a used car on Craigslist or is it a bad idea? I've found a car I would really like but I'm afraid that it's a bad idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just the default HTC keyboard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever had an issue where you can't type a character name? I'm stuck at character creation because I can input a name. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 03:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is S-on or off? And I think I have developers edition but I'm not sure if I do. I bought this off Amazon so Idk much about this phone :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
