<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject1446</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 19:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 15:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd prefer if the bits where they are themselves was live action filmed during the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 15:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a little short film. It will be on my portfolio to get into college. I've done skits and stuff before but this is my first time working on something serious with other people acting in it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 14:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm shooting my first short film today and currently getting ready for the actors coming over. I'm pretty nervous and very excited.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colin the Carpet Man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 14:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the excuse they use for the comics, I don't know if it's been mentioned in the TV show. But in the comic universe they've said the Zombie mythology was never a thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 12:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's amazing how different Spaced is about Star Wars between the first and second season. Mostly because Phantom Menace came out between the two.

Also the voice of Darth Maul is featured in both.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 11:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Looking forward to it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 11:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it helps that they're playing characters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 11:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's the face OP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 10:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking forward to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 10:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! Thank you so much. That's perfect. I'll make a post here when it's done, and I'll send everyone who was in it PM's is well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah on WTF, I think, Rob was talking about how he doesn't really consider himself and actor and see's himself being a writer or a director after Sunny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you seen the original Star Wars movie? If not, please read on. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 00:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a few friends who have never seen Star Wars and I've recorded them telling me the plot of the movie from what they've heard in pop culture. I'm going to edit it into a big supercut to try and create a story that resembles some amount of sense, and I'll probably animate some of it.

However I need more clips to make it the way I want. So you haven't seen Star Wars, have a spare five minutes and half a camera/webcam/camera phone could you please record yourself describing what you believe the plot of Star Wars is beginning to end?

Then just pop it onto youtube and post it on here or PM me. Obviously if you do those things I'm assuming you don't mind the footage being put into the final project (Which will just be put onto youtube.)

I believe this has been done before but just with one person, plus this is just a little Summer project for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 00:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm also from Ireland and was very confused while reading this thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 21:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone actually sort of did this. They watched every movie referenced in season one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need all of the spoilers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really, really loved the last scene in this with the homeless people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been just as long as last time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sky are normally pretty good at airing things close to it's original airing so I'm very happy about this. It'll fit nicely there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit. This loop really could go on forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 13:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While were on the topic of CBB crossover universes. The comedy bang bang tv show and the movie "The Interview" have a big connection in that Ben Shcwartz plays an agent in both, but is only named in CBB. So in my head canon it's the exact same character.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 12:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0425112/trivia?tab=mc ref_=tt_trv_cnn

This is going to be tougher than I thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 12:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be impossible though, since the references will always be to previous movies. Everything you watch will have been made before the movie you watch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If someone else creates this chain I'll do it. I just might not be that good at spotting the chains.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I want to see what it's like. DVD's, webplayers, nothing will do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 21:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy shit, that shark is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Hot Fuzz Challenge: Watch Hot Fuzz from start to finish but every time there is a movie reference you have to pause Hot Fuzz and watch the movie being referenced. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chrome extension that lets you watch movies backwards on Netflix </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there was a lot of stuff happening behind the scenes with that one though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm back now!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 15:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're releasing it on a radio show that's not UTU2TM?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm going to be in this tinychat all day if anyone wants to come chat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 15:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://tinychat.com/khsunny786

Subreddit: /r/teenagerstinychat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 19:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you just ruined What We Do In The Shadows funniest jokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a very strange trailer. It felt like a clip cut out of an actual trailer.

Also yay the invisible friend. He's not really a monster he was just a human stuck in a world of monsters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A new series was just published a few years ago and they still always put out reprints. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've gotten excited about this project "finally being made" too many times in the past. I won't believe anything until there is a trailer.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah Blue Screen is still used a lot, but it was used the most up until they changed to green for Superman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They mostly used blue screen until Superman. And then they were like: shit we need a new colour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 15:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real life of this sub is actually in "new." A lot of great discussion happens there that never even makes it to the front page. If you stick to "hot" you're going to have shitty time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 20:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also the list of other names they were going to call Magnitude is the list of names Jeff says as he says bye to everyone leaving the party.

Magnitude will always be Ben from Tracy Beaker to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 20:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does that mean we will probably get that episode, because I love that lineup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 20:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they release some other poster in that style for them movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the Heidecker Gelman ep everyone is talking about in the AMA? Is it real or a bit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scott, when are you we going to get an Entourage recap on CBB for the movie??? I need to know what happened.

Edit: whoops someone already asked this. By the way if people do want to see Scott's take on the entourage movie he popped during the entourageathon and spoke about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clips of the muppets with the muppets edited out so it's just celebrities talking to themselves. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 14:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
