<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject7326</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 16:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey folks,
my LoL username is Deathpact Angel, and I am a Gold V midlane main on EUW severs. my favorite champs are Katarina, Zyra, Syndra, Diana and Ahri. I also can play decently with any other role, but each only with a few champions. I play a lot with my bf (a jungle main). If you wanna play with me, just send me a message or add me ingame.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 16:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joined in, not too much life there currently on EUW, but I guess that'll change when we get bigger here :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 16:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, wasn't me... well, Ill just repost them, fortunately it wasnt so much of them still :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 16:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just so its complete, here my data again


    Summoner Name: deathpact angel
    Server: EUW
    Smurf? yes, Pairidaeza
    What you are willing to help with: general things, I'm better at mid/adc supp than as top/jung tho
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 16:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the hell are all my posts deleted?

Anyway, I think she's doing good, LB got the nerfhammer and Kassadin the permaban, so along with Fizz I think she's top tier AP assassin atm, especially since she got a buff last patch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 16:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it even a yordle? He seems pretty big for one, doesn't he...

Also, the monster-thingy that's attacking the village, is it just me or does he look a lot like Vel'Koz? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 14:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> on the left there is the summoner that you get earlier. since you get flash last, flash goes on f.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 16:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one who just gets an "no access" message when opening that link? (and yes, I'm logged in at the site...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 13:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That Poland can into space! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 21:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Halle Berry as Karma. Doesn't even need a new haircut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Really, continents map? Well, at least better than last time [ft. low difficulty] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 13:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
