<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject9001</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 05:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure they'd take you anyways, you'd just be in debt afterwards :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 04:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My kitten does that too! I haven't got a clue why, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 04:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something like this triggered my fear of deep/dark water. I was 11 on a vacation with family in Florida, we rented a boat to go snorkeling. I swam maybe 50 feet from the boat, when I felt something stinging. I looked down and there was jellyfish all around me. I completely freaked out, and almost drowned. Still have nightmares about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 04:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do the exact same things! But I eat my boogers because I enjoy it. It's nice too, because I rarely get sick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 00:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No white after Labor Day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 20:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reply! This was very useful, I looked it up and she does seem to have many of the symptoms associated with this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 07:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the advice! I'll definitely try cleaning out her nasal passages, just to see if it makes things a little easier for her. I don't think the kibble was too large, as she has no trouble eating pieces of meat bigger than the dry food. As soon as I have extra money I am planning to take her to the Vet, but until then I'm trying to take care of her as good as I can :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favorite picture of Valerie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 05:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
