<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject8683</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: In the Halo video game series, why were the Forerunners so afraid of The Flood? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 06:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why were they willing to wipe out all life on a galactic scale to keep The Flood from spreading? What would have happened had The Flood been allowed to spread? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IT workers/computer repair techs of Reddit, be honest-- do you browse through the files of a customer's computer during repair? If so, what's the weirdest/funniest/most disturbing thing you've found? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 13:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know that there are probably more Redditors who don't listen to rap than who do, but this blew my mind so much I couldn't help it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 03:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the scariest thing you can think of that could realistically happen any second? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 12:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE hate when people on YouTube beg for likes, comments, and subscriptions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 06:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd think it defines a person's entire being. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheap ways to keep a laptop cool? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 22:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use [this laptop cooler](http://archive.benchmarkreviews.com/index.php?option=com_content task=view id=688 Itemid=66 limit=1 limitstart=2), and it helps a little, but my laptop still get pretty hot to the touch (only on the speakers above the keyboard, which is where I assume the processors are). 

According to Core Temp (a program I use to monitor the processor temperatures, the highest I usually go is about 65-68° C. I don't think that's really gonna damage the computer, but I also use a couple of high-end programs (mostly for video editing), so keeping it cool would help a lot for that. Plus I just hate the feel of a hot laptop, especially in the summer.

I'm really strapped for cash so I can't buy much of anything to help. What can I do to at least mitigate this issue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the funniest reason you or someone you know has had to go to the hospital for a non-life-threatening injury/injuries? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 22:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think people in the early 1800s thought the world would be like in 200+ years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-07 18:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need to convert large files (anywhere from 1-3 GB) from MKV/WMV/AVI/FLV to MP4, but my laptop has serious issues with overheating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-07 18:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can barely convert a 5-minute video file without my processor damn near hitting 90° C (it's Intel Duo Core if that matters). I'm scared my computer will burst into flames (hyperbole alert) if I try to convert a file that's one or two hours long

Any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend told me that I live like a prisoner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-07 01:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I spend 12 hours a day in a room with no light (I live by myself, in the basement of a two-story house), eat crappy food since I never have the energy or will to actually cook, never have friends over, and I go outdoors maybe once a week, only for 3-5 minutes at a time.  


Plus the fact that every day is pretty much just me doing anything I can to keep from going insane and make it until tomorrow without losing my shit. He said that sounds like the life of someone serving time.  

And I think he's right.  

Depression is a prison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Windows LPT: Alt+Enter while a file is highlighted to bring up its properties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 15:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead of right clicking and going down to "Properties" (even though it's really just right click, up arrow, enter, but still).

Just discovered this accidentally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Other than homosexuality, what isn't widely accepted by society, but should be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 02:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: To quickly quote and reply to a post on Reddit, highlight the portion you want to quote and press "Reply." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 01:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will automatically add it to your reply in quote format.  
Please be nice if I'm retarded and everyone already knows this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do wild bulls gore everything in sight at a rodeo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-04 23:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The people in the rodeo aren't a threat to the bull, and the bulls aren't attacking people for food, are they?

Also, how do they keep the bulls so docile before they're released? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were convinced that you were trapped in a dream and unable to wake up, what would you do to prove the world around you isn't real? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-04 17:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prove to yourself, that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your best real-life "ba dum tch" (rimshot) moment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 17:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your best "Made a mistake that ended up working in my favor" story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 08:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why are the suffixes of "motorcycle" and "bicycle" pronounced differently? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 06:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stand-up comedians of Reddit: How do you deal with hecklers or a crowd that isn't into your act? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 02:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Find a slutty enough girl, and this might just work. Otherwise, you might get slapped </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 03:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE hate it when you're searching for something on your computer's hard drive, and the search starts too soon because you hesitated while typing your search string? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 03:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use a PC, not sure if this is an issue with Macs.


Just wait until I press Enter, you piece of trash! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holy SHIT my laptop is overheating like a bitch. What are the best ways to keep this from happening? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 01:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To start, my laptop is a Dell Precision M6400 workstation. It's pretty powerful compared to the average laptop, so I expected a little bit of overheating here and there, but it's really bad now, even with my CM Storm laptop cooler.

I recently replaced my charger and battery (thanks to help from r/techsupport), after I had been using a lower wattage AC adapter for a while (because the original one died). The replacement adapter was only 90W where as the new one I just purchased (and the original) were 210.

When I was using the 90W adapter, the computer didn't overheat as much as it is now, which, ironically, is the reason I bought the new charger to begin with. I thought the stronger adapter would lessen the overheating, but it's actually gotten worse.

I haven't been doing much. Using the internet with 4-6 tabs open, no embedded videos (like YouTube and the like), no high-end programs idling in the background. Usually only Notepad, Windows Explorer, internet browser, AIM, YIM, Task Manager, and uTorrent are open at one time. Sometimes iTunes as well, and the CPU usage is consistently remaining extremely low (low single-digits). Despite this, the 
laptop is hot to the touch (on the speakers, which are located [above the keyboard](http://www.blogcdn.com/www.engadget.com/media/2008/09/m6400-precision-dell.jpg)). I've also got 99.9 GB free on my C drive and 49 free on my E drive (capacity 465 GB individually). 

[Here are my specs](http://3image.com/images/2013/06/30/Spec.png).

How can I keep my laptop from overheating?

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Complete control of the Earth: 50 alien tree leaves. The look on Hobbes' face in the last panel: Priceless </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 01:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is "Jason" used almost exclusively as a given name, when most other names with a "-son" suffix are surnames? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 15:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do my converted files always end up much larger in file size than the original file? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 20:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use either a program called "Any Video Converter," or "4Videosoft MKV Video Converter."

The converted file (usually to MP4, so I can watch it on my Xbox 360-- usually being converted from MKV or AVI) always ends up way bigger than the original file. Is it the program? Is it the video types? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a feeling you love that some people might find weird? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 00:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It was the NSA, wasn't it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-24 05:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Calvinball is a game in which you simply make up the rules as you go... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-23 20:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't Calvin and Hobbes just alternate between making up rules that contradict the most recent rule made up by the other? How does anyone ever win? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need a new battery and AC adapter for my Dell Precision M6400 laptop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-23 16:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.blogcdn.com/www.engadget.com/media/2008/09/m6400-precision-dell.jpg

I'm having a problem finding an AC adapter, though. This one:

http://www.discountelectronics.com/product?product_id=6631 product_model=302

Is the one listed under "Dell Precision 6400." However...

http://www.discountelectronics.com/product?product_id=4505 product_model=315

This one looks exactly like the one the laptop came with, and the first one is definitely not the one the laptop came with.

What do I do?

**NOTE:** I posted this last night, but got no responses. I apologize if re-posting so soon is against the rules, but I need this fixed as soon as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has karma ever struck you down, in an amusing or extremely specific manner, for a misdeed you committed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-23 16:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need a new battery and AC adapter for my Dell Precision M6400 laptop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-23 02:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.blogcdn.com/www.engadget.com/media/2008/09/m6400-precision-dell.jpg

I'm having a problem finding an AC adapter, though. This one:

http://www.discountelectronics.com/product?product_id=6631 product_model=302

Is the one listed under "Dell Precision 6400." However...

http://www.discountelectronics.com/product?product_id=4505 product_model=315

This one looks exactly like the one the laptop came with, and the first one is definitely not the one the laptop came with.

What do I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE sometime look at a picture of someone and imagine what the person would look like if he/she was bald? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-22 06:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I firmly believe this is the funniest story arc in the entire series. I've never laughed so much at non-punchline panels while reading C H </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 01:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What infomercial product have you or someone you know bought that turned out to be as good as (if not better than) advertised? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 16:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love the Rush Hour movies, but this is just wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-13 19:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm about to take Xanax for the first time-- is there anything I should know? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 19:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone who's taken it/is taking it, how did it affect you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you, or anyone you know, ever found anything in your home that was hidden by the previous occupants? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-03 03:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some of them actually make less than minimum wage, for goodness' sake... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 17:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mom's deadpan tone here is a hilarious inversion of how Calvin's parents usually react when he pulls this stunt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 06:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best part about this strip? It's absolutely true. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 04:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My mother always told me that the only thing better than being nice is being nice in the best way possible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 03:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the hell did Calvin set all of this up without his dad noticing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-18 21:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE feel like a badass ninja when you're able to find your away around in the dark without bumping into anything? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 03:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Windows 7 "minimum and maximum processor state"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 02:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do these options, found under Power Options -- Advanced Settings -- Processor Power Management, mean? I tried Googling it, but I had a hard time understanding how people were explaining it since I now next to nothing about advanced computer hardware.

Could someone possibly put it in layman's terms for me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who have been to jail-- which cliches about prison are true and which ones aren't? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-11 06:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most amazing coincidence you've ever witnessed/heard of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 22:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think is the biggest secret being kept from the general public? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 01:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously, being a major secret means you probably don't know the true story, so most responses will probably be in the form of "The real reason _______ happened," or "What really happened at __________." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My internet goes out at random times during the day, for about 2-3 minutes at a time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 15:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And when I say it "goes out," I don't mean that my modem/router doesn't pick up a connection. It still does, and I'll stay connected to my wireless network on my laptop, but web sites won't load. However, if I have something running that runs perpetually and doesn't have to be reloaded (like Xbox Live, instant messenger programs, torrents, etc.), they will stay connected to the internet (i.e., torrents will still download, I can still send/receive IMs, can still play games online, etc.).

When this happens, nothing on my router/modem changes. All the lights are lit, and it shows that I'm connected to the internet.

Does anyone know why this might be happening and how I can fix it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those companies that offer to reduce your debt-- how do they do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 06:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can you owe this amount, and all of a sudden you owe less?

Sorry if this sounds stupid; I know next to nothing about finances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one who never noticed Calvin has a peg leg in the first panel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 00:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My internet goes out at random times during the day, for about 2-3 minutes at a time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 03:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And when I say it "goes out," I don't mean that my modem/router doesn't pick up a connection. It still does, and I'll stay connected to my wireless network on my laptop, but web sites won't load. However, if I have something running that runs perpetually and doesn't have to be reloaded (like Xbox Live, instant messenger programs, torrents, etc.), that will stay connected to the internet (i.e., torrents will still download, I can still send/receive IMs).

When this happens, nothing on my router/modem changes. All the lights are lit, and it shows that I'm connected to the internet.

Does anyone know why this might be happening and how I can fix it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the easiest way to stream video to my Xbox 360 from my laptop? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 13:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can already stream music that's on my laptop, and listen to it on my 360. How would I go about doing the same with video?

Thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VLC media player doesn't show elapsed time/time remaining when playing .m2ts/.ts files </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-27 12:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I use VLC media player to play the .m2ts/.ts files I have on my computer, it just shows "00:00" no matter how long the video is. I also can't skip back and forth through the video with the "Forward/backwards five/ten seconds" commands. It doesn't do this with any other video format.

Is there any way to fix this? The files I have are very big (1 GB at the smallest), so I want to avoid having to convert them to another video format if possible.

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE constantly think of "DAE" posts they want to make, but then never get around to it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 04:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My emotions are extremely herp-derp-- I feel sad when I should without a doubt be happy. What's the problem? Can it be fixed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 07:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use the term "herp-derp" in the title because, like always, I try to use humor to heal the situation, but it is serious.

The only way I can describe it is this: I feel sadness and depression like everyone (I've been really depressed for about ten years, but that's not the most important part), but... when I feel (or SHOULD feel) happiness, it doesn't feel like happiness. It feels like a different type of sadness. Stronger and more pronounced. Like I'm going to cry, but I **know** it's not from being saddened or depressed.

I feel this when things in my life are going perfect and couldn't be better. Right now is a good example. I just came into some money, I may have finally gotten some anti-depressants that work, and I have literally nothing in my life to worry about.

So why do I feel like sobbing? Why does this happen EVERY TIME that I should be jumping for joy and grinning ear-to-ear? Is this normal? Is there something wrong with my brain that triggers a "sadness" reaction to a "happiness" stimuli? Can this be fixed?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Challenge: Post a strip in which Calvin is smiling in each panel that he's seen. Only one post per message. I'll start. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 01:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE get slightly annoyed when someone types "lol" with the first "L" (and only that letter) capitalized? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-18 07:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol

Like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does science acknowledge as existing even though no person has ever seen/felt/heard/etc. it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 22:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE get slightly annoyed when you can hear a vocalist take breaths during a song? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 01:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who live in/have lived in a country with an official language other than English, what's the most commonly known English phrase by people who don't speak it fluently? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 03:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever caught a salesperson in a lie about one of their products? Where were you, what were they lying about, and how did they react once caught? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 04:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think the worst part about depression is that it sometimes becomes difficult to find the will to do things you know you would enjoy normally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 01:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a couple of hobbies that I really enjoy, which are video games and video editing. Right now, I have nothing to do for the rest of the night, and instead of indulging myself in either of these activities, I can't find the will to do much other than pace back and forth across the room or sit on the edge of my bed literally doing nothing else.

Sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever been naked in public? Tell us the story. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 09:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most memorable drug trip you've ever been on? What did you see? Where were you? How long did it last? What drug were you using? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 07:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most amazing/interesting human-like behavior you've ever seen from an animal (whether in person or not)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 23:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What abbreviations stand for something other than what most people think/thought they stood for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 05:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDIT: Or really, any type of numerical or letter label that isn't what it appears. For example, different mediums have given varying representations of the "S" on Superman's chest. In the 1978 movie, it's described as the coat of arms of the House of El. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is the type of stuff you learn when a psycho ex-girlfriend tries to run you down in her Hyundai </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 00:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you from ten or fifteen years ago knew the current you, what about you would surprise him/her the most? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 07:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "It's no use! It's no use! Everybody gets good enemies, except ME!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-03 04:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE sometimes wash the dishes without using dish detergent? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-02 23:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only Calvin could turn disobeying his mother into a freestyle sport </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-02 02:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most common crime in the United States (amongst people who get caught)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-30 23:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best play on words you've ever heard? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 18:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whenever I think about my fate as an atheist in the event that God actually exists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 04:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What would it mean for something or someone to exist "outside of time"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 07:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been trying to wrap my head around this concept for a long time, and I got nothin.

Help me out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is the female body built for painful childbirth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 10:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nature generally does its best to give a species good reason to continue reproducing, right? That's why sex feels so good, why we're attracted to certain people, etc.

If that's the case, why is childbirth so painful for women? Isn't that completely counterintuitive to what nature usually dictates? It could essentially be a logical reason for women to NOT want to give birth-- nature usually makes sure to, at the very least, not give someone a reason to not reproduce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's something you've done because you saw it on TV/in a movie, and then you ended up regretting it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 02:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This happens to me far too often. I hope I'm not the only one </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 00:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "But Mom, it's their NATURE!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 23:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why/how do some people die/lose consciousness with their eyes open? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 02:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The second-to-last panel makes me feel very, very badly for Calvin's mom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-18 03:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Scientific definitions of fact, hypothesis, law, and theory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-17 01:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently, the word "Theory" is closer to the typical use of the word "Law" than "Theory." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some frustrating things you deal with regularly that you know you should do something about, but you don't? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-16 17:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever asked a question that you now wish you didn't know the answer to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-16 10:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone you know ever compare you regularly to a fictional character? If so, who and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 06:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me: Squidward. Monotone voice, little tolerance for people acting silly for no reason (i.e., SpongeBobs), constant -_- facial expression

What about you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sasquatch/Bigfoot has always been my favorite cryptid. What are all the arguments for and against its existence? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-10 02:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll focus on the [Patterson-Gimlin film](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lOxuRIfFs0w) a little bit, plus some basic zoology. If I'm wrong about anything, or you disagree with something ambiguous, feel free to say so. I don't necessarily believe everything I list below-- I'm just taking what I've heard and throwing it out there for you guys to go after in any way you see fit.

For:

* The alleged suit used in the P-G film has never turned up, even after 45 some odd years
* Many men have claimed to be "the guy in the suit," and their stories all contradict one another (although honestly, fake or not, this might be expected)
* In the P-G film, the alleged creatures has arms nearly as long as its legs, completely unlike a human, even one in a suit
* Some claim that if you look closely at the forehead, you can see the crest moving up and down, which would be indicative of muscles and skin, not rubber
* Some claim that Roger Patterson and Bob Gimlin simply did not have the resources to pull off such a massive, long-lasting hoax
* Some claim that the alleged creature seen in the P-G film walks in such a way that would be almost impossible for a human in a suit to replicate

Against:

* A minimal breeding population of large primates would have to number in the thousands, and if that's the case, there's very little chance that they could escape detection, especially for this long
* Primates do not swing their arms when they walk like in the P-G film
* There is no fossil evidence of anything that would fit the description of what we know as Bigfoot or Sasquatch
* Bodies are never found, nor is fecal matter
* Nests, colonies, etc. are also never seen or discovered
* Apes do not hibernate during cold winters, and as a result, it would be nearly impossible for a Bigfoot to survive an entire northwestern United States winter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a consensus stance on the Patterson-Gimlin film in this subreddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 00:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you all feel about it? Fake? Real? A guy in a suit?

I've seen cases made for both sides, and I wanna hear what the members of this subreddit have to say on the subject. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scumbag Brain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-06 19:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scumbag Brain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-05 07:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think I need to avoid interacting with attractive women for approximately the rest of my life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-05 00:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's not why you think. Well, it might be.

I used to be the type of guy who would talk to random good-looking women in public at the drop of a hat. You know "Hey, how you doing?", make small talk, attempt to get phone number. I was almost always woefully unsuccessful, but I generally didn't get discouraged.

Anyways, eventually, I realized that I had to draw the line at some point. So the fact that I had very little success, plus the fact that I know I'd make a shitty boyfriend anyway, made me decide to stop coming onto women at all.

Anyways, I was walking home from the store today, and I saw a cute chick. She wasn't super hot or anything, but she'd have been worth talking to if I didn't have my personal decision not to do so. We were both standing at the corner, trying to cross a busy intersection, but the traffic took a while to slow down enough for us to get across the street.

Of course, me being stupid, I couldn't help myself.

I said "This intersection could use another stop sign, couldn't it?" and smiled slightly. I don't know why I said it, but I do know that I had absolutely no desire to try and sweet-talk her.

But nobody told my brain, apparently. Because at that point, she agreed and laughed, at which point we were both able to cross the street. I walked back the way I was going and didn't pay her any attention, but I felt sick to my stomach that I didn't take the opportunity to hit on her. This was over an hour ago, and I still feel like crap.

tl;dr- [This](http://www.quickmeme.com/meme/3rbso0/) is what happens if I interact in any way with any attractive woman ever.

Fuck you, scumbag brain.

**EDIT:** Well, at least I can use this situation to confirm that I'm definitely forever alone. It's good to know.

You're okay, scumbag brain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have over 2,000 short (2-4 minutes) video files that I need to watch and then rename or delete. What's the most efficient way for me to do this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 00:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These videos are clips that I've recorded from my television with a capture device.

Not only am I a little (read: a lot) over my head with the sheer number of files I've recorded, but they also are all in 1080i high definition. My computer isn't built to play that type of video smoothly, so watching them at all is a chore and it's almost impossible to do so without significant skipping.

Does anyone have any advice for how I should go about this?

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever been pepper sprayed/maced? Tell us the story. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-25 01:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scumbag Brain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 06:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the point of making the sandwich at all? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-05 19:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I (23m) am a somnophiliac-- I have a sexual fetish for sleeping/unconscious women </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-03 23:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Somnophilia

Ask me anything that you can think of about this. Nothing's off limits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is pretty much me. Yeah, I'm a wuss. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-03 06:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "There's just one thing to do. We'll mail ourselves to Ostrlya. Climb in." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 06:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calvinception </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-23 23:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could someone help me find a psychiatry center in my area at which I can get an assessment and diagnosis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-18 14:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in the Philadelphia area and just want a psychiatric assessment and medical diagnosis. I don't need therapy or counseling or anything.

I tried using Google, but I couldn't find anything. Maybe someone who's more experienced with this can help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am a somnophiliac. I get sexually aroused by sleeping/unconscious women. AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-18 10:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would someone who's on camera while working get in trouble for hitting on someone on the job, even if it didn't interfere with their work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-17 08:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, a police officer. Say a cop pulled over a woman because her car matches the description of a vehicle they're looking for. Turns out, wrong car.

The cop flirts with the woman and gives her his phone number (not taking forever to do, so that he can get back to patrolling), all while being recorded on the dash cam. Would he be reprimanded? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good Guy Charlie Kelly (x-post from r/iasip) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-16 04:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What physiological factors determine one's reaction to strong sedatives? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 20:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I had a colonoscopy this morning. I was nervous the entire time before the procedure and didn't want any part of it. Now I'm done, giddy from the drugs they gave me, and I'd do it again in a minute. What's something you thought would be absolutely horrible but ended up being not so bad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 16:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus, I got a good laugh from the doctor after the procedure. I told him I understand why they say you shouldn't drive, but I feel like I could walk home or take a bus. He responds, "Well, some people get drunk and think they can beat up Mike Tyson. That's how you sound right now."

I couldn't help but laugh out loud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just took "liquid oral bowel prep solution" for my colonoscopy this morning. It tasted like salt dissolved in cough syrup. Reddit, what's the worst thing you can remember tasting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 11:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever blacked out for a non drug/alcohol-related reason? What happened? What did you remember before and after regaining consciousness? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 07:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never blacked out for any reason, and my last girlfriend used to black out randomly... it sort of piqued my interest, because she'd always be able to tell me right before it happens.

Educate me, Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone here suffered from chronic, long-term depression and then been "cured"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-14 05:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean the type of depression where you rarely feel any semblance of happiness. How does it feel to be "cured"? What's it like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a black man who lives in the inner city. I enjoy listening to rock music and watching pro wrestling. What are some things about you that are considered contrary to the stereotype of your culture? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-12 23:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I feel right now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 12:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is it illegal to cook certain animals and not others? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-08 03:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently, one can be arrested for animal cruelty if he/she cooks or attempts to cook a cat or dog, but not other animals such as lobsters.

What's the difference? Am I missing something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE fear that they're losing their mind if a bunch of weird things happen in one day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 10:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this constant paranoia that something strange happening means I'm coming down with dementia or psychosis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If depression is the cause of my insomnia, will treating the depression treat the insomnia simultaneously? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 08:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm no psychopharmacologist or anyone who'd be considered halfway knowledgeable in this field.

I have to take over-the-counter sleep aids for my insomnia (which I haven't been "officially" diagnosed with-- I just know I have trouble sleeping without sedatives), and I have been doing so regularly for at least two years.

The maximum recommended dosage of diphenhydramine HCL (the main active ingredient) is 50 MG. I took 100 MG all at once about two hours ago (my body's built up a tolerance). I feel slightly sleepy.

I don't want to keep doing this because I feel like it could become dangerous (although I haven't started hallucinating yet, which I understand is the main side effect of an overdose).

If I get treated successfully for depression, will my insomnia wear off too, if it's a result of depression? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sudden Clarity Clarence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 06:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My sister recently got evicted and didn't want to go live with my grandmother. I told her it's probably not a good idea for her to move in with me, since we'd probably clash. She responded by starting a fistfight with me. How has someone unknowingly confirmed your suspicions about them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-05 11:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On the surface, a comically anthropomorphized animal takes pride in not being human. Dig deeper, and you find a profound statement regarding the nature of morality. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-04 22:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've hit on at least 200 women that I don't know and who don't know me. I have, at best, a 5% success rate. AMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-04 00:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There have been certain times where my success rate increased/decreased in a certain environment (or maybe based on some other deviation).

Ask me anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good Guy Firefox </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-03 06:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What third-person action/adventure/shooter games have a combat system similar to the new Batman games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-03 06:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm speaking of Batman: Arkham Asylum and Batman: Arkham City.

The combat system I mentioned is how the game engine allows you to dodge and counter enemy attacks in real time with specific animations for doing so, as opposed to having generic "Block" and/or "Roll" options.

Which next-gen games have combat systems like this?

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's something you do that almost everyone else also does, but the way you do it differs from most? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-03 03:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, I wear jeans like lots of people do, but I only wear black jeans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mail carriers of Reddit-- is there a particular house on your route that you love/hate delivering to? Why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-02 22:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Multilingual redditors-- just how hard is it to learn a second language after using only one for so long? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-01 00:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm 23 years old. I just ejaculated (while awake) for the first time ever. AMA (x-post from CasualAMA). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 18:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Background info:

I'm not a virgin, although I have only had sex with one woman (multiple times). I think she wasn't very good, because I didn't feel anything at all whenever we had intercourse.

She gave very good oral, but no matter how close I was to the point of orgasm/ejaculation, I could never cross the threshold so to speak. I never came. Not once.

As for the title, yes, I specified "while awake" since I have frequent wet dreams.

I also don't masturbate, but I get aroused and horny like one would expect. I watch sleep fetish porn (I have somnophilia-- a fetish for sleeping/unconscious women).

I found some really good material tonight after I started to look for more since I couldn't sleep (that's gotta be ironic somehow). While I was watching, I was getting closer to the point of orgasm than I usually get while watching porn, but I still didn't think I'd cum.

Then, all of a sudden, it happened. It was (obviously) a feeling I'd never experienced before, and it caught me off guard. I was basically going O_O the whole time.

Ask me anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm 23 years old. I just ejaculated (while awake) for the first time ever. AMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 09:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Background info:

I'm not a virgin, although I have only had sex with one woman (multiple times). I think she wasn't very good, because I didn't feel anything at all whenever we had intercourse.

She gave very good oral, but no matter how close I was to the point of orgasm/ejaculation, I could never cross the threshold so to speak. I never came. Not once.

As for the title, yes, I specified "while awake" since I have frequent wet dreams.

I also don't masturbate, but I get aroused and horny like one would expect. I watch sleep fetish porn (I have somnophilia-- a fetish for sleeping/unconscious women).

I found some really good material tonight after I started to look for more since I couldn't sleep (that's gotta be ironic somehow). While I was watching, I was getting closer to the point of orgasm than I usually get while watching porn, but I still didn't think I'd cum.

Then, all of a sudden, it happened. It was (obviously) a feeling I'd never experienced before, and it caught me off guard. I was basically going O_O the whole time.

Ask me anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know this is likely considered sacrilege... but here's why I think Hobbes is a stuffed animal and a product of Calvin's imagination when he's "real" (long read warning) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 06:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know Watterson has said that he doesn't think of Hobbes as either a doll who comes to life when only Calvin is around, nor a stuffed animal who's only real from Calvin's perspective. But I see evidence that, in my opinion, **Hobbes is a stuffed animal whose personality, in the sense of Calvin's imagination, represents Calvin's moral, rational, conservative side**. I'll explain why below.

Throughout the entire Calvin And Hobbes series, Hobbes doesn't once address Calvin's parents. This is because Calvin, essentially (according to my theory, which I'm by no means citing as fact), is both Calvin AND Hobbes. He can't talk to his parents as "Hobbes" because he's too busy being "Calvin."

Speaking of Hobbes interacting with people other than Calvin... not even Calvin's **duplicates** acknowledge Hobbes' existence. You would think that if Hobbes was a real tiger in any way, shape or form, Calvin's clones would be able to talk to him and view him as a real tiger.

Also consider this-- whenever (even though it rarely happens) we see Hobbes writing, his handwriting is eerily similar to Calvin's. This is what first tipped me off that "Real tiger" Hobbes and Calvin are basically the same person.

Hobbes also disagrees with a lot of Calvin's plans, but goes along with them anyway. Hobbes actually likes girls, unlike Calvin, but yet he's still the First Tiger and "El Presidente" of GROSS. Many fans have speculated that Calvin secretly has a crush on Susie-- perhaps he expresses this through Hobbes.

Some might argue, "Don't you remember how Calvin said that Hobbes can climb to the tree fort where they hold their GROSS meetings, and Calvin himself can't?" This is a good point. As silly as it sounds, I honestly think Calvin just throws Hobbes up into the fort, which would explain how he can reach the fort "without climbing." When we [actually see](http://www.gocomics.com/calvinandhobbes/1987/07/26) Hobbes attempt to climb a tree, he's unable to.

Hobbes also shares many of Calvin's opinions and "knowledge," despite the two being so different on the surface. Hobbes helps Calvin cheat in class at least once (despite Hobbes being morally upstanding for the most part), he does his homework and gets the answers just as wrong as Calvin, if not worse (once answering "Atlanta, Georgia" to a subtraction problem), and he believes in Santa Claus.

You'll also notice that Hobbes almost NEVER refers to Calvin by name. Everyone else in the strip does-- Susie, Mom, Dad, Miss Wormwood, Moe, even the principal of Calvin's school. But not Hobbes. Because why would Calvin refer to himself by name? Calvin, however, *does* refer to Hobbes by name on a regular basis.

Like I said, I know a lot of people might feel like I'm "devaluing" the strip by formulating and writing up this theory, and you're certainly entitled to that opinion. But I'd ask that you don't drag this post down by making excessively negative comments.

Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am a 23-year-old male who has never had an orgasm or masturbated, and I have a foot fetish and a fetish for sleeping/unconscious women. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-28 05:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also am not a virgin, and I have frequent wet dreams (they don't even have to be sex dreams when my body decides to unload while I'm sleeping).

I feel the need to make one of these every time my body reminds me how strange I am by making me wake up wet and sticky.

Ask away. Nothing's off limits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whenever I look back and realize that my only girlfriends have all been psychopaths... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-27 05:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Trying to be helpful" rage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-24 00:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People react differently to violence in different neighborhoods. Who knew? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-23 06:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When has a plan to make a move on someone of the opposite sex (or same sex if applicable) gone horribly, horribly wrong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-23 01:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend just told me that an attractive woman was working at the store across the street from my house. I had to loan my Debit card to my dad (long story), so I only had three bucks in cash. I needed bread anyway, so I figured I'd buy a loaf and make a move while I paid for it. In, out, easy.

I get to the store, find out that they're $3.39 each (but also buy one, get one free, so eh). After asking the attractive girl in question and realizing I didn't have enough cash, I had to go back to the house and grab 50 cents in quarters.

I figured it was okay, though. She held on to the loaf of bread, so now I have an excuse to get in her line as opposed to another one. I grab another loaf of bread and wait in her line.

Then one of her co-workers opens another line. I offer to let the person in front of me go first so that I could stay in the line I was in, but he had a full cart and I only had one loaf of bread. Then I tried to use the "But [attractive girl] has my other loaf of bread. She's holding it hostage," and gave a forced laugh.

Her co-worker, totally oblivious to what I was trying to do (understandably-- she had no way to know), cheerfully said "Oh, that's okay!" and took the first loaf of bread from the girl I had gone to talk to. So now I was stuck in this new line, and had to leave the store without even coming close to making a move, AND I looked kinda stupid/poor/both for not having more than three dollars in cash on me.

**tl;dr-** Went to store across the street to talk to hot chick and buy bread. Didn't have enough for bread. Had to go back home to get more. She ended up not even ringing me up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There has to be a correlation... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-23 00:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could ask one question to any person who ever lived, who would you ask and what would you ask him/her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-22 03:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A girl once told me that she likes how my hair flakes easily, because it makes my scalp feel good to the touch. Reddit, what's the strangest thing you've ever been complimented on by the opposite sex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-21 07:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I like your Christ. I do not like your Christians. Your Christians are so unlike your Christ."- Mohandas Gandhi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-21 01:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly misattributed, but a good quote nonetheless in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am a 23-year-old male. I've never experienced an orgasm and I have both a foot fetish and a fetish for sleeping/unconscious women. AMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-20 22:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I remember seeing this on Kenan and Kel. Why HAVEN'T they invented a peanut butter and jelly doughnut? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-20 00:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Landlords of Reddit-- what's the funniest/most interesting story of eviction that you've experienced? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-19 03:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm (M 23) going to my first therapy session on Tuesday. Is there anything I should know? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-19 00:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is it the "Right hand of God" and the "Left hand of Lucifer"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-18 23:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this indicative of how ancient man perceived right-handedness as "normal" and left-handedness as uncouth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you noticed anything woefully unrealistic about porn that bugs you every time you see it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-18 05:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watch sleep fetish porn (i.e., porn with "sleeping" girls being fucked), and in at least half of the videos I've seen, the guy tricks the girl into taking sleeping pills, which promptly knock her completely unconscious within about 3 minutes.

I take sleep aids every night for insomnia, and not only do they not put you in a state of complete blackout to the point that a man can ravage you sexually without you awakening, but they take at least a half hour before you even START to feel anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This happens to me far too often </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-17 21:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wish I had the balls to say this to a hot chick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-17 01:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I wrong for this situation that happened with a girl today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-14 09:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to the store and noticed an attractive young lady working the cash register. I smiled at her, made small talk, and paid for my items. As I was leaving, I doubled back and asked if I could take her out for coffee. She smiled and said yes, but seemed hesitant. 

I told her that she didn't sound as if she was sure of her answer. Then, sort of randomly, she said "This is kind of inappropriate..." I asked her how so. She quickly changed the subject and said "I don't even like coffee!"

I calmly told her that she didn't have to actually get coffee if we went out. At this point, she said "Sure, we can go to Starbucks one day." Almost as if she was trying to get rid of me. But she said yes, so I asked for her phone number. She asked me to get it from one of my friends who had been in the store with me, but who had left before I doubled back to talk to her.

I could tell something was wrong, so I just told her I'd come back later. 

My friend was waiting outside, and he said he'd hook me up.

Sure enough, later that night, he came by later, along with her and a couple other people. We hung out for a little while and played cards, but eventually, me and the girl got in an argument because she said something about her boyfriend. I took exception because I felt that she was wrong for saying yes to me when I asked her out if she's with someone.

She claimed that she "liked my approach" so much that she just instinctively agreed to go out with me. I was confused and a little annoyed, because I felt like if you're with someone, you don't just forget that you have a boy/girlfriend. You just say "No thank you, I'm in a relationship right now."

I felt like I was being led on unfairly.

What think, Reddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm so proud of myself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-14 06:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I never hang out with anyone. I can't stand being around people. Despite this, I had company over tonight and had the most fun I've had in years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-14 05:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the first time in an extremely long time that I've ever felt un-depressed for a long period of time. I had five friends over-- nothing huge. It wasn't a giant party or anything. But they smoked and drank (I did neither-- you can have fun without those things), we played cards for a little while... hell, me and one of the girls got in a little bit of an argument, but by the end of night, we hugged and made up (at her request, even).

Anyways, through all my rambling, the point is that I had fun. I'm not a social person. I would never call myself that and neither would anyone who knows me. Being alone is usually the only time I can say I'm close to being happy, and I think that this probably applies to a lot of people here. 

What I'm saying is that you might, just might, have a good time if you hang out with the right people. If you don't like to have jokes played on you or to be ribbed/talked about by your friends, even in a sort of friendly way, don't put yourself around those types of people.

Find guys (or girls, or both) that you get along well with and who won't start any problems. People that will be mellow and won't ruin your good time. People who will make sure you're enjoying yourself and not let you stay depressed.

tl;dr- Socialize with the right people. There's a good chance that you'll enjoy yourself, and you won't feel depressed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scumbag brain'd if you do, scumbag brain'd if you don't... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-14 02:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh, my God... Susie is just like the stereotypical "Good-looking girl who likes douchebags" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-13 23:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's constantly nice to Calvin, she wants to spend time with him and lets him in her house even though he almost always treats her like crap.

I can't believe I didn't realize this sooner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blizzard, hurricane, flash flood, severe heat wave... what's the worst weather you've experienced where you live? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-13 23:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing I can remember is a huge blizzard we had in Philadelphia in the early 90s I think. 36 or so inches of snow.

I didn't care because I stayed in the house all day anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am a black man who spends an abnormal amount of time (for anyone) on the internet. AMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-13 09:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I listen to mostly rap music. I live in "the hood." I know people who sell drugs (and I know a little about the drug game). I've stared down the wrong end of a revolver and was once the owner of a shotgun (although I never had to so much as load it).

And I'm also a huge internet nerd. Ask me stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is the "naughty female teacher" look so pleasing to men? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-13 09:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it about the look-- the glasses, the professional attire-- that satisfies so many men? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some homophones you know of that you think aren't commonly known? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-13 07:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://dictionary.reference.com/browse/Homophone?s=t

*a word pronounced the same as another but differing in meaning, whether spelled the same way or not, as heir and air.*

* Lichen/liken
* Undue/undo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over a decade later, I feel like Calvin would be still asking this question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-13 07:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever had an overly attached boyfriend/girlfriend? When did you realize he/she was overly attached? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-12 20:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first "girlfriend" (although she'd probably say otherwise since the relationship was so short) once saw a good-looking girl around my age working the register while we were shopping for clothes. The girl I was with knew that I have no qualms about making small talk with hot women in public, so we had this doozy of a conversation:

* Her: Don't talk to that cashier when we get to the counter.
* Me: And what if I do?
* Her: Then I might have to cut her eyes out.
* Me: O_O...

So of course, when we got to the front, I talked to her anyway. I didn't flirt-- I was just making small talk. "Hey, how are you," that sort of thing. I even made her laugh when I remarked about Mondays being terrible or something or another.

Anyway, the girl I was with leaned up and whispered in my ear, harshly, "What did I tell you?"

I didn't say anything. I was laughing hard on the inside, though. Then I decided to give her a test, since I knew she wasn't one for public displays of affection:

* Me: Put your arm around me.
* Her: ... no.
* Me: Do it, or I'm gonna start talking to her again.

At this point, she put a death grip on my arm that I will never forget. I was shocked, amazed and flattered at the same time.

I also knew I had to break it off with this crazy bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wish I could say that this didn't actually happen to me. I really do. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-12 20:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Female cashier asked me if I was cold, since I had on a skintight tank top and cargo shorts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-12 20:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Literally just happened to me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-11 00:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "No matter what, no matter when, no matter who... any man has a chance to sweep any woman off her feet. He just needs the right broom."- Alex Hitchens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-10 23:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've said it before, but I hate to be around people who have success with the opposite sex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-10 00:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My roommate is on the phone right now with some girl, talking about "taking care of her" because apparently she's sick or something. So far, he's lied about his age, height, and relationship status (he has a "girlfriend" who he cheats on regularly).

I think if I wasn't making this post, I would have leapt up and screamed "SHUT THE FUCK UP!" by now.

If I'm on a diet (especially an unwilling one), don't eat sweets around me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time for some positive thoughts. What's the best memory you have of an attractive guy/girl being nice to you when you didn't expect it and/or when they didn't really have to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-09 00:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in math class about 6 or 7 years ago (I was around 16), and I sat behind a girl I really, really liked. She was very pretty, but she was actually a grade ahead of me, so I was even more scared to talk to her than usual. One day after the bell rang, she started talking to one of my (few) friends, and when the girl I liked looked at me, I knew my friend had told her I liked her.

She walked over to me, and of course, my heart was ready to leap out of my chest. She asked me with a smile, "Do you really want to ask me out?"

I said, "Yeah, but you'd never go on a date with me..."

She responded, "How do you know if you don't ask?", still smiling.

I hesitated, looked into her eyes, and sighed. "Would you like to go out with me?"

She continued to smile and simply said, "I'd love to."

I melted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Is it realistically possible for any animal to evolve and overtake humans as the dominant species of Earth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-08 22:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I feel about myself every time I see a "DAE" post that I can answer "Yes" to </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-08 18:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best communities for sleep fetishists? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-07 23:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've signed up for FetLife and joined this group:

https://fetlife.com/groups/6837

But I figure the more communities I find, the better my chances of finding a woman with whom to fulfill this fetish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is FetLife a community more for online-only discussion, or can it also be used to meet people for casual sex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-07 21:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't find anything on the site itself (or the Wiki page-- I am very new to the site in all fairness, however).

Has anyone met someone on FetLife, or know someone who's done so?

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ever since a friend of mine heard the term "Broseph," he adds an "-eth" or "-eph" suffix on random words-eth (like that). What's the silliest slang you've ever seen someone make up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-06 22:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does depression ever get to the point where it's so powerful that it can't be treated/cured? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-06 18:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My doctor prescribed me a brand of anti-depressants about two months ago. The first few doses were small, so my body could acclimate gradually. Taking it for the first time made me feel high (in a psychoactive way, not in a "The opposite of low, I'm super happy" way). Didn't make me feel "un-depressed," though.

As my system got used to the effects, they lessened until I stopped feeling anything from them at all. I was still depressed, even taking doses that were four times larger than when I started (40 MG compared to 10 at the beginning).

I stopped taking them cold turkey about a week ago because I couldn't afford to pay for them anymore. I feel no different now than I did while I was taking them, nor compared to before I first took them.

I'm looking into counseling, which could lead to better treatment, but I've been depressed for like 10 years. I'm convinced it's too late for me, so I shouldn't even bother.

Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE worry that members of the opposite sex will judge them for minor flaws of their house (jumbled wires, and old/out-of-date stove, etc.)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-06 06:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Nielsen company is going to pay me to let them record data from my house regarding which shows my roommate and I watch. AMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-06 02:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A representative just came to my door, gave me a gift basket, paid me a $20 "incentive," and bought me and my roommate pizza for participating. Everything seemed absolutely legit-- he left plenty of paperwork explaining everything, a business card, didn't make us pay anything or ask for personal information like a social security number.

Ask me anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why doesn't Reddit have some sort of "Bump" system? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-05 22:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find myself having to create the same post multiple times if I want more feedback on it. This would avoid that, especially since doing so sometimes gets you bombarded with "REPOST" comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you rather be viewed as someone who never gets mad or someone who people are afraid to anger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-05 17:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every time I hear the chorus to Where The Hood At ("You better bust dat if you gon pull dat") </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-05 16:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meme dad discovers lolcats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-05 15:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
