<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject3364</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 07:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apply anti-perspirant right after getting out of the shower. Definitely helps a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 07:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a brave mama. Just goes to show how much emotions animals truly have.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can fourth graders teach world peace? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 08:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A closeup on my kitty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 23:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 01:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll splurge on foundation and eyeliner but never on mascara. I find a lot of drugstore mascaras are just as good as the high end ones!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 01:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just came back from the vet and they found about 7 bites on her. They gave her a week's worth of antibiotics and she's looking good so far. Thanks for the help everyone :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cat got bitten by other cat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 05:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cat was playing in the backyard today and the neighbours cat crawled from under the fence and started chasing my cat. She got really scared and ran inside but it wasn't until later that we realized that the other cat bit her twice on her butt. We applied some polysporin but she is walking sort of funny now. Both my cat and the neighbours cat are up to date on their vaccines. 

We're taking her to the vet in the morning but I was just wondering if anyone could provide any info regarding what to do otherwise? It's my first experience with a cat bite. Kind of panicking right now :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 22:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kristen Stewart and Kristen Stewart  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just one of his many posts about himself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 02:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 18:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canada doesn't use pennies anymore so technically, it isn't worth anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 09:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which pizza do you take off first? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 08:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cat loves watermelon, too.. But can only eat it if I chew it up for her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
