<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>train_subject2704</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 16:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scared the shit out of me.. Not the bike.  The track, being on one. So nervous i didnt enjoy it. Any advice? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First time on a track today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 16:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 16:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 250 i had before was great height. For reference im 5'3.  The 600 is a bit tall for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 05:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Helps when you link me to it ;)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 04:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the girlfriend and mine is the green one c: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 22:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're sexy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 13:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't enjoy skyward sword at all. In fact I didn't like it so much I never bothered to finish it.  The controls for swimming I thing irritated me the most about it. And all the other bs that came with it. One of my favourites is MM. I can say I've beaten it more then any other one.  But anyway the point is I think I actually hated skyward sword. Wii controls in general I find too flailey and I find myself disliking the entire motion control system. Just my two cents.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 05:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Horses should be moved down :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 23:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> woo this is going to be me once i finally get my zx-6r certified c: can't wait for spring. Just upgraded this year from the 250r </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 23:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how did you find the final product? Did it make your legs spread further apart by doing it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 21:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> got the yarn at micheals (craft store) i cant remember what type it was as i dont have the package anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 23:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6oz/170g/315 yards 100% acrylic medium c: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 22:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep im a vet tech. Snake came in very flat and we wanted to see if there was maybe an obstruction or something causing the listlessness, turned out to be viral </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 22:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too, then id have a fleet c: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> this is the Gryffindor scarf I made to match the slytherin one I posted earlier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 21:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 21:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have to get back to you on the exact yarn I need to find the label that was on it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
